<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@ImKnotTheOne @newsmax @gregkellyusa Its less than 1/2 of a percent. Whats needed is an update to hiring policies then have consistent, adequate  proper officer arrest training. The other half falls on the inner city communities whose people regularly engage in criminal activities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @gregkellyusa So glad I am retired. I hope all the police in all Dem run cities leave in mass exodus. Sadly, this is the only way those communities will learn. Perhaps then theyll elect law and order Republicans.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The Democrat insanity just never ends... thank God in 2022, we will take back the house and the senate... as nobody wants these radicals leading the country!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @JoeBiden @TheDemocrats @VP @canine2 @rigatoni7 @imUrB00gieman @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @IngrahamAngle @TheLeoTerrell @greggutfeld @JesseBWatters Exhibit A : https://t.co/b9X6kHrqHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC Democrats cant help themselves... they are a high control, morally bankrupt, anti American, anti Police, and a divisive, hate based, political party. @JoeBiden @TheDemocrats @VP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@madisongesiotto This despicable clown? https://t.co/feH4pkTz9c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JennaEllisEsq @Liz_Cheney Liz is no better than her war profiteering father, Dick. And 75 million of us will make sure RINO Liz doesnt get reelected. @GOPChairwoman @GOPLeader @SteveScalise @LeaderMcConnell @DonaldJTrumpJr @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @JesseBWatters @greggutfeld]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@imUrB00gieman Yes Joe Biden is a racist. I present you Exhibit A ... https://t.co/035s6lwKBv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwainForSenate Yes!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomborelli @imUrB00gieman @CNN @JoeBiden @CDCDirector Did you say Fauci and the CDC?  https://t.co/Wtpy88QeuI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottBaio @BillGates Hey Bill... https://t.co/fEr0zFpGJp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EWErickson @rigatoni7 @Liz_Cheney Erick, Liz is a RINO. And, 70+ million of us will make sure Liz doesnt get reelected. Hows that? @EliseStefanik @SenTedCruz @laurenboebert @SteveScalise @seanhannity @LeaderMcConnell @TuckerCarlson @mtgreenee @GOPLeader @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @HouseGOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mchooyah sorry a little slow on the uptake here as I was banned on Facebook for 7 days so just found this image. Thanks for your service, Rob. https://t.co/8kDmwjr8Us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rigatoni7 @CIA The CIA is no longer the Central intelligence agency, its now the Central Intersectional Agency! What a total joke! How will CIA protect USA with woke employees?! The rest of the world is not woke! @KatiePavlich @greggutfeld @JesseBWatters]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto F#%k  @Facebook ! Cant wait until Donald Trump gets his new platform so 75 million of us can drop Twitter and Facebook!  @DonaldJTrumpJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLeoTerrell Yes!  Thank God! Can we also get rid of Reps Omar and Talib with AOC as well?!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams @KatiePavlich @DanaPerino @JesseBWatters @greggutfeld Juan, why are you forgetting to mention that INFLATION is up in many areas! Gas, food, etc. But you cite the stock market? Inflation is going up!   Plus restaurants cant hire people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rjc1960_richard @thetoyman1 @greggutfeld @FoxNews @TheJuanWilliams @KatiePavlich @DanaPerino @JesseBWatters Juan, shut the f#%k up  stop saying everybody get the vaccine! Theres too many side effects - From paralyzed to blindness! Idiot @JoeBiden  doesnt even know what hes doing on masks!  https://t.co/Xw1GEdymPm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KevinKileyCA While @GavinNewsom  releases 63,000 felons in CA.. Now watch crime rise!  #RecallGavinNewsom @Caitlyn_Jenner @Kevin_Faulconer @johnandkenshow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@imUrB00gieman Once again a black person   is resisting/being disrespectful to law-enforcement which isnt helping society heal. Shes  a teacher who files a false complaint? @POTUS perpetuates this. @LASDHQ @BillHemmer @johnrobertsFox @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @canine2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Ya think? Catch up Ronna.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y Tony, so I guess the CIA is no longer the Central intelligence agency? Its now the central intersectional agency!   How do woke CIA employees deal with real world non woke nations in their duties to gain information and protect us?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarterCenter @POTUS @FLOTUS Isnt that sweet... Two of the worst presidents in our history. At the rate Biden is going, well have the 19% inflation rate  peanut farmer Carter had in the 70s!  @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @canine2 @rigatoni7 @charliekirk11 @imUrB00gieman @cvpayne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv Who cares.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut Bill @BillGates has replaced her with a robot. Its the only thing that can handle his zero personality. Hey Bill, ... https://t.co/sfSNVw7VV6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Good! I hope more Seattle cops leave! No one should work under those city @CityofSeattle conditions w/ @MayorJenny ! @seattletimes @SPOG1952 Sadly the residents of Seattle will suffer until they remove their current Dem city officials! @GLFOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrJustinBarclay @rigatoni7 Defund all teacher unions! @NEAToday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch Tell me again why we are giving this C19 vaccine to young people that have a 99.9% virus survivability rate?  @pfizer @CDCgov @US_FDA @FoxNews @newsmax @OANN @TuckerCarlson @JesseBWatters @WhiteHouse @JoeBiden https://t.co/brGqdFSEX9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera Hey genius, what do you expect when @JoeBiden pays people to just sit on their asses? (ie Socialism). You dont understand basic human behavior.  @greggutfeld @seanhannity @TheLeoTerrell @TuckerCarlson @johnrobertsFox @IngrahamAngle @canine2 @rigatoni7 https://t.co/usDL9gM6PK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @CNN @MSNBC @ABC @HARRISFAULKNER @CBSNews @NBCNews @newsmax @JoeBiden @VP @T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @WHCOS @GOPLeader Joe, with this new info , what are you doing to hold China accountable for killing 500k Americans? https://t.co/U8uaEp1BEz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays No. Do you understand how long an intensive investigation can take?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch Tom, what election laws did Ohio state officials violate when conspiring w/ big tech to censor election posts? Election tampering? What can you do to get prosecution from law enforcement or do you file a lawsuit against them?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rigatoni7 @KristySwansonXO Joe cant even walk walk up or down a flight of stairs, do you expect him to tell the truth? https://t.co/wtjhgQi72b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv @rigatoni7 @canine2 @Recall_Gavin this is why @GavinNewsom will be recalled! 70% of the 63k crooks released will re-commit crimes thus re-victimized 44k people! This is insane! @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @billmaher @Caitlyn_Jenner @johnandkenshow @KevinKileyCA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBATV #boycottNBA @NBA @Lakers and China lover/police and white hater  @KingJames ! https://t.co/PDnZ9YqQlS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @BernardKerik what I dont understand is the New Jersey state AG @NewJerseyOAG says the city of Newark has great policing. So why doesnt @LoriLightfoot use Newarks policing model to clean up Chicago? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut @FrankLuntz is a freak. Hey Ronna,   @GOPChairwoman  @GOPChairwoman @GOP drop Luntz from being a GOP advisor! Hes a RINO  completely useless. He doesnt represent 75 million Trump supporters. Understand? @DonaldJTrumpJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wilderfortruth Hunter Biden you say ? Hes busy... making a movie... https://t.co/NQPKzFrRwu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Wait... shouldnt LeBum James @KingJames (@NBA ) be leading that march? He loves China! https://t.co/AMBoWgncGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom @Recall_Gavin @GOPLeader @billmaher @rigatoni7 @canine2 @FoxNews @SpeakerPelosi @NextRevFNC @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @Kevin_Faulconer @Caitlyn_Jenner @BeastJohnCox @benshapiro @johnandkenshow Newson  endangers Californians! #RECALLnewsom https://t.co/GUn10XIaJN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Uber @spikelee @johnlegend So you guys support getting the vaccine? I wonder how this lady feels since shes now paralyzed from her 2nd Pfizer vaccine shot?  https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Yes! Thank you Gov DeSantis! @GovRonDeSantis  Now lets get Texas @GregAbbott_TX ,  @govkristinoem South Dakota and  @GovKemp Georgia to join in !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_LoveLike_JESUS Amen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KevinKileyCA Newsom and his ego were pissed off at Huntington Beach who challenged him in court so he set out to punished Orange County.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader No Kevin, pure dementia based insanity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SebGorka Because of Dems... https://t.co/oG52W9CgvG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@madisongesiotto https://t.co/xkjLM1aCOY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrMichaelBurkes Actually I would support a DeSantis / Candace Owens ticket or a Tim Scott / Burgess Owens ticket]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@___FacelessMan @imUrB00gieman @45_FT20 @earthing5000 @_mexodus_ @PaulMer53 @Cynthia36444750 @FKN_HeartThrob @USAVeteran5 @HannahE7291 @NomadTrucker01 @Yomama86753O9 @Bree1914 @451Dav @digi11111 @DannyMack100 @twk4usa @jAlmz5 @ScienceDaddio @Jacfam2 @PRESIDE28399984 @anth_Xth @Teddy_MBGA @SamEnnes @Parker733191012 @Terry10661013 @ZeroDarkKitty @America52096996 @Russell99451758 @Teddy_2748 @BluehandRising @JackiMiller424 @PatriotSera @MrBobLablah @MomWarrior_00 @sweatsglitter @AngelofOz_1111 @badplfer @Timeflies @txark76 @CeeBeesHoney @LionInWinter44 @LiisaJust @ImaP91 @Queen_Avatar_ @BlackDogz3 Folks, vaccine food for vaccine thought ... so be safe! A lady was paralyzed after 2nd Pfizer shot ... https://t.co/NMzSpOsimo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Read_N_Learn @RDVarley Its because its successful Republican leadership @GovRonDeSantis vs the usual failed Democrat leadership @NYGovCuomo as the reason.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stillgray You mean Obama? https://t.co/oa6gZuRaiW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sdennee60 @realstewpeters Steph, but is this? https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realstewpeters Meanwhile.... https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonrantz @Elizabethrz007 Heres another reason Ill be ignoring the science of this vaccine which has still not been long-term tested.... https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @BillMcCombs3 Dana, have you seen this? A lady becomes paralyzed after her second shot of the Pfizer vaccine.... https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Are we sure these people were vaccinated? Speaking of the (Pfizer) vaccine.... @CDCgov hey Rochele, you said this vaccine was safe. https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Having dementia does this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kelliekelly23 @Elizabethrz007 @gatewaypundit Well at least its better than losing your legs from the covid shot! https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut Yup.... look ! https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EpochTimes Vaccine? No thanks! https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prageru Having a relationship with God through Jesus ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Ronna, yet another reason why Im not getting the vaccine.... https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TyBSaunders @RNCResearch No using that idiotic common core math 2+2 = 22!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RNCResearch Did you say vaccine? A lady became paralyzed after second Pfizer vaccine shot.... https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden @VP @FoxNews @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @JesseBWatters @johnrobertsFox @CNN  @johnlegend @CDCgov @SenateGOP  @GOPLeader @greggutfeld @rigatoni7 @canine2 @NextRevFNC @IngrahamAngle  Lady paralyzed after 2nd Pfizer vaccine... https://t.co/NMzSpOaGXO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BuzzPatterson @thehill @VP @Twitter  They wont.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill @VP @JoeBiden @WHCOS @PressSec Yeah Kamala  for the Mexico Cartels bringing illegals over our border that youre doing nothing about!!  @CNN @MSNBC @ABC @CBSNews @NBCNews @FoxNews @seanhannity @BillHemmer @johnrobertsFox]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @JoeBiden Explain the potential epic Gov intelligence failure re UFO activity/tech  its  ability to penetrate our best defenses. Hoping its not foreign. @rigatoni7 @canine2 @T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @SaraCarterDC @seanhannity @LeaderMcConnell @GOPLeader]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CypressCollege Who is this idiot teacher berating a student re: Police?! Remove her! @seanhannity @GLFOP @TuckerCarlson @GOPLeader @KevinKileyCA @canine2 @rigatoni7 @johnandkenshow @IngrahamAngle @johnrobertsFox @HARRISFAULKNER @greggutfeld @JesseBWatters https://t.co/8UXBYsEOKD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sassytallblond Although not surprised can you provide additional evidence? Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miles_commodore @chuckanw No we should not. What we need is someone like Ron DeSantis and or Tim Scott with a VP like Candace Owens or Burgess Owens.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @GOPLeader @FrankLuntz Ronna, what are we doing with Frank Luntz? This slimy bad hair piece guy doesnt represent us Patriot voters! GOP has become disconnected from its core base! Its why 75 million are sick of the GOP and support Trump!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CawthornforNC How is  @JoeBiden going to visit the border when he cant even get up Air Force Ones stairs? https://t.co/7F0zsGV6Vk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y Tony, as a former law-enforcement its beyond logic as to why the @FBI didnt seize Hunters lap top evidence from @RudyGiuliani when he offered it.  And I thought things would change after Comey was fired, but I was so wrong!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden Joe, what the hell is wrong with your brain?! Patriotic means resisting Gov (unscientific mask) overreach! Covid hospitalization  death rates are lower than the seasonal flu! My god youre OBTUSE! @HeyTammyBruce @seanhannity @canine2 @rigatoni7 https://t.co/bEaDpJKN6l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@canine2 @JoeBiden if Joe Biden goes full panic mode over a lost mask ( hes been vaccinated!), imagine what hell do when a serious military threat from China, Iran, Russia or NK occurs? Joes embodies weakness. @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @imUrB00gieman]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto I supported Trump but I dont think he should be president again. We need someone like either Ron Desantis or Tim Scott as President with a vice president like Candace Owens or Burgess Owens. @GOPChairwoman @DonaldJTrumpJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LAPPL Det McBride, please have your members stop working overtime for Lakers related events. LeBron James threatened an Ohio police officer and put him at risk so there must be a consequence. The NBA wont do squat. Thank you and be safe out there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich @rigatoni7 Besides idiot @JoeBiden still wearing a mask on Zoom, why is Kamala Harris @VP and Nancy Pelosi @SpeakerPelosi seated in the back wearing masks? Havent they had their vaccine?  #vaccineSideEffects]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaniceDean @NYGovCuomo And Cuomo committed several crimes deserving of full prosecution by @NewYorkStateAG and or @TheJusticeDept .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sfmcdevitt @TPostMillennial And homely ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngelWa33017557 @TPostMillennial Its easy to defund  @TheView ...simply stop watching it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPostMillennial So a moronic privileged (and homely) white woman (who once wore a black face),  @JoyVBehar of the divisive @TheView , is telling a black man @SenatorTimScott about systemic racism? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Speaking of dysfunctional government... https://t.co/DePuNAHIsZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeresaFreeThink: Lin Wood: The pandemic in this world is child sex trafficking.  https://t.co/VSAJXyxcFi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WHCOS And you dolts have a fraud named Fauci and a politicized CDC. @CDCgov https://t.co/pz1ag2y7aX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WHCOS STFU you useless manipulative clown. Joe stills wears a mask  he was vaccinated! 75 million see through the BS you spew while youve destroyed 1000s of jobs, ignore a border crisis,  push race baiting, woke culture  cop hatred! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhiskeyRiff  McConaughey is a joke. @Matthew78506135]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut Is? It was also under Obama thanks to scumbag lying piece of crap, @Comey https://t.co/5rkbtvCWwP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenboebert Lauren, Its difficult to watch  @JoeBiden blabbering on @FoxNews about @Amtrak - a horrifically run org! And with removing millions of vehicles this will impact trucking! @TRUCKINGdotORG @GOPChairwoman @marthamaccallum @GOPLeader #bidenlies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@imUrB00gieman Looks like GW Bushs daughter! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OANN @JoeBiden is a racist, clueless and leaderless puppet for Obama. https://t.co/mJaH7ePU0o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut Juanita, its just one of many red flags regarding this vaccine. Heres just a few more ... https://t.co/DaAOv9O5ek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Good! @seattletimes @CityofSeattle @SPOG1952 @NYCPBA Every cop in every dysfunctional Dem driven city should leave! Dem dont care about cops! And now no one wants to be a cop! All thanks to Libs/Dems! @DNC @KatiePavlich @GillianHTurner @CNN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @JohnFBachman Of course @DNC all democrats ie @JoeBiden @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @AOC et al dont want children to know the truth-its how Socialism works...by controlling peoples access to information! @usedgov @johnrobertsFox @greggutfeld @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kaitlancollins Meanwhile we have leaderless  @JoeBiden wearing a mask AFTER  his vaccination!  @seanhannity @canine2 @TuckerCarlson @CDCgov @johnrobertsFox @KatiePavlich @MarkMeadows @GillianHTurner This is why theres anti vax  #vaccinehesitancy ! Plus this https://t.co/ktqovB274b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y Precisely Tony.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnrobertsFox @GillianHTurner @guypbenson @FowlerShow Folks, youre missing the core issue. If blacks are disproportionately killed by police, its due a  disproportionate involvement in acts of crime that lead to more police contact! Then this occurs ... https://t.co/duqlsLfqa0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mirandadevine @RudyGiuliani So the @FBI is gets a chance during a search warrant to collect evidence re Hunter Biden case but refuses it? The FBI does have an investigation into Hunter? This defies logic. Something is not right. @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @GreggJarrett]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>