<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[This morning @MyFDOT is beginning to install speed tables on a section of West University where two pedestrians have died in recent months.   @DrB_OnMedia has the details: https://t.co/DnbwYp507h via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heads up: The Alachua County health department has announced a series of walk-up #COVID19 vaccine clinics in Gainesville.   The first one starts at 11 am today:  https://t.co/d7wyoF9CNj via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gov. Ron DeSantis used executive action to ban vaccine passports and end all local COVID-19 emergency orders on Monday. #LocalNews #Florida #COVID19   https://t.co/RtGFQWSU3x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Alachua County Sheriff's Office has arrested two suspects for the theft of two vehicles and multiple break-ins of cars at the Arbor Greens development in Jonesville. #Alachua #LocalNews #Monday   https://t.co/GU2gTcLCR3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A driver and passenger died in an Saturday morning crash on West University, according to the Gainesville Police Department (GPD). #Gainesville #LocalNews #Monday   https://t.co/H62mcWXJXE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Sports beat: Williston softball crushes top seed Hawthorne to win district title  https://t.co/vUusCT3Hk4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @RowdyEHSRams boys tennis team made it to state for the first time in six years.   They lost in the semis to Satellite, but head coach Don Reeder says the best may be yet to come: https://t.co/zTbOiHbQpa via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@suzettemcook has the details on why the Westgate @Publix is closing tomorrowincluding renderings of the future store that will sit in its place: https://t.co/mODSmYPbZL via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Children's Trust of Alachua County board has approved $1.1 million in funding for more than 2,000 additional free or reduced-price seats for Alachua County young people to participate in summer camps.  #Alachua #LocalNews #Summer #Friday   https://t.co/gBmd23fxkv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenbpoe: 28 cases and 0 deaths reported on 1,342 labs today. Totals are now 24,635 cases, 275 deaths, and a two week positivity rang]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Near the east end of the stage, a limited quantity of Pfizer COVID-19 vaccines will be administered on a first-come, first-served basis. #Gainesville #LocalNews #Friday   https://t.co/4OvluJqsOy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @FloridaGators family and especially @GatorsFB and @GatorBoosters are remembering the late Stumpy Harris as a great supporter of Gator athletics: https://t.co/mf2wT5M6gQ via @NewsGainesville (Don't miss the classic cars pics!)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're excited to announce our new corrections tool is now live!   On each story at @NewsGainesville, you have an opportunity to click "Suggest a Correction" to help us improve accuracy.   It's part of our commitment to be the most trusted source of news in North Central Florida! https://t.co/FSQe6rOdyC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Alachua County Sheriff's Office (ASO) is asking for the public's help locating a missing man. #missing #Alachua #LocalNews   https://t.co/df70Ja9Zkq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attention all iguana and tegus owners!  #LocalNews #Thursday   Tag your reptile day at UF is June 12.   https://t.co/8acoMh8rHM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Alachua County Parks and Open Space Department has announced the reopening of Squirrel Ridge Park after a significant renovation project.  #LocalNews #Alachua #Wednesday #Community  https://t.co/VjUwvSyPGo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mayor Jordan Marlowe and the rest of the Newberry Commission voted to request that Alachua County establish a rural highway improvement program and move that same road to the top of the list. #LocalNews #Wednesday #Alachua  https://t.co/3ROSIrZ4KG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Sports beat: Trenton softball rides the arm of Darian Ingram to advance  https://t.co/Gn58Lf0ZD9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No more busy signals, missed call-backs and competing registration systems! Now, for residents of Alachua County, those issues are a thing of the past. #Covid19 #Vaccine #Gainesville  https://t.co/J5gSiLIlrP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UF Health and the Florida Department of Health in Alachua County are joining forces for a virtual COVID-19 vaccine town hall on Thursday. #COVID19Vaccine #LocalNews #Alachua   @UFHealth  https://t.co/JYt9d1NTCh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The City of Newberry conducted a swearing-in ceremony on Monday with new Commissioner Tony Mazon taking his seat for the first time. #LocalNews #Tuesday #Newberry  https://t.co/RdicdtjnP8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The City of Newberry will fund a $50,000 report on behalf of multiple cities in an effort to move forward the exploration of a regional wastewater facility in western Alachua County. #LocalNews #Monday #Newberry  https://t.co/b8CUyJfdfQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Levy County Emergency Management has announced three vaccine pop-up sites are scheduled this week in Bronson, Chiefland and Cedar Key. #Monday #Alachua #COVID19Vaccine   https://t.co/ek84UqiHOH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@AlachuaSchools has relaxed its #COVID19 protocols and announced masks will be optional in the 2021-22 school year.   Details at @NewsGainesville: https://t.co/REfC75fQ1a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CorfmanParks: TODAY from 10am-2pm be the solution to the problem.  The National Prescription Drug Take Back Day addresses a crucial pu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is National Drug #TakeBackDay, so check your cabinets for unneeded prescriptions and turn them in.   And then check out what a retired Coast Guard Admiral is doing to combat the #opioidcrisis: https://t.co/uf1JZXrPg6 @ShepherdFlorida @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Check out my @NewsGainesville sports newsletter every Monday  Friday.   Today I gave props to the Santa Fe College softball]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The big screen is about to light up again in Gainesville!   @suzettemcook has details on @RegalMovies re-opening plans for tomorrow: https://t.co/J9KLDTaWBR via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Alachua County health department is holding three walk-up #COVID19 #vaccine clinics Fridaytwo in Gainesville and one in High Springs.   Details here: https://t.co/tcw6F4YDVT via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday a circuit court granted Levy County an injunction against the organizer of the CrabFest music festival.  Now the organizer is calling for a protest Saturday in Williston: https://t.co/CGLbmRvoYp via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Hyatt Place hotel will feature 145 rooms, a pool, a lounge, a restaurant and 1,800-square-feet of meeting space. #Gainesville #Wednesday #LocalLiving  https://t.co/zv6oWFOuzT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Yesterdays verdict showed that no person is above the law and that all of us will be held accountable for the crimes we commit." #Gainesville #LocalNews #ChauvinTrial   https://t.co/qILkWBvAOf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Santa Fes Zane Starling shuts out North Marion   @SFHSRaiderBSBL wins 4th straight  https://t.co/8tj7nTfZLb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A student at Newberry's Oak View Middle School reportedly found a gun in student's backpack on Tuesday and turned it over to a teacher.   Click the article below to see more details. #LocalNewsMatters #Wednesday #Alachua  https://t.co/RRWJ47T3MK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A jury found former police officer Derek Chauvin guilty of murder and manslaughter charges in the killing of George Floyd.   Gainesville Mayor @laurenbpoe expressed "love and solidarity" with those affected. https://t.co/Ytk9EMvBbG @NewsGainesville  #GeorgeFloydverdict]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We hope to offer an approachable and enjoyable sushi experience CEO Chris Kramolis said in a press release. We love creating an atmosphere for people to relax and lessen the intimidation-factor for Sushi." #Sushi #LocalBusiness #tuesdayvibe   https://t.co/adaiNvQKvb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[High Springs Chamber of Commerce is putting on the 44th Annual Pioneer Days Festival this weekend in downtown High Springs.  #LocalNews #Tuesday #HighSprings   https://t.co/OSfmAqZbjI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Click on the story below to watch the video of Trevor Cartmill jumping over the rooftop of Sturge's lounge at Ellie Ray's RV Resort.  #localnews #Florida #Monday   https://t.co/9ljOajCvac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenbpoe: I applaud @GNVChamber for their new Inclusive Gainesville initiative and look forward to partnering with them to ensure suc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Sports beat: Oak Hall School boys lacrosse wins the district title  https://t.co/C3V01phvZW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Greater Gainesville Chamber this week launched Inclusive Gainesville, a new initiative aimed at equitable economic development and inclusion. Click the story below to read up on all the details! #Gainesville #LocalNews #Diversity   https://t.co/3rR62W32ve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The season is on the line for the Buchholz boys lacrosse team, but so is a district championship. #Lacrosse #Friday #Bucholz @ThePrepZone   https://t.co/Rx8k5Syfud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Gainesville Police Department (GPD) is investigating a fatal wreck that occurred Wednesday night in north Gainesville. Click the link below to read more. #LocalNews #Friday #Gainesville   https://t.co/MaZJ98UaA7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aHaySan: 46 cases and 0 deaths reported today. Totals are now 24,021 cases, 262 deaths, and a two week positivity range between 1.92-5.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A joint effort at Ben Hill Griffin Stadium yielded 17,250 vaccinations in its first week, as officials aim to ramp up to 20,000 weekly doses through mid-May. #LocalNews #Gainesville #Thursday   https://t.co/Il3wtVJ8yl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Sports beat: Buchholz boys lacrosse advances to district championship game  https://t.co/ZawFcvJEog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FDOT to evaluate safety of road in front of Alachua Learning Academy after last week's head-on crash.   @suzettemcook has the details:  https://t.co/nRzXUiW63v via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ch_Anderson_: I had a wonderful time chatting with Mike Galland of the @ShepherdFlorida radio show. I shared with Mikes listeners my e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Power of the Purse raises money for the domestic violence centers economic empowerment program. Traditionally in October, this year it's happening now through April 17!  Don't miss out! @peacefulpaths #Gainesville #tuesdayvibe   https://t.co/NOAf0qLiza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Experts explain what's up with all those caterpillars we're all seeing (spoiler alert: they sting!): https://t.co/lRrU3NzNiz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You know those vending machines games that seem to never allow you to get the best prizes?   Well, Gainesville resident T.J. Pyche proved they're not rigged!    @suzettemcook has the story:  https://t.co/gvmUXpYVOU via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This month @NewsGainesville is highlighting the #opioid epidemic with a series of interviews. Last week, we heard from a recovering addict, and this week, we hear from family members who have been affected: https://t.co/OKFGyi5RoS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After a head-on collision in front of an Alachua school, the principal is taking action: https://t.co/NYl6B6tx3p via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UF's Disability Resource Center is hiring four ASL interpreters -- which would give UF the most of any school in the state.   @DrB_OnMedia has the details: https://t.co/FPNULOm441 @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than three decades after a serial killer paralyzed Gainesville, ABC's "20/20" program is airing a true crime special feature on the infamous Gainesville Ripper. #gainesville #localnews #Friday   https://t.co/mMK4mv8rZz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Newberry Commissioner Ricky Coleman has released a statement on his condition and recovery.   @suzettemcook reports: https://t.co/uGTHcmFvRd via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Sports beat: Clay (Green Cove Springs) edges Santa Fe in No. 1 vs. No. 2 showdown  https://t.co/bLJFbzokAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShepherdFlorida: It was a pleasure to meet Rev. Charles Brown, Senior Vice President  Chief Program Officer of #BridgesInternational.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heads up: Florida Highway Patrol reports there's a 26-acre controlled burn today in Paynes Prairie State Park in Alachua County.   FHP says the fire may affect travel on US 441 today and into overnight hours.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess what? @Publix is joining the self-checkout trend.   Reporter @suzettemcook has the scoop: https://t.co/EjF34M59rO via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrB_OnMedia: Couldnt let @CheneyAUG write ALL the #Masters related stories this week. ;) https://t.co/wb03h9pI0x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, hello, #Masters with fans. We've missed you.   Between highlights from Augusta, check out Camille Broadway's report on how golf courses could key a great bee comeback: https://t.co/RBQYqyw8uR  @DrB_OnMedia via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@GainesvillePD is offering a $10,000 reward for information to help solve 27 cold cases.   We have details and a link to the list here: https://t.co/M7YXcXru4m via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A vehicle crash in front of an Alachua school has parents calling for change:  https://t.co/7OvJ9ThDEZ via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Santa Fe baseball hosts Clay (Green Cove Springs) in a key district game  @SFHSRaiderBSBL is ranked No. 1 in Class 4A, while]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can see the full roster and team stories here: https://t.co/IusnFL28xJ https://t.co/ThoKntXKqv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The School Board of Alachua County tackled testing misinformation at Tuesday's meeting: https://t.co/qBNeUGGi5V via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crabfest is a long-time Williston tradition, but it won't be happening this year. @suzettemcook explains why: https://t.co/Ga3PtKmiH8 via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A teen driver totaled an Alachua County Fire Rescue ambulance on I-75: https://t.co/u9y4Rfd0fq via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DEAWashingtonDC: Its a gorgeous morning    for another Tip of the Week!  Check it out   And check out https://t.co/oQyKLsKrKy fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A pair of Lincoln Middle School students grabbed two of four statewide spots to compete in a national math competition next month.   We've got details here: https://t.co/vaJiRFJwNs via @AlachuaSchools and @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The two candidates running for a Newberry Commission seat in next week's election will face off in a debate tonight.   @suzettemcook has the details: https://t.co/ritVvGXLrd via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Dyngus Day!  If you aren't already familiar with it, Tim Price (@66cubs) explains here: https://t.co/qXJxIGezvR via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, and check out the Kyle Baldry interview at @NewsGainesville: https://t.co/DQrCRPbFfn https://t.co/GNWjeeG7pl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking: @UFHealth announces plans to vaccinate up to 5,000 people Monday at huge stadium event: https://t.co/U20O20KN3r via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GainesvilleGov: The 2021 Neighbor Survey is now open! Tell us what we are doing well  what we can improve. Have a say in setting our p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Santa Fe stars Ross, Jenkins lead the 2021 All Area Basketball team for big school boys: https://t.co/3qtDZzI58k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@CoachElHarris leads the inaugural class of Coaches of the Year for the 2021 All Area Basketball Team presented by @NewsGainesville and @ThePrepZone: https://t.co/pIhPuVrf7R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In our latest Holiday History feature, Tim Price (@66cubs) explores the origins of #GoodFriday: https://t.co/NWyT9muu6O via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ridaught: Sports beat: Gainesville softball gets the win on Senior Night  https://t.co/HSx9Wtz2J4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alevine014: Alright, @PresidentFuchs and @UF, you actually got me for a second....  I have to admit.... https://t.co/XMcgoAfgJY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Authorities have recovered the children. Details at the same link below: https://t.co/htwXCuIyVe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heads up: @RegalMovies has moved back the dates for reopening its Gainesville theaters: https://t.co/rn0juJ9vQ8 via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're like us, your phone went off this morning with an Amber Alert from the Columbia County Sheriff's Office.   We've got details on that abduction here: https://t.co/r8IWLzfWWB via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking for some heartwarming #ThursdayThoughts? Checkout this couple celebrating their 70th wedding anniversary!   https://t.co/KEKCyGrx6m via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShepherdFlorida: On Thursday, April 1st we will be hearing from recovered addicts on what its really like to struggle with addiction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Click below to check out our picks for the 2021 All Area small school boys basketball team! Congratulations guys! #Basketball @ThePrepZone   https://t.co/oJC59uQ517]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know today is #ManateeAppreciationDay?   Florida Fish and Wildlife is urging vigilance to protect these mammals that are dying in increasingly high numbers: https://t.co/6gPRnvqDuu via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At Tuesday's BOCC meeting @KenCornell18 and fellow commissioners discussed the likelihood of increasing property taxes this year.   @suzettemcook has the details: https://t.co/cyhu8anO47 via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anthony92662839 Thanks for tweeting the story! When your players get their plaques, please tweet us a photo and we'll share it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Anthony92662839: All Area: Columbia backcourt anchors big school girls https://t.co/aWk8seVQXE via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part two of our All Area Girls Basketball team selections!  Presented by Mainstreet Daily News and The Prep Zone! Great job ladies!  @LeyahHouston @NahaviyaPaxton @anzarria_100 #basketball   https://t.co/ayoRmCa898]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want some good news?   The big screen is about to light up again in Gainesville!   @suzettemcook reports on @RegalMovies latest announcement for @NewsGainesville: https://t.co/icKCvqtrqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today the Alachua County Sheriff's Office announced the arrest of two men it says are confirmed gang members: https://t.co/3qY8bgUxN2 via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @THSlady_tigers: Congrats Bri and Samarie on being named 1st team All-Area. https://t.co/57RMTV8CXy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Presenting the 2021 All Area Girls Basketball Team for small schools! The first of 5 articles coming out this week-- click below to read more!!  Congratulations ladies! #basketball @ThePrepZone   https://t.co/ZZ94eUvqac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight @GainesvilleGov Commissioner-at-large Reina Saco and City Manager @leefeldman will host a town hall to discuss affordable housing, #COVID19 and more: https://t.co/n4K9rth6qG via @NewsGainesville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CorfmanParks: Imagine if this occurred on the @RideSunRail or @GoBrightline  #TrainsGoneWild https://t.co/ckbR8xUkot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking: Authorities say vandals took a Newberry train for a joy rideand caused $60,000 in damages.   @suzettemcook has the story:   https://t.co/kteIkiavsH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UF researchers are looking for students to participate in a major study about #COVID19 spread among college students.   Details here:  https://t.co/SNYZeMmdC3]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>