<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Jill Mortimer has a fantastic plan for Hartlepool. Shell work with me to deliver more quality local jobs, extra investment  more police on the beat.   On Thursday, vote Conservative  deliver the positive change Hartlepool needs. https://t.co/k5Y9g0DFKk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives:  Your vote is crucial to help us deliver on your priorities  On Thursday May 6th #VoteConservative https://t.co/oarKHP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conservative Mayors across the country such as @andy4wm in the West Midlands are delivering jobs and investment while keeping your taxes low.  On Thursday, vote for the Conservatives. https://t.co/XgN8yAtUus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight we remember PCSO Julia James.   My thoughts are with her friends and family.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday I visited the fantastic Barry Island with the Welsh Conservatives.  They have a great plan to create 65,000 new jobs  bring massive investment in transport infrastructure.  So on Thursday, vote for @WelshConserv  https://t.co/o03ZvrWxP5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: Today Prime Ministers @BorisJohnson and @NarendraModi agreed a 2030 Roadmap for UK-India relations.  Here are some of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today @NarendraModi and I spoke about how we can overcome the pandemic and strengthen the ties between our two countries.  We agreed an ambitious plan to bring our economies and people closer together  the beginning of a new era in the UK-India relationship.   https://t.co/1BD3Na8lw7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: More than 6,500 new jobs will be created around the UK thanks to 1 billion of new UK-India trade and investment.   h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives: 48 hours to go  Vote Conservative  https://t.co/0pAvn5uMhk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives: More than 50 MILLION doses of coronavirus vaccine have been administered across the UK  https://t.co/UD64JLmddp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive been campaigning today with Tees Valley Mayor @BenHouchen. His plan is delivering massive investment and new jobs to the area, including 18,000 good local jobs at the new Freeport.  Vote for Ben Houchen on Thursday so he can keep delivering! https://t.co/NoZqybOCTU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks to the extraordinary effort of everyone involved, 50 million doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have now been given to people across the United Kingdom.   Please do come forward and get your jab when asked to do so. https://t.co/T2X38I2zxB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Labour have taken Hartlepool for granted for 57 years. On Thursday, vote Conservative  deliver the positive change Hartlepool needs.  @Jill4Hartlepool has a fantastic plan for Hartlepool. Shell work with me to deliver more local jobs, extra investment  more police on the beat. https://t.co/7Bf3mcK4DA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: The legal limit on the number of mourners at funerals will be lifted in England at Step 3 of the Roadmap, so family an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks to the help and generosity of @boconline, last night a delivery of much-needed oxygen cylinders was sent from the UK to India.  We stand by our friends in India during these difficult times. https://t.co/o4b1sikVL6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My message on Northern Irelands centenary year. https://t.co/x5giX4bMwT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am deeply moved by the surge of support the British people have provided to the people of India and am pleased the UK Government has been able to play our part in providing life-saving assistance.  The UK will always be there for India in its time of need. https://t.co/RQdiZZJyxl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 million people across our United Kingdom have received two doses of a COVID vaccine.  Thank you to everyone who has made this possible.  Please keep coming forward to get your jabs to give yourself maximum protection from the virus. https://t.co/oZ1mm8DsVD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know how challenging this time has been for those in care homes.    With data continuing to head in the right direction  as restrictions ease, I am pleased that from 4 May residents can now leave their homes to reunite with their loved ones outdoors.   https://t.co/48OMCCCWTQ https://t.co/zGmw5uMFcO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im very grateful to the postmasters who shared their harrowing stories with me yesterday about the terrible impact the Post Office Horizon IT dispute has had on their lives.   We will stand with them to find the answers to what went wrong and ensure this never happens again. https://t.co/bSQlT6qVxC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: If you're aged 40 or over, or if you turn 40 before 1 July 2021, you can now book your COVID-19 vaccine.   https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives:  Were getting on with delivering our manifesto promise of 20,000 police, with 8,771 already recruited!   On T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you want to give London a fresh start, if you want safer streets and a mayor who backs the police then vote for @ShaunBaileyUK on Thursday 6th May. https://t.co/4WF7qBlHm7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On what would have been @CaptainTomMoores 101st birthday, its brilliant to see the nation taking part in #CaptainTom100.   His astonishing life brought hope and joy to millions across the country, and raised an incredible 38.9 million for the NHS. https://t.co/cU9FmvRIs2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Devastating scenes at the Lag B'Omer festival in Israel. My thoughts are with the Israeli people and those who have lost loved ones in this tragedy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last night I was delighted to join an Iftar with some of the many Muslim key workers and volunteers who have been helping us in the fight against COVID-19. https://t.co/WGzSxdxKv2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its fantastic to see young people back at school and seeing their friends again.   Weve put children and young people at the heart of our recovery plans, and we will continue to give them all our support. https://t.co/bJBTpOk8nr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: We have recruited , new police officers, beating our target of putting , more officers on our streets in the f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pritipatel: One of @BorisJohnsons key promises was to put an extra 20,000 police officers on our streets to cut crime.  Im delighted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm proud to say we've recruited 8,771 new police officers in England and Wales, well ahead of our target of 6,000 more officers in the first year of our recruitment drive, and 20,000 over three years. https://t.co/FMWas20DKZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our brilliant Vaccines Taskforce has secured an extra 60 million doses of the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine. This is fantastic news and an important addition in keeping us protected into the autumn and winter. https://t.co/fGARe7h8Wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want to thank Arlene Foster @DUPleader for her dedication to the people of Northern Ireland over many years. She will continue to play a vital role as First Minister until June and I hope that she stays in public service for years to come.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great news that the European Parliament has voted overwhelmingly in favour of our zero tariffs, zero quotas Trade and Cooperation Agreement.   Now is the time to look forward to a new relationship with the EU and a more Global Britain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines have saved thousands of lives so far and now this data shows they could also protect others by cutting transmission of the virus  which will be crucial in helping us beat the pandemic.  I urge everyone to book their jab when called.  https://t.co/DOCoeFYjyC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dame Cheryl Gillan was a great servant to the people of Chesham  Amersham. She made a huge contribution to our party and country, and we will sorely miss her.  My thoughts are with her family and friends. https://t.co/CjSLQ6JsOg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today I spoke with President Kenyatta @StateHouseKenya ahead of the joint UK-Kenya Global Education Summit.  We agreed to work closely together to ensure 175 million more children get into school around the world. Theres a huge amount the  and  can achieve together.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A quarter of UK adults have received 2 doses of a COVID vaccine, giving them maximum protection against the virus.   This is a huge achievement made possible by the tireless work of so many across our country.   Please keep coming forward to get vaccinated when you are called. https://t.co/yDPkehJJNV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fantastic news that 16,500 young people have now started jobs through our Kickstart scheme.   These fully-subsidised placements for 16 to 24-year-olds offer a vital first foot on the jobs ladder.   Find out more about the scheme and how to get involved: https://t.co/XYOPwZ1V61 https://t.co/EwaQixqzIY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fantastic to be in Wales today, campaigning with our @WelshConserv candidates.   The team have a plan to drive forward Wales' economic recovery, creating 65,000 new, well-paid jobs and investing in infrastructure like the A55.  Vote Conservative on May 6th. https://t.co/OKfslGXy5d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran's decision to sentence Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe to another year in prison is cruel, inhumane and wholly unjustified. She must be allowed to return to her family in the UK and we will continue to do all we can to get her home.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We stand side by side with India in the shared fight against COVID-19. Vital medical equipment is on its way from the UK to India to help stop the tragic loss of life from the virus and well continue to work closely with the Indian government during this difficult time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the story of the UK vaccine rollout which has already saved thousands of lives.  A huge thank you to everyone involved from the scientists, to our NHS, the Armed Forces and the many volunteers.   I urge everyone to take up the jab when youre offered it. https://t.co/sXWzG952pG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today we pay our respects to the ANZACs who fought at Gallipoli, and remember all those who have fought with courage so that we may live in peace today. Their bravery, fortitude  spirit of mateship live on.    They will not be forgotten. #AnzacDay2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: A Beacon of Hope: The UK Vaccine Story.     Watch below or on Youtube: https://t.co/C0ETBduoTN https://t.co/ELY77ZES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK is hosting a Global Education Summit this summer and leading efforts in our @G7 Presidency to get 40 million more girls into school.   I spoke to @Malala this morning about how girls education is one of the smartest investments countries can make as we build back better.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a landmark achievement by the team at @UniofOxford who developed the COVID-19 vaccine.   Malaria kills hundreds of thousands of children a year. An effective vaccine holds out the possibility of ending this global tragedy.   https://t.co/9ZiKfzO27s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I welcome the Court of Appeal's decision to overturn the convictions of 39 former sub-postmasters in the Horizon dispute, an appalling injustice which has had a devastating impact on these families for years.  Lessons should and will be learnt to ensure this never happens again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy St. George's Day!  https://t.co/ivCHymH0UP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The worlds tropical forests are the lungs of our planet and yet were losing these great, teeming ecosystems at an unconscionable rate.    Im pleased the UK is joining this hugely exciting coalition to protect our tropical forests and tackle climate change. https://t.co/qb65SDhXX9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our shared duty is to honour and remember all those, wherever they lived and whatever their background, who laid down their lives for our freedoms at the moment of greatest peril.  My statement on the Commonwealth War Graves Commission report. https://t.co/ft6LxGzGPh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can build back better from this pandemic by building back greener.   #LeadersClimateSummit https://t.co/Uu9Xc8gr6d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets make this decade the moment of decisive change in the fight against climate change.   My statement at the #LeadersClimateSummit convened by @POTUS: https://t.co/HJhYmwRWMc  #BuildBackGreener | @COP26 | #EarthDay https://t.co/Ke1CXMUFmd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: My statement at the #LeadersClimateSummit convened by @POTUS https://t.co/wlpoFbvwcv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The commitment from @POTUS today to cut US emissions by 50-52% by 2030 is a game-changer. It will have a transformative impact in the global fight against climate change.   I commend the President's leadership and look forward to working together for our planet ahead of @COP26.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In supporting #StephenLawrenceDay we are reminded of Stephen's many talents, and our duty to stop racism and give young people the best possible future.   My thoughts are with Stephens parents Doreen and Neville, and the many families that have lost loved ones in their prime.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've reached a significant milestone with 1 in 5 adults now having had two COVID-19 vaccine doses. This is a huge UK-wide effort that has already saved thousands of lives.   Thank you to everyone involved. https://t.co/pGoSpyMC1O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would like to send my warm wishes to Her Majesty The Queen on her 95th birthday.  I have always had the highest admiration for Her Majesty and her service to this country and the Commonwealth.  I am proud to serve as her Prime Minister.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I welcome last nights announcement. This is the right result for football fans, clubs, and communities across the country. We must continue to protect our cherished national game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was appalled by the death of George Floyd and welcome this verdict.  My thoughts tonight are with George Floyds family and friends.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The decision by Chelsea and Manchester City is  if confirmed  absolutely the right one and I commend them for it.  I hope the other clubs involved in the European Super League will follow their lead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccination programme has shown what the UK can achieve when we bring together our brightest minds.   Our new Antivirals Taskforce will seek to provide another vital defence against any future increase in infections, saving more lives. https://t.co/VpGnxPr6bf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: An update on coronavirus (20 April 2021) https://t.co/sj7DxbLrGT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were setting the most ambitious target to cut emissions in the world.   We want to see world leaders follow our lead in the run up to @COP26, as we will only build back greener and protect our planet if we come together to take action. https://t.co/EvQhLDGbEx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Earlier @OliverDowden and I met with representatives from the @FA, @PremierLeague and football fan groups to discuss action against the proposed European Super League.    No action is off the table and we are exploring every possibility to ensure these proposals are stopped. https://t.co/QZMGRnXDcF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives: We're helping people get on the housing ladder with just a 5% deposit through the new Government backed mortgage guarant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its fantastic that weve been able to enjoy some more freedoms with family and friends since 12 April.  As we continue with our cautious roadmap, please follow the rules and remember hands, face, space and fresh air. https://t.co/qdqBlX7K5l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to be back at the pub again, and to see so many reunited with friends and family.    Weve worked so hard to get to this point. Lets keep going. Remember hands, face, space  fresh air. https://t.co/g3ApAkpNNM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The clubs involved must answer to their fans and the wider footballing community before taking any further steps. (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plans for a European Super League would be very damaging for football and we support football authorities in taking action.   They would strike at the heart of the domestic game, and will concern fans across the country. (1/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Memoriam HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, 1921-2021. https://t.co/QoKgxOYnt5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: The Prime Minister paid tribute to His Royal Highness The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh yesterday at Britannia Roya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HRH The Duke of Edinburgh incarnated the finest traditions of the @RoyalNavy.   Today I saw cadets become officers at Britannia Royal Naval College, Dartmouth, the college The Duke passed out of prior to his distinguished naval career.   Our thoughts remain with HM The Queen. https://t.co/ANHtrpD2Y4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Vaisakhi to Sikhs in Britain and around the world.   #Vaisakhi signals hope and renewal, and as we look ahead  cautiously but optimistically  to what the coming months may bring, I want to say a huge thank you to Sikhs for your forbearance and fortitude. https://t.co/RAByjFfIZb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @JoeMurphyLondon on a well-earned retirement after a spectacular innings in the lobby.   You were always as fair and as kind as you could be under the circumstances.  I wish you all the best for the future.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have hit a hugely significant milestone by offering jabs to everyone in the nine highest risk groups, giving them the protection vaccines provide against COVID-19.   I want to thank everyone involved in the vaccine rollout, which has already saved many thousands of lives. https://t.co/VQWo9axoLG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ramadan Mubarak to all those observing Islams holiest month this year.    Im afraid that again this year it is necessary to follow the rules to stay safe but I hope this month of fast, prayer and charity brings much peace and reflection to all Muslims.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Earlier I paid tribute to HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh in the @HouseOfCommons.   The Duke's unstinting service gives us all a model of selflessness and of putting others before ourselves. https://t.co/Tq9lH2up3I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I spent many happy hours sparring with her on Question Time. She will be much missed. (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sad to hear about Baroness Shirley Williams, a kind and thoughtful member of the once radical centre left. Even when we disagreed - as we often did - she had the gift of sounding so completely reasonable at all times. (1/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday was a record-breaking day with 475,230 people receiving second doses. More than 7 million have now been fully vaccinated.   Thanks to everyone involved in this extraordinary effort which has already saved thousands of lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is ten years since the death of my friend Sir Simon Milton, an outstanding servant of London and of his country. We miss you, Simon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My statement on the death of HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh. https://t.co/cjlSsERXPV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On the death of HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh. https://t.co/rZlbY1matF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The science is clear: vaccines save lives.    New @PHE_UK analysis shows COVID-19 vaccinations have prevented over 10,000 deaths.   Its important that you book your jab when the NHS contacts you.   https://t.co/YxlPKeUKn5 https://t.co/R7SQ3xIp1R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last night in Truro I saw the outstanding work of doctors and nurses at the Royal Cornwall Hospital. Thank you to the entire team and the whole of our NHS  https://t.co/bKGVSWeaaJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 million people have now had their second jab.  Yesterday over 400,000 second doses were given.  A huge thank you to everyone helping to make this happen  it is an incredible achievement that has already saved thousands of lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It was fantastic to meet with businesses in Cornwall to hear how they are preparing to reopen and welcome customers back on Monday.  The next stage in our roadmap is a significant step towards reclaiming the freedoms COVID has taken from us. https://t.co/s7Ry99TIsX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sad to hear about the loss of Peter Ainsworth - a delightful colleague  passionate about his causes, especially the environment. We shared a corridor  often found ourselves charging late for the division. He has been taken far too young. My thoughts with Claire  their family.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am deeply concerned by the scenes of violence in Northern Ireland, especially attacks on PSNI who are protecting the public and businesses, attacks on a bus driver and the assault of a journalist. The way to resolve differences is through dialogue, not violence or criminality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We set out our roadmap and were sticking to it.   Thanks to your efforts and the vaccine rollout, from Monday we will move to Step Two of our roadmap  reopening shops, gyms, hairdressers and outdoor hospitality of all kinds. https://t.co/LJojqMpAuY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will follow todays updated advice, which should allow people of all ages to continue to have full confidence in vaccines, helping us save lives and cautiously return towards normality. 3/3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the regulators have said, this vaccine is safe, effective and has already saved thousands of lives  and the vast majority of people should continue to take it when offered. 2/3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @MHRAgovuk and JCVI for your important work looking at the AstraZeneca vaccine, which has updated on the potential for extremely rare side effects. 1/3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Moderna vaccine rollout begins today, starting with Carmarthen in Wales. We have ordered 17 million doses that will be going into arms across the UK in the coming weeks.  Please get your jab as soon as you are contacted.  https://t.co/i9fAMASKD3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@AstraZeneca has been at the heart of our fight against coronavirus, and they are also playing a big part in our efforts to #BuildBackBetter from the pandemic and make the UK a science superpower. https://t.co/3TtBKzv80x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very promising news that the @ValnevaSE vaccine shows a strong immune response and will progress to Phase 3 trials.  If it is successful and meets our robust safety standards this vaccine will be manufactured in Scotland, providing a crucial weapon in our battle against COVID. https://t.co/Xr79bIGsmS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I spoke to President Zelenskyy @ZelenskyyUa this evening regarding our concerns about destabilising Russian military activity on Ukraines border.  I reiterated the UKs unwavering support for Ukraines sovereignty and territorial integrity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We set out our roadmap and were sticking to it.  It is by being cautious, by monitoring the data at every stage, and by following the rules  remembering hands, face, space and fresh air  that we hope together to make this roadmap to freedom irreversible. https://t.co/EQM74Muu3p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: An update on COVID-19 (5 April 2021) https://t.co/7MwrBSklfm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Always full of wise advice and good humour, she was much loved on all sides of the House of Commons and will be sorely missed. My sincere condolences to her family and friends. (2/2)]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>