<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW, many of which are open seven days a week. To find your nearest clinic visit https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is asking everyone in these areas to be especially vigilant in monitoring for symptoms, and if they appear get tested and isolate immediately until a negative result is received.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This catchment includes about 42,000 people and takes sewage from the following suburbs: Dulwich Hill, Marrickville, Summer Hill, Lewisham, Ashfield, Haberfield, Petersham, Lilyfield and Leichhardt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health was notified this evening that fragments of the virus that causes COVID-19 have been detected in the Marrickville Sewage Network.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some details from the venues above have been updated from earlier today, and some are new venues. The full list of venues of concern will be updated shortly and will be available at https://t.co/pqkRdfh3cR. People are urged to check the website regularly for updates.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ PUBLIC HEALTH ALERT  NEW VENUES AND SEWAGE DETECTION   NSW Health can advise that new venues of concern have been identified and others have been updated as part of ongoing investigations into a COVID-19 case reported earlier today. https://t.co/dhtFBkrcdm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tdclancy Hi Tracey, Prince of Wales Hospital COVID-19 Assessment Clinic (Building 14B, Ground Floor, Avoca Street, Randwick) is currently open 8am to 10pm, seven days a week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksyd2015 @GregHuntMP Thank you for your feedback @ksyd2015. We're looking into this now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*UPDATE* Albion Street Centre Laverty Pathology Pop Up Clinic will be open 8am-8pm today (Wednesday 5 May), and then 8am-6pm Monday-Friday. Saturday and Sunday hours are still to be confirmed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These venues are in addition to those announced earlier today, with the full list of venues of concern available at https://t.co/pqkRdfh3cR. People are urged to check the NSW Health website regularly for updates, as new venues are added.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone who attended any of the following newly identified venues at the times specified is asked to immediately get tested and isolate until NSW Health provides further advice. This applies to everyone, including those who have been partially or fully vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ PUBLIC HEALTH ALERT  NEW VENUES   NSW Health has been advised of new venues of concern in Sydneys eastern suburbs and CBD visited by a confirmed case of COVID-19. https://t.co/jOZIjDtxqx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information and to find your nearest clinic, visit https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roselands Drive Through Clinic - Off Roseland Avenue, Roselands Shopping Centre open air car park, 2196. Open 8.30am  4pm 7 days a week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer Hill Drive Through Clinic - 7 Prospect Road, Inner West Council Works Depot, 2130. Open 8.30am  4pm 7 days a week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albion Street Centre Laverty Pathology Pop Up Clinic - Albion Centre, Crown Street Entrance, 150 Albion St, Surry Hills NSW 2010. Open 8am-8pm Monday-Friday, to be confirmed for Saturday and Sunday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rose Bay Laverty Pathology Drive-through Clinic - Lyne Park, Vickery Avenue Car Park, Rose Bay. Open 8am-10pm Monday-Friday, 8am-6pm Saturday and Sunday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bondi Junction Laverty Pathology Drive-through Clinic - 38 Waverly Street Level 2 Car park Bondi Junction. Open 8am-10pm Monday-Friday, 8am-6pm Saturday and Sunday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ St Vincent's Hospital (East Sydney Community and Arts Centre) - 34 Burton Street, Darlinghurst NSW 2010, access from palmer Street entrance. Open 8am-10pm Monday-Friday, 8am-4pm Saturday and Sunday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clinics are open at the following locations. Bookings are not required unless specified:    Bondi Beach Drive-through Clinic - Park Drive North, Bondi Beach, drive-through entry on junction of Campbell Parade  Beach Road. Open 8am-10pm Monday-Friday, 8am-4pm Saturday  Sunday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you experience mild COVID-19 symptoms its vital to come forward for testing immediately, even if you have been fully or partially vaccinated. Please self-isolate until a negative COVID-19 result is received.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 #testingclinics are open with extended hours in the Sydney and the Eastern Suburbs areas.  See full thread for details. https://t.co/VI9wEPwFVN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksyd2015 @GregHuntMP The Australian Governments vaccine eligibility tracker can also be used to book your vaccine, if you are eligible and bookings are available. It does not ask any questions relating to religion: https://t.co/RwqJh5wWit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1997_lyndsay Hi Lyndsay,  A pre-departure negative COVID-19 test is required for travelling or transiting through Australia. For more information see https://t.co/lwRyH2KpoB.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW, many of which are open seven days a week. To find your nearest clinic visit https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This list of venues of concern will be updated regularly as investigations continue. People are urged to check the NSW Health website regularly: https://t.co/pqkRdfh3cR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone who attended one of the following venues at the times specified is asked to immediately get tested and isolate until NSW Health provides further information.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Close contacts are being urgently contacted, tested and isolating. The man visited a number of venues while potentially infectious.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW PUBLIC HEALTH ALERT  COVID-19 CASE  NSW Health has been notified this morning of a new COVID-19 case in a person who resides in Sydneys eastern suburbs.  Urgent investigations into the source of the infection and contact tracing are underway. https://t.co/8vX7sIrjCB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Dr Jeremy McAnulty provides a #COVID19 update for Wednesday 5 May 2021. https://t.co/2ATcf2aFg3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is treating 108 COVID-19 cases, one of whom is in intensive care and being ventilated. Most cases (97 per cent) are being treated in non-acute, out-of-hospital care, including returned travellers in the Special Health Accommodation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW. To find your nearest clinic, visit: https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As these latest cases in Perth show, COVID-19 can re-emerge at any time. NSW Health urges everyone with the slightest of cold-like symptoms to immediately isolate and be tested, and to remain in isolation until a negative result is received.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health reminds all travellers that an entry declaration must be completed if you have been to WA within 14 days of entering NSW.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone currently in NSW who has been in Perth since 27 April should check if they have been to a place of high concern. If you have, please immediately isolate, get tested, and call NSW Health on 1800 943 553.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Due to the latest COVID-19 cases in Western Australia, anyone who has been in Perth since 27 April should, prior to travelling to NSW, check the NSW COVID-19 concerns notice and exemption at  https://t.co/Oy2F0mKApH to determine if they have been to any places of high concern.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health administered 4,588 vaccines in the 24 hours to 8pm last night. The total number of vaccines administered in NSW is now 695,724, with 219,594 doses administered by NSW Health to 8pm last night and 476,130 administered by the GP network and other providers to 11.59pm.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There were 13,543 tests reported to 8pm last night, compared with the previous days total of 5,601.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A previously reported overseas acquired case, omitted from reporting yesterday due to a record update, has been re-instated in the total case count. This brings the total number of cases in NSW since the beginning of the pandemic to 5,317.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW recorded no new locally acquired cases of COVID-19 in the 24 hours to 8pm last night.  Ten new cases were acquired overseas to 8pm last night. https://t.co/IP9EhQHasL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NSWChiefNMO: Happy International Day of the Midwife to all the talented midwives @NSWHealth I hope you reflect on the contribution you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JessOreilly1997 Hi Jess. Detailed information is available in weekly COVID-19 surveillance reports: https://t.co/qty0m40Hot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is treating 105 COVID-19 cases, one of whom is in intensive care and being ventilated. Most cases (98 per cent) are being treated in non-acute, out-of-hospital care, including returned travellers in the Special Health Accommodation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW. To find your nearest clinic, visit: https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health urges everyone with the slightest of cold-like symptoms to immediately isolate and be tested, and to remain in isolation until a negative result is received.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is contacting people who have arrived from Perth since Tuesday 27 April, and has screening teams at Sydney Airport to meet new arrivals.  As these latest cases in Perth show, COVID-19 can re-emerge at any time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is working closely with our counterparts in WA and will update advice as necessary to ensure the safety of the NSW community.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health reminds all travellers that an entry declaration must be completed if you have been to WA within 14 days of entering NSW: https://t.co/MAR2iV31SL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone currently in NSW who has been in Perth since 27 April should check if they have been to a place of high concern. If you have, please immediately isolate, get tested, and call NSW Health on 1800 943 553.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW COVID-19 concerns notice and exemption: https://t.co/Oy2F0mKApH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Due to the latest COVID-19 cases in Western Australia, anyone who has been in Perth since Tuesday 27 April should, prior to travelling to NSW, check the NSW COVID-19 concerns notice and exemption to determine if they have been to any places of high concern.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The total number of vaccines administered in NSW is now 677,262, with 215,006 doses administered by NSW Health to 8pm last night and 462,256 administered by the GP network and other providers to 11.59pm on Sunday 2 May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health administered 3,984 vaccines in the 24 hours to 8pm last night.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There were 5,601 tests reported to 8pm last night, compared with the previous days total of 7,920.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW recorded no new locally acquired cases of COVID-19 in the 24 hours to 8pm last night.  Seven new cases were acquired overseas to 8pm last night, bringing the total number of cases in NSW since the beginning of the pandemic to 5,306. https://t.co/dB0cTs03t5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Dr Jeremy McAnulty provides a #COVID19 update for Tuesday 4 May 2021. https://t.co/9nJxFciXKx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you or your partner considering IVF? To ease the cost of pre-IVF fertility testing, the NSW Government offers a one-time $500 rebate to eligible residents. For more information, visit the NSW Health website: https://t.co/UVGQ6HUtjS https://t.co/e4v2HT6bEK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@manpageman @_vTg_ @shutter_j If you need information about COVID-19 or the COVID-19 vaccines, call the National coronavirus and COVID-19 vaccine helpline on 1800 020 080. Please note the call centre is unable to book appointments on your behalf.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is treating 101 COVID-19 cases, one of whom is in intensive care and being ventilated. Most cases (98 per cent) are being treated in non-acute, out-of-hospital care, including returned travellers in the Special Health Accommodation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW. To find your nearest clinic, visit: https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As these latest cases in Perth show, COVID-19 can re-emerge at any time. NSW Health urges everyone with the slightest of cold-like symptoms to immediately isolate and be tested, and to remain in isolation until a negative result is received.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is contacting people who have arrived from Perth since Tuesday 27 April, and has screening teams at Sydney Airport to meet new arrivals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is working closely with our counterparts in WA and will update advice as necessary to ensure the safety of the NSW community.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health reminds all travellers that there continues to be a requirement to complete an entry declaration if you have been in WA in the previous 14 days before entering NSW: https://t.co/MAR2iV31SL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone currently in NSW who has been in Perth since Tuesday 27 April should immediately check if they have been to a place of high concern. If you have attended any of these venues at the relevant times, please immediately isolate, get tested, and call NSW Health on 1800 943 553.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This provides tailored advice for people in NSW who went to locations visited by confirmed cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prior to travelling to NSW, anyone who has been in Perth since Tuesday 27 April should check the NSW COVID-19 concerns notice and exemption to determine whether they have been to any places of high concern: https://t.co/Oy2F0mKApH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- They have published a list of locations visited by confirmed COVID-19 cases while potentially infectious here: https://t.co/wb6RF7geFb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Western Australian Government announced on Saturday 1 May that a Perth hotel quarantine worker and two of his household contacts had tested positive to COVID-19 -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Healths vaccination clinics generally operate Monday to Friday. As such, there may be limited or no vaccines administered on weekends and public holidays due to planned closures.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The total number of vaccines administered in NSW is now 672,362, with 211,022 doses administered by NSW Health to 8pm last night and 461,340 administered by the GP network and other providers to 11.59pm on Saturday 1 May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health administered 18,686 #COVID19Vaccines during the week ending Sunday 2 May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There were 7,920 tests reported to 8pm last night, compared with the previous days total of 9,000.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW recorded no new locally acquired cases of #COVID19 in the 24 hours to 8pm last night.   Five new cases were acquired overseas to 8pm last night, bringing the total number of cases in NSW since the beginning of the pandemic to 5,300. https://t.co/rkC3kCiYHA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As smoke from hazard reduction burns causes poor air quality across Sydney and parts of NSW, NSW Health is warning people to take precautions. Monitor air quality online: https://t.co/1JSuTtPpSd https://t.co/LMRlBPxDne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mhcsnsw: We wish all celebrating today, a joyous and safe Orthodox Easter.   Hear from Reverend Father Fadi Nemme, St. Michael the Arch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most cases (98 per cent) are being treated in non-acute, out-of-hospital care, including returned travellers in the Special Health Accommodation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To find your nearest clinic, visit: https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.  NSW Health is treating 103 COVID-19 cases, one of whom is in intensive care and being ventilated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health urges everyone with the slightest of cold-like symptoms to immediately isolate and be tested, and to remain in isolation until a negative result is received.   There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health has begun contacting people who have arrived from Perth since Tuesday 27 April, and deployed screening teams to Sydney Airport from 5.30am today (Sunday 2 May) to meet new arrivals.  As these latest cases in Perth show, COVID-19 can re-emerge at any time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is working closely with our counterparts in WA and will update advice as necessary to ensure the safety of the NSW community.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health reminds all travellers that there continues to be a requirement to complete an entry declaration if you have been in WA in the previous 14 days before entering NSW.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone currently in NSW who has been in Perth since Tuesday 27 April should immediately check if they have been in a place of high concern. If you have attended any of these venues at the relevant times, please immediately isolate, get tested, and call NSW Health on 1800 943 553.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prior to travelling to NSW, anyone who has been in Perth since Tuesday 27 April should immediately check the NSW COVID-19 concerns notice and exemption to determine whether they have been to any places of high concern.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[on Friday 30 April.    The Western Australian Government yesterday announced a Perth hotel quarantine worker and two of his household contacts had tested positive to COVID-19, and published a list of venues of concern these positive cases visited while potentially infectious.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health administered 646 vaccines in the 24 hours to 8pm last night. The total number of vaccines administered in NSW is now 667,889, with 211,022 doses administered by NSW Health to 8pm last night and 456,867 administered by the GP network and other providers, to 11.59pm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There were 9,000 tests reported to 8pm last night, compared with the previous days total of 10,227.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW recorded no new locally acquired cases of COVID-19 in the 24 hours to 8pm last night.   Three new cases were acquired overseas to 8pm last night, bringing the total number of cases in NSW since the beginning of the pandemic to 5,295. https://t.co/MXmTMoqASv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Dr Jan Fizzell provides a #COVID19 update for Sunday 2 May 2021:  https://t.co/kwoo8ebels]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VOTINGindepend Detailed information on overseas travellers can be found in our COVID-19 weekly surveillance reports: https://t.co/qty0m40Hot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health reminds all travellers that there continues to be a requirement to complete an entry declaration if you have been in Western Australia in the previous 14 days before entering NSW. The entry declaration is available on the Service NSW website: https://t.co/KD83ztO0Uz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone currently in NSW who has been in Perth since 27 April should immediately check if they have been in a venue of concern. If you have attended any of these venues at the relevant times, please immediately isolate, get tested, and call NSW Health on 1800 943 553.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prior to travelling to NSW, anyone who has been in Perth since 27 April should immediately check the Western Australian Health website to determine whether they have been to any venues of concern, and to follow the public health advice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The West Australian Government has announced a Perth hotel quarantine worker and two of his household contacts have tested positive to COVID-19, and has published a list of venues of concern visited by these positive cases while potentially infectious: https://t.co/wb6RF7geFb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PUBLIC HEALTH ALERT  WESTERN AUSTRALIA https://t.co/msFQvnLecK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RonanNeto10 Hi Ronan,  Australian Government advice for international travellers remains unchanged regardless of your vaccination status. More information can be found at https://t.co/0ETyn6aEff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mhcsnsw: This weekend for all celebrating Orthodox Easter, we wish you peace and joy. Hear from religious leaders across NSW about how]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Dr Jan Fizzell provides a #COVID19 update for Saturday 1 May 2021. https://t.co/WarN6KvFn3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is treating 110 COVID-19 cases, one of whom is in intensive care and on ECMO. Most (96 per cent) are being treated in non-acute, out-of-hospital care, including returned travellers in the Special Health Accommodation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 300 COVID-19 testing locations across NSW. To find your nearest clinic, visit: https://t.co/LmeATIQK4Z or contact your GP.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>