<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis @volusiaschools @mtgreenee @marcorubio @MattWalshBlog @RepMattGaetz @mattgaetz Unmask Our Children #saveourchildren #unmaskourkids @VolusiaSheriff @VCEmergencyInfo https://t.co/Cg97CtbtPZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SheriffChitwood @ScottBaio @RonPaul @GovRonDeSantis #SAVEOURCHILDEN UnMask our Children #unmaskourkids Please! https://t.co/Cg97CsTSrp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VolusiaSheriff @volusiaschools @CountyOfVolusia @VolusiaMoms @VCEmergencyInfo Unmask our Children #unmaskourkids #SAVEOURCHILDEN #scamdemic https://t.co/KJ29HjkQFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtgreenee: I get told every single day how many enemies I have in the DC Swamp.  That's ok: I represent the people, not the politicians!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[$verb #NASDAQ #ZingerNation Power Hour | Rory Cutaia Interview https://t.co/8Xh6X8kbcW via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ABC Stop lying ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxholeMedicine You cant testify against your husband... wishful thinking ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Open the Gates ~ maybe she will squeal on him. https://t.co/HF5BsmDbkm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Im not convinced that Joe Biden won 1 state]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/3Mtq9Jfhzt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntonioSabatojr: Stealing an election #TheBigLie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#UnmaskOurChildren https://t.co/RJnlQatQKi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@3sidedstory #unmask our children]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sedan_land @ebolds @SenatorTimScott @TimScottSC You obviously dont follow his career nor listen to his position.  It transcends color  party lines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/1HMgtkcl2t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BlueLivesMatter @KingJames https://t.co/MZvg0bqNxW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RebekahRadice: Smart people surround themselves with even smarter people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HotepJesus: Did you tell your kids you love them, today?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CRRJA5: Just Sayin  https://t.co/tutKvqc9E5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Swesbutte: Heh BLM. We don't negotiate with terrorists]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dirtbag Criminal https://t.co/BhctzDbKwJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Ive watched the video of Mitt Romney getting booed at least 15 times.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yeah ! https://t.co/YZf6hncY9n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Bill Gates is practicing medicine without a license.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unmask Our Children #saveourchildren @SenatorTimScott @SenTedCruz @SenateGOP @KristiNoem @RandPaul @SenMastriano @JohnCornyn @SenateFloor @USArmy https://t.co/hWvlECnI1i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unmask our children  @GovRonDeSantis @pastorlocke @KristiNoem @GovMikeHuckabee @GovKemp @GregAbbott_TX @marcorubio  #SaveOurChildren https://t.co/UckwznvDVs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spectacular ! https://t.co/DStr3mdQgW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BuzzPatterson ... And your thoughts on the #scamdemic #vaccine ?  Drum roll please.... https://t.co/nEISTqijcO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepPfluger: I am absolutely infuriated by the news that 33 Guatemalan citizens were found in a home inside the Midland city limits. Mak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: They should replace Dr. Fauci with a Magic Eight Ball. Much cheaper and just as accurate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wdunlap: @SebGorka How many times can we be LIED to! Lockdowns  Sanitation efforts proven not necessary No evidence of asymptomatic tr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hfields95: My name is Harrison Fields.  I proudly served the Trump Administration and worked with the GREAT @kayleighmcenany.  I had to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laralogan: UH OH: Evidence Shows the Intel on Israel that John Kerry Shared with Iran Was Not in the Public Domain as Claimed by Biden']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drsimonegold: Dr. Vladimir Zelenko, an early adaptor and pioneer of the HCQ protocol, has been nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize.  This]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @silversucker: $TTCM  #NFT   Here is a list of patents owned by $TTCM   https://t.co/hcSfqoTmrM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PasReport: If a black person espouses a #Conservative view, they are labeled as an #UncleTom  traitor to their race. People try to jus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Every day of this Administration is a lie. This man didnt win the Presidency. He is an imposter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JasonMillerinDC: Allowing a racist slur against Tim Scott to trend confirms social media's activist bias https://t.co/1Gk1vBq25Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Feisty_FL: If Joe Biden got 81 million votes, why cant he get 10 million views?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RodFair2: ......... I'll Wait https://t.co/ySCeazOvh7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SexCounseling ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cmcjjpp @smdftbAGAIN @NewEmergingKing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cmcjjpp: @smdftbAGAIN @NewEmergingKing I was so wrong about this guy initially. Im ashamed to say the media had me fooled in 2016. But]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Komarus_Huey @smdftbAGAIN ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Komarus_Huey: @smdftbAGAIN So funny how the media manipulated people into hating this nigga lmaoo I was literally in attendance at wres]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@raebachmusic ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida says No ! https://t.co/E97QSvZQUV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RonDeSantisFL Rockstar ! https://t.co/E97QSvZQUV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love our governor ! https://t.co/E97QSvZQUV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackthealleyCa1 @CRRJA5 @mosperus https://t.co/JoLcj3DDLl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackthealleyCa1 @CRRJA5 @mosperus 98 police officers were killed this year so far ... where is their justice?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @christicash11:  @KingJames - you have a phone  call  #BLM does not care about anything but making $$$ and buying mansions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepVernonJones @SenatorTimScott They are the biggest racists]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chicago1Ray: BIDEN was (SELECTED) not ELECTED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @seanhannity: 100% KENNEDY: Dems Put All Their Faith in Government, Republicans Put Their Faith in People https://t.co/yFwQiwKU60]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickAdamsinUSA: The Biden Administration is suspending travel from India.   Joe Biden is a xenophobe!  That's how this works, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AmyKremer: This video is making the left crazy for some reason....  https://t.co/ZPbXefppJ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tripsmoolamoola: @Tautachrome_Inc @67harley @RoboticGladiat1 totally, time to talk a #TomBrady partnership $TTCM @Tautachrome_Inc #NFT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tripsmoolamoola: $TTCM woohoo, lets get em! plenty of #NFTs projects to go after, about time we take this up another notch, cease or de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LesleyRHafalia: $TTCM oh boy all those people companies etc that have made #NFTs gonna owe this company a LOT of $$ for Patent Infringe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tripsmoolamoola: $TTCM u bet, just search all the companies that has done #NFTs not realizing they have infringed our patents! this is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@67harley Hope this is a springboard $ttcm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @67harley: Interesting! $TTCM #NFTs https://t.co/v3Q2jPsCtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@P8R1OT Some people should be vaccinated 5x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newtgingrich: With Antifa releasing a video threatening to kill the mayor of portland and releasing his home address membership in anti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ @KingJames - you have a phone  call  #BLM does not care about anything but making $$$ and buying mansions https://t.co/DyuigeBEZB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #saveourchildren https://t.co/tfwohUvtOW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SFloef: Support your local farmers. More important now than ever. https://t.co/7TGwquA3ks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sfm_42: Make Mexico great again... Biden slogan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sfm_42: Joe Biden's America]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @xGratitude333: @Tautachrome_Inc Know a potential project of interest? Feel free to tag them here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tautachrome_Inc: Tautachrome $TTCM has engaged its patent attorney firm Thomas  Bacon to review projects/companies which may be infrin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @olivia_trades: Weeeeee!!! $TTCM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ebolds @SenatorTimScott Hes the front man because he is intelligent, caring and a leader who leads from the front to support our Republic. Proud to support @TimScottSC @SenatorTimScott]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dharmajunky @SenatorTimScott Well said.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@monica_dantonio @SenatorTimScott Stop weaponizing race.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenatorTimScott Thank You Tim.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard ThankYou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenatorTimScott Thank You Tim Scott for standing up for us while the Democratic Party is weaponizing race.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorTimScott: No amount of backward bigotry will shake my faith in the goodness of America.  I meant what I said on Wednesday night]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @votetimscott: Thank you to the over 21,000 donors from all 50 states for helping us cross $1M raised in support of common sense and com]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jimmy42854687: IMPEACH. WHITMER..... she needs to be removed from office now...!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#backtheblue #BlueLivesMatter #policelivesmatter https://t.co/N0UA00OJiS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where is the support @KingJames ? @TheRock ? https://t.co/N0UA00OJiS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzPatterson: Biden said Buy American but what I heard was Bye, Americans.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RandPaul: FL is open. TX is open. TN - mandates repealed. Even NEW YORK has set a firm date to fully reopen (not soon enough)  But stil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @petluver4Trump: Requiring proof of vaccination is a HIPAA violation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BurgessOwens The fact that they can make it trend is systemic racism against white people throughout the lying media.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BurgessOwens: The same people who are making Uncle Tim trend are the same people accusing all conservatives of being racist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BuzzPatterson ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzPatterson: Were screwed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GitRDoneLarry @RobSchneider ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GitRDoneLarry: . Wheres the ballsy late night comics on this stuff? Its GOLD!! GOLD Jerry! RT @RobSchneider:  https://t.co/q5ftQ5jahH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorTimScott: As I said last night: Locking vulnerable kids out of the classroom is locking adults out of their future. 2020 was the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikepompeo: In his first address to a joint session of Congress, President Biden completely ignored the border crisis  which is exactl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepVernonJones: Stacey Abrams is nothing but a hustler for white liberals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzPatterson: White liberals are the most racist people in the US.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rediculous but funny as hell  https://t.co/QtYQUt8dWi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RudyGiuliani: The DOJ in late 2019 covertly obtained access to my iCloud and never notified me.  They invaded the attorney client relat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DineshDSouza: What happens when a white female ignoramus presumes to lecture a thoughtful black man about the reality of systematic rac]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>