<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/mWxcrTYia0 on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tonight's live stream!  https://t.co/cpDXqdGmgF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tonight's live stream @7cst where we are discussing more cdc covid changes, vaccine passports, and loosening mask restrictions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/w3FmMBrvo5 on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden addresses congress, FDA proposes a ban on menthol cigarettes, and travel from India is banned. This is your Weekend Wrap-up!  Watch at: https://t.co/LxsPEqitsA  Or listen at: https://t.co/Kr9jZFa9Hz https://t.co/5N9fJORoDk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We the people are the government? #BidenAddress #constitution]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Menthol is racist! https://t.co/eQvuOUKlot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRealOJ32]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: Marketing suggestion for @Ford  for the new @FordBroncoLife.  #FordBronco #ford https://t.co/xfI2YkwKEh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marketing suggestion for @Ford  for the new @FordBroncoLife.  #FordBronco #ford https://t.co/xfI2YkwKEh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eI9UQDDGSN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week we are once again joined by @JohnOdermatt of @LionsofLiberty to discuss the trial and conviction of Derek Chauvin. #ChauvinTrail #DerekChauvin #BlackLivesMatter #PoliceReform  Watch at: https://t.co/eI9UQDDGSN  Listen at: https://t.co/fAh9P56xvy https://t.co/qhxUydbkdY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/5oS7H4tFeo on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BNicholsLiberty So is he going to pull in $80bn from tax evasion to even cover that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnOdermatt A what?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnOdermatt: If youve been wearing a mask outdoors up to this point, waiting for the CDC to give you permission to unmask, then I hav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnOdermatt: I predicted this one yesterday. I hope Im wrong.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will be going live at 7:30 to discuss the Derek Chauvin trial with @JohnOdermatt of the @LionsofLiberty Podcast. Don't miss it!   https://t.co/4KxkAAOVx1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tonight's live stream where we will be joined by @JohnOdermatt of the  @LionsofLiberty Podcast to talk about the Derek Chauvin trial. 7:30pm cst   #GeorgeFloydTrial #DerekChauvin #BlackLivesMatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The LGBTQ community turns on Caitlyn Jenner over politics, the House attempts to make DC a state, and another police shooting provokes Lebron James to respond emotionally or possibly incite violence. This is your Weekend Wrap-Up.   https://t.co/fq3wiVdnNy  https://t.co/8rE0GXzdiS https://t.co/LI5eZqbliN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/Fx8YwG2lUK on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night we will be joined once again by @JohnOdermatt of @LionsofLiberty to discuss the infamous Derek Chauvin conviction. Don't miss it live at 7:30 pm cst.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of joining Forrest of @VanzotM  on the Squeaming Podcast. Was a fun conversation, make sure you check it out!  https://t.co/9nS2OjKoZI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Never stop talking! https://t.co/htH2i5Snuv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: Both sides are playing politics with human lives as the Whitehouse refuses to call the issue at the border what it is:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Both sides are playing politics with human lives as the Whitehouse refuses to call the issue at the border what it is: a crisis. Don't miss it this week's episode! #BidenBorderCrisis #BorderCrisis #KamalaHarris   https://t.co/yDcL14NH1C  https://t.co/dFp2Bupb5h https://t.co/S437nZBn5F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/Hmbl2D6Fhb on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tomorrow's episode! https://t.co/eXeudZV5cU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will it take for the administration to call the situation at the border a crisis? When the expected 1M end up there dying in 120 heat this summer? #bordercrisis #KidsInCages #BidenBorderCrisis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight we are going to take a look at the record influx of immigrants at the southern border, Biden's policies that led to and are addressing, the Whitehouse refusal to call it a crisis, where VP Harris fits in the mess, and more. Don't miss it!  7pm cst  https://t.co/dpgMoe04r4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tonight's live stream where we will be discussing the crisis at the border. 7pm cst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrisspangle But did you ever throw one?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. and Russia relations are straining, Biden plans to withdraw all troops in Afghanistan, another mass shooting, and police shootings make the headlines. This is your Weekend Wrap-up  https://t.co/w8anO34DGd  https://t.co/lNvAdZPvAH https://t.co/UR7Ryqtlpm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/kL2c1LBblp on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: The author's of the Bill of Rights intended them as protected individual rights they believed were naturally theirs. C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The constitution is absolute and binding as We The People want it to be.  https://t.co/zX3VhUvohr https://t.co/Kd00ycQJ9h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The author's of the Bill of Rights intended them as protected individual rights they believed were naturally theirs. Check out this week's episode! #billofrights #2A #Constitution #GunControl  https://t.co/LttyrewyvY  https://t.co/zX3VhUvohr https://t.co/ND8LTH3MCc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/WPSDfcI4Zt on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YKddB03Sui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight we're going to be discussing just how absolute the constitution actually is. Live 7pm cst. Don't miss it! #Constitution]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warnings of real life Jurassic Park and Planet of the Apes scenarios,  Fauci is in denial, BLM founder gets backlash over home purchase, and Biden appoints a disaster to the ATF head. This is your Weekend Wrap-up.  https://t.co/k77L9mvfmt  https://t.co/x5lyyAuElS https://t.co/QrY9mKFOiq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/yN1TMB2F1G on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New episode, don't miss it! #UBI #socialism #stimuluspackage  https://t.co/CxzZUXHWu5 https://t.co/0zqwu4vKKr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week we take a dig into the idea universal basic income and how a corrupt government could use it to strip away your freedoms. Check it out! #UBI #Tyranny #stimuluschecks  https://t.co/75C1iSpfkc https://t.co/p0GRo3PeDc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/JIk9260B1L on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/90ki2V20ob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Live stream starts in 30 min. Tell your friends!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tonight's live stream as we talk about universal basic income. #UBI #stimuluschecks #Tyranny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Georgia passes "oppressive" voter laws, causing the MLB to pull the All Star game, and a man wo attacked the Capitol with a car and knife is said to be a follower of Louis Farrakhan. This is your Weekend Wrap-up. #VoterID #MLBAllStarGame #CapitolAttack  https://t.co/s5Cy1tKxRp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/puHg1iIQ3p on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bfXujeT1V5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You do not want to miss today's episode where we discuss guns with Kerry Slone @thereal_SnS, gun and women's self defense advocate and founder of We The Female. #GunControl #secondamendment #realfeminism   https://t.co/RvfX44gxkd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/cwoAIczkKR on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With gun law bills on the table and shootings making the headlines, it is a good time for us to talk about guns. This week we are joined by Kerry Slone @thereal_SnS, founder of We The Female and gun rights advocate. Check it out! #GunControl #2ndamendment https://t.co/KGa4jufywF https://t.co/9TUVf0FRQY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tomorrow's episode with Kerry Slone @thereal_SnS https://t.co/T8gjPkBW7N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight's live stream with Kerry Slone @thereal_SnS will begin shortly. Don't miss it.   https://t.co/f4zD6x8W5t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tonight's live stream  less than one hour as we will be joined by Kerry Slone @thereal_SnS, gun rights activist and founder of https://t.co/U56ruwP15D #GunControlNow #2ndAmendment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/AjJ6TJJiJ7 on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cargo ship blocks international shipping, Biden's first official press conference is less than impressive, and the crisis at the border continues. This is your Weekend Wrap-up.  #SuezBLOCKED #BorderCrisis #bidenpressconference   https://t.co/f1OucpjOoR  https://t.co/whVklqwSr0 https://t.co/k9NkRhFUV1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On tomorrow night's live stream we will be joined by the founder of https://t.co/U56ruwP15D, gun rights advocate and certified firearms instructor, Kerry Slone @thereal_SnS. We will be discussing the continuing hot topic of guns. 7pmcst Do not miss it! #GunControl #2ndAmendment https://t.co/EP8ixbmqB9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: Don't miss this week's episode where @MarcDClair of the @LionsofLiberty  took us on a dive into the mystic age beyond]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HeyRemso: Two weeks left for the @SecondPrintPod giveaway! Tap the link for details! https://t.co/MijEIfVW2t https://t.co/ZqYFICF3S1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss this week's episode where @MarcDClair of the @LionsofLiberty  took us on a dive into the mystic age beyond reason and ration.  #TheDimAge  https://t.co/65SRNZ9A02]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thereal_SnS: @anthonyvclark20 My AR is my home defense weapon of choice. Hubs is military  deployed often. An AR gives me the ability]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week we had the privilege of having on the show the legendary @MarcDClair of @LionsofLiberty. Join us as Marc breaks down the mystical age beyond reason we are living in. #COVID19 #Biden #TheDimAge  https://t.co/65SRNZ9A02 Or listen at https://t.co/kpwTQfD3Ns https://t.co/iY7NIkLtIA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/dnZM8Hr6oS on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everybody is talking about Biden's microphone glitch when Yoda is hanging out with the Saudi crown. #SaudiArabia #yoda #TheDimAge  https://t.co/ORJ5Ln5bHh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[going live in a few! https://t.co/JWvD0almcZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going live in one hour where we will be joined by @LionsofLiberty legend @MarcDClair. You don't want to miss it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do not miss tonight's live stream where we will be joined by @MarcDClair of the @LionsofLiberty. 8pm cst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do not miss tomorrow night's live stream episode as we are joined by @MarcDClair  of the @LionsofLiberty Podcast. The episode will be bumped back to 8pm cst to accommodate his schedule and get as much time with him as possible, so do not miss it! https://t.co/2KH6uFJ2pi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Andrew Cuomo is investigated by the FBI, Biden is not making friends with other world, and Asian hate is an ongoing pandemic we hadn't heard of. This is your Weekend Wrap-up!  https://t.co/M7b7TDA2Bc Or watch at https://t.co/5qMEx6ITxQ #AsianLivesMatter #Cuomo #Biden https://t.co/aQf8fJ4YU3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/4HFAnYlv4v on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RYMCoffee: Government creation of protected classes is why things like Jim Crow laws existed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: How much of the monstrous stimulus package is actual covid relief and how much is going to pork spending and progressi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HeyRemso: No one literally understands whats going on with the black Superman situation EXCEPT LITERALLY ME. Come get some nerd-know]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How much of the monstrous stimulus package is actual covid relief and how much is going to pork spending and progressive agenda programs? Check out this week's episode! #StimulusChecks #Covid_19 #stimuluspackage https://t.co/QYL5xz55o2 Or watch at https://t.co/iw8UNwt17c https://t.co/6Pn997Z5W4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/TnEe17nvNX on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tomorrow's episode! #StimulusChecks #CovidReliefBill https://t.co/ml6IihZWLc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are going live! Invite your friends.  https://t.co/kDaGBibUWF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On tonight's live stream episode we are discussing the massive stimulus bill just signed into affect. Don't miss it! #Covid_19 #StimulusChecks #Biden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Biden promises Independence Day if we follow the rules, Governor Cuomo gets the boot, the family of George Floyd gets a big payout, and gun bans are in the works. This is your Weekend Wrap-up.  https://t.co/YAihXB2Tci Or watch at https://t.co/82bPp5Y21K https://t.co/cvTmaVcAs1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/HkgrF8cVr3 on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss this week's episode where we dig into #cancelculture. #MrPotatoHead #DrSeuss #cancelcancelculture  https://t.co/dmrPijomdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mr. Potato head, Dr. Seuss, and Gina Carano. All have been the subject of outcry blaming "cancel culture". Check out this week's episode! #CancelCulture #potatohead #DrSeuss  https://t.co/fT0Y7sSo5Y Or watch at https://t.co/dmrPijomdu https://t.co/24pDKZO1xS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/jdGAO7oWFI on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tomorrow's episode https://t.co/UICUzMRnuo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the near future, your entire livelihood will be determined by how well you fit into a box of acceptable norms. #CancelCulture]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/myHB6Ta2PK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us in less than an hour for our livestream episode as we talk about cancel culture. There will be call in opportunities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7pm cst tonight. Live stream. Don't miss it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Don't do that to me! I had to Google acdc to make sure they hadn't broke up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: Congress votes on the latest stimulus package, states end their mask laws, the Pope visits Iraq, and babies are racist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinWax It started going down hill when they can't after the comedians]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GavinWax: Cuomo is basically threatening to take down the entire Democrat political establishment in New York if they go after him.  Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congress votes on the latest stimulus package, states end their mask laws, the Pope visits Iraq, and babies are racist.  This is your Weekend Wrap-up!  https://t.co/Ax9jwDqVug Or watch at https://t.co/nkDJNHvf7Y https://t.co/ezqH0yHqGJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/hHT97qby4G on #Podbean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QxL2rJwYkY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jEj0Kqn3Ec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breakthebellpod: Biden orders his first strike in the Middle East, a right of passage for  presidents. This week we attempted to unders]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>