<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Alejandro Fernndez's daughter shows off her figure in latex leggings when dancing sensually in avideo https://t.co/r4yLZphMdC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carolina Sandoval surprises by 'shaking' her hips with all the attitude and intriplicate! https://t.co/kNwslxmImj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They order the release of a secret memo from William Barr so that they would not indict DonaldTrump https://t.co/NLQwccapml]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How sexy! Diego Boneta sets fire to the networks by appearingshirtless https://t.co/9d3uQ415pw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dodgers collapse almost inexplicably and lose their fourth straightseries https://t.co/W1GQZaYBWT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crisis in Venezuela: a new Electoral Council and 4 other recent events that may have animpact https://t.co/xW0N5pElKM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pain and indignation of the relatives of the victims of the metro accident inCDMX https://t.co/noMQjkcCnw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[William Levy appears very happy with his wife after rumors of an allegedinfidelity https://t.co/4JHokW6Xwy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Idaho lottery player won 2 jackpots  in 2weeks https://t.co/ZqoeJt7gzc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[San Diego County approves free attorneys for detained immigrants in OtayMesa https://t.co/9wdBu5med9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dorismar poses on her back to show off her perfect tan with a tiny blackbikini https://t.co/goKDBocErW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LeBron will be out for the next two games to rest hisankle https://t.co/Wvm5vcH46Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The simple explanation of the photo of the giant Biden with the tinyCarters https://t.co/4tueT57o4r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Ambassador's Daughter': Season finale and second-season premiere is Univision's ace up thesleeve https://t.co/15U09s3Oi3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Between music and anecdotes, the Menudo say goodbye to RayReyes https://t.co/pi0KclR31r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MLB suspends Paul Campbell for 80 games fordoping https://t.co/Yp3kT0krGa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks to a bottle of water, they arrest an alleged Hispanic serial rapist; there were seven victims in SanAntonio https://t.co/hLU94K4bzE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[International clubs and athletes express their support for the victims of Line 12 of the CDMXMetro https://t.co/0gdO1jAIjO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Univision vs Telemundo: 'The Ambassador's Daughter' loses ground to 'Looking forFrida' https://t.co/ygG46wHhgn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Severe storms continue to plague the southern United States with floods andtornadoes https://t.co/OoX1CbCM0a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eduardo Yez confesses that he has been recorded inprivacy https://t.co/PMrMurWCZU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American Airlines will no longer accept a passenger who attacked a flightattendant https://t.co/LKkvNdxKNO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Melinda Gates, the most powerful woman in philanthropy who divorces Bill Gates after 27 years ofmarriage https://t.co/utK8T9IpA6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lili Estefan confesses that she earned 50 dollars in 'GiantSaturday' https://t.co/c1SzdLvPVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Infantino asked to be careful when talking about the sanctions for the SuperLeague https://t.co/57goAknrlf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enrique Guzmn goes with everything! He has already formalized the complaint against Gustavo AdolfoInfante https://t.co/BjxK6D6lQv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two women sue LAPD over violent arrest at trafficstop https://t.co/7FrPtFyMDz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Macabre freeway find: worker finds human foot on Los Angeles-areafreeway https://t.co/KskYSYVt1X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking! Paul Campbell suspended for 80 games fordoping https://t.co/y5YxBYgDiJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All you need to know about a Non-Fungible Token orNFT https://t.co/GPaIournae]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love her so much !!!: Dulce Mara shows off the beauty of her daughter Mara Paula with her first photoshoot https://t.co/3PZTgLUN98]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 kills one in four Californians in nursinghomes https://t.co/j6mQglQOlm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These are the rivals of the Tri olimpico on their tour ofEurope https://t.co/bbCK57nYcD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The referee said 'fuck you' to LeandroParedes https://t.co/GWYlIQq6jP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden Administration Makes Tremendous Progress in Custody of ImmigrantChildren https://t.co/SeOwxOsjKw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does the fight go down? Saunders rebuked Canelo, did not show up for the confrontation and asks to change the size of thering https://t.co/wRGOHg2W3g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Derek Chauvin's defense calls for a new trial for the ex-cop in the George Floydcase https://t.co/taAJtOH4Rs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pochettino: We are very disappointed https://t.co/wKgPwOVn65]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sports world showed support for victims of Line 12 of the CDMXmetro https://t.co/WuRQUtcC0K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Compton one step away from electing the first Latino mayor in itshistory https://t.co/7iKTamdpCw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg extends his controversial empire in Hawaii and buys 600 acres for $ 53million https://t.co/uuV8FQjxPy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what Carrie Fisher looked like in her firstrole https://t.co/8yrpHozn9T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What trick Jeff Bezos used to make it big in Amazon's earlyyears https://t.co/SRWarIOeLA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer vacations can be ruined due to lack of chlorine for swimmingpools https://t.co/8x00HOD3e7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carolina Sandoval ready to reduce her breasts: I don't want to have two moreballs https://t.co/ZeSgsOypYu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After being criticized for head-butting her mother, Brbara de Regil defends herself: We get tooheavy https://t.co/6fvyXgdypf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Video: Di Mara's stomp left PSG with 10players https://t.co/s08bUnLJmZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three men die in Anaheim in the brutal crash of a Mercedes-Benz that was captured onvideo https://t.co/Qj9UpsTnfb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Which is more important, high or lowpressure? https://t.co/PO1qYDxLu7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pablo Iglesias, leader of Podemos and the populist left in Spain, leavespolitics https://t.co/gR5EmxtIxO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1.2 million California families can be left without up to $ 4,200 for not filingtaxes https://t.co/N0KqEJz9b6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Video: Madness seized the Manchester City dressingroom https://t.co/vTNi9l3GjS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid Vaccines and Tests Boost Sales at CVS HealthPharmacies https://t.co/EpPVyVNfY9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latino leaders ask to sanction police officers and suspend Chicago footchases https://t.co/qP3H8SVn1C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[eBay could accept cryptocurrencies as a paymentoption https://t.co/BdonU822hY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You will never be white: LASD agent is victim of verbal attack and shares the video of themoment https://t.co/7h6BgvOJiO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guardiola: Now is the time toenjoy https://t.co/2cKtQR2qRM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After a decade of effort Manchester City reaches its first Champions Leaguefinal https://t.co/reFiWNONcl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ACLU denounces Los Angeles sheriff's harassment of families of shootingsvictims https://t.co/QE8TuPxEHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how famous people reacted to the tragedy on Line 12 of the Mexico Citymetro https://t.co/lqOHUlWLiL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The chronology of Johnny Depp'sslump https://t.co/FUUkBSIBTK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you have negative karma with money? Learn to eliminate it and improve yourfinances https://t.co/qBBilgAOz2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How a Mexican immigrant succeeded with a cart of sweet potatoes in NewYork https://t.co/ujiN5yv43x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Identify 3 Hispanic dead from the boat that allegedly carried immigrants from Mexico to SanDiego https://t.co/WJ4zu2Mgj6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aiways U6: another zero-emission SUV that joins the Chinesefirm https://t.co/fEJmgifhCR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Discover this car that exceeds 1,000 hp and is powered byhydrogen https://t.co/0lCu4QI2zP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Braless and in a thong, Demi Rose poses in the sand and swings on aswing https://t.co/lC4EIStfWZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Collapsed wagons are removed from Mexico City Metro Line12 https://t.co/N3hLssMuCq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Weeknd will continue to boycott the Grammy Awards, despite the change inregulations https://t.co/n1oLuKhw5B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nayib Bukele and Justice in El Salvador: It is an extremely serious event and takes us back to the worst attacks on democracy that affected our region in the 20thcentury https://t.co/vD0p8uyTSc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Death of Keishla Rodrguez: the case of the Olympic boxer accused of killing a pregnant young woman that shocks PuertoRico https://t.co/4Z4wD2LJWC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is the White House open to the IRS sending a fourth stimuluscheck? https://t.co/mKBDxXH2gG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pandemic Fears and Stimulus Checks: Why So Many People Still Don't Want to Go Back toWork https://t.co/Qag8t7dxNt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Renaud shows off her body with a yellow bikini while walking on thebeach https://t.co/1QHDS1jKLL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What should NEVER be done on a fullmoon https://t.co/uSw6k7Xyl2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mexican Migrants Exceed Expectations and Set New Record for Sending Remittances from the UnitedStates https://t.co/JuSQU332v1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How much the dollar in Mexico today Tuesday, May4 https://t.co/RttxGJ9NK1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Death toll after Metro accident in Mexico City rises to 24; only 5 bodies have beenidentified https://t.co/uRxJuBvXEw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LaLiga opens file to Messi for lunch heorganized https://t.co/hzMSryuLf8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are Bill Gates and Melinda Gates divorced after 27 years ofmarriage? https://t.co/sYW1MDy86U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mother's Day 2021: What is the ideal flower for mom, according to her zodiacsign https://t.co/1So325EAeT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden agrees not to tax anyone who earns less than $ 400,000annually https://t.co/KzJza1iCvq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ninel Conde sensually wiggles her hips wearing a tight sports outfit withholes https://t.co/0O9jiyG6RT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sistine, beautiful daughter of Sylvester Stallone, shows off the most intimate corners of hermansion https://t.co/wvAAhCPpih]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is Biden's plan for 70% of adults to be vaccinated to return to some normalcy on July4? https://t.co/xbjl1Ur8Gk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In video, Chiquis Rivera and Ana Brbara twerk with theirbacks https://t.co/AuyftQX0J5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What rituals to do to receive and harness the positive energy of the 2021 eclipseseason https://t.co/4xYiITRNui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats prepare plan B to pass immigration reform that would give citizenship to undocumentedimmigrants https://t.co/JbL1UJcNKN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When the delivery of the third stimulus check ends and its relationship with Plus-uppayments https://t.co/KQmuil0jgY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the beautiful and luxurious penthouse that Kate Winslet just sold in NewYork https://t.co/JQd6unNJvN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The shocking images of the collapse of a section of Line 12 of the Mexico CityMetro https://t.co/ysJFFFMxcQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is May 4 Star WarsDay? https://t.co/dyXKxrPg1X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is there a chicken shortage inAmerica? https://t.co/P05JwiWSHS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carmen Electra shows off her statuesque figure by modeling colorfulswimsuits https://t.co/XhQjdNIdm3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The controversial history of Metro Line 12 that collapsed and caused at least 23 deaths and 79 injuries in MexicoCity https://t.co/eV3zilyyV0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least 19 dead and more than 800 injured in Colombia after protests against taxreform https://t.co/afHEfLH661]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will happen in your social and work relationships with the entry of Mercury intoGemini https://t.co/WpCxdQMLO6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ramos, Mendy and Valverde are the news of the Real Madridsquad https://t.co/zKtry0tXps]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Wahlberg, is that you? The actor is shown with 14 extrakilos! https://t.co/t5v4E9Kyvq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miguel Herrera will be the new coach ofTigres https://t.co/kHRa6QPozl]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>