<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNGeneva: From protecting human rights to negotiating trade rules, the work done by the international organizations in #Geneva affects]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Colombia: Estamos profundamente preocupados por los acontecimientos ocurridos en Cali, cuando la polica ha abierto fuego contra manifestantes y se han producido muertes y heridos.  Los Estados tienen la responsabilidad de proteger los #DDHH y facilitar la reunin pacfica. https://t.co/MVPjrHqLZE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#EU new rules for online terrorist content can harm #FreeExpression. Very short deadlines for content removal incentivise automation and encourage censorship. EU #DigitalServicesAct should avoid dangerous shortcuts and ensure independent oversight of content removal by States. https://t.co/AkF8ozOAWt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Colombia: We are deeply alarmed at developments in Cali overnight, where police opened fire on demonstrators, and a number of people were killed  injured.   States have a responsibility to protect #HumanRights and facilitate peaceful assembly.   https://t.co/urHl2qNzsg https://t.co/ymn2DaP4RT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #ElSalvador: The decision by the Legislative Assembly to dismiss the magistrates of the Constitutional Chamber of the Supreme Court of Justice and the Attorney General seriously undermines democracy  the rule of law  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet: https://t.co/s5LzZnUghP https://t.co/UlLOBCwCCO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: The work of journalists and media workers will be crucial for the world to recover better from the devastation of this crisi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theyre doing everything they can to stop information flowing to the Myanmar people  the rest of the world Thar Lun Zaung Htet, a journalist who fled his country in fear 4 his life. On #WorldPressFreedomDay, he  thousands others still face grave danger https://t.co/6X6qCRRywU https://t.co/xSpOdq5BhX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In order to fully celebrate the bravery of journalists in their determination to keep the public informed, we must demand that their rights are respected, protected  fulfilled  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet: https://t.co/ukbDVhCAU8 #WorldPressFreedomDay #StandUp4HumanRights https://t.co/XWvwhgI8no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The collective leadership of the EU is key in combatting inequalities and ensuring that no one is left behind, within  outside its borders  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet gives recommendations on economic and social rights ahead of #EUSocialSummit21  https://t.co/O6H45Zj5pQ https://t.co/boJhTi2V1Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attacks, arrests and the criminal prosecution of a journalist has an additional chilling effect of dissuading other journalists from critically reporting on relevant issues  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet on #WorldPressFreedomDay: https://t.co/ukbDVhkZvy  #StandUp4HumanRights https://t.co/DnPYpRMx4F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNHumanRights: #PressFreedom can bring life-saving information in moments of crises; provide a basis for public participation; and help]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@swiss_un   has donated $30K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PressFreedom can bring life-saving information in moments of crises; provide a basis for public participation; and help ensure accountability and respect for human rights  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet on #WorldPressFreedomDay: https://t.co/ukbDVhCAU8 #StandUp4HumanRights https://t.co/tRAJKOgdIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Countries where people trust their institutions consistently show higher levels of political participation. The way in which]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CorteConstEcu  #Ecuador: Felicitamos la decisin de @CorteConstEcu  el aborto en casos de violacin ya no podr ser penalizado. Implementar esta decisin ser un paso decisivo para la proteccin de los #DerechosHumanos de las mujeres y nias vctimas de violencia sexual.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Ecuador: We welcome @CorteConstEcus ruling  abortion in cases of rape may no longer be criminalized. Implementing this decision will be a decisive step for the protection of #HumanRights of women and girls victims of sexual violence.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Economic growth risks leaving huge numbers of people behind without  effective,  accountable,  transparent,  participatory institutions  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet outlines how #SDG16 can guide governance transformation.  Learn more: https://t.co/EuIemA1Csm https://t.co/i8hcr92icE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Chad: We are deeply disturbed by the apparently disproportionate use of force  incl. use of live ammunition  in the context of protests. Chad is bound by int'l human rights law to protect  respect #HumanRights, incl. freedom of peaceful assembly  https://t.co/CFzSp5THfh https://t.co/NPrp6XptLs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Bahrain: We are disturbed by the use of unnecessary  disproportionate force to dismantle a peaceful sit-in at Jau prison. Lack of health care in overcrowded Bahraini prisons has been an issue for years, but has become a chronic problem during #COVID19  https://t.co/mEnYMqhDYN https://t.co/z6q4GoR112]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@qatarmission_ge   has donated $20K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK @QatarAtUN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In these difficult times, women and girls need support more than ever. We have said repeatedly how they have been disproportionately affected by the pandemic and the resultingsocio-economic crisis. Lets do more, not less. #StandUp4HumanRights #IStandWithHer https://t.co/Q13FTG7osF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNMigNetwork: There is no one-size-fits-all approach to GCM implementation  New guidance aims to bring the 360 vision of the #GCM to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: We are all equally entitled to dignity, respect and justice, without discrimination of any kind. #StandUp4HumanRights]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@monaco_onu   has donated $49K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Inequality and discrimination are two of the biggest challenges of our time, stretching across all spheres of life.  The pan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Both the health and the socio-economic crises brought by #COVID19 are borne by many of those who have been left behind  and are being pushed further behind  in the Americas," UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet says.  Read full speech  https://t.co/Zj35tjqj6v https://t.co/ee0gzefObF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNHumanRightsEU: The #COVID19 pandemic can be the moment the  turns towards hope, #solidarity  a shared sense of global community. Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNTreatyBodies:  UN #HRCttee finds that Roy Rivera Hidalgo's abduction from his home in Nuevo Len is an #EnforcedDisappearance. The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@HUNMissionToUN   has donated $18K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #EarthDay is an opportunity to stand up for the right to a healthy environment. Today, we take a moment to recognize and support the work of environmental defenders.  #EscazuNow #Escazu4All #EscazAhora #EscazuAgora @CIDH @DESCA_CIDH @eclac_un https://t.co/45gDiv5dZq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet welcomes the entry into force of the #EscazAgreement, a pioneering treaty aimed at protecting both the environment and its defenders in Latin America and the Caribbean. Read more: https://t.co/jvkFpJIlg7 #EscazNow #EarthDay https://t.co/Msprd4oSCU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Climatechange is deadly and destructive, it is caused by people  it must be stopped by people. Our new publication links climate change and human rights violations. UN Expert, Ben Schachter, answers questions about the publication:  https://t.co/RLn1NUS4w4 #StandUp4HumanRights https://t.co/oXftdFHJfb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GeorgeFloyd verdict shows it is possible to achieve human rights that apply to everybody equally. When we ask for antiracism to be centred, is for this understanding that part of justice is accountability. - UN  expert @dominiqus https://t.co/dSM7mwKMWg #FightRacism #WGPAD https://t.co/qdh1aPi2DF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNTreatyBodies: On #EarthDay UN #ChildRights Committee calls for children empowerment  urges States to: put environmental literacy at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GeorgeFloyd: Verdict is testament to courage, perseverance  justice.  Now is "the time to critically examine the context in which [his] killing took place by revisiting the past  examining its toxic traces in todays society -@mbachelet https://t.co/WxZZNKUg8o  #fightracism https://t.co/UKlUyiLztz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@GermanyUNGeneva   has donated $303K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Decriminalise use of drugs  expand access to harm reduction and social care, experts say at the UN Commission on Narcotic Drugs. A surge on war on drugs, for small possession, violates human rights. It impacts on the right to health and is not effective: https://t.co/7fmlGFct1r https://t.co/VnZbnLSZit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["#COVID19 has disrupted the livelihood of small-scale farmers and the entire global food supply chain"  @mbachelet: #UNFSS2021 represents an unmissable opportunity for joint action towards sustainable and climate positive #FoodSystems.  Full speech  https://t.co/F74vX2O5ug https://t.co/WxG5xFgJUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet welcomes verdict in #GeorgeFloyd murder trial. But for countless other victims of African descent and their families, in the #UnitedStates and throughout the world, the fight for justice goes on.  Read  https://t.co/gE6ZJ7Uol0  #FightRacism https://t.co/LyieaeraJV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: To achieve racial justice and equality, we must decisively uproot the entrenched legacy of discriminatory policies and syste]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @unescoNOW: REGISTRATION IS NOW OPEN!  Mark your calendars  Let's support independent news media and the role of journalists in prod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hickspeggy: This is just the beginning. George Floyds death led people across the world to call for racial justice. Now we need to do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My dream is that if I say Im a Dalit and Im at the table, I should be respected just like anybody else. @sitara1  is the General Secretary of the National Campaign on Human Rights in India - @dalitrights. https://t.co/3qH8NJjzm9  #StandUp4HumanRights #FightRacism https://t.co/afpOOtuyob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNTreatyBodies: UN Committee on #MigrantWorkers issues findings on #Chile  #CMW welcomes the Law on Migration  Foreigners but remain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Reparatory justice  requires making amends for centuries of violence and discrimination, including through formal apologies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Behind racism  like other forms of hatred and discrimination  lies a failure to acknowledge and confront the legacy of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Equality and genuine inclusion of Roma, people of African descent, Jews, Muslims and others will require action on structural issues, including racial profiling  socioeconomic disparities, as well as reparatory justice  @mbachelet tells an EU conference: https://t.co/ioRqv8ggh0 https://t.co/CxgdsQO72O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @free_equal: Finding a safe place to call home can be challenging for many #LGBTIQ+ migrants  particularly if they are #transgender. Se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UN_SPExperts: UN experts strongly reject #UKGovernment-backed report into racism, saying it further distorts and falsifies historic fac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@CallforCode   has donated $149K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFO2ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would you choose to save our planet? Go to our new Tiktok account to see our latest video about #humanrights and #climatechange! https://t.co/sF02M36MLs https://t.co/ih0NdWHn8O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@USAID_Colombia donated $ 2.1M to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFO2ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What choice would you make? #humanrights #environment #climatechange https://t.co/Xc4ANFIG3d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Latin America  the Caribbean have been hit particularly hard by COVID-19. Worldwide, the most vulnerable, including indigen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNHumanRightsEU: #Poland: National Human Rights Institutions are key to protect  promote #HumanRights, #RuleOfLaw. We urge Poland to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: We need to anchor our recovery efforts in human rights, building a new social contract with opportunities for all, as @UN Se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Human rights are our only vaccine for hunger and poverty. For discrimination and inequality. For the lack of universal healt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Wikimedia: Join us in one hour for #WikiForHumanRights, a special #EarthDay live event to answer your questions about environmental hea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow us on our new Tiktok channel! Watch our new video on #climatechange... through the lens of #humanrights  https://t.co/Oe5w1s4qpC  #climatecrisis #standupforhumanrights]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Wikimedia: TOMORROW  Celebrate #EarthDay by editing @Wikipedia!  We're adding content to teach others that environmental health as a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hernan Santa Cruz Dialogue in #Ukraine: Social reforms will assist in massive reduction of poverty and inequalities  UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet says that it will also strengthen social cohesion and economic resilience.  Full speech  https://t.co/h9QgAsm48e https://t.co/GDjsGWZ4p6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breakthrough in Madagascar- Primary and secondary school children across Madagascar will receive basic human rights education thanks to a landmark agreement signed with the Ministry on National Education.   Link to the story: https://t.co/Ug3OR6GEBC https://t.co/CmC4y5SiDz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today  Join the @Wikimedia Foundation, @UNHumanRights, and @UNEP for a live discussion on the importance of information on @Wikipedia and beyond about the human right to a healthy environment. #WikiForHumanRights #Wiki4Climate #EarthMonth https://t.co/IuuDT7LA4O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To claim your rights, you must know your rights. This #EarthMonth, join #WikiForHumanRights to help share critical information about human rights and the environment on @Wikipedia. Learn more at a @Wikimedia, @UNHumanRights, and @UNEP event on 15 April! https://t.co/IuuDT7LA4O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: We cannot go back to what led us to a crisis like this one.  We must recover better.  #StandUp4HumanRights]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone needs access to information about how climate change impacts their lives and their rights. Help make this knowledge available on @Wikipedia! Join this live event with @Wikimedia, @UNHumanRights, and @UNEP to get involved: https://t.co/IuuDT7LA4O #WikiForHumanRights]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNHumanRights: Join our #WikiForHumanRights campaign to help share critical info about the links between human rights  the environment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@UKMissionGeneva @FCDOHumanRights donated $854K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Register for our April 15 event on the #humanright to a healthy environment: https://t.co/IuuDT7LA4O  Speakers:  @SREnvironment, @AgyepongJoy, @SBenfeld, and @nickibeckerok   #WikiForHumanRights #Wiki4Climate #StandUp4HumanRights  @UNEP @Wikipedia @Wikimedia https://t.co/bKnXPBZC5h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: We need active participation from all sectors of society. The private sector has played a crucial role in the response to th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Myanmar: @mbachelet fears the situation is heading towards a full-blown conflict. She urges States to urgently apply concerted pressure on the military to halt the commission of grave human rights violations and possible crimes against humanity.  https://t.co/Y57YtqePLx https://t.co/WBp95EPn1c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Myanmar: UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet urges States to take immediate, decisive and impactful measures to push military leadership into halting its campaign of repression and slaughter of its people.  Read  https://t.co/Y57YtqePLx  #StandUp4HumanRights https://t.co/XEzG0C4Ekt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join our Hernn Santa Cruz Dialogue, which will look at #Ukraines social protection  pension system. This Dialogue series aims topromote economic, social  cultural rights + the right to development.   April 15, 9-11:30 Geneva https://t.co/5yR0wouQre #standup4humanrights]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join our #WikiForHumanRights campaign to help share critical info about the links between human rights  the environment on @Wikipedia. Learn more at our launch event on 15 April: https://t.co/IuuDT7LA4O    @Wikimedia @UNEP #Wiki4Climate #StandUp4HumanRights https://t.co/zu1xEcwVkj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Discrimination is at the core of many, if not all, human rights violations. To recover into societies that are truly  and s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ UN Human Rights Chief @mbachelet urges UK Parliament to amend proposed law that risks undermining key human rights obligations by shielding military personnel operating abroad from accountability for torture and other war crimes. Read  https://t.co/xJogFkl5RT https://t.co/tst2B32paF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UN_SPExperts: UN experts express serious concern over series of harsh new legal and administrative measures adopted by #Cambodia in res]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At a #UNGA Consultation for a Permanent Forum on People of #AfricanDescent, @mbachelet highlighted the @UN's role, saying the new Forum could serve as a platform to generate ideas about how to reverse the injustices that lasted for decades.  https://t.co/9Q76rEFV8N #FightRacism https://t.co/2SRuHIjIv5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UN_HRC: In a landmark for least developed countries and small island developing states, 160 @UN member states have sponsored a decision]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@SweMFA  donated $12.6M  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK @SwedenGeneva]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Christof Heyns, a @UN_SPExperts  @UNTreatyBodies expert who has died aged 62, was an inspiring human rights advocate. His warmth, optimism  generosity equalled his expertise. We will miss him terribly. https://t.co/JFAuPCnXpA https://t.co/59d35T78FW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[West Darfur: We are appalled by the latest resurgence of violence in #Sudan that has left 87+ people dead and 191+ injured, and forced thousands to flee their homes.   https://t.co/dCT1AhET8o  Photo: Displaced persons, mostly women and children, in North Darfur, Sudan. https://t.co/oy62E9DID6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Poverty Inequality Discrimination Nationality Migration status  All major reasons why millions of people lack access t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: #PrimaryHealthCare is essential to an equitable recovery from the #COVID19 pandemic and ensuring preparedness for future public he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: #PrimaryHealthCare must be the cornerstone of the health system if we are to address #HealthEquity.   Health is a human right for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: Health workers have been on the frontlines of the pandemic and now must be first in line for the #COVID19 vaccine -- everywhere.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: The challenges we are facing pre-date #COVID19 and the pandemic is  making the situation worse. We must undo generations of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UN_SPExperts: The rise of #HateSpeech disproportionally targeting Sinti and Roma in social media demonstrates the urgent need for measu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@PHinGeneva donated $100K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Wikimedia: On 15 April  Join us, @UNHumanRights  @UNEP to discuss the importance of information on @Wikipedia about the human right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNTreatyBodies: #CEDAW: Libya violated the human rights of an activist working on womens rights by failing to investigate and prosecut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Offline and online the same rights must be protected. The digital space must become truly open and safe for all. Defend the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UN_BiH: .@UN  statement   Calling for urgent action to end violent pushbacks  collective expulsions of #migrants, asylum-seekers ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@MYGenevaUN donated $30K  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFwrzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: As a society, we have a choice: Struggle to get back to normal  even though normal is what brought us to where we are tod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@EU_Commission donated $1.2M  to support our Office's #humanrights work. You can donate too: https://t.co/P6PnCFO2ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UN human rights system plays a crucial role in ensuring a human rights-based response to the #COVID19 pandemic and achieving #SDGs.   Learn more in the 3rd Volume of the CCSA report, https://t.co/hrkk0WwDnn #recoverbetter #standup4humanrights https://t.co/6MC3PkuJuh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #SouthSudan: Community-based militias were responsible for 78% of killings and injuries caused to civilians in 2020 as well as abductions and conflict-related sexual violence during attacks in pockets of the country  New report  https://t.co/UWXe7O3Z3S https://t.co/9mDAGqkvM7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Syria10: "We must advance effective accountability for the severe #HumanRights violations committed by all parties"  @mbachelet calls for action to support a future for Syria's people in which human rights are respected, protected and fulfilled. Read   https://t.co/kATGdx359R https://t.co/d76o888Qyn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mbachelet: Profound inequalities in access to and spending on #healthcare have been a grave challenge even before #COVID19. The future]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>