<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[From Dr. Maquat: "How our cells process and utilize mRNA, both in heath and in disease, has captivated my attention for decades. I am honored to be recognized for research accomplished by the many members of my lab" https://t.co/d48tLPSwax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Dr. Lynne Maquat @WilmotCancer @UR_Med on receiving the 2021 Alpert Prize @harvardmed for her work on RNA function. We are so fortunate to have Dr. Maquat here in #ROC. https://t.co/1hGXcFSu6t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to meet up with our @WilmotCancer community engagement team at #roc public market; encouraging smoking cessation and providing information on cancer screening. https://t.co/CHpXt6niIu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is fantastic for @WilmotCancer and so deserved for Dr Marples, who continues longstanding expertise in radiation biology here in #ROC.  So appreciative of the Sobels generosity. https://t.co/CS0c6yUYIA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brentuximab Vedotin Combined With Chemotherapy in Patients With Newly Diagnosed Early-Stage, Unfavorable-Risk Hodgkin Lymphoma. We @WilmotCancer were pleased to collaborate with @DrAnitaKumar and colleagues @sloan_kettering. @ASCO_pubs   https://t.co/gEQHiXC7M6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Expanding the Toolbox of Adoptive Cell Immunotherapy: a nice summary of a novel T-cell approach to lymphoma treatment in JCO by my @SWOG colleagues Drs. Stiff and Hossain. @asco_pubs https://t.co/EP9Yp2iw1K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamChodak: "Let's end cancer as we know it." - Joe Biden #SOTU  I'm becoming more and more convinced I might see that in my lifetime.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: Dr. Melissa Loh received a Health in Aging Foundation New Investigator Award from @AmerGeriatrics. Congrats, @MelissaLoh2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nice figure! https://t.co/OJwdd1DQW2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just announced @SWOG meeting: @WilmotCancer is number two in accruals, demonstrating our commitment to offering our patients cutting edge clinical trial options. Kudos to our entire clinical trials team on this achievement. https://t.co/bAlDGXqdc5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone was excited about the snow this morning! #ROC https://t.co/yiKeaB83tI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very excited about this upstate NY collaboration focused on cancer disparities. @WilmotCancer @RoswellPark https://t.co/BT7DcEbrd5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NCICTEP_ClinRes: Newly Activated #NCTN #Lymphoma Trial: (S1918) Testing CC-486 (Oral Azacitidine) Plus the Standard Drug Therapy in Pat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SWOG: A reminder that @SWOGs S1918, testing the addition of azacitidine to standard drug therapy in patients 75 or older with newly di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[End of a Fantastic Voyage: Steve Cannistra opines on his very successful tenure as Editor-in-Chief at JCO. I'm humbled to take the reins in June. My best to Steve on his retirement. @ascopubs https://t.co/5etqsjAzRA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So inspiring! Thanks to Dr. ODwyer for her outstanding compassionate care. @WilmotCancer https://t.co/oxiyB92o8R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: "...this is our opportunity, to make a difference."  That's how @isaac_s_harris  other Wilmot researchers view cancer re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting ready!  7pm tonight. Some fun surprises planned. @WilmotCancer https://t.co/6plKWhWjne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First-Ever Oncology Internship Program Aims to Boost Diversity in Cancer Care Workforce #ROC @DrCarlaCasulo @WilmotCancer @oreganruth @ASCO  https://t.co/aDxLN2jumk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beautiful day to cut the ribbon on the new PET/CT and IR suite @WilmotCancer @ur_noyeshealth    in Dansville. Congrats to Amy Pollard on great career and appreciate ongoing support from Saunders family. @UR_Med https://t.co/Q1DQ5fSz1Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AACRPres @AACR Congratulations Dave!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: We are very excited to share that @UofR's @WilmotCancer / @urochestermed was selected as 1 of 5 medical schools in the co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An exciting time for @WilmotCancer community outreach and engagement: a new STTR grant evaluating text messaging strategies for tobacco cessation. Congratulations to Dr. Cupertino. https://t.co/iRP9h9krz2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A very thoughtful commentary on an important anniversary from @AnnaLynnWiliams #JCO @ASCO_pubs https://t.co/N169EH3Nbv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great visit today to @News_8 to plan @WilmotCancer virtual Discovery Ball on April 15. Met some friends in the lobby who may make an appearance as well! Thanks to @AdamChodak and @MaureenMcGuire8 for their support. https://t.co/CNaA8427rl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Support our @WilmotCancer Discovery Ball, happening virtually next month on @News_8  I'm giving in honor of my patients. Eager to work with @AdamChodak to make this a special event. #ROC https://t.co/c03LUKkl7C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This important study informed our @SWOG S1918 trial, activated today which incorporates this tool. Excellent summary by my colleague @SoniSmithMD in accompanying editorial. @ASCO_pubs #JCO https://t.co/CYrIxDPmlX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pembrolizumab followed by AVD in untreated classical Hodgkin lymphoma: more data on checkpoint blockade supporting our @SWOG North American Intergroup S1826 randomized trial of AVD-nivolumab vs. AVD-brentuximab, open in all NCTN groups. @NCICTEP_ClinRes  https://t.co/l1wqtbzEuX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A pleasure to participate, but missed the Cologne experience. Talks were fantastic. #ishl https://t.co/iybdl6S8ua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HayderSaeed_MD: Excellent editorial by @SoniSmithMD on elderly DLBCL #lymsm eval, looking forward to S1918 making a difference in this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An appropriate moment of reflection at noon today during clinic @WilmotCancer https://t.co/VQJDgGi8HY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: Thank you to countless women @WilmotCancer, @UR_Med  @UofRwho have dedicated their careers to helping make life better]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepJoeMorelle this is a very important initiative and @WilmotCancer is in full support. Our new chair of medicine @oreganruth has dedicated her career to study of triple neg disease. #TNBCDay #ROC @UR_Med @PlutaCancerFdn https://t.co/p8LjoBomB1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrRaulCordoba: Interesting concept about #age and the ultimate prognostic score in #Hodgkin #Lymphoma. Age by itself is a poor progno]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrRaulCordoba: We are starting doing geriatric assessment #CGA in clinical trials enrolling older patients with #Hodgkin #Lymphoma. We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking on Tuesday about treating older patients with HL. A great international line-up! @WilmotCancer #ISHL https://t.co/aE5CfJg5mr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Precision Medicine in DLBCL: Are We There Yet?  A really thoughtful commentary on R2CHOP by Dr. Davies. @ASCO_pubs #JCO  https://t.co/SXWgP89DSL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inspiring story of  Treating T-Cell Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia @WilmotCancer featuring Dr. O'Dwyer and discussing particular challenges in AYA population.  https://t.co/rLZtx13DDY via @curetoday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: We're proud to join @AACR as well as 130 scientific organizations  cancer centers in signing this letter to @POTUS that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very nice and important work that informs our @SWOG S1918 trial in older patients. Editorial pending as well putting this into broader perspective. @SoniSmithMD @DrLizBrem @ASCO_pubs https://t.co/tSpEBTpIe7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have an outstanding team ! @WilmotCancer https://t.co/zB4zVdgv9i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UR_Med: Scientist Lynne Maquat received the acclaimed Wolf Prize in Medicine for her extensive fundamental discoveries in #RNA biology]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oreganruth: Broadening performance status eligibility in cancer clinical trials can increase accrual and participant diversity.  Congra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zinc: @WilmotCancer researcher studies its role on p53 and cancer.  https://t.co/KL3YQ2XHzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We @WilmotCancer are working every day on this fight for our patients in #ROC and our surrounding catchment area. https://t.co/sots3r3axP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An honor to introduce Dr Allison (Nobel laureate) who is joining our @WilmotCancer Community Conversations in Cancer today. We are hearing inspiring stories of how clinical trials can improve outcomes. https://t.co/f6fcJIMfGD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impact of Clinical Trial Eligibility Criteria in Patients With Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma: An important analysis from our colleagues at Mayo and Iowa. Our new @SWOG NCTN trials are attempting to address this. @ASCO_pubs @MaurerStats  https://t.co/KQy7UlHM5e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fresh Faces, New Energy:  @Wilmot How our new scientific recruits are transforming research in #ROC. A great read.  https://t.co/YGxCx0d0SK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoyed working on this with my colleague Dr. Brice. We have different approaches to treatment, and present a harmonized summary in this rapidly changing field. Our @SWOG S1826 managed to get a mention!  https://t.co/46lNXVvN17]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Go Pack Go!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great @ASCO_pubs #jco study from @WilmotCancer @DrAllisonMags representing our geriatric oncology program. https://t.co/cHPQGxJgfg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: We're excited about the energy a group of junior cancer researchers bring to @WilmotCancer Institute. #URochesterResearch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @Jeevisha_Bajaj @WilmotCancer on @ASH_hematology Scholar Award. https://t.co/58RcRHpefx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We @swog will look into this. @DrDanPersky https://t.co/cp2eYNzLNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out our Special Series on Immunotherapy for Hematologic Malignancies: a compendium of fantastic, up-to-date reviews by leaders in the field. #JCO @asco_pubs @charliecraddock   https://t.co/K39NpHx4iH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We at #JCO @ASCO_pubs eagerly await our next group of fellows. I encourage all interested to apply. @ASCO https://t.co/ADWoXD2Zfn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worth a read to see all that my @SWOG colleague @SoniSmithMD has accomplished. I feel very fortunate to work with her. https://t.co/0LnJG0QLzs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My best present today from science and @UR_Med   Moderna COVID vaccine! And bonus special appearances by Strong CEO and COO. I feel very fortunate. Happy holidays to all. https://t.co/tUoaMROnqF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: We need to give. The world is a better place for it.  That's what Bob Coombs says when it comes to the reason why he pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: Happy holidays from @DrJFriedberg  all of us @WilmotCancer Institute. #ROC https://t.co/21p0gs5WRa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MediHumdani: Dr. Munshi @MunshiPashna providing update on the development combined @ASTCT @TheEBMT @CIBMTR HCT/CT guideline project in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations @KunleOdunsiMD  We will miss you in upstate NY, and look forward to future collaborations @WilmotCancer https://t.co/cBAjdUGyL1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: . @WilmotCancer team has launched a new fully-remote program that will help any adults in our 27-county region quit smoki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrAEvens: Yes! Relapses in #cHL usually occur early but they continue thru 5 yrs (as seen in PET-adapted S0186 updated data by @huntsma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASCO_pubs: Editorial: Parsing the paradox of myelodysplastic syndrome https://t.co/mBGO7UNLlu by @MikkaelSekeres #mdssm #JCO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BroeckelmannPJ: Great #JCO @ASCO_pubs editorial and discussion of our recent analysis of polychemotherapy v ASCT in relapsed HL after i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Catching up on Ed sessions: Nice talk on epigenetics and DLBCL by my @SWOG colleague Dr Amengual @columbiacancer #ASH20 https://t.co/Z3wzECRATf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SharonCastelli2: @JustinekahnMD @MaurerStats COG analysis #ASH20Poster2072 is rationale for inclusion patients&gt;=12 #ASH 2029 Poster3470]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Makes #ASH2020 session even better!  #ASHFromHome https://t.co/U9wKWcVcME]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I agree this could be game changing. https://t.co/YJ3c4OHTI9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our HL collaborative study in older patients demonstrates reasonable efficacy with BV-containing doublets. This is an appealing option for the very old and those with comorbidities. #ASH2020 https://t.co/FbP51AgSPe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pleased we are able to contribute with our long term data from @SWOG S0816. @DebbieMStephens https://t.co/CwrCvmFstw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bispecific antibody session (moderated by @Wilmot Cancer Dr Barr) demonstrates outstanding preliminary results for several products across many histologies. Hoping to see limited duration strategies moving forward. https://t.co/p4TclDkyoB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anitajkumarMD: Awesome to collaborate with experts in #HodgkinLymphoma, #geriheme and #predictionmodeling! #DissertationAim @AngieRodda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Max Topp: Great scientific session on bispecific antiCD20s #ASH2020   CRs reported post CAR-T. Several exciting options, in indolent and aggressive lymphomas. https://t.co/gj4gFR2q6b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Wang: VLS-101 phase 1 with responses, including complete responses #ASH2020  My colleague Dr Barr enrolling patients @WilmotCancer https://t.co/AHgLEsbQkP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our @WilmotCancer team is well represented #ASH2020   My congratulations to these investigators #ASHFromHome https://t.co/bJc2MaX8eQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: To hand off a concept to a clinical team that can run a study  its really, really difficult, but weve done it."  Read]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome aboard; you have made a great choice @WilmotCancer #ROC https://t.co/Mz5ugg9wTk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations @lauracalvi3 on funding from @NASA ! https://t.co/09ISzh5Xtc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a most unusual year, rounds on inpatient service today continue to remind me to be thankful for my health and the privilege of working @WilmotCancer with a fantastic compassionate team.  My best wishes to all for Thanksgiving. https://t.co/EIkHr5dWaD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We @WilmotCancer are dedicated to overcoming challenges in cancer prevention, diagnosis and care in our rural catchment area. Great ongoing collaboration with @CCHP_URMC #ROC https://t.co/XbvjYrwkpG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This project was started by our @WilmotCancer lymphoma fellow Dr Carolyne Delage who died tragically in a bicycle accident. The manuscript is in honor of her life, and her contributions. An important observation for our pts on BTK inhibitors. https://t.co/3DG2HvyXuI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrAEvens: Great monthly S1826 call: stage 3/4 #HodgkinLymphoma NCI study led by @SWOG @cityofhope Dr Herrera w/ @eaonc @ALLIANCE_org @C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great interview.  So happy that Dr Cupertino has joined our @WilmotCancer team, as we expand our focus on #ROC as well as our large rural catchment area. #FLX https://t.co/XaEN0fKlPa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant wait to welcome Dr OReagan to @WilmotCancer #ROC. https://t.co/ogWWSNCCTq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A great night watching @springsteen #LetterToYou  His best since The Rising; and lyrics so appropriate for this time. Highly recommended!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome aboard; we @WilmotCancer look forward to working with you! https://t.co/IqMVmvj0Op]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: Our own @DrJFriedberg speaks with @MSchwartzWHAM this morning about blood cancers  how support from the @LLSusa helps ad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoying my conversation; back on at 7 AM to discuss our lymphoma research program @WilmotCancer https://t.co/z9h4ReSGKB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nice article detailing impact @SoniSmithMD has had on patients @UCCancerCenter   She is also an inspiration to countless mentees, particularly on our @SWOG lymphoma committee https://t.co/027pwqhdYU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great cover story featuring @isaac_s_harris @Jeevisha_Bajaj and our other star research recruits. @WilmotCancer Dialogue hot off the press; look for it soon. #ROC https://t.co/ESuYt8WFLn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One Way to One Day Prevent Cancer: Map the Fundamentals of How Cells Go Awry  @WilmotCancer https://t.co/NiCR9vpMnB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a priority @WilmotCancer with an increasingly older aged catchment area. Our clinical trial accrual over represents older patients through intention and our specialty geriatric oncology clinic @rochgerionc https://t.co/PqCqz8O9C4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coping with Cancer: great discussion with @whec_DDewberry about clinical trials @WilmotCancer  https://t.co/DJgigmJR0y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are so excited to welcome @oreganruth to @WilmotCancer where she will be our Associate Director for Mentoring and Career Development! https://t.co/4BwfFj8jFx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrLizBrem: Today! Excited to connect with everyone on this important topic! #lymsm #GeriOnc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BroeckelmannPJ: Excited to see our #JCO Understanding the Pathway paper on CD30 CARs in Hodgkin lymphoma online @ASCO_pubs: https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ROC_CMSR: @ROC_CMSR is proud to celebrate faculty achievements. Dr. Laura Calvi (@lauracalvi3) is the inaugural SKAWA Foundation Profes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WilmotCancer: Starting off this Sunday morning of the #WilmotWarrior Walk with some #gratitude from @DrJFriedberg.   Thank you to every]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>