<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeauxDawn @weldonmcgill Many thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GYamey Looks like I'm in good company, will listen, thank you Dr. Yamey!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GYamey: 3 rock star birthdays today:   Ian McCulloch, Echo  the Bunnymen (The Cutter remains a classic)  Gary Daly of China Crisi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AliceFromUGA Many thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Annie447 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NicolleDWallace: Thank you @PeterHotez]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace Many thanks again!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DemFromCT Many thanks Greg!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarcelinoKHOU Many thanks Marcelino!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@morgfair Thank you so much, really kind!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaneatLFPress Thank you Jane!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jodyvance Thank you Jody!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saribethrose Thank you Sari!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many thanks for all your kind birthday thoughts for tomorrow, cinco de mayo. Without your support and kind wishes, the antivaccine crush would have been intolerable. I wont forget it, gracias, thank you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace You are the best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wildcatdds: @PeterHotez @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector And you, Sir, are a mensch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, she was right to make that statement, and I agreed with her. This B.1.1.7 variant is awful and at the time none of us knew if the vaccine vs UK variant would win out. And even now we dont really know. In her position I would have probably made the same call, she saved lives https://t.co/LZrUESD7Io]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShoshanaHantman @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector Definitely]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @terrikern: @PeterHotez @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector Takes one to know 3 - YOU ARE THE FOURTH!!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stevegoldca: @PeterHotez @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector 4. Some guy named @PeterHotez]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@famdoc @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector Is it? Im always open to learning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ebkesq123 @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector Thats kind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ebkesq123: @PeterHotez @WHCOS @ASlavitt @CDCDirector And Peter Hotez!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres what we didnt say today:   3 great Americans who led the vaccination of our nation out of this awful epidemic are 3 landsmen (look it up) @WHCOS Ron Klain @ASlavitt Andy Slavitt, @CDCDirector Rochelle Walensky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good thread from @jbkrell https://t.co/6kaoudaZiR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@The_KD_Houston @thenewsoncnbc @POTUS Yes of course, they do, and we are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProperLookout: @EmilyDeCiccio @PeterHotez @thenewsoncnbc We're talking about paying people to take winning lottery tickets off our hand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best: @Yamiche https://t.co/vGgoIP6yhy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmilyDeCiccio: Covid vaccine incentives make U.S. look like a nation of sulky adolescents,' @PeterHotez tells @thenewsoncnbc  https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suburbsboymom @DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace Many thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great pic. Im privileged to have worked with both the President and the First Lady. The POTUS in his role championing guinea worm and river blindness control @CarterCenter the FLOTUS for creating Every Child By Two, now @Vaxyourfam : smart committed and kind, no surprises https://t.co/5Agt3EtX7D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thenewsoncnbc: President Biden announced a new Covid vaccine goal today: Get 70% of U.S. adults to receive at least one dose of a Covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many thanks @thenewsoncnbc for hosting me today. The @POTUS announcement was good news, but I do worry about widening a blue-red state divide, now top blue/blueish states 50-60% vaccinated bottom deep red states 33-36% vaccinated. Thats a problem https://t.co/2fEnbBEVnK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZerlinaShow: Anti-vaxxers and science skeptics are nothing new. So why can't we navigate around them on Covid?    Social media, disinfo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will go on @thenewsoncnbc @CNBC to speak on todays events]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InOurBackYards: Canadians  eh?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZerlinaShow: Liz Cheney is under fire from members of her own party for... telling the truth. @Elise_Jordan  @MichaelSteele explain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suburbsboymom @DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace I have an article about this under review so hopefully soon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeadlineWH: "I don't know what's gong on at Fox News, but there's some kind of tear in the matrix, but it is very concerning that they']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bobmiller42 @NicolleDWallace @DeadlineWH @Timodc Its partly in my Daily Beast article today]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many thanks @NicolleDWallace for hosting me @DeadlineWH with @Timodc re: we must reach not just 70% of adults, but actually 70% of entire US population, which means essentially all of adults and adolescents. It also will require vaccinating Canada Mexico https://t.co/FB0r9o511N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrBabinski: Well said @PeterHotez and thank you. #Covid19Ca #VaccineForAll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeDroitca: Un expert amricain veut que les tats-Unis aident le Canada https://t.co/hfrDIxFkVQ https://t.co/1MDx3faLQR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RosemaryKnarr Thats my hope as well]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im scheduled to join @NicolleDWallace on @DeadlineWH at 4:20 PM Eastern, 3:20 Central]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InlandCaGuy @socalmom I think it will be made open access soon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: "Sure, the odds are stacked against us," writes @PeterHotez. "But I believe we can achieve 80 to 85 percent vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @socalmom: Thanks, Dr. @PeterHotez - this was hopeful.  https://t.co/R6eDG8AZwE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @troy_patterson: @PeterHotez THANK YOU for mentioning Canada in the segment you just did on @CNN. We need to change the course of this p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OthalieGraham: Thank you so much for caring about Canada and for mentioning them on @CNN  today! @PeterHotez]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilHyndman: @PeterHotez THANK YOU for your comments on CNN just now about our country (Canada). Your comments couldn't be more correct]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@snowballsrfree @AlisynCamerota @VictorBlackwell @POTUS I didnt say that, heres my understanding https://t.co/0hs0muVu4d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4. I discussed some of these aspects in my @thedailybeast article out this AM https://t.co/NI8toJ0ths]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3. We must help India  accelerate supply chains for their major vaccine manufacturers, and recognize a domino effect as India now wont export vaccine to Africa, we need a coherent overarching foreign policy for vaccine diplomacy. So far not articulated from WH or State Dept]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2.  Well need to vaccinate Canada  and northern Mexico  to also halt virus transmission in the US. This means more than sending a few million AZOx doses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1. The conservative lobby and four polls now showing that 40-50% of Republicans wont get vaccinated. We must expand our outreach to conservative groups. Remember its not 70% of adults we must reach, its 70% of total population, and that means almost all adults]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many thanks @AlisynCamerota @VictorBlackwell for hosting me following @POTUS remarks important to optimize access for those who want to get vaccinated. I was enthusiastic about his comments, but also there were a few elements missing, here they are: https://t.co/OuOCx5k19S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCDHate: "A report from the CCDH found that just 12 anti-vaxxers are responsible for almost two-thirds of anti-vaccine content circulat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking at the just released fact sheet: @POTUS doing everything possible to ensure that anyone who wants to get vaccinated can. And thats great, and important, but not sufficient for reaching conservatives who are dug in, we must help them too https://t.co/SkzViYUDv9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looks forward to speaking with @AlisynCamerota @VictorBlackwell on @CNN 3 PM Eastern, 2 PM Central]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @biannagolodryga: The Tree of Life Synagogue shooting was one of the most painful and personal tragedies I've covered. The congregation']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricBAndRagout: @sara_carrion_ @PeterHotez I guess he IS trying to save me, after all...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kate_griffin: @kathleenlenihan @PeterHotez And factor is stress during a pandemic year, changes in fitness, nutrition, sedentary lifest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kate_griffin: @lacepurplesky @kathleenlenihan @PeterHotez Actually, many of my patients reported last year changes in their cycles, inc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whenever someone starts a conversation, Im not antivaccine but...  remember the guy who told you its not about the money because it will be all about the money.   Fox News night programming has launched a very destructive antivaccine campaign in 2021. I dont understand why https://t.co/W5DVlwbeG5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its impressive how so many false statements can be packed into a single tweet, but will focus on the first: I take Zero Big PhRMA funding, grants, contracts, personal funding or otherwise. The guinea pig statement makes no sense, like some type of AI assembly of antivax words... https://t.co/SS3VW9msZO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iamstillresist1: @PeterHotez @RuhleOnMSNBC @SRuhle @mollymhunter @stephgosk The Truth Zone ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricDortenzio: Avec @PeterHotez pour animer la session de questions rponses ! @franceinhouston @FranceScience]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RuhleOnMSNBC: The FDA is expected to approve the Pfizer covid-19 vaccine for some kids as early as this week.  Co-Director of the Cente]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: "Vaccines are working, and its important we dont get distracted by a moving target that has been seized upon by the fa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RyanGir64147787: @HoudeFamily @PeterHotez He's such a kind, brilliant man!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanGir64147787 @HoudeFamily Many thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @usisraelbsf: BSF Board Member @PeterHotez has always been an unrelenting champion of science and evidence-based research - especially t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EClinicalMed: NEW RESEARCH: Accelerated #vaccine  rollout is imperative to mitigate highly transmissible #COVID-19 #variants .  @Aliso]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4/4 I discuss some of these aspects in my new @thedailybeast article this AM     https://t.co/NI8toJ0ths]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/4 In the US Im concerned about a widening disparity across different states. The blue or blueish states in New England, NY, CA, NM now with 50% vaccine coverage, but deep red states GA AL TN LA ID WY under 35% we need greater outreach to conservative groups]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/4 globally US needs to shape a more coherent foreign policy and vaccine diplomacy framework, balancing the needs to support COVAX, India  and the need to help vaccinate Canada  and Mexico  to slow virus transmission across North America, also our @TexasChildrens vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/4 Many thanks @RuhleOnMSNBC @SRuhle for hosting me with @mollymhunter @stephgosk discussing the challenges of the US vaccinating internationally and nationally https://t.co/40oVp8HVOF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RuhleOnMSNBC: COMING UP: @SRuhle has breaking coverage of the day's most important stories all on @MSNBC.  @stephgosk @mollymhunter @Pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My latest opinion piece @thedailybeast   Forget Herd Immunity. Heres How We End This COVID-19 Nightmare https://t.co/NI8toJ0ths]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TCRG2012: @PeterHotez https://t.co/wxXC64zXKs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In my writings and public remarks, Ive been working to make the case that antiscience and some antivaccine belong in the same category as other disinformation and hate groups. So far, I dont have all the dots connected, but its awfully close.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its a fair point, but I do this after some discussion thought. A reason I remain on Twitter: to reflect and educate on how antiscience disinformation operates: the players, their methods, their increasing sophistication, links with other hate groups, some find it instructive. https://t.co/OO6yAatfq7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheCaroleShow: I am so thankful for @PeterHotez.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important question. And the answer is...I have no clue. Like everyone else, I have hypotheses and speculations, some boring and dreary around ratings (most likely) others more provocative around international intrigue (but less likely). We just dont know https://t.co/PeYgXUVuHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So its clear there is a direct line from antivax ringleaders to Fox News producers, mutually benefiting both parties]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They said HPV vaccine causes infertility and miscarriages and now copy paste that onto COVID19 vaccines. Remember whats happening. Antivax forces are getting ready to draw a line in the sand against any approvals for adolescents 12-15 years old]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So heres the actual deal: as we worked to discredit fake antivaccine links to autism and with some success with my Rachel book, the antivaccine lobby needed a new thing. So they went after the HPV vaccine and made the same fake assertions about its links to reproductive health]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow, right out of the antivaccine playbook, except more nuanced fine tuned. Diabolical: Fox News has recruited clever writers, with science backgrounds, to press their political agenda, discredit scientists, promote doubt and instability. The Murdochs pay better wages than Putin https://t.co/W5DVlwbeG5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetsIsArt: Thank you @PeterHotez]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another statement coming out tomorrow...stay tuned]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We expect to have a statement about this soon, focused on both the immediate urgencies on vaccine development and making vaccines now for LMICs vs long term approaches  https://t.co/3P8spyXghA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many thanks @PnPCBC for the opportunity to explain - based on our shared history, humanitarian goals, and obvious common sense - why America can and must do more to help vaccinate Canada  I will do my best on this side to keep on pushing and digging https://t.co/iuwz3zhKAH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mbeisen Agreed, tomorrow in The Daily Beast I will explain why Ive even stopped using the term]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HoudeFamily Many thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HoudeFamily: @PeterHotez was on CBC News. Was like seeing a friend on tv . Not only is he my go-to on all things COVID19 related, but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JInterlandi So sorry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChelseaClinton: Looking forward to this conversation later this week. If youre interested in #vaccines and vaccinations for kids and y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MiaGabrielson: @PnPCBC @PeterHotez @POTUS @davidcommon Thank you for your support ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rue29Napa: I completely agree! Thank you @PeterHotez https://t.co/wu24EWijJ1]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>