<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Wales Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 5th May.  54 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 211,692.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 5,551. https://t.co/BfuwfvliuD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guernsey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 5th May.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 822.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 14. https://t.co/Oo4NRfOuEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England regions by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 29. https://t.co/03TsxBcXjA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland local government districts by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 29. https://t.co/0NeAhf9PZ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Scotland local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 29. https://t.co/BJiFOBFAvi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ London boroughs by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 29. https://t.co/qs6BHAg1AD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 29. 2/2 https://t.co/cKTiK1y19C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 29. 1/2 https://t.co/01Kec7q3Tb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  383 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 250,672.  2 new deaths reported, giving a total of 4,908. https://t.co/eQ0bEjhfJM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jersey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,234.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 69. https://t.co/p0IbR4yvv5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 1,590.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/DfaNjqTpy6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  1,659 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,865,013.  3 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,186. https://t.co/klzmyLvRme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 50,297,911 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +208,362 doses in the latest 24hr period.  34,667,904 people have received their first dose, with 15,630,007 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/9sFPjJo8Hv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Kingdom Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  1,946 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 4,423,796.  4 new deaths reported, giving a total of 127,543. https://t.co/csXECGr7ow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  83 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 120,501.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 2,146. https://t.co/P5B6QosOjJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  139 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 226,644.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 7,660. https://t.co/pt8BeWHnAD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS England reports a further 7 COVID-19 hospital deaths occurring over 7 dates.  26 were reported last Tuesday, 34 two weeks ago  33 three weeks ago. https://t.co/gIikdw9aI1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FYI this is two days worth of data.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guernsey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 822.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 14. https://t.co/O5WhY85pTG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wales Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Tuesday 4th May.  65 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 211,638.  1 new death reported, giving a total of 5,551. https://t.co/c17Jf9PGbt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pouriaaa Once weve opened up (aint sitting outside in this weather!) the steaks  are on me! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexisBrassey I shall do them tomorrow when all nations have reported the data.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 50,089,549 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +254,552 doses in the latest 24hr period.  34,588,600 people have received their first dose, with 15,500,949 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/UIktRPQtr4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Monday 3rd May.  453 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 250,290.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 4,906. https://t.co/T6TeYvnXHE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@igdstrachan @PHE_uk tweeted it. https://t.co/GxfDsO0lKr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Kingdom Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Monday 3rd May.  1,649 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 4,421,850.  1 new death reported, giving a total of 127,539. https://t.co/nZkszBnd1K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Tweetpop121 Yesterday. https://t.co/qJVsMc12wO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guernsey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Monday 3rd May.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 822.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 14. https://t.co/H1UmANU5KH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Monday 3rd May.  64 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 120,418.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 2,146. https://t.co/EAI7yrpcDi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Monday 3rd May.  132 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 226,505.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 7,660. https://t.co/8I8cUdkouy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS England reports a further 3 COVID-19 hospital deaths occurring over 2 dates.  4 were reported last Monday, 1 two weeks ago  11 three weeks ago. https://t.co/Hcj9K8Xe7v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of deaths of people who have died within 28 days of a first positive test, by date reported. #coronavirus #England #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/cRDW7VW5Ag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of individuals who have had at least one lab-confirmed positive test result, by date reported. #coronavirus #England #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/MZHExa5tKx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of deaths of people who have died within 28 days of a first positive test, by date reported. #coronavirus #NorthernIreland #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/aWzHWDoLIb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ United Kingdom Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of deaths of people who have died within 28 days of a first positive test, by date reported. #coronavirus #UK #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/iCTITfCFln]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ United Kingdom Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of individuals who have had at least one lab-confirmed positive test result, by date reported. #coronavirus #UK #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/ItdfO5bXe2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  402 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 249,838.  1 new death reported, giving a total of 4,906. https://t.co/ukYLcZPF0b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  1 new case (person positive) reported, giving a total of 1,590.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/sjj6gOSIeS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  1,377 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,861,901.  13 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,182. https://t.co/LlMxNkVK8d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 49,834,997 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +515,479 doses in the latest 24hr period.  34,505,380 people have received their first dose, with 15,329,617 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/k6Y4hLTNKE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Kingdom Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  1,671 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 4,420,201.  14 new deaths reported, giving a total of 127,538. https://t.co/6b6epZbtbJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Scotland Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of deaths of people who have died within 28 days of a first positive test, by date reported. #coronavirus #Scotland #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/XzkBn3aJuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of individuals who have had at least one lab-confirmed positive test result, by date reported. #coronavirus #NorthernIreland #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/NsdfaGQTFA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Scotland Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of individuals who have had at least one lab-confirmed positive test result, by date reported. #coronavirus #Scotland #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/QB4Q8VPVIl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS England reports a further 3 COVID-19 hospital deaths occurring over 2 dates.  6 were reported last Sunday, 9 two weeks ago  11 three weeks ago. https://t.co/wqzSGfyOG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  146 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 226,373.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 7,660. https://t.co/1a9lx5SvNy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  69 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 120,354.  1 new death reported, giving a total of 2,146. https://t.co/5t4rXBBxKP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Wales Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of deaths of people who have died within 28 days of a first positive test, by date reported. #coronavirus #Wales #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/EYdCFSStve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guernsey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 822.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 14. https://t.co/9yMcq2ek5r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Wales Coronavirus (COVID-19) weekly overview of individuals who have had at least one lab-confirmed positive test result, by date reported. #coronavirus #Wales #Corona #covid19 #Covid19UK https://t.co/9WgzqWnXhf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wales Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Sunday 2nd May.  79 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 211,573.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 5,550. https://t.co/eWiyd4KBJu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Saturday 1st May.  569 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 249,437.  3 new deaths reported, giving a total of 4,906. https://t.co/k1gKVhEAsc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Saturday 1st May.  2 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 1,589.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/PrA1CrO3Jz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Saturday 1st May.  1,642 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,860,524.  6 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,169. https://t.co/A4UryjtprF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 49,287,257 doses of a COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +535,113 doses in the latest 24hr period.  34,346,273 people have received their first dose, with 14,940,984 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/Mr1UpmAUX6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Kingdom Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Saturday 1st May.  1,907 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 4,418,530.  7 new deaths reported, giving a total of 127,524. https://t.co/FTSJL14hn4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS England reports a further 16 COVID-19 hospital deaths occurring over 8 dates.  20 were reported last Saturday, 28 two weeks ago  34 three weeks ago. https://t.co/lRwm1NNfUo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Saturday 1st May.  90 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 120,285.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 2,145. https://t.co/jdFUNl8CbG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Saturday 1st May.  175 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 226,227.  1 new death reported, giving a total of 7,660. https://t.co/keL9l16CTt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England regions by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. https://t.co/yYLwmPBLRT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland local government districts by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. https://t.co/FjzIdjcUI8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Scotland local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. https://t.co/vE00CPFAvZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Wales local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. https://t.co/ATckcf66ju]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ London boroughs by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. https://t.co/SadhyHyEt4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. 2/2 https://t.co/nVJtlVxCv5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 25. 1/2 https://t.co/HJbc2wrg2R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jersey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,234.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 69. https://t.co/5o8sZimjIF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 1,587.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/ufaC8qbuKL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  545 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 248,870.  4 new deaths reported, giving a total of 4,903. https://t.co/TuFFm70Awh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  2,046 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,858,882.  14 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,163. https://t.co/uzmJdL1NTL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 48,748,962 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +610,953 doses in the latest 24hr period.  34,216,087 people have received their first dose, with 14,532,875 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/vIZh3a0GRK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Kingdom Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  2,381 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 4,416,623.  15 new deaths reported, giving a total of 127,517. https://t.co/XycEgjwQhB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  108 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 120,195.  1 new death reported, giving a total of 2,145. https://t.co/qD2MBSqjHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  191 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 226,052.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 7,659. https://t.co/IKrqUmNvcZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS England reports a further 14 COVID-19 hospital deaths occurring over 10 dates.  19 were reported last Friday, 18 two weeks ago  33 three weeks ago. https://t.co/pLyTozEWAp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guernsey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 822.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 14. https://t.co/hV0Up1mVt8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wales Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Friday 30th April.  36 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 211,494.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 5,550. https://t.co/B1ZiFzFiTf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  474 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 248,326.  3 new deaths reported, giving a total of 4,899. https://t.co/O3LpRr9R7t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jersey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  1 new case (person positive) reported, giving a total of 3,234.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 69. https://t.co/T9ZmPEvUp7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 1,587.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/UVW0dcNDhl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  2,103 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,856,836.  15 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,149. https://t.co/EtIbFBOZ3e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 48,138,009 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +597,025 doses in the latest 24hr period.  34,094,048 people have received their first dose, with 14,043,961 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/MQGdPub55a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Kingdom Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  2,445 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 4,414,242.  22 new deaths reported, giving a total of 127,502. https://t.co/111j4N7rS1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  95 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 120,087.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 2,144. https://t.co/tyN7ztiLVj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  178 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 225,861.  5 new deaths reported, giving a total of 7,659. https://t.co/PCwTbdlwQW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS England reports a further 13 COVID-19 hospital deaths occurring over 7 dates.  22 were reported last Thursday, 28 two weeks ago  34 three weeks ago. https://t.co/foqP6QH7AA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wales Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  69 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 211,458.  2 new deaths reported, giving a total of 5,550. https://t.co/CDKomKMd8R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guernsey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Thursday 29th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 822.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 14. https://t.co/P0JRmcbDsA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England regions by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. https://t.co/znppyWaQw2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland local government districts by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. https://t.co/KMqVJQxDQi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Scotland local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. https://t.co/OEP5BkLYAU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Wales local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. https://t.co/jP62SYeOru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ London boroughs by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. https://t.co/tLt7Q7VMdM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. 2/2 https://t.co/mJkX9ACEDN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ England local authorities by highest number of COVID-19 positives per 100k population.  7day rolling rate by specimen date - ending Apr 23. 1/2 https://t.co/IMUfqzNs64]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ireland (ROI) Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  371 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 247,857.  13 new deaths reported, giving a total of 4,896. https://t.co/myP5sytrRR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jersey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,233.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 69. https://t.co/tdxjcOHXzG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 1,587.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/l8TIYRnlgO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  1,829 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,854,733.  27 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,134. https://t.co/tGW4xmQvNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 47,540,984 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +495,593 doses in the latest 24hr period.  33,959,908 people have received their first dose, with 13,581,076 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/K8jj9tErRM]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>