<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#HealthSpotlight South Africa aims to vaccinate around 1.1 million people against #COVID19 by the end of March as it ramps up its vaccination programme. The second batch of the JohnsonJohnson vaccine arrived in the country two days ago. https://t.co/jA62vvm4Ic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As announced by His Excellency President MC Ramaphosa, the cumulative number of COVID-19  cases in South Africa is 1,513,393 with 1168 new cases identified since the last report. https://t.co/TLqVBCyMRE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Get the vaccine to lower your risk of severe illness or risk your life," advises Dr Angelique Coetzee, Chairperson of the SA Medical Association.  #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/sWzsuBH8Y5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While the rapid rollout of the #COVID19 vaccine to healthcare workers continues, we must continue to stay safe and practice non-pharmaceutical interventions. https://t.co/L3cRWerNWE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,512,225. https://t.co/AF2Y0MZLM7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The second  batch of JohnsonJohnson vaccines has arrived in South Africa. Watch live coverage of the arrival from SABC News. #Sisonke  https://t.co/u6sEIaT5tS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SA reaches its first #COVID19 vaccination milestone early!  Read more here:  https://t.co/Cf9tH0WPZ5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Africa's second tranche of JohnsonJohnson #COVID19 vaccines have touched down at OR Tambo Int! It comes as the majority of initial doses received two weeks ago have been administered to healthcare workers via the Sisonke Project https://t.co/VB3nqRZo17]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,510,778. https://t.co/xf2OdfpG1N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccine offers you the promise that your doctors will be protected and able to help you when you may need them whether for COVID-19 or another reason. Dr Daniel Israel, Johannesburg General Practioner. https://t.co/RP3Jdl8HDi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 vaccine rollout programme in SA has been extremely successful so far, says Prof Glenda Gray, principle investigator of the JohnsonJohnson vaccine.  https://t.co/XFqhoIy0v2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Healthcare worker Clement Nhlanhla Ngcobo from Charlotte Maxeke Hospital in Johannesburg tells us why hell be taking the #COVID19 vaccine. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/AKfdKdlVP2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Healthcare workers, in private  public service, are being vaccinated for #COVID19 in phase one of SAs vaccine rollout programme. Sheila Kanyarosokie from Melomed Belville Hospital in Cape Town agrees the vaccine is an important tool in our #COVID19 battle. #IChooseVaccination https://t.co/ruDHfZQbu0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The number of healthcare workers vaccinated under the Sisonke Protocol is 52,647 as of 6pm, 25  February, 2021. https://t.co/S8r7yR6m7C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pillay: Registration information for being vaccinated will include the location of your work place and the EVDS will assign you to a centre close to that location and communicate that information back to you after it has been determined #VaccineRolloutSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pillay: The vaccine is able to provide 100% protection from mortality. #VaccineRolloutSA  "We really need to encourage all our healthcare workers to be vaccinated," he says.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pillay: An ensemble study found that JJ vaccine is 57% effective against moderate to severe #COVID19  #VaccineRolloutSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pillay: Provinces will develop lists of vaccination sites and of those that need to be vaccinated #VaccineRolloutSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Health DDG Dr Anban Pillay described the three-stage #VaccinationRolloutSA plan: Phase I: Alll health sector workers  Phase II: Essential workers Persons in congregate settings Persons over 60 years Persons over 18 years with co morbidities  Phase III: other persons over 18 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johannesburg GP Dr Sheri Fanaroff shares her experience and excitement about receiving the #COVID19 vaccine. Dr Fanaroff is a general practitioner in private practice and among thousand of healthcare workers who have been vaccinated over the past week.  https://t.co/GgfAyfvhyY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,507,448. https://t.co/EWDnoEdfcr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In conversation with Professor Jeffrey Mphahlele, Vice President of the SAMRC. Here, marketing manager George Daniel, asks the Professor about possible side effects of a #COVID19 vaccine.  https://t.co/11ZC0yWLlJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joburg general practitioner Dr Mark Holliday says take the shot. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/LQxSL3BX2z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A tribute to the Covid19 frontline healthcare workers at Charlotte Maxeke Johannesburg Academic Hospital.  https://t.co/uPSZb4u43w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,505,586. https://t.co/dLgCg4nl20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Healthcare workers across the country are being vaccinated against #Covid19. The vaccine launch was a momentous occassio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Health Minister Dr Zweli Mkhize announced in parliament today that the next batch of 80,000 doses of JohnsonJohnson vaccines will arrive this Saturday, 27 February 2021.   Read the latest on SA's COVID vaccine rollout here:  https://t.co/eeuMVVGHNg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Vaccines have been used for hundreds of years to protect communities from diseases', says Jackie Maimin,  ICPA CEO and pharmacist. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/gCgIVELBZB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,504,588 with 792 new cases identified since the last report. https://t.co/s5pIT46eui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Health Minister, Dr Zweli Mkhize, addresses the media in Western Cape at Khayelitsha hospital as the first healthcare workers were vaccinated with the Johnson  Johnson vaccine. Listen here: https://t.co/nRRha6TsW5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A message from Dr Abdul Aleem Rawoot, an orthopedic surgeon in Cape Town, on why hell be taking the  #Covid19 vaccine. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/iuqwaW5ARN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctors are excited about being vaccinated in the 1st phase of our #Covid19 vaccine rollout. The 2nd phase of the plan will mean a decrease in the number of  #Covid19 patients being admitted to hospitals, says Dr Sangeetha Thomas at Charlotte Maxeke Hospital. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/4w8D5hasKM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,503,796. https://t.co/cwT7KXSQfO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A message from Father Michael Weeder, Dean of the St. George's Cathedral in Cape Town. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/tkPgcFHfaC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NDOH and the Sisonke Programme have allocated one third of all vaccine doses available for private healthcare workers. This follows productive discussions between the department  the private sector. https://t.co/vub322YLre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HealthSpotlight More than 10 thousand  healthcare workers have been vaccinated since the start of the vaccine rollout in SA on Wednesday. Heres a look at the arrival  launch highlights. https://t.co/50h5RKhhhx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Phakama Ngxokela, from the Pharmacy Department at Khayelitsha District Hospital in Cape Town, says the #Covid19 vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sinovuyo Jiya is a secretary at Khayelitsha District Hospital in Cape Town. She urges her community to support the government and take the vaccine. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/pzmF5iv1rH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,502,367. https://t.co/c6WgjT79vy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Juanita Arendse, Chief Director for Emergency and Clinical Services Support in the Western Cape, encourages healthcare workers to get the vaccine, to protect themselves and their communities. https://t.co/FuGZr5pZtI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Take the #Covid19 vaccine to stay safe and protected from the virus", says Jo-Annke Snyders from the Pharmacy Department at Khayelitsha District Hospital. https://t.co/cDq3GrqkT6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A proud moment for the CEO of Khayelitsha District Hospital, at the countrys vaccine launch this week. David Binza says the vaccine is our only hope of getting immunity from the #Covid19 virus. https://t.co/GG5JPrfEMf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reginald Memani is head of security at Khayelitsha District Hospital. Here he emphasizes the importance of taking the vaccine. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/KfZLiHdkzr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mubhashira Mohameda, Pharmacist at Khayelitsha District Hospital, encourages her fellow healthcare workers to get vaccinated to protect themselves and their loved ones. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/UA6stwrUIQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Businesswoman and member of the Ministerial Advisory committee for social behavioural change, Yamkela Makulpula, says vaccines will save lives, and together we can rebuild our economy. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/xqeU9j2ylj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sheila McCloen, Deputy Director for Comprehensive Health Programs at the Khayelitsha District Hospital, says the #COVID19 vaccine will help to keep her and her family safe. #IChooseVaccination https://t.co/HYcMTJEMMr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The number of healthcare workers vaccinated under the Sisonke Protocol is 6524 as of 6pm, 19 February 2021. https://t.co/P9fTpT1B6q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feeling happy after being one of the first healthcare workers in the country to take the jab is  Manyano Sojiji from Khayelitsha District Hospital inn Cape Town. https://t.co/eMgPbC2sif]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Healthcare worker Cwengisa Dadirai is an administration clerk in the trauma unit Khayelitsha District Hospital. She received the #COVID19 vaccine yesterday. https://t.co/nLAYOxw4Dl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Sa'ad Lalri, an Emergency Physician at Khayelitsha District Hospital, was one of the first healthcare workers to get vaccinated yesterday. He says the vaccine is our armour in the battle against #COVID19. https://t.co/yUFm5Olk2V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The number of health care workers vaccinated under the Sisonke Protocol is 2260 as of 6pm 18  February 2021. https://t.co/CEwwItosG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Cyril Ramaphosa was among the first group of people to be vaccinated with the #COVID19 vaccine in Khayelitsha yesterday. The President hailed the launch of the vaccine rollout  as a milestone for South Africans. https://t.co/vBxgoSxsjU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A momentous occassion at Khayelitsha Hospital on 17 February 2021 as healthcare workers, President Ramaphosa and Health Minister Dr Mkhize received the first doses of the #COVID19 vaccine.  #IChooseVacciNation #VaccineRolloutSA https://t.co/pokuD9wjRb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,496,439 with 2320 new cases identified since the last report. https://t.co/bBbGz58ZQL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: President Cyril Ramaphosa receiving the #Covid19 vaccine. #IChooseVacciNation #VaccineRolloutSA https://t.co/lYJjftWDMl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Health Minister Dr Zweli Mkhize receiving the #Covid19 vaccine. #IChooseVacciNation #VaccineRolloutSA https://t.co/ILb1O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Thank you to President for his support and making time to be here, thank you to the media. This must give hope and encou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Receiving the #COVID19 vaccine at Khayelitsha hospital earlier today. #IChooseVacciNation #VaccineRolloutSA https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Arrival at the Khayelitsha Hospital where South Africa's first #COVID19 vaccine will be administered. #IChooseVacciNatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: The President and Minister of Healths  #Covid19 vaccine dose is prepared by healthcare workers. #VaccineRolloutSA #ICho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: The podium has been set for an official media briefing once the first doses of vital #COVID19 vaccines have been adminis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: Media houses are lined up in anticipation of the South Africa's first #COVID19 vaccine being administered today at the K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: The first batch of Johnson  Johnson Covid-19 vaccines have arrived  at OR Tambo International Airport. #VaccineRolloutS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,494,119. https://t.co/vhGtZ0QQXp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sheila Kanyorosokie, a student at Melomed Bellville Hospital in Cape Town, says the #Covid19 vaccine will strengthen oir immunity against the virus. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/4Zn77ngKU6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay safe from #Covid19 during your pregnancy by taking special care to follow all non pharmaceutical interventions against the spread of the virus. #PregnancyAwarenessWeek https://t.co/DvcqT51oIm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is no reson to stop breastfeeding if youve tested positive for #Covid19. Make sure you follow precautionary measures when breastfeeding to avoid spreading the virus to your baby. https://t.co/jS92FJ4k4d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can still breastfeed if you have symptoms of or confirmed COVID-19, but take steps to avoid spreading the virus to your baby. #PregnancyAwarenessWeek https://t.co/EChYAh8ypu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 492 909 the total number of deaths is 48 094 and the tota]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,491,807. https://t.co/YXoEbXKCJs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pregnancy Awareness Week aims to strengthen pregnancy education and stress important issues that promote healthy pregnancy and safe motherhood. Watch Dr Manala Makua, chief director of womens, maternal and reproductive health on SABC News.  https://t.co/B9hXjJulvD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Africa commemorates STI/Condom week this between February 10 and 16 every year to raise public awareness around condom usage and STDs as well as to root out stigma and discrimination relating to these.  https://t.co/a1izB3WZDU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pregnancy Awareness Week takes place in February each year and is a way to strengthen pregnancy education and stress important issues that promote a healthy pregnancy and safe motherhood.  https://t.co/lnVAPnVCc0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[National Epilepsy Week seeks to raise awareness and educate the general public on epilepsy and the urgent need for improved treatment, better care, and greater investment in research.  https://t.co/ZsWYodKkq7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Absalom Nkosi, cardiologist at Melomed Gatesville Hospital, says hes ready for the #Covid19 vaccination. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/tGpMqP7frR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Director of HIV Prevention Programmes in the National Department of Health,  Dr Thato Chidarikire, spoke to Newzroom Afrika about the Condom and STI Week Campaign aimed at educating people about sexual health.  https://t.co/E2CxUqjYA1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,490,063. https://t.co/jMa0OJYOa1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our pharmacists have contributed to essential patient care and wellbeing of the public during the COVID19 pandemic. Anri Hornsveld from the PSSA tells us why she chooses to vaccination. #IChooseVacciNation https://t.co/vrdi24QF5L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Healthcare workers at Charlotte Maxeke tell us how they think vaccines will impact on the spread of #Covid19. #IChooseVaccination https://t.co/Rj52I9yNT8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,487,681. https://t.co/BN69Ih54EQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The choice to vaccinate against #Covid19 is an ethical one, says Health Deputy Minister Dr Joe Phaahla. @healthza https://t.co/p1Q80CkVJ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medical experts unpack the Presidents announcements on South Africas  #Covid19 vaccine strategy in an interview with Leanne Manas on SABCs Morning Live. #SONA2021  https://t.co/7uMcp7TaXJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In his SONA this evening, President Ramaphosa announced the procurement of 12 million additional doses through the Covax scheme and another 20 million doses from Pfizer. #SONA2021 https://t.co/Wj0EeQfUpP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Cyril Ramaphosa has confirmed that the first batch of the Johnson  Johnson vaccines against COVID-19 will land in South Africa next week. #SONA2021 https://t.co/3bdOv0jWGl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases in South Africa is 1,484,900 with 2488 new cases identified since the last report. https://t.co/VXyM0yOv53]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Tladiso Motsema at Melomed Tokai Hospital in Cape Town says vaccines are our hope to fight the #Covid19 pandemic. https://t.co/vUIia2HSJI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof Glenda Gray, the country'slead investigator for the JJ trial, and thechief executiveof the SAMRC, talks to Refilwe Moloto about the new direction our vaccine rollout plan will be taking.  https://t.co/Jxv8z6dJEk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The first phase of South Africas vaccination programme will target healthcare workers. Zamimali Jali, a specialized auxiliary worker at Charlotte Maxeke Hospital in Johannesburg, says that the vaccine will help curb the spread of the virus. https://t.co/IDEPbnOHDj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Regardless of whether you have medical aid or not, all healthcare workers who are going to be vaccinated need to register on the EVDS https://t.co/qNjcSEpXjW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As a healthcare worker, what information do you need to provide when registering for your #COVID19 vaccine? Find out more. https://t.co/XULeeh9mcU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As a healthcare worker, when you have secured your date and venue to be vaccinated, these are the items you will need to take with you https://t.co/gVEMnkQVwu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you a healthcare worker? Register for your #COVID19 vaccine using the link below. https://t.co/56lW2GwfIC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cumulative number of COVID-19 cases identified in South Africa is 1,482,412. https://t.co/hrSznbJ8oB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The rollout of vaccinations for Phase One will continue as planned, but we will be using vaccines developed by JohnsonJohnson rather than those from AstraZeneca https://t.co/XjhQxmviB0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The rollout of vaccination will proceed in the form of an implementation study through partnerships by the SAMRC and NDoH https://t.co/iuwOq1eNzF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will happen to the current doses of AstraZeneca vaccine already in SA will depend on the advice from leading scientists. https://t.co/sSlKeThh7n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Until we reach population immunity from #COVID19, we must continue adhering to non-pharmaceutical interventions like wearing masks, social distancing and practicing good hand hygiene https://t.co/kKLnN1pYhC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrZweliMkhize: As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 479 253, the total number of deaths is 46 869 and the tot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clad in her PPE armour, Portia Makamu, a cleaner at Charlotte Maxeke Hospital in Johannesburg, plays a vital part in protecting fellow staff and patients by meticulously disinfecting and cleaning all ward surfaces. Thank you for your commitment in keeping us safe, Portia. https://t.co/rapYXn6Uxr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HealthcareHeroes Nurses from Charlotte Maxeke Hospital in Johannesburg. They are among the thousands of healthcare workers who are on the frontline of the #COVID19 battle. We thank you all  salute you. https://t.co/03OPPSCXYm]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>