<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASN_Org: #ASN21: Our #CentralEurope section includes #Baltic countries and #Moldova and will feature 24 exciting panels.  https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASN_Org: #ASN21: #Balkans section -  this post if you are going to attend one of the 24 panels. And if you are planning a zoom marath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASN_Org: Wedn, May 5, 8am ET - see you on zoom!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidstroup: One thing that has been lost in the spate of virtual conferences during COVID are the opportunities for grad students and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isn't factless optimism great?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gsoh31: In the end, England will contain only five or six universities, and each department will contain about 4,000 to 5,000 students.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Staedtler: For what does it profit a man if he wins Hartlepool but loses Scotland?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BristolDolt It's certainly in that recipe book.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrDomPimenta: How it started:                          How it's going: https://t.co/EmbIl9OGm5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK government seems to have the goal to make its population less educated. https://t.co/FUSBh4KXtS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UCUCommons: The government's 'priorities' clearly include HE providers failing and exiting the 'market' which they themselves created.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Parents_Utd: Quest for Justice   As part of our Birthday Week of posts, we reflect on the impact of the full attendance policy on famil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UWankings: You also can't just talk about inclusion and promotion as internal issue, either, it has to be practiced across the sector.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @willpooley: luv to open a document for a piece of writing i havent touched since september and it is just a list of bullet points like:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroKatie: The US still has about 700 deaths per day from COVID and less than half of Americans have had even one dose of vaccine so p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kit_Yates_Maths: Why were the people, now lamenting our childrens lost youth through school closures, not calling for stronger mitigat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroKatie: There are lots of things that might be deemed safe under general circumstances that someone might choose not to do. If it c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sstroschein2: Next week 12 and up vaccines start in US. Fingers crossed for younger kids soon.  https://t.co/Ou8r8FrZO6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next week 12 and up vaccines start in US. Fingers crossed for younger kids soon.  https://t.co/Ou8r8FrZO6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: In order to avoid school closures and lockdowns, we need to ensure we limit transmission within schools and back into the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: It's a myth that children are not at risk. There were an estimated ~43,000 children living with long COVID at the end of M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: The DfE is looking at possibly doing away with face coverings in school on the 17th May- despite a review conducted over E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanJSinclair: Daily cases of covid in the UK are, relatively, very low. So doesn't it make sense to push for Zero Covid right now? Woul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ldobsonhughes: Todays tone deaf school email: children must not work from sofas or soft furnishings. They are not optimal learning en]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Muinchille: The @uniofleicester train crash continues. Global boycott  for a university established by British veterans of WWI to educa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pedantka @alicecbennett Approve!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carolyneholmes: Nothing like receiving an email that says I misunderstood the questions on the evaluation form and gave you some 1s w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterAr18228396: May reason prevail in @leicesterucu's industrial action against a management who must surely realise by now that they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TigressEllie: If the LFT system in schools/home for children were working as Gov would like we would be seeing a steady decline. Instea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karamballes: Telegraph "Everyone needs to manage their own personal risk"  Also Telegraph "Forget about the risks, get out there and st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["All best from New Zealand," says the nice email signoff.  Sigh.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tln1Jo4oGc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me, last week:  This online conference will be great! Don't have to worry about leaving the kid!  Reality:  Yeah well between all my obligations, I will just "be" at my obliged sessions only, won't get to attend panels to learn new areas, or have any research conversations.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jpaulgoode @davidstroup Fab!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jpaulgoode: Types of #nationalism paper. h/t @davidstroup for help with this one! https://t.co/ACaVMfV1KJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JanRynne @BrianKiely2 :(]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @estwebber: Tbf it would be difficult for Bill Gates to sustain his marriage now he's in the arms of so many women]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nasirfmusiqi Yes. Fingers crossed and hoping variants won't spread too much. Worrying that the Indian variant increasing now in London (C Pagel thread) - but will try to ration out the worries.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nasirfmusiqi Thank you! Good news is welcome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nasirfmusiqi I hope so. I am worried there might be a difference among vaccine types? Astrazeneca here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nasirfmusiqi I hope so. Is that for Astrazeneca too?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Simon_the_Pratt @bctallis @SevaUT ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @loisrp: Even if you are fully vaccinated, please consider this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanmills405: This is so true. While papers' headlines scream "we can all hug again" and more start to ignore the current mask and dist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dwalz23 @OliveFSmith Sending support.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OliveFSmith Ps thanks for listening in! It makes a difference to know others are thinking about this too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OliveFSmith I don't know. I am scared about long covid in kids. Scared that so few people have even heard about it. Upset that I am supposed to pretend a 70 percent risk.of transmission post-vaccine is 100 percent. Tired of gaslighting from govt, schools, employers.   I really don't know.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @redhistorian: "A prime minister cannot serve two masters". New blogpost, on why the funding of Johnson's flat matters to our democracy,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Parents_Utd: As part of our week of Birthday Celebrations, our 5 Point Plan lays out a Sensible, Safe and Sustainable approach to educa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are likely about to enter the most dangerous phase of the pandemic for anyone unvaccinated or immuno-compromised. Including children.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HullLecturer @edhollox @RuthHolliday1 Agreed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StigAbell: Few things are more British than al fresco dining in the rain next to a roundabout. https://t.co/VQ62DByHcH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GabrielScally: Always believe the patient until you know for certain whats going on. I remember learning the lesson a long time ago.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BDStanley: If there's one thing communism got right, it's the absence of street advertising. Granted, there wasn't a whole lot to adver]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson_MP: I'm pleased to announce that we have vaccinated 50million people, we will scrap social distancing in June and you can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @acupunctureUSS: I've just been referred to a gaslighty analysis that appears to deny the asymmetric growth of UK HE. So let me spell it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: This is really concerning, and consistent with data from W. Bengal, and Maharashtra also showing growth of B.1.617 against]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrischirp: YES, overall London numbers have dropped A LOT since Feb  there is no indication (yet) that they are rising.   BUT we've s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emayfarris ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bridget_Brown_: My 2 year old has covid.  We have been rule followers. I'm the mom who doesn't even let my kids play with neighbourhood]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethharding: Nice mail from student: Thank you for being a professor who is understanding of the fact that it's okay to not have eve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreshAirSchools: What is the ventilation likely to have been like inside a warehouse?  Feels relevant if these are to used to estimate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LizzieGadd: What I love about this picture is the esteem in which Jacinda Aherns colleagues clearly hold her. I mean look at their fac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrancesorFran: https://t.co/ZLfPyCSoVt. Excellent article @byameliahill articulating the challenges faced by families with long Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LongCovidKids: This is our concern. #LongCovidKids #LongCovid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LongCovidKids: Many parents have experienced poor care for their children, including diagnoses of anxiety in the child and even, in so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LongCovidKids: Weve allowed the common understanding to spread that children dont get Covid /or if they get it, they dont get it b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fascinatorfun: BBC Weekend News -Liverpool rave  Can anyone save a clip from this news 20 mins in to end In particular 22.35 where the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrBenLitherland: The last decade has been an absolute disaster for British universities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: As I say in the interview, I cannot believe this was approved by an ethics committee. It looks like trials conducted withi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: The trial requires people to have a -ve LFD prior to entering. These tests are inaccurate  MHRA recently suggested that g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSSTAFFCOVID19: Good luck to @BorisJohnson scrapping social distancing. Theres a good percentage of the population not vaccinated so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trishgreenhalgh: Remember our #CovidRiskChart in @bmj_latest? People said we should have added quantitative estimates of risk. So we go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReicherStephen: The pandemic has shown us how well a public health system works (the roll out of vaccines) and how private systems fail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DMinghella: Excellent podcast on this. H/T @AdamSButler65 for highlighting. https://t.co/JoYanJGS7L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Schubone:   PLEASE READ IF YOU CARE ABOUT PERFORMING ARTS EDUCATION     The Office for Students @officestudents has proposed a 49%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ASN21 emails flying fast and furious. See everyone in a few days! @ASN_Org https://t.co/3MqXFlizZ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One good thing about Britain's broken politics: the eloquent and insightful diagnoses of what caused it.  https://t.co/1wgVnGlDWO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dr2NisreenAlwan: Again language is purposefully used to shape expectations. To me return to normality means all the pandemic learning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RuthHolliday1: Is HE only about making money now? Only running the most profitable courses? Only recruiting the (international) student]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @seefryar: I was not ready to teach an entire system that I belonged in it and deserved respect.  Yeah. That. I wasnt either. And yet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@burnsy20790591 @ArisKatzourakis I really hope so, thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikegallacher1: A perspective: I work an average of 60+ hours a week, drive 2500km and move 200-300 pallets of food around the country.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mE4F4wVX1G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Things I wish were reported in the news. Stats from @LongCovidKids https://t.co/yfvMWJWbEV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julietast2 @ArisKatzourakis That would be great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BDStanley: Time for polisci, then (with apologies to @xkcd, https://t.co/TdF6kMhTkk) https://t.co/KQI5BQdzVc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricGordy: It had to be done. Types of Balkan Studies paper. (courtesy of  to @xkcdComic, #TypesOfScientificPapers, https://t.co/31Fwyx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EricGordy @xkcdComic ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Who trawled our dossiers of evidence to create statements as co-claimants. We are the doctors who understand what really]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: I dont often get angry, but I feel really rattled tonight. EveryDoctor has devoted a significant portion of our limited]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArisKatzourakis Fingers crossed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important.   https://t.co/WNS4DTFNWa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lizmorrish A good reminder that it was good to leave the US.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenCoverdale ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scottjshapiro: NYC is dying, its a ghost town https://t.co/xik4aTCDfn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's not over until primary school kids are covered too. https://t.co/Z8pIFnHQk3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trishgreenhalgh: This is misleading. This virus spreads through the air, potentially long distances, when people cough, sing, speak  e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DGBassani: It happened!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karamballes: I don't get how much of the UK media still platform anti-maskers when they apply the discredited masks are harmful argumen]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>