<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[PHE data show up to 50% reduction in transmission of COVID from first vaccine. 3 implications:  1) Getting a vaccine helps protect others  2) This is likely to be improved by getting your second dose  3) If people you meet are vaccinated it reduces your risk- but not completely. https://t.co/5ost4UcjhS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am really delighted that Professor Chappell FMedSci will be taking over as Chief Scientific Adviser at DHSC and lead for the National Institute for Health Research (NIHR) from August. https://t.co/nsvRaFWuY9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Positive news from the Valneva COVID-19 vaccine phase 1/2 trial. Many thanks to the volunteers, researchers and for NIHR support. If confirmed in larger trials this adds a new class of vaccines to help UK and international    efforts to control the pandemic. https://t.co/z3bOFMPO5r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sir Paul was the leading health protection expert of his generation, and a great public health leader. His extraordinary knowledge and calm in a crisis protected many across the UK who have never heard of him. He was also a wonderful man. https://t.co/E2XGJEdHL9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over one million people in the UK have participated in research on COVID-19, with support from NIHR and the NHS. This is a remarkable testament to the public-spirited approach of UK citizens to defeating this disease. Thank you to every person involved. https://t.co/TGwaq7nX5X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news confirming efficacy of the Novavax COVID vaccine against original and B.1.1.7 variants. The UK trial recruited from 35 research sites across the UK, with the first patients recruited in Blackpool. Many thanks to the volunteers and NHS staff who made it possible. https://t.co/UxkKtc7sH5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This change is a result of the remarkable efforts of the public to bring case numbers down. Deaths and infections are still very high and the NHS remains under significant pressure. If we continue to follow the guidance, cases will continue to fall. https://t.co/8rtHgtjj0h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Treatment of COVID-19 in hospital is steadily improving. This important trial result from RECOVERY for tocilizumab is another step forward. Many thanks to those who conducted the trial across the NHS and NIHR network, and those who volunteered to take part. https://t.co/uauhGR4cL6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is a lot of discussion of vaccines at the moment. For those who would like to understand how vaccination developed, and how vaccines for childhood diseases and emergencies including COVID-19 are used, I gave an online Gresham talk on this, link below. https://t.co/7FJ7fnKdFW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A highly effective vaccine to add to the medical countermeasures against COVID-19 trialed in the UK. If it gets MHRA approval this increases our future resilience, including against the B.1.1.7 variant. Many thanks to all trial volunteers and those who conducted the research. https://t.co/JIqtu9UglA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The situation in the NHS is very serious and the number of people in ICU is rising rapidly.   We are improving our knowledge on how best to treat people in ICU thanks to research, but hundreds of people a day are currently dying.  We must all take the lockdown very seriously. https://t.co/ByWz4ejwz5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID cases are rising rapidly across the UK in large part due to the new variant.   The NHS is treating many more COVID patients and vaccinating vulnerable citizens. NHS staff deserve our profound thanks. But we must act now or the NHS will come under even greater pressure. https://t.co/rF0Zwy0hQf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The first AZ/Oxford vaccines were given today. This is very welcome; congratulations to all involved. Vaccines give us a route out in the medium term.  The NHS is however under very considerable and rising pressure in the short term. We must all follow social distancing for now. https://t.co/tvzMBPnkfx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is good news, it significantly increases supply and flexibility of vaccines to combat COVID in the UK and internationally. Many thanks to the scientists, research funders (including NIHR), research clinical staff and above all the many volunteers who took part in the trials. https://t.co/QzF3aRzKIZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My annual report brings together data to highlight major health issues we must tackle including cancers, cardiovascular disease, mental health and infections. It identifies where in England they are heavily concentrated and trends in health over time.  https://t.co/ixTpu54FOB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is a great day for medical science, and the future.  Congratulations and thank you to the NHS workers, trial volunteers and scientists who have made this a reality.   The pandemic is not over and relaxing too early would be dangerous. But this is a significant moment. https://t.co/zlDekDTyhe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CMOs for England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland have written to doctors about winter, the COVID vaccine and the need for ongoing research. And above all to thank them.  Here is our letter https://t.co/u4IoHNQo3h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The independent regulator authorised the first vaccine for use against COVID-19. This is excellent news and a step towards normality.  It will take until spring until the vulnerable population who wish to are fully vaccinated. We can't lower our guard yet  https://t.co/nqe5CGI1v2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a very encouraging step forward.   I would like to say a huge thank you to those who volunteered and the researchers around the country.   The regulators will now do their independent analysis for safety and efficacy but this is another important advance. https://t.co/Iz1ZEzJ7x7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A letter from the CMOs, GMC, Medical Royal Colleges  NHS to UK doctors.  There has been a remarkable, ongoing response from the profession to COVID. The second wave will be challenging - your continuing work to reduce COVID and non-COVID harm is massively appreciated. Thank you. https://t.co/yNLqnbjrND]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Preliminary news that the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine is effective demonstrates the power of science against COVID. We must see the final safety and efficacy data, but it is very encouraging.   It is essential we continue to suppress COVID, but it is a reason for optimism for 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Official @ONS data on COVID infections from 17th-23rd Oct has been published.   Over 50,000 new infections a day, and it is rising in almost every region of England. Deaths and pressure on the NHS are increasing.   We all have a role in reducing the risk of passing the virus on. https://t.co/P9g5xLwQE7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For those who are interested in public health beyond COVID-19, last week I gave a Gresham lecture on the role of the State in public health. It examines where the public expects State action, where it does not and the contested areas.  https://t.co/uBBmv4Ax4F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTedros @JulianWTO_UN @WHO COVID is a global challenge that needs a global response. This includes international science and support for all nations. Thanks to @WHO for global leadership in tackling COVID and its indirect impact on other major health problems.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: You cannot, in an epidemic, just take your own risk. Unfortunately, youre taking a risk on behalf of everybody else.  Ear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonathan Van Tam lays the situation out clearly. We have through the extraordinary efforts of the whole population got COVID rates right down. They are now rising again especially in those aged 17 to 29. If we stop social distancing COVID comes back. We all need to protect others https://t.co/9uYMSLkbnp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important supporting evidence that steroids significantly reduce mortality in patients with severe COVID. This is true of hydrocortisone as well as dexamethasone. Safe, cheap, well known drugs and available everywhere.   Thank you to those who took part in these trials. https://t.co/1lthgTQulk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8WY1kJfgKX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As with many of the choices we face on COVID this is about balancing risk. We encourage all parents and school staff to read it.   @CMOWales @DrGregorSmith]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK CMOs and DCMOs have summarised the current evidence on schools and COVID-19.  https://t.co/VlErkF8iLr  The risk of a child coming to significant long term harm from COVID solely due to school is very low. The risk of harm to many children if they don't go to school is high]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is fantastic that already 100,000 people have volunteered to register for trials of COVID vaccines. The faster we can test them the quicker we may be able to find safe, effective vaccines. Taking part in studies is a major contribution to reducing the threat of COVID. https://t.co/WF1F5Rdh2W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A very warm welcome to the new FY doctors starting to work for the NHS today.   It remains a remarkable profession to be part of, whichever path through medicine you take. I would also like to thank those who joined early to help with COVID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flu can have serious consequences and vulnerable people can die of it. Having a vaccine will protect you and others.   This winter more than ever, with COVID-19 circulating, we need to reduce all avoidable risks. If you're eligible please get the vaccine when it's available. https://t.co/bISGpKRiaY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is encouraging news. A long way to go, but a testament to the remarkable scientific effort in the UK and around the world to combat COVID-19. https://t.co/1lrWRI9wtZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting vaccines for COVID tested is essential. People across the UK can register their interest to be approached to join vaccine studies. Please consider volunteering. The generosity of the public in taking part is essential to identify effective vaccines. https://t.co/e8NM9Rweup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We should all be grateful to the citizens of Leicester, who have been following public health advice. This keeps families safe and also protects the wider community from COVID. This from Ivan Browne, the city's director of public health sets out what is needed. https://t.co/KAby6OOivF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 has gone down due to the efforts of everyone but is still in general circulation.  If we do not follow social distancing guidance then cases will rise again. Naturally people will want to enjoy the sun but we need to do so in a way that is safe for all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is the pre-print of the paper showing survival benefits of dexamethasone in people with severe COVID-19. An important read for those treating the disease. Thanks again to all patients, NHS staff and researchers involved in this important trial. https://t.co/nxN2kCd6eD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today the UK CMOs changed the COVID alert level from Level 4 to Level 3.  This reflects steady and continuing reduction in infection due to the efforts of the public. The pandemic is not over and we must all keep to social distancing rules to continue this improvement. https://t.co/0PMLd2VYQK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the most important trial result for COVID-19 so far. Significiant reduction in mortality in those requiring oxygen or ventilation from a widely available, safe and well known drug. Many thanks to those who took part and made it happen. It will save lives around the world. https://t.co/zRIaHulHOe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 100,000 participants around the country have already taken part in @NIHRresearch on COVID-19.   They will improve outcomes for others in the future by helping us better understand the disease, develop treatments and test vaccines. Many thanks to all who volunteer. https://t.co/mDLg5Eb5kH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This report by @PHE_uk is a vital step to understanding the disparities in risk and outcomes of #COVID19. The disparities in mortality by ethnicity due to multiple factors are very important and need to be addressed systematically. https://t.co/M8wuvQlAvI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From today people should self-isolate if they develop a new continuous cough or fever or anosmia.  We have been monitoring emerging symptom data on COVID-19 and adding anosmia slightly increases sensitivity, and may lead to earlier isolation. https://t.co/LnhGrVEyEm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a major milestone. Information from this trial will help us work out how best to treat #COVID19   Thank you to all the patients who volunteered to participate in the RECOVERY trial; it will help many people in the future. https://t.co/1nSMUZlbtX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clinical trials and studies are essential to find effective treatments for COVID-19. As hospital admissions fall due to the actions of the whole population in social distancing it is even more important a high proportion of those eligible and willing to volunteer are enrolled. https://t.co/QZHyILI1Xw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week I gave a @GreshamCollege lecture for members of the public who want to have a broad overview of COVID-19. It also provides more detailed answers to some of the good technical questions I have been asked over recent weeks.   https://t.co/UrnLQBuvIE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today with fellow UK CMOs, the @NHSEnglandNMD and @PHE_uk Medical Director, we wrote to the medical profession to express our admiration and gratitude for their response to COVID-19 as we move to a new phase. https://t.co/DIdLUDB7Bv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is really important - if you need urgent medical care, the NHS is ready to help you. COVID-19 does not change this.   People who might be having a heart attack, stroke or life-threatening emergency usually do much better the faster they get medical care. https://t.co/j35nbzYfY5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This thread is as good a summary as you will get about the remarkable work in local authorities and the wider community by outstanding public health professionals and many others. I completely agree.   This local response and leadership will remain essential in the next phase. https://t.co/0QodbEEUsR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This call will enable our academic partners to provide additional evidence on the effect of ethnicity on the impact of Covid-19, including health and care professionals and other key workers. This is an important but complex question where research can help provide solutions. https://t.co/7ldFPKXUEF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So far, more than 5,000 people have been recruited to the RECOVERY trial, researching COVID-19 treatments.   Thank you to all those who have volunteered, it will make a major difference to the treatment of future patients. https://t.co/S146Fiw5v8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS staff look after others: they must also look after themselves. Mental as well as physical health is important during this potentially stressful time. This helpline, staffed by trained volunteers is there for everyone who works for the NHS. https://t.co/qfr6JAxQfa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The faster people are recruited to clinical trials and other studies, the sooner we will get the evidence so patients can get the best possible treatment   Those who volunteer for studies will help others in the future  UK CMOs  @NHSEnglandNMD have written to clinical colleagues https://t.co/HhA3KH5y5E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New guidance on PPE has been published. This was a collaborative effort across a range of professional groups, including the Medical Royal Colleges and experts in the field. The guidance is in line with WHO and expert advice. The UK CMOs fully support it. https://t.co/D4Tugp6N82]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you want to understand the science behind COVID-19 and the reasons for actions like social distancing then leading UK scientists have developed a reliable online resource to help   https://t.co/tfvIfBIHBk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After experiencing symptoms compatible with COVID-19 last night, in line with the guidance, I will be self-isolating at home for the next seven days.   I will be continuing to advise the Government on the medical response to Coronavirus, supported by my deputies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At this stage of the epidemic we need everyone to stay at home except in specific circumstances.   The NHS depends on us making it difficult for the virus to spread. We all need to make changes. This will be very disruptive but it is essential to keep the community safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is very important that people who are at very high risk protect themselves by staying at home at all times.  Guidance has been published listing these conditions and the actions to take.   https://t.co/yQAbIRgsTu https://t.co/EoCTNDJSGY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New guidance has been published on what you need to do to protect yourself, protect others, and protect the NHS.   Please take a few minutes to read this important advice on #COVID2019   https://t.co/m3AtRoVWeZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday, the government laid out new measures needed to protect you, others and the NHS.   This clip lays out some of the details and more information is online https://t.co/m3AtRoVWeZ https://t.co/hABeuPbxS0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As COVID-19 puts pressure on services doctors will have to work differently for their patients. The UK CMOs, medical director NHS, Royal Colleges and GMC are clear that in emergencies doctors must be supported to work in new and unfamiliar ways. This letter is for all doctors. https://t.co/jDVvZR0iLs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This announcement by WHO reflects the changing global situation. There is ongoing transmission in multiple countries, including the UK.   The UK has been planning for a pandemic. There will be challenges ahead and we need everyone to play a role. https://t.co/IeNbWSZzrB https://t.co/xnFSKmL935]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today the government published the action plan for COVID-19. It outlines what we are doing now, and what we intend to do, to contain, delay, research and mitigate. We need to ensure our actions (including tradeoffs) and our timing are grounded on science. https://t.co/Ugz9PBQZwG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PHE_uk:  Today @CMO_England has updated advice for travellers returning to the UK from specific areas affected by #COVID19. Find out m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you for the discussions with the great infection team @NewcastleHosps who treated the first two COVID-19 patients in the UK.  I learnt a lot from their experience about the practical clinical issues. Excellent NHS care. https://t.co/8P1pjBhCLd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK CMOs met in Edinburgh today about continuing our coordinated COVID19 response  among other public health issues. https://t.co/rqBTiexk7n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you for hosting me. Really interesting to learn from your insights on rural and coastal health, as well as see the great work happening in Berwick. https://t.co/5w6iB89nI9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I could not agree more. We should all be very grateful for the extraordinary work of our front-line teams. https://t.co/zj5zDur4Vd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is the end of supported isolation for the 83 people at Arrowe Park. I want to thank them, and others who have self-isolated at home, for their patience and resilience. It is a major contribution to containing the COVID-19 virus. https://t.co/0JRjX5LTMu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eight people have tested positive for coronavirus in the UK of 1,114 tested to date. We are grateful to all those who are following public health advice by self isolating, ringing 111, and coming forward for testing to protect themselves, their contacts and the wider community. https://t.co/ScybyyTULh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Update on #coronavirus:  A further patient in England has tested positive for coronavirus bringing the total number of cases]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A key part of responding to the novel coronavirus outbreak is to develop drugs, vaccines, diagnostics and a thorough understanding of the virus.   @NIHRresearch and @The_MRC are launching this call for research to ensure new scientific avenues are explored. https://t.co/3Dtn6avT1R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: We've launched a new public information campaign on #coronavirus.  Help us spread the message:  Download assets: https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Today we've pledged 20 million to develop new vaccines for #coronavirus and future infectious diseases.  Health Secretary @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today @NHSEnglandNMD, @PHE_uk and I have updated our advice to medical staff regarding the novel coronavirus.  https://t.co/CD7yNSlRaB https://t.co/72BpTeLysp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Update on #Coronavirus:  @CMO_England statement on two confirmed cases in England.   https://t.co/lAQUTk8qm4 https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: #Coronavirus update:  The @WHO have declared that this is a public health emergency of international concern.  Read the join]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We should all be very grateful the dedication, technical expertise and skill of our @NHSEngland,@PHE_uk and wider health colleagues. They are ensuring anyone who might have novel coronavirus can be tested and if necessary they will be treated safely and quickly. https://t.co/x6GjchY9Cl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: UPDATE on #coronavirus testing in the UK:  As of 2PM on Sunday 26 January 2020, a total of 52 tests have concluded:  52 were]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following discussions with the UK Chief Medical Officers and at COBR, I have issued the following update on the novel coronavirus: https://t.co/acabJcr4Xj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An update in Parliament from Secretary of State  @MattHancock on the #CoronavirusOutbreak summarising the current situation, initial response and UK preparedness. https://t.co/fUfUo27AwF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today with @NHSEnglandNMD and @PHE_uk we have issued additional advice on the novel coronavirus for medical staff within the NHS and other medical professionals. https://t.co/YtR1Arpku0 https://t.co/JMK0SOK1Ck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: We're working with @PHE_uk and @NHSEngland to monitor the Coronavirus situation:  https://t.co/5fBvOA4lvl   PHE will be on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Paper co-authored by President/Chair/Medical Director of @AoMRC, @RCPLondon, @RCSnews, @rcgp, @ukmedschools, @gmcuk,@NHS_HealthEdEng, @NHSEngland and all UK CMOs @CathCalderwood1, @CMOWales, Dr McBride.  This is something the medical profession can decide to do itself and should.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Multi-morbidity is increasing: it is an issue the medical profession needs to address.  Increasing specialisation only makes sense if we also maintain and celebrate generalist skills throughout our careers. This BMJ article with leaders of the UK medical profession explains why. https://t.co/AfV4SPmZ76]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Future advances in medicine rely on the public's willingness to help others; taking part in medical research studies is a fantastic contribution to health.   We are very grateful to everyone who has volunteered. https://t.co/cpR1fJwsoc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The flu season has started relatively early this year.   It is important that those most vulnerable to bad outcomes from flu, including pregnant women, those with several health conditions and those aged 65 or over, do not put off having their#flujabs. https://t.co/Ni7a1EVEYc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to you and the WHO team @DrTedros for the warm welcome to the UK delegation to discuss major health issues. We look forward to continuing working together closely. https://t.co/I1wNjRD94z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A really broad and useful discussion. Directors of Public Health and local government are central to improving the health of the nation.  I look forward to working closely with you and colleagues across the country. https://t.co/FophNJ59IK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see 2 reports of reductions in antibiotic use in both humans and animals. Resistant infections in humans rose 9% in a year however. Safely reducing antibiotic prescriptions remains a priority. Reports by @PHE_uk  @vmdgovuk https://t.co/VuzAjxNJCl https://t.co/BzUHr4KNmN https://t.co/SvWNHOTlDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Public health research should help people have the most enjoyable and fulfilling lives they can have, which are also the healthiest lives they can have.  One of the points I made when @FoundSciTech interviewed me for their podcast https://t.co/ml2TmzNXIY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To pass the one million mark for participants in NIHR supported #research studies is a significant milestone. This will improve health outcomes for people in the future. This is due to the generosity of patients and the public, without whom vital health research couldn't happen. https://t.co/QyEXZUI1rv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deputy CMOs Prof Jonathan Van-Tam, Prof Jenny Harries and I have had our #flujabs    It is important that all healthcare workers get their flu vaccine. It will help protect them, their colleagues and patients #ValueofVaccines https://t.co/dRLcGJa8fH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Professor Dame Sally Davies has published her final report on childhood obesity today. Obesity is a central issue for anyone interested in improving the health of children. As she says we need bold action on many fronts. https://t.co/0HCNdX8bZ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flu can be deadly. That is why the UK is offering the vaccine to around 30 million people this winter.  I urge everyone eligible - over 65's, pregnant women, all primary school children and people in at risk groups - to get the jab. It helps protect you and those around you. https://t.co/pWgCZkTWk9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is my first morning as Chief Medical Officer after taking over from the outstanding Professor Dame Sally Davies.  She was a superb CMO.  I look forward to meeting the opportunities and challenges ahead with colleagues across public health, NHS and the wider health community https://t.co/ctw5yELapL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jersey Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,233.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 69. https://t.co/tdxjcOHXzG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  No new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 1,587.  No new deaths reported, giving a total of 29. https://t.co/l8TIYRnlgO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England Daily Coronavirus (COVID-19) Report  Wednesday 28th April.  1,829 new cases (people positive) reported, giving a total of 3,854,733.  27 new deaths reported, giving a total of 112,134. https://t.co/tGW4xmQvNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 47,540,984 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in the United Kingdom.  +495,593 doses in the latest 24hr period.  33,959,908 people have received their first dose, with 13,581,076 of those having a second dose (fully vaccinated). https://t.co/K8jj9tErRM]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>