<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@j_g_allen @UW Thank you, Joe! I'm grateful to be a part of the #HealthyBuildings team!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[University of Washington and Harvard - an article featuring my academic and professional work for both: https://t.co/J6zEHpM1os   #healthybuildings #solarpanels]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FavoriteHorror OH MY GOD lol!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobinCogan @jljcolorado @JasonKamras @IAQinGWN @WBahnfleth HEPA air filtration works great, both in theory and in practice, as shown by many studies. Germicidal UV, if properly installed, also works great.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LaurenWeberHP:  Is your child in a classroom with unproven air cleaner technology?   Our investigation found over 2,000 schools acro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Instead, they are going with upgraded filters in HVAC systems, portable HEPA air cleaners in classrooms, and open windows when possible.  https://t.co/jqXT2puozt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richmond Public Schools superintendent @JasonKamras (HS classmate) asked me whether to buy ionization systems for schools. Decided against it based on ASHRAE recommendations and my advice. Here's why: https://t.co/lpMjkSmMmy @IAQinGWN @WBahnfleth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KalpnaSolanki1 https://t.co/QV38ZDdNTl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SO glad to see @WHO update on transmission!  short-range: aerosols containing the virus are inhaled or droplets contact eyes, nose, mouth  long-range: poorly ventilated and/or crowded indoor settings, because aerosols remain suspended in the air and travel &gt;1 m https://t.co/J3uDAsvSXN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LazarusLong13 @j_g_allen Thanks! The driver spread it to the others, right? Air flow was probably from the vents in front towards the back. Spending two hours downwind of an infected person is a lot of exposure, even if it were outdoors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andy_grieshop @katierandall @EThomasEwing @jljcolorado Now that the deadline has been extended, we will submit an abstract.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@safetyjanelle @akm5376 One study found that four layers of silk was pretty good. https://t.co/63KzqC13TS https://t.co/QDcYpHPMM5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@j_g_allen Paper says the heat was on, so I assume the windows were closed. But I thought heat was all outdoor air, not recirculated. Maybe it's recirculated?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@akm5376 Depends on the specific microfiber, but on average it's better than other fabrics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plain cloth masks help, but they do not make you superwoman or superman. Here, people wearing cloth masks got infected sitting in a van (small, confined space, heat on, windows closed) for 2 hours. This is why it's so important to use a layered approach with your precautions. https://t.co/QxqwewmnZK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marinavance: Main recommendations here, but do watch the short YouTube video for more details! https://t.co/eY6Lvizess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marinavance: Recommendations for band class/practice/rehearsal to minimize the risk of COVID transmission.  (cc @ShellyMBoulder) https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfCharlesHaas @CathNoakes Oof, and it was a 2-hour trip. That's a long time to be sitting in a small space with an infected person.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@citlanx @dylanhmorris @petervikesland @MicroLevitator]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosol peeps: What do you think of the laser sheet scattering technique? How would it compare to direct number counts or scattering-to-mass instruments like DustTrak? /2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Portable air cleaners in hospital room https://t.co/9qiVjEXzrX "...hospital room...with an excellent ventilation rate (~ 14 ACH) can clear the aerosols in 20 min. However, with the addition of two air cleaners, the clearance time became 3x faster (in 6 min and 30 sec)" /1 https://t.co/kt80gS9194]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC has historically recommended 3', even for SARS-CoV-1. Based mainly on studies showing bacteria grew on petri dishes up to a certain distance away from a person talking and limitations in visualizing small particles. /6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Problems: this fosters misunderstanding about infectious particles not remaining airborne and codifies a particle size based on tuberculosis that does not apply to other diseases /5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["It is this conflation of particle transport through the air and particle deposition in the lungs that appears to be the source of the error in distinguishing between droplet and aerosol transmission routes as defined by a 5 m threshold." /4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["yet the 5 m distinction is clearly not based on what stays airborne but on what reaches deepest in the lungs...." /3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["tracing the origins of the 5 m threshold...ultimately revealed a conflation between various understandings and definitions of 'aerosols.' Most contemporary sources use this threshold only to explain which particles stay suspended in the air for longer times,..." /2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1) Where did the 5-m cutoff for aerosols in disease transmission come from? (It should really be ~100 m)  2) Where did the 6' rule come from?  @katierandall @EThomasEwing @jljcolorado Bourouiba  I traced the history in this preprint https://t.co/rTgO4qZT5x /1 https://t.co/NJsZUUOKYf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep Yes, this nails it. Thank you for distilling something useful out of the morass.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BradSiroky @zeynep @bellwak @washingtonpost This is a much better take on the paper!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This story cites data from Ireland showing that 0.1% of cases resulted from outdoor transmission. It won't happen randomly, rather when you're close to others for a long time, mostly likely talking with them. https://t.co/EG3rp8Iabs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccinated and ready to hit the gym? Heres how to assess the risks. https://t.co/oEoXeTMUNa Look for distancing, ventilation, regular cleaning. With Drs. Gebo @MonicaGandhi9 @CorsIAQ and me. No paywall ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep The reporting has run off into la-la land. I talked with @bellwak @washingtonpost, who might run a clean-up article, but the real story isn't nearly as exciting/alarming.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And here's @dylanmorris's excellent thread on the preprint: https://t.co/CxjvKKBSKX https://t.co/B0NUkJKsiA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2 in large droplets survives best at low RH. Similar pattern to other enveloped viruses. Mechanistic advance based on solute concentrations and temperature. Now published https://t.co/ewuJ3v1RAG With @dylanhmorris @QishenHuang @petervikesland Munster Lloyd-Smith et al. https://t.co/bO6XflFQQB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Commissioncovid: New publication on #school #infrastructure; better ventilation  air cycling reduces risk of #COVID19 transmission tod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An important point by @HuffmanLabDU that I forgot to mention in my quick summary of our Lancet Commission report on schools. There are so many co-benefits of having better air quality in schools: better academic performance, reduced absenteeism, reduced asthma. https://t.co/88tobKd2NY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: I like the helpful summary chart that the #CDC updated today . Organizes relative safety of various activities into indo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a good way of boiling down the new guidance on masks: "fully vaccinated Americans don't need to wear masks outdoors anymore unless they are in a big crowd of strangers". I could quibble about a crowd of friends and family that's not vaccinated, but this is pretty good. https://t.co/Q9cKg2lwea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrispyke Yes, great point. See my retweet of @WBahnfleth 's addition.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good point from @WBahnfleth about regular HVAC maintenance (monthly/quarterly/semiannually/annually) following ASHRAE 62.1-2019 Table 8-1 (https://t.co/f8cCDfJiWJ), part of which is shown below. https://t.co/HB3MMTnMLF https://t.co/4KXTuQdSwI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WaterWarriorOne @ErinBromage @CorsIAQ @MIT @cdc @BrianSmallbrook @NBCNews @CNN @ABC @JeromeAdamsMD @FoxNews @DrEricDing @EpiEllie @EpiCOVIDCorps CNBC got the headline wrong.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Key points from new Lancet Commission report on schools: 1 Check HVAC system every 3-5 yr; monitor CO2 to ensure performance 2 Ventilate w/ clean outdoor air beyond minimum std 3 Use best filters possible for your system 4 Add portable HEPA air cleaners if needed 5 Consider UV https://t.co/K36D6Ud2wA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Latest from our Lancet Task Force.  Pandemic relief for schools must be applied to enhancements that are evidence-based, pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am beaming that Dr. @marinavance  received an NSF CAREER award! She earned her PhD in my group, and her work on engineered nanoparticles informed our thinking about viruses. @VirginiaTechCEE https://t.co/Z3mTMN1QnN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNBC @zeynep The way the model is set up, there is the same amount of virus everywhere in the room, at all distances. It is an assumption the researchers made. /3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNBC @zeynep Suggestion: "Coronavirus can accumulate in the air to hazardous levels if ventilation is insufficient" /2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNBC Please fix this headline, as the model they used ASSUMES that the room is instantaneously and continuously well-mixed, like if you blow a smoke ring, it immediately spreads evenly throughout the room in zero seconds. The headline is a tautology. @zeynep /1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep @jljcolorado This is a silly headline, as the model ASSUMES instantaneously and continuously well-mixed conditions, like if you blow a smoke ring, the moment it exits your mouth it immediate spreads evenly throughout the room. Under such conditions, of course distance doesn't matter!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NotALegume This counts as a large droplet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drkristenkc Great work! Having been at this a while, I'm actually surprised we have come this far on airborne transmission in a relatively short amount of time, given the entrenched dogma and outright resistance to it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaredBlm @j_g_allen Found one at https://t.co/vGdWBwUrZu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaredBlm @j_g_allen Glad to hear you thought of this, too! I first mentioned this last year. It's in my tweets somewhere.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It has been fun collaborating with scholars in history, science technology  society, and rhetoric to look at mask use in during the 1918 flu pandemic. We looked at old photos to evaluate mask use. https://t.co/qvT9x6jDIg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_allysonchiu: Do you need to wear a mask outside? @PaulSaxMD (@BrighamWomens), @linseymarr (@virginia_tech)  @PollittKrystal (@YaleSPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LongDesertTrain As long as the HEPA filtration system was running and properly removing aerosols from the recirculated air, this level of CO2 is OK.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: The risks of no masks outdoors is low. But...how low?  Turns out we can 'trick' our covid-19 risk calculator to make it rese]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is amazing to me that our COVID-19 precautions plus pre-existing immunity to flu have completely crushed flu this past year. Must celebrate with my flu collaborator, @Lakdawala_Lab!  https://t.co/QrhBNqERtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WaldenOakville I am so happy to hear this!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I also should have said that  cognitive bias could prevent someone from seeing the evidence for what it is. This is something I constantly fight in my own head. https://t.co/sA5yeSNhEt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As more people get vaccinated, my rule is changing, but this is how I've operated for the past year. https://t.co/uebJ3RGBzV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HuffmanLabDU @adamsmiller @albertareporter I stand by my quotes, but I am not one of the "top aerosol scientists in the world." I'll own up to being one of the top scientists at Virginia Tech who studies viruses in the air, while recognizing that it's my students and post-docs who do the real work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: ICYMI: Resource page on COVID transmission  prevention (focus on airborne aerosol spread) is up to: 580+ media article]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep "This manuscript provides evidence that inhalation of aerosols at short range may be more important than deposition of large droplets. The results have important implications for infection control practices." /3 @AbraarKaran]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep "The existing assumption that large droplet transmission dominates at short-range while aerosol inhalation transmission is important only at long-range does not incorporate a modern understanding of aerosol science." /2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep I reviewed this paper in Jan 2020. Here's what I wrote: "This work is hugely important in challenging the existing dogma about how infectious disease is transmitted in droplets and aerosols...." /1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hforout Thanks! That project has been on hold for the past year, but this paper is a great nudge to pick it up again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CathNoakes: If you are thinking of buying a UV wand device to disinfect surfaces - don't. Most don't work and some are dangerous. Nice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great thread by @jljcolorado explaining @TheLancet article about airborne transmission. His stringent critical thinking has helped refine our analyses and interpretations over the past year. https://t.co/SrzXrtEWVr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great visualization of how aerosols move through an airplane. Air changes out every 2-3 minutes and passes through a HEPA filter that removes aerosols. Very important to minimize mask-off time. https://t.co/CtODEYWCOk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CappaSnappa They should see https://t.co/GwlZKPZqEG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dominicdentist2 @CathNoakes @SmallRedOne https://t.co/LnhaEhYIIi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Discoforever_ All the close conversation isn't great, but it's a lot better than if the same group of people were indoors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ashishkjha is sooo good at boiling down the evidence to a clear message for the public. https://t.co/gE1HI2Gr95]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@j_g_allen @Poppendieck You're too kind. You have modeled clear communication and action for all of us. I'm standing on the shoulders of giants (e.g., Li @Don_Milton Morawska Tang), and it is only by a massive community effort that we have come so far, across all fields, in the past year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: This is the week the dam broke.  #CovidIsAirborne  @linseymarr @jljcolorado @DFisman @kprather88 @AndrewMIbrahim, Julian Tan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep @j_g_allen @trishgreenhalgh @jljcolorado @DFisman @Rschooley YES! Welcome to my world for the past 13 years. So incredibly at odds with current scientific understanding! I have been going around saying that the medical textbooks are wrong, and people think I'm weird...which I am.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Don_Milton So. Many. Rejections. due to poor fit with the journal. I want to thank @RSocPublishing Journal of the Royal Society Interface for having been a welcoming home for our work. They publish "research at the interface of the physical and life sciences."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Don_Milton Your work and Bill Lindsley's helped keep me going! It's felt so strange to go from being fringe, crazy, ridiculed to mainstream!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kprather88 Right back at you. Without your voice and leadership, we would not have come nearly as far.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, the "airborne route is likely to be dominant." https://t.co/Iw91MCfTsE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Beaches and parks are some of the safest places you can gather, said Linsey Marr, an expert on airborne virus transmission at Virginia Tech." https://t.co/cDgpwG5d3a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attempts to reduce the spread should also be focused on reducing super spreading events. Follow Japan's 3Cs: avoid crowds, avoid close contact, avoid closed, poorly ventilated spaces. And wear a mask. https://t.co/LYkWOhjKQr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bmj_latest: "It is now clear that SARS-CoV-2 transmits mostly between people at close range through inhalation. "  Why does it matter a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: More on this @bmj_latest, packed into 1 page https://t.co/gmiY7PcxXn @linseymarr and colleagues https://t.co/oWETrICHnD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Kudos to @EmilyAnthes capturing the nuance around new airplane study by friend and collaborator Byron Jones (We prev publish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShellyMBoulder: Measurements and Simulations of Aerosol Released while Singing and Playing Wind Instruments.The preprint of our paper i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@j_g_allen Public and private schools around here are also closed on Wednesdays for "deep cleaning." When pressed, they told me they needed the teacher prep time to handle remote students.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great work by Mark Hernandez to help make restaurant dining safer, beautifully illustrated in the article. I love that the restaurant posts its air quality metrics. This was a high-priced demo, but there are good lessons to be learned. https://t.co/vC0IccdY60]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @amymaxmen: NEW @CDCMMWR study on planes: -57% reduction in being exposed to SARS-CoV-2 w/middle seats vacant, when multiple passenger]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidElfstrom I wasn't sure if that was a joke when you first posted it, but looking through your tweets, I'm afraid it isn't.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @benshingler: "People tend to latch on to the first thing they hear, which was to wipe down your groceries, a year ago," said @linseymar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[222 people infected at a gym in Quebec City + 356 related cases. With input from one of my heroes, Tellier (whose papers on aerosol transmission inspired me long ago), and me. https://t.co/QUqw0AdzM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShellyMBoulder has been on top of best practices for bands and choirs from the beginning. Use masks with slits, bell covers, limit rehearsals to 30 minutes; skip the plexiglass https://t.co/0EpBbQZRDY https://t.co/E6FrkFPveL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yup. I know we don't have direct evidence, but indirect evidence suggests that many respiratory viruses spread mostly through the air. Makes sense, right? There may be some exceptions. The default assumption of large droplets also lacks direct evidence. https://t.co/amFW4xQYu3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bXLpedestrian Depends on what's in the water you use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Poppendieck: It turns out I have a day job.    Our modeling work of aerosol risk reduction approaches in schools. 1) Require masks. 2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll be talking at this @theNASEM workshop tomorrow on humidifiers as a source of particulate matter, humidity and bacteria and virus survival, and pH in droplets. https://t.co/US4ciqNnTY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here, experts weigh in on air ionization systems. Stick with proven air cleaning/disinfection methods: ventilation, filtration, properly installed UV. Thanks to @marwa_zaatari for leadership on this. https://t.co/Dtk4yNu6vu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember Gaiter Gate? @MicroLevitator nicely explains a new study showing that large droplets can break up when hitting a 1-layer mask, but velocity needs to be high. Under these conditions (coughing and sneezing), you shouldn't be out in public. A 3-layer mask blocks them. https://t.co/HqoSLIwsTh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fartleksburpees @kprather88 Not yet. One of many million dollar questions!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>