<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Mask up idiots #MaskUp #MaskedSingerUK https://t.co/mkr6UgLn82]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @luquion: https://t.co/vOqHTs9gDJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Scamdemic10: @robkall @Chris_RoyMtl Masks are super effective  https://t.co/OUWrfwujQk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieEmma85: This video of Whitty saying what the nation needs to hear right now should never be forgotten - even though it keeps get]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robkall @Chris_RoyMtl Masks are super effective  https://t.co/OUWrfwujQk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Liz6716 Imagine a whole country listening to the advice of this inept mouth breather]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All life is now is rotating tracksuits......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facts https://t.co/GdUBUoW2ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KirstinChap @newski79 @laughlaugh97 @GeorgePapa19 You know Q anon is total bullshit..... if the inauguration didnt wake you up, nothing will]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pedromakee: @Femi_Sorry MUST WATCH! For anyone who still doesnt realise how this corrupt Govt has exploited COVID to line the pockets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@latimeralder You are on fire lately]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @latimeralder: What did you do in the Great Covid War, Daddy?  I stayed home and Protected the NHS, my sweet  You're so brave - my hero!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@latimeralder Cognitive Dissidence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peston @BorisJohnson Dont look at the phone cable...... look at the bullshit lies and deceptions Boris and his team keep banging out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaMaraPhoto3: Today I ask you for your positive vibes, thoughts  prayers for a young man who is awaiting a postponed life saving opera]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeIAmBen1 The garden centres are open as they are essential retail for health and well being purposes.   However gyms are closed?????? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gr33nbot: https://t.co/yFV8vJcELi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MetroUK Grow up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR @Daily_Express Im sorry Adam you seem like a nice guy. But read between the lines. Theres no way pubs will be open in the spring.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Cotton Masks are ridiculous inside. Like putting up a barb wire fence to keep out the wind!  You say this now, but if they do mandate it, you will get in line just the same as the rest of the sheep!  This will not end until people wake up and fight back!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iWaltonUK @hslvee2003 @bryanh1979 @pennyone Yea it was all bull ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @BorisJohnson Turn it in Piers you Nause!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndyBird21: A virus so fucking deadly and so fucking contagious that theyre offering you 500.   Wake up you gullible twats.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Are people who question lockdown dangerous and wrong?  @mrmarkdolan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdamWill_ @chezzy8080 100%. Its weird as fuck!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chezzy8080 I had a manager at greggs scream in my face today cos I was not wearing a mask. People have lost all sense of reality]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkREvansJedi He will just double down and say this is all part of the plan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You know when Simon parkes was speaking about people feeling lost and lied too when the TRUTH comes out....  that must be how you Q anon fanatics must be feeling right now.   Biden is your president   Sorry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRisAlive Wake up people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wtoletsgo @Polish__Patriot @DougBillings Do you honestly think he talks shit? Even though he has sex with aliens 4 times a year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Roydini25: George Orwell's "1984" contains the lines: "Everything other than working was forbidden: walking in the streets, having fun,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pie_sees You have had a touch bro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatpetewoods No no no its definitely real, military generals drop memes on telegram all the time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatpetewoods Someone is playing a blinder ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hyten is not sending memes from Telegram. Wake up... that makes no sense!   Unfortunately nothing is going to happen today. Sorry Americans but Biden is your president.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is this knob in a hat the go to on American politics?  #GMB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CmWilters I bet youre fun at parties will]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kbeanie93: Going to be reporting Dr Hilary to Ofcom after his comments regarding vaccine safety on GMB. I urge you to do the same!  htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 Good work. Thanks for sharing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@C0lieCakes @GayleFox13 @receiptprovider @Johnheretohelp Please wake up ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COME ON MAN.... if you buying this Q anon crap and think that American General Hyten is sharing memes on Telegram ready for Trump to stay president! Wake up!  Especially if you following Simon I have sex with aliens Parkes!   Plz wake up https://t.co/o8fNBtCq0M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MMMHappiness1 @talkRADIO What is it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllenKearney7 @receiptprovider @Johnheretohelp ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@talkRADIO Full hazmat suit would be more appropriate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COME ON MAN.... if you buying this Q anon crap and think that American General Hyten is sharing memes on Telegram ready for Trump to stay president! Wake up!  Especially if you following Simon I have sex with aliens Parkes!   Plz wake up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DogDuffy Cos its not...... why would he be on telegram sharing memes?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Megan86974730 This military general dropping memes...... oh ffs ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocBCSays I just checked it out. I would guess thats a BS account. Would a military general be dropping memes ffs ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Carl31508201 Parkes went on tv and says he fucks aliens. Why would anyone choose him as an outlet for the truth?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TN_MamaBear_Q So theres a military general dropping memes on telegram.... sorry to be a killjoy... but thats not him]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Carl31508201 Whats the go button?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jw56012025 @RabbitLover_17 Oh ffs ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocBCSays Quick question... why would a military general update the public via social media in any situation?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlContrite @Hollypops3109 Absolutely nothing is happening..... q anon people will double down with the timing isnt right.  Well if Trump has the evidence they say, I would say BEFORE the inauguration is a good time to speak up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are doomed as a species! https://t.co/bSkasDpySY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan You twat piers ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown *youre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@djzetek @robertmccahill2 @ianbrown Ask Robert.... these bits of cloth magically eradicated influenza #miracle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 https://t.co/SuKqxeuiMj heres where to complain, he was on at around 8:30 spreading his nonsense.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 Good work. He needs to be chopped down a peg. He is spreading potentially dangerous information]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown I am agreeing with you Robert. Its a modern day miracle.... the flu disappeared right when covid came along.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown I mean its a miracle Robert! The flu is all but gone..... thousands of years in the making and then its gone in a puff of smoke. #miracle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown Heres another one for you babes https://t.co/Obu9EjUwwG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown Heres another one babes https://t.co/ExzJmkTIlX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown I think you should re read it and then try interpreting the information.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown Hmmmmmm all seems legit https://t.co/fokhqEn1y0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Femi_Sorry You dont understand market speculation then femi.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 Absolutely nothing. A new president]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertmccahill2 @djzetek @ianbrown So social distancing/masks works for the flu but not covid! Ok bro https://t.co/CO0u5kz7fU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Berumster Unfortunately. This will be the case. Then the conspiracy people will double down and say its part of a bigger plan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: MESSAGE TO THE AUTHORITIES: To the Powers that shouldnt be: Stick your digital health passport and your vaccine that isnt a v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@covid_500 *kung flu.... spell check]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The king flu is suspiciously following flu season. Expect numbers to die down in the next 5/6 weeks. At that point the gov will hail their own efforts as a great success.   Congratulations sheeple..... you have been truly scammed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR This whole thing is a disgrace. Nothing surprises me now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanniiWatty @GMB Report Dr Shillary below. Disgusting behaviour. It takes 2 minutes   https://t.co/SuKqxeuiMj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dehars @GMB Exactly that. What is so hard to understand ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Simbo2020 @GMB It was the major part of the debate and it was deliberately left out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heachy_1979 @GMB Report Hilary to ofcom. Absolute scum bag   https://t.co/SuKqxeuiMj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@o2brain @GMB You do realise the vaccine doesnt stop someone carrying the virus?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paul75224582 @GMB @piersmorgan Why is that Paul you absolute here?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GMB I urge everyone reading this to make an official ofcom complaint against Dr Hilary. His advice was both misinforming and misleading and contrary to NHS advice.  https://t.co/SuKqxeuiMj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Will Easter be ok for a little bit more freedom? Oh please Fhrer Whitty?   Tell me what I can and can't do, oh unelected d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RSJosh Yes it can. No one mentioned this absolute key piece of information that completely changes the debate. Tossers!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nicolegaultxx @GMB @piersmorgan He is a disgrace.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GMB Dr Hillary should be sacked. No sane dr would make the recommendations he just did. He is a disgrace!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Heres some good news for you Adam. The world eliminated influenza last march. Check it out.... what a miracle..... https://t.co/tuYuFHKAAE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tnybtmghty @catturd2 I listen with an open mind. But if you believe that then you are smoking crack]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Ahhhhahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are a nation of pathetic compliant sheep..... we would never have the balls for a movement like this https://t.co/R939QVbuOz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @city_affairs: ITALY: Restaurant owner: "We are  all opening up" Crowd cheers. #IoApro #IOpen #WeOpen https://t.co/TktJZ37Afw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeanCollins66 No chance.... we are super compliant. If boris can cancel Xmas at 5 days notice. Nobody has the balls to play that game]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR 3 weeks to Flatten the curve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LucieJessicca Ive seen a lot of this too ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMindsculpter You cant say too much..... they give you that look like you have lost it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@47united @LiveLancs What like a basic understanding of sarcasm? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Berumster You are now complicit in a murder..... how can you live with yourself???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews You dont say]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bruce_bwkm: Then what's the fucking point of the vaccine?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh ffs  https://t.co/kqMPKwUnEj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh we have truly landed as a species   https://t.co/OjkzTmPhfH]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>