<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_YvonneBurton: This woman captures so eloquently how so many of us feel  https://t.co/qHXZKLDu7t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Id love to see you stand in a room with the millions of parents who witnessed their baby regress.  I TRIPLE DOG DARE YOU.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Yeah, get your vaccine that doesnt stop infection or transmission!!   Dude you arent a doctor.  So JUST STOP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VoteJenaPowell We shouldnt need legislation to give us the right to freely breathe oxygen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ayasgirls3101 @GovMikeDeWine If they did they wouldnt mandated a year into this bullshit scam.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HCareworker @GovMikeDeWine What test determines a variant.  Not PCR.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Contagious doesnt equal deadly.  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine No one cares about your fake emergency.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lunar_Witch91 @GiGi11932617 @GregWes74873311 @GovMikeDeWine Covid is spread by aerosols by symptomatic people.  Aerosols go right through masks and stay in the air for hours if not days.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lunar_Witch91 @GregWes74873311 @GovMikeDeWine No science supporting masks.  None.  Zero.  Zilch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lunar_Witch91 @GovMikeDeWine Vaccine doesnt stop infection or transmission. Sorry to tell you that now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Significant carriers?  PROVE IT.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine You will never ever get your filthy hands on my children.   You are disgusting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SissyDavis6 @robbiemarieoh @thebadegg3 Flu shots have been mandated for 10+ years to healthcare workers.  Nobody cares until it affects them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebadegg3 Nope.  Not my kids.  We stopped vaccinating them years ago and I certainly am not going to change my mind about that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulReindlSD In your dreams!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@larkel14 @RobertR48823058 @PaulReindlSD If you dont have symptoms you arent contagious.  Jesus.  No symptoms = no disease.  Breathing doesnt kill others.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulReindlSD Who said?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OhioSense: All of @MikeDeWine's false claims refused by @ohio_data in a minute forty seconds with one graph and a lot of questions. Hom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CindyB13723 @GovMikeDeWine Like masks?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@denise_dewald @GovMikeDeWine   real doctors understand thee immune system and how to support it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@candlek58 @GovMikeDeWine Go see your grandkids.  Try to remember when asymptomatic used to mean HEALTHY.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CF3_87 @GovMikeDeWine Im one of them. And my coworkers who are taking the vaccine are dropping like flies.  Meanwhile their doctors try to convince them that all the reactions are normal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine No it isnt. Over 80% of deaths came from people aged 80 and over with 2 1/2 comorbidities.  Its about as predictable as it gets.  God help us with this stupidity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@demeatloaf @GovMikeDeWine You can have mine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Better extend it to mental health services for teenage lives lost that your lockdowns caused.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Yawn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ewarren Minimum wage jobs are meant to be careers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ewarren Is my hourly going to double as well?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElementNo_5 @GovMikeDeWine Reduced cycles on PCR test.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slimysloth4 @buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine I have been doing these things the entire past year without a mask or vaccine. Been exposed to Covid nearly 10 times between my own child and patients and yet STILL HAVE NOT GOTTEN SICK.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slimysloth4 @buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine Evidence of this please.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine Denial of what?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buck_lao @wendyjohnson420 @GovMikeDeWine . Nope.  Manufacturing the spike 1 protein. Better educate yourself]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aubrey_huff Real pandemics dont need to be advertised.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MapperJim @MandieHiznay @GovMikeDeWine Has the vaccine been testing for carcinogenic potential?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Misskb721 CDC circa April 2020. Has been since removed. https://t.co/FYUZ7jY53M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FullMeasureNews How is this even a question?  Of course it isnt fair!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoKeys910 Guess the libs didnt enjoy sub $2/gallon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine Ps.  Your vaccine does not stop infection with SARS-CoV2 nor does it prevent transmission so theres that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine It actually does.  Have you studied human physiology?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine And why bother with the vaccine when you still have to mask, isolate and social distance?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buck_lao @GovMikeDeWine Keep up your virtue signaling ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wendyjohnson420 @GovMikeDeWine Congratulations. You have turned your body into a Covid manufacturing plant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndreaRyanMuncy @mckalal1 @GovMikeDeWine Look up pathogenic priming and you will learn more about WHY there has never been a successful vaccine for SARS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MandieHiznay @GovMikeDeWine This vaccine is cancer in a vial.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SammyJochimsen @GovMikeDeWine Jesus.  Do not get any vaccines while pregnant!  They were not tested on pregnant women.  None of them are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Why wasnt the vaccine tested on anyone over the age of 65 but its that age group that needs it the most?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Why was priority given to young healthy health care providers and teachers over the most vulnerable???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine If they are so safe, Why did you and Fran FAKE getting your vaccines??? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@energywrk2 @jackwindsor Sell out to China.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Zetetic3 @tallGOPgamerguy @jackwindsor Communist university.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jackwindsor Oh there is so much more you could say.  She destroyed Ohio and turned us into communists with her masks symbolized a new cultural and behavioral change.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jackwindsor @JaneyMurph In her dreams.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@m_teubl @GovMikeDeWine Yep.  I coworker was hospitalized right after her first shot and very sick for a week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pnk0729 @GovMikeDeWine .  Ohio is one of the most repressed states in the nation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlueGangsta64 @GovMikeDeWine Why?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Helenad66359383 @GovMikeDeWine Why not?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HiddenAgenda420 @GovMikeDeWine Our schools have been open full time since August]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeanEversole @GovMikeDeWine Just hold your breath.  Show you care.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProjectileTeeth @GovMikeDeWine Sure they are the ones who are at risk right?  And since the vaccine doesnt stop transmission it makes sense to protect those who are most vulnerable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@osusteelersJen @GovMikeDeWine The vaccine doesnt prevent infection or transmission so....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lbopper77 @GovMikeDeWine Prove that kids spread Covid.  Prove it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Lies.  Lies lies lies lies lies lies lies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobCanon5 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mashable How about we just breathe oxygen?  You know, the good old fashioned immune boosting way?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FitnessMamma Wow.  Cant retweet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kmeghan @GovMikeDeWine Our district has had in person school all year so I guess it can be done safely]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlassBalloon @GovMikeDeWine You can have all 5 of ours.  Well 10 I guess since there are 2 doses of poison.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine You can stick your vaccine straight up your ass.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RyanRallyOh: A pandemic so deadly you need laws to force to comply. Constant media advertisment to remind you it's there. Posters in ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Move this ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobCanon5 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine ASYMPTOMATIC SPREAD DOES NOT EXIST.   healthy people do not make others sick!!!! For Christs sake stop already!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine You are an embarrassment to Ohio.  what goes around comes around and dont forget that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saintant @TedPetrou No America doesnt. You fool. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saintant @TedPetrou Because they have massive pollution. If you want communism move to China.  I will help you pack.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saintant @TedPetrou Masks are a device to spread fear and oppression and demonstrate compliance. That is all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Karageorgos15 @TedPetrou People who work and children are being forced to wear them 7 to 9 hours a day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0313dw @GovMikeDeWine Youd be much better off getting on a treadmill rather than injecting a poisonous vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine New year, old propaganda!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelBrian330: I miss the Pre-COVID pandemic days, when no one ever died  germs were nonexistent.  #FAUVID #SCAMDEMIC2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zvrk31 @martyschladen @crampell @GovMikeDeWine Regardless of the reason for refusing vaccination those not getting it are equally dangerous no?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Frederi64496113 @zvrk31 @martyschladen @crampell @GovMikeDeWine I would like to know the difference between a vaccination and an inoculation since the two terms have been used interchangeably since vaccines have been around.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ghtway Sounds unbelievable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Frederi64496113 @zvrk31 @martyschladen @crampell @GovMikeDeWine Please explain the difference]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@martyschladen @GovMikeDeWine Thank god.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ghtway Tell me more!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@frankly410 @GovMikeDeWine @OHdeptofhealth You can have mine princess!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine @OHdeptofhealth Fuck you.  Fuck you.  Fuck you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Prove it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine Eff you.  You have singlehandedly destroyed the mental health of 11.7 million Ohioans you bought out NWO BASTARD.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lainyj12 The symbolism of masking, especially of children, demonstrates that you are willing to silence them.  To take away their faces.  Makes me physically ill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Freedom1796YA Barely.  But not dead from Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@and_kell Covid vaccine is autoimmunity in a vial.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jennybethm Would love to save the link for this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lori20052008 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebadegg3 @buckeyemompart4 Right?  This is the most egregious attack on healthy people I have ever witnessed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine @OHdeptofhealth Nope.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovMikeDeWine More lies.  This is the first vaccine of its kind.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>