<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SunRisenShine7: @Freedom4Canada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JESSESINCLAIR: @ProvoGal01 Have you tried the @JCCFCanada ? Also @Freedom4Canada is in the process of a class action lawsuit in Alberta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey Hinshaw @CMOH_Alberta, how many people received the regular influenza A/B shot this year? Do you have those stats? https://t.co/6nIw8n7fWa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: You are in the midst of WW3.  No mushroom clouds? Decades in the planning organised attack is much clever than that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How do we go from 38,000 Canadian cases of flu in 2019/2020 to absolutely zero? Answer: Because they have all been repurposed as covid. https://t.co/6TV2lGYeaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#collateralresponses #covidsheds #covidlies https://t.co/16DVPcwuQw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you think we're "small fish", you've got it all wrong. We are a silent majority. Your title to this "story" is OVERDRAMATIZED and inaccurate. https://t.co/W09oWKuAQh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeniseInCanada: @MarkFriesen08 Everyone needs to retweet this video.  Don't just click the LIKE button.  One of the ways that our voice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How? Mental health illness due to the ramifications because of #covidsciencefraud https://t.co/lK60Wyb9vk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CoryBMorgan: Every business deemed "non-essential" was very essential to the people who owned it and worked there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: If Dr Fauci and Pres Biden want to see my medical records per vaccine passport, I want to see theirs. What vaccine did th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thevivafrei: The government has now learned that it can punish the citizens for its own incompetence and corruption, and - if it succes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brett, after weeks of trying to get you to see this thing is a hoax, this thing is a hoax. Is it not evident by now that the PM has no idea and doesn't want involvement, because he's focused on #TheGreatReset #giveyourheadashake https://t.co/gkec3nIpbG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: I prefer dangerous freedom over peaceful slavery.  Thomas Jefferson, letter to James Madison, January 30, 1787]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: Seems to me, this should be the first graph in articles about the covid vaccines. https://t.co/iNuT73Pw39]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is discouraging. Trust your gut, this guy's #DougFordResign a nut'bar. https://t.co/lGKCnViaUx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierrePoilievre: Did the Prime Ministers top advisor Rick Theis know that WE was paying the Trudeau family when he helped them get a g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are you driving the Conservative Party into the ground? Is this why Harper ran interference to stop Charest. Because you were the chosen one to do it for Klaus; to let Trudeau win: Make it look like you're opposing Liberals? #fakeleader #Erinslies #klausboy #inbedwithchina https://t.co/Xhl0KmaW75]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Because I understand what clinical trials conclude in 2023 means.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @staceykate1973: After begging him not to, my friends dad got the shot today. She texted him while I was there to see how he was doing-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess what CBC Edmonton, there's more comin'! This thing is about to rear it's ugly head, along with the truth about how we've had herd immunity for months and the coFlu is coGone. #CBClies #FreedomOfSpeech #freedomvictory #wewin #thepeoplewillwin #freedom https://t.co/W09oWKuAQh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is an interesting post at a times when Canada (Alberta too) is seeing many similarities from that time period. https://t.co/S4svTluRs4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @baracudabarbie: All the mystery deaths, od's, heart attacks, tremors, brain disease! They won't be able to hide them for long! People w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really? And you're worried more about this more than what's happening to small business owners in Alberta? #calgaryheralddistractions #notevenrealmedia #fakenews https://t.co/jHZhdTqaSI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would you consider that this is happening to Canadians? WAKE UP CANADA. There will be no tomorrow if you wait today. Fed up? Let's go! Join the movement. #FreedomOfSpeech #freedomofreligion #freedomofthought #freedomofexpression #freedom #jointhemovement #freedom4canada #love]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundofmusak: Prove me wrong. https://t.co/EqsjD4gTXU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nuff said! #jointhearmy #freedom4canada #FreedomOfSpeech #freedomOfExpression #freedom #FreedomFighters #yyc #yul #yyz #yqb #yeg #yvr #yhz #yyt https://t.co/2A5tVXw1s0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, there is Rally tomorrow (Sunday) at 13:00 (1pm), Calgary Courthouse Downtown. Every Sunday. Please come out! We provide and assist with co-ordinating rallies. We do not organize them. They come together with other members of the whole. Look forward to seeing you tomorrow. https://t.co/pCII0AEjjh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Did @BillGates and Melinda Gates get vaccinated? Can they prove it to me?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mverbora: How to optimize your immunize system based on clinical evidence.   - hug people close to you - expose yourself to nature - me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It should be shelved, for at least 10 years. Ridership way down due to pLandemic. https://t.co/JDhdFFs39U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlobalCalgary please wipe the buIIsh!t from your cameras' lens'. This is not true and you know it. No evidence. None. #freedom #FreedomOverFear #FreedomOfSpeech #FreedomToProtest #globalTVlies https://t.co/bVc6qnbjoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOT A THING! @jkenney is gaslighting Albertans. You lie like the old rug in your shed Kenney. The whole reason for these lockdowns is to get deeper into the agenda, moving towards "vaccine passports". @GlobalCalgary lies for Trudeau. https://t.co/nNv6GKgGDc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrissaccoccia1: Visit your family! https://t.co/BoqU0j5Dqd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RapleyAllison: Not Using Ivermectin, One Year In, Is Unethical And Immoral https://t.co/9fJcBycdFG @HomeniukJ @jkenney @shandro @RebelN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RapleyAllison: #BeBraveWHO @WHO @jkenney @CMOH_Alberta @shandro @HomeniukJ @RebelNewsOnline]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @N33Ama: Something to ponder https://t.co/M3bCSYelMW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeonardRoxon: Why indeed are our Veterans   other Canadians, homeless  without shelter, but tent cities can be set up so fast for tho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealKeean: Everyone who said "yeeeah, no thanks," to Trudeaus third-world vaccine rollout must feel really vindicated right now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkFriesen08: Two types of establishment premiers in Canada. Those that embrace communist/fascist globalism and those that are afraid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SheilaGunnReid: As Pastor Coates was offering a prayer inside, the RCMP and AHS were outside trying to enter and disrupt the service.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Because it's a distraction and a psyop. https://t.co/6lncdVRnrX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @derekjamesfrom: Emergency group challenges Kenney, Hinshaw to debate over COVID restrictions - https://t.co/yWEQH9MEni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonMartinCTV: My latest blog: After that devastating auditor general's report, why does Tam still have a job? https://t.co/5HAKsL1bb9 v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fight for the Canadian Charter of Rights and Constitution Brett. Fight for Freedom. These people did. https://t.co/B47UhhqViQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: Breathless, insanity animated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimMurp77852985: This might put our tax system into prospective. https://t.co/RqIafqwW77]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[True story. Ding! Ding! Ding! @thevivafrei wins statement of the week. #truth #everybodyknows #JUSTSAYNO https://t.co/tAD7r2e28c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealKeean: If Alberta separated and closed the rail lines and roads on our borders, we would have Trudeau groveling at our feet. We']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkFriesen08: So now its basically just the blind sheep that are keeping this bs going in Canada and Its provinces while keeping the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: The world continues to be in denial of what, and whom, we are dealing with. And, he is not alone. He is joined by his o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, this is political pandering. Both @erinotoole and @michellerempel pretend to be opposition. The reality is they are working to leverage the lockdowns, "vaccines" and "vaccine passports". Both are fired. #everybodyknows #JUSTSAYNO #freedom #FreedomOfSpeech https://t.co/I2mKFZbaqp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: As long as you think China is the enemy, then the actual enemy of Western people will win. The actual enemy, opposed to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Most important warning Ive ever sounded in my life, with the least time left to take action:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeonardRoxon: Fact! https://t.co/UOgq9pNAGV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nusakan007: Franois Legault:  Avez-vous fini de propager votre haine ma gang de complotistes dents!? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Vaccine Passports are unconstitutional. Period.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierrePoilievre: Some ministers give no answers.   This chap gives 3 answers to the same question and says: pick one! https://t.co/un]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: Can we find any Canadian leader able to defend freedom-or are they all in the pocket of others? Gov. DeSantis to Take Exe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: They divide with fear. We unite with courage. They divide with politics. We unite with facts. They divide for control. We uni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AnthonySabatini: BAN VACCINE-PASSPORTS NOW!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PaulMitchell_AB: "Alberta nears end of 'extraordinary' flu season with zero cases recorded"  Yes, they think you're that stupid.  #Defu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: Belgian health minister pretends to take the vaccine. But there is no needle. Why not? https://t.co/YzwxvQaEzJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: Is this a joke or a scam... https://t.co/HFOEHoTHyi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: Nothing misleading about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#childabuse https://t.co/nHDKfkeeRG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perfectly worded. #criticalthinking #everybodyknows #covid19 #JUSTSAYNO #freedom #bodilyautomony https://t.co/usUpIRHjNZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHO do you work for? Bill Gates, Kenney or the taxpayer? Answer: You were NEVER elected by the people of Alberta. RESIGN. https://t.co/XTX8yaTiSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Full stop on this junk jab. #covishield is #covijunk https://t.co/I6aGKGC4Np]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CMOH_Alberta crickets! #everybodyknows #JUSTSAYNO #hinshawisfired https://t.co/uc2VEJA0mi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Safety is last. You do not care about public opinion. If you did, this would have stopped for plebiscite months ago. You're done. #JUSTSAYNO #everybodyknows #covid19 #freedom #bodilyautomony #covidlies #premiersarefired #hinshawisfired https://t.co/25LcWWLzuR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JUSTSAYNO #everybodyknows https://t.co/I6aGKGC4Np]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JUSTSAYNO https://t.co/0e1xY9Tgqh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is just you peddling more lies. The evidence is the PEOPLE who ended up with blood clots. That's the overall increase in risk. #youarefired #gaslightingalbertans #everybodyknows #covidlies #JUSTSAYNO https://t.co/xxS51EguiX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rare Deena? #gaslighting This is happening all around the world with AstraZeneca's junk jab. Give your head a shake. https://t.co/3dxl2OuAR7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBatman1961: In the bush in Queensland, just realised I had to wear a mask, property size 1,000,000 acres]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Question: What's worse, not saying anything and wishing you had or fighting for what is rightfully yours? There's merit to staying the course. Keep your foot on the gas. #freedom #FreedomOfSpeech #wisdom #libert #civilrights #everybodyknows #justsayno https://t.co/j9LSgtniQW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In case it is unclear, these stats are compiled courtesy of the JCCF. #everybodyknows #jccf #justsayno #covid19 #covidgames #covid #FreedomOfSpeech #freedom https://t.co/7USqviTthH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let's make sure this one gets circulated over and over until it's broken. Vice joined fake news awhile ago. This proves it. #covidgames #covid19 #politicalliars #canadianpremiersarefired #everybodyknows #justsayno https://t.co/Zr9QH3F4RI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This post speaks for itself. #everybodyknows #covid19 #covidgames #politicalliars #justsayno https://t.co/GsaaqDqnqb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nurses and doctors are DONE! They're coming out in droves now. Canada is waking up. Premiers, MLAs, MPs: How much longer can you uphold a lie? Answer: You're done. #everybodyknows #justsayno #covidgames #politicalliars #allpremiersfired https://t.co/CAbV3NN71M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This belongs to every Canadian. a inclus le Qubec aussi. Alberta, Qubec, Ontario, Saskatchewan aren't going to put up with a 3rd lockdown. Let's be clear. Full stop. We're coming!#canadianconstitution #canadiancharter #freedom #covidgames #politicalliars #COVID19 https://t.co/iaAF90swoA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This type of discriminatory segregation is UNWELCOME in Canada.10 provinces, 3 territories, Full stop. Premiers MLAs and MPs colluding and capitulating, you're done! #covid19 #vaccinepassport #vaccinepassportbullshit #bodilyautomony #kenneyisfired #legaultisfired #fordisfired https://t.co/nmq1WoeYpD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SunRisenShine7: @JAReveley @MrDamienBlack 2 | cc @lootlogic @DeniseInCanada @Freedom4Canada https://t.co/gTn3vhnT9T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SunRisenShine7: C'mon @calgaryherald Please elaborate why there are concerns by the public, that you are not willing to publish correct]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A now and then. L'anne passe et au prsent. #quoideneuf #whatsgoingon #FreedomToProtest #freedomworthfighting https://t.co/5u6ZgoDDP3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do you think? #nowmorethanever #goteam #yyc #freedom #freedomworthfighting https://t.co/XmQ7os2lJ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is truly something else. Why would a pharmaceutical company want anything to do with these assets? Answer: Control. #notnownotever #keepgoingkeeppushing #pfizerlies https://t.co/Xyj6iUNWhu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This isn't a vaccine Deena. You seem to not know that yourself. Question: What does Pharma call it? https://t.co/JWL6zfWiL5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: https://t.co/M3mpWIT745]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadian Tire called, "We found your handcuffs in their store Kenney." https://t.co/LKeEmQ2Fyl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same thing Cuomo did in New York State. Uh oh! Kenney, you gonna spenny some time in the slamma when this is did. #unjustifiableacts #unprovenscience #RemoveKenney #RemoveDougFord https://t.co/LKeEmQ2Fyl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Roman_Baber: "Saying we are all in this together is laughable." "Only the private sector pays in lost dreams, high stress, financial de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cowboy_cuban: Canada is out of control.  The military needs to remove the corrupt ruler.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: https://t.co/fqrnXU63YN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: https://t.co/dvzImc4epA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Seriously what a psychopathic a-le, and I dont like to swear. We elected a team to manage the pandemic and the answer is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is fruitless. #LondonReal #brianrose #nextLondonMayor https://t.co/kC3sSTAi1O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: https://t.co/22lH0wgexO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LET'S DO THIS THING! #NurembergCode2021 #inhumane #unconstitutional #classactionlawsuit #GTFO https://t.co/mc8qKcbZqW]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>