<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JesseKellyDC: Remember when Elizabeth Warren lied about being and Indian her whole life and then ran for president and took a DNA test]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bucketoftea @dnforca The thread isnt talking about shedding *the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealImSorryMum @dnforca Its possible if vacccines were not kept at the right temperatures etc. they would have lost their efficacy. -mRNA ineffective. What a great ploy to minimize the adverse reaction count at first, then 2nd jab! Bam.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dnforca: @BrianBu47119667 Itll come down to a) is it possible and b) what type of transfer. If were talking just a hand shake then ye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jess56779593: @dnforca Well its in the Pfizer document themselves that you can be environmentally exposed to a vaccinated person - so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dan613 @lindajc0606 @dnforca Anecdotes are the canary in the coal mine. Ignore at your peril]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dnforca: @DeniceMarin Short term in not concerned about. As long as theres nothing permanent as we all know, the long term data isnt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeniceMarin: @dnforca Yes I personally got sick and felt icky 2x around 2 vaxxed people that come to my house multiple times per week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chewie65354432: @BurcherClaire @dnforca A lot of people here are jacking up against the vax, vax passports, lockdowns etc. But there ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chewie65354432: @BurcherClaire @dnforca If you check, you will see Britain has also given big pharma indemnity. Most Australians do not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chewie65354432: @BurcherClaire @dnforca All very well and good but here in Australia, doctors have now been given indemnity from prosec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next time you pump that hand sanitizer.. https://t.co/GZRa3yslXH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RustyAway @missymohum @Narvuntien @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @DamienHamilto17 @IBergwiesel @DianeDenizen @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @StormSignalSA @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @RoyPentland @Osprey0 @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @Barbarajdurkin @RijpeW @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @MedBennett @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly @Fauntleroy1934 @DigDougFTW @DunsanyJack @garner_forest Hydrogen is another doomed idea. You need at least 4 separate energy-intensive steps to deliver hydrogen as transport fuel. That means its not economically viable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @DamienHamilto17 @RustyAway @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly I dont think youre helping your side. Everyone can see youre confused, cant think and have no ability to work though a logical process or argument. Perhaps thats typical among wind  solar proponents.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nickdixoncomic: Taking off the masks is crucial now. As many have said, masks are the only thing keeping this going. Theyve admitted t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikolovScience: Watch this psychological experiment from 2015. It explains the sheeple behavior by millions of people we witnessed over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Anti_Lie_System: @reenasharma38 i know. Amazing the masses believe the CO2 propaganda. We need more CO2, not less. There are food short]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ellymelly: The fact that people are afraid to speak in the West shows us how far our freedoms have fallen. Say his name. #Soros - bring]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theyre using India to scare everyone again. Wake up. https://t.co/GqMqyui6rw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kaki385: My sister has a new Tesla.  When its charging, in their garage, they cant run other appliances including their AC. Now I und]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lizmh70 Yep I do, ~2 years ago.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I prefer to call it vaccine free as in: are you getting the vaccine? A: No I am vaccine free https://t.co/P7JlnuzKhw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SandraWeeden: Scots in hospital with severe headaches and side effects after vaccine jabs.  It is NOT KNOWN which vaccine those affe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ct22332044: It needs repeating, why are cases exploding after vaccination rollout?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@21WIRE @JamesDelingpole WTF is this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @freethetruth2: @21WIRE Grotesque, macabre.  As usual no normal human being around for miles, only these staged, choreographed extras in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reenasharma38: plenty of VIROLOGISTS SAYING THE SHOTS ARE DANGEROUS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Wiltster: Vaccine Passports are about totalitarian control and little else. The people who vociferously advocate for them are either ps]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: Major Study Finds "Abundance of Patients Admitted to Hospital With Covid Within Seven Days of Vaccination"   No shit, S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @G3MM420: @749Joanie https://t.co/scWJG1M2WI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marcus94543161: Theyve something very bad planned. https://t.co/LgZhxPD3NG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @crbarnes001: Imagine a world where doctors were paid on results. How quickly would pharma be dropped in favour of good diet and exercis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaveAtherton20: In an era of run away global warming, Britain has the coldest April for nearly a 100 years and the 3rd coldest on recor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/p34FcE0IMd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThinkingSlow1: This is from Klaus Schwab's COVID-19: The Great Reset  Lockdowns never made sense from disease control perspective, but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @RustyAway @DamienHamilto17 @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly ..also Silicon tetrachloride, a byproduct of producing crystalline silicon, is also highly toxic. This isnt for glen - the PV insustry stooge, its to educate others of the damaging impact of solar PV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @RustyAway @DamienHamilto17 @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly According to cancer biologist David H. Nguyen, PhD, toxic chemicals in solar panels include cadmium telluride, copper indium selenide, cadmium gallium (di)selenide, copper indium gallium (di)selenide, hexafluoroethane, lead, and polyvinyl fluoride. Cont..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @RustyAway @DamienHamilto17 @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly Youre a PV industry shill. Moronically claiming that PV is made of silicon, and ignoring the huge eco-problem from millions of PV panels being dumped to contaminate our land and water. You have no value beyond allowing us to expose the damaging impacts of solar PV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DamienHamilto17: @GlenSkurka @RustyAway @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @Dia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DamienHamilto17: @GlenSkurka @novakglobal @RustyAway @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @Storm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @RustyAway @DamienHamilto17 @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly Whats your obsession with silicon? Were talking about the other components in solar PV - the toxic ones - that will leach into the soil. Solar PV is not getting recycled.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @RustyAway @DamienHamilto17 @Fiddlers__Green @Sizzlechest2020 @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly Why dont we list all the other toxic components in solar PV.  Masses of PV panels will decay and leak toxins into ground  ground water *for ever - because they are NOT being recycled. Think about how big that eco-disaster is before installing made in chyna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @latenitebobbyd: There is NO WAY we can fix the problems we have in; Academia, Hollyweird, Sports, Judicial System and really everything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: Honestly, if you are waiting on permission from the government to hug your friends and family, then you're already a lost ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WatchtowerRome: When I wonder how we got to this place where people dont care about who is governing them and how, I always desperatel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeiselLoo: @WatchtowerRome @Winston49640075  just tell me what to do!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow and RT https://t.co/RO2VMiWbEw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WatchtowerRome: @aidanheff42  Yes, Aidan, this is all of us. We need to band together as likeminded nations ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WatchtowerRome: Australia...we have a country to save.  Who is with me?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@latikambourke @monica_2978 The masses are wising up. Dont be asleep.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @latikambourke: Another impossible threshold Australia is **belatedly** setting.  Kiss goodbye hosting Olympics et al.  The world is nev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotSweetThing: Stop waiting for the government to tell you it's safe to go back to normal. It's never going to happen. You have to go b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Forensic audit in AZ. Including UV scans to separate genuine  fake ballots. Ongoing. https://t.co/oyGYpcyNvE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DisemSila: Spread far and wide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its not good, parts of Australia going to foreign ownership. https://t.co/ZEqBiDEFcE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mrgazmaz: @Avalon95765108 Show her the Freedom of information site and look at the instantaneous deaths and injuries from the different]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sarahlou2905: @Avalon95765108 #HerBodyHerChoice tell her to remind her peers coercion to take and treatment or medicationand  it is a v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Vidallena_: @Avalon95765108 @saneandbrave The peer pressure she feels is precisely how they have designed it! Social media influencers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McavoyHilary: @Avalon95765108 There are loads of us not having the vaccine.  Don't believe MSM.  You can always have it later on, but y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JerseyGirlK8: @Brian_R_Wright @Avalon95765108 @stoicmel This article is perfect.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: @Avalon95765108 If you want a link to a Telegram group with all the adverse reactions being posted, let me know!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Warnzwifey: @Avalon95765108 Say you do not wish to discuss it. Refer to Yellow Card site. My daughter gets the same, surrounded by ppl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oaklandcottage: @Avalon95765108 @DCGreenZone1 I am a retired nurse..I will not be taking this unapproved experimental gene therapy, nei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza GOO Patriots want DJT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jordan120 Ppl thinking about keeping away from people whove had the jabs..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jordan120: Just going to say it. I will absolutely not date someone who has been "vaccinated"; whatever their reasons for getting it ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Eljay2602: There is absolutely NO celebrity that would ever convince me to have the jab... ever!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Catch V for vendetta and Hunger Games next time youre in front of the TV - for some insights. And get motivated. https://t.co/jKoO4SLrsz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drsimonegold: Dr. Vladimir Zelenko, an early adaptor and pioneer of the HCQ protocol, has been nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize.  This]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15-Year-Old Boy Dies Of Heart Attack Two Days After Taking Pfizer Vaccine, Had No History Of Allergic Reactions  https://t.co/kR067SwJDh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @highnoontide: @MartinBrampton @FriendsOScience @ozhomeschool @johnson_wrjohn1 @markp1950 @eric84701331 @AndryGiles @weberj502 @ronniere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tangomitteckel: @mightysparty @AndryGiles @JaggerMickOZ @MartinBrampton @johnson_wrjohn1 @markp1950 @eric84701331 @weberj502 @FriendsOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinBrampton @johnson_wrjohn1 @markp1950 @eric84701331 @weberj502 @FriendsOScience @ronnieressler @AndryGiles @Phlark1 @jhwalker6751 @Barbarajdurkin @TransparentEner @bazakel @donahugh216 @no2wind @GZzyzyx @MedBennett @MccloudClan @Sheer_Light @MLatikainen @Tangomitteckel @CPR1881 @Michael_D_Crow @ianbrow97534170 @Boi_dBoi_d @zorg_ontzorgt @RoyPentland @highnoontide @JEdward02 @JaggerMickOZ @ECOWARRIORSS @JohnSmi50968113 @luckystiff4 @manifesto2000 @RedDragonFly19 @toddynd @portun81 @LawsonUBS @Libertyworld @TeaJunkie1 @ozhomeschool @DanCady @Lawson1999 @UkraineTrollbot @compassionsays @PaulHBeckwith @GreyTonka @204Girl0574 @cyclicaltrends @HtServadac On the contrary my green amigo. We have our eyes wide open, thats how we see the lies  the corruption in climate alarmism, the bad science, the money, but most of all the fact that all metrics are within statistical norms or better.1940s hotter, 70s colder   is greening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlenSkurka @Fiddlers__Green @RustyAway @MedBennett @Barbarajdurkin @Robin_Hagues @StormSignalSA @DianeDenizen @Osprey0 @RijpeW @lamphieryeg @JamesAnth5 @Narvuntien @DamienHamilto17 @RoyPentland @Tangomitteckel @FriendsOScience @reeta_iceburg @IBergwiesel @TQMKA @TheDisproof @ElQuesoSabio @MikeDel21893959 @Cypress_NL @notclimatedepot @DawnTJ90 @JBalsich @ReckedRik @KCTaz @Geoff4273 @flavinkins @cieloyla @AlaMerQld @no2wind @BrknMan @DerekBarge @thinks_about_it @NBPAustralia @Over400ppm @rmack2x @HuntsonMark @HtServadac @PaprikaLady @Dardedar @Homer4K @RushhourP @Bananenrijperij @NickAPalmer @1000Frolly @Fauntleroy1934 With wind solar you just offshored the generation of your electricity to (Chyna) so your electricity generation is now made with coal in a communist country by poorly paid oppressed people, instead of creating jobs in your own country with stringent environmental rules. Well done]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you want to help but dont know how, sign:   End all requirements to wear face coverings immediately - Petitions   (may need to be UK subject or resident) https://t.co/1Ysz1dnua1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rmwire: @MatthewJshow Turn the country back to the rightful winner of the 2020 election... Donald Trump!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what being indoctrinated looks like. In reality we are in WW3, many people have been poisoned. We can only hope people power and whitehat military can turn it around. https://t.co/aA3gEz8uyd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SharpieDj: And back on the rona track..  How did our government convince so many younger people (60 and below) that they were likely to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JWSpry: Climate Emergency!  Climate Crisis!  Existential Threat!  Tipping Point!  THE next time you hear, or read any of these]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reeta_iceburg: @rosepetals_zina @DawnTJ90 @FrankDoolin @IBergwiesel @BrknMan @RustyAway @300cba @rmack2x @Narvuntien @armsnana @JamesAn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MortyAUS There is no situation in India. Look at the numbers, minuscule. All hyped up by corrupt media. What do you see here? Anything ? https://t.co/5AOL7oi86W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinBrampton @johnson_wrjohn1 @markp1950 @eric84701331 @weberj502 @FriendsOScience @ronnieressler @AndryGiles @Phlark1 @jhwalker6751 @Barbarajdurkin @TransparentEner @bazakel @donahugh216 @no2wind @GZzyzyx @MedBennett @MccloudClan @Sheer_Light @MLatikainen @Tangomitteckel @CPR1881 @Michael_D_Crow @ianbrow97534170 @Boi_dBoi_d @zorg_ontzorgt @RoyPentland @highnoontide @JEdward02 @JaggerMickOZ @ECOWARRIORSS @JohnSmi50968113 @luckystiff4 @manifesto2000 @RedDragonFly19 @toddynd @portun81 @LawsonUBS @Libertyworld @TeaJunkie1 @ozhomeschool @DanCady @Lawson1999 @UkraineTrollbot @compassionsays @PaulHBeckwith @GreyTonka @204Girl0574 @cyclicaltrends @HtServadac There is no climate crisis, emergency, breakdown or whatever name you come up with next. The only crisis we have is elite power crooks getting rich, attempting to grab more power (communism) and gut the middle class. And they are using useful idiots to do it for them. Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bluebramble73 @RyanRallyOh No! never had a vaccine to travel. Perhaps you're referring to Yelow Fever? with around 50% death rate among patients with symptoms? Covid flu: dodgy figures = 2% death rate mostly over 70yo. YF vax is 90 yrs old  only recommended. Cv injection has no longitudinal study! dumass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blovereviews @JEdward02 @bazakel @highnoontide @RoyPentland @markp1950 @JaggerMickOZ @ECOWARRIORSS @ianbrow97534170 @MartinBrampton @eric84701331 @JohnSmi50968113 @luckystiff4 @Boi_dBoi_d @manifesto2000 @RedDragonFly19 @toddynd @GZzyzyx @portun81 @FriendsOScience @Barbarajdurkin @LawsonUBS @Libertyworld @TeaJunkie1 @ozhomeschool @DanCady @no2wind @Lawson1999 @Michael_D_Crow @MedBennett @UkraineTrollbot @compassionsays @PaulHBeckwith @GreyTonka @204Girl0574 @cyclicaltrends @HtServadac @tsjets1 @DuncanRice1 @TangRoy17 @noturbine @GillesnFio @LesleyJ62456075 @MarkELacey @HVACPerformance @GlenneDrover @PhilMarsom @TexCIS @DougieG @0Sundance We need more info on the scale, cost and viability of recycling batteries. Currently: https://t.co/lOpnsb377U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @highnoontide: @bazakel @RoyPentland @markp1950 @JEdward02 @JaggerMickOZ @ECOWARRIORSS @ianbrow97534170 @MartinBrampton @eric84701331 @J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @prisoner1968: "F.O.I Request shows only 596 died of Covid-19 in Scotland during 2020 and Hospital Deaths were below average."  https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Digital17959317: Yes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@richardcordle1 Youre wrong on all counts: - Covid mRNA are not really vaccines - mRNA has never b4 been permitted, not tested long term, who knows what will happen after 4 months or a year - doesnt look like vaccines did  very much - why does big pharma not take any responsibility for damge? https://t.co/ZSpaMED38w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @noreward_norisk: Doctors take the Hippocratic Oath in which they vow to do no harm.   What happened?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SylviaDeeDee: They are getting rid of your ability to heat your home because they are getting rid of fossil fuels.  They plan to get ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @luisbaram: John: I got the vaccine. May I now stop using masks? Doctor: No. John: Am I now immune to the Chinese virus? Doctor: No. Joh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @continu_um: Ask yourself. Why would Twitter go to such lengths to censor an expert in his field?  Why can't I post a link to this video]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Stratford_: IF the virus had been purified and isolated, the vaccine would contain some of it.  Instead, we either had engineered]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamBridge3: Klaus Schwab of The World Economic Forum says that everyone in the world needs to be vaccinated. Current population is 7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CromwellStuff: Expectations are so low of MPs now, we accept a doorstop as PM! After Theresa May we get him, he proves to be useless, a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Notyour28981739: There are only  4 covid vaccines available here.  2 of them are "paused" b/c of serious safety  concerns.  That's 50%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We knew covid modeling was accidentally on purpose completely wrong.  The media wont dig in  expose it because most are compromised. We cant trust scientists today because we dont know whos pocket theyre in. Many have prostituted their reputation. Need a BIG CLEANOUT!! https://t.co/4SpNyS3Wo0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikolovScience: Bill Gates is the largest farmland owner in the US having 242,000 acres in 18 states. But why is he buying farmland? Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StoneSculptorJN: Are your friends trying to pressure you into getting the   You can always make new friends   You cant get a new]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Martin the green is in favor of all things that control the people. Do you like BillG@tes? Do you support blocking out the sun? Do you like communism? How about fascism? Is there much difference? Do you admire social score, or the CCP?]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>