<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@_RichardHall @chrislhayes yes, but...... HES LITERALLY HEMMINGWAY!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichaelLaRosa46 @FLOTUS Remember when Melania gave Donald a heart for Valentine's Day? https://t.co/9dLW9sA5fU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d Quacken Caucus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @gtconway3d Someone call the golden escalator crowd!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris @amyklobuchar Meanwhile Im eating salad with a comb going Wheres the forks???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elwasson @senrobportman This is right on. People parsing what Trump said at the rally are missing the point. It's what he *didn't* say -- knowing his supporters intended to attack the capitol -- that is more damning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EliStokols @maggieNYT 74.2 MILLION]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPCarney @oliverdarcy @donie @kevinroose The cultural shift we need is for republicans to stop manipulating these fragile and dangerous people with lies  Stop weaponizing the mentally ill is a good start]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPCarney @oliverdarcy @donie @kevinroose Heres the basic republican pitch: dont vote for the democrat or youll be covered in spiders!! Im like you I hate spiders  Republicans have cornered the market on lunatics who dont want to be covered in spiders  We dont need to fix their brains. Just stop lying to them!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrLindaMD @joshtpm @nicolejames What the fuck is https://t.co/gAti2n9CHK? Why are we retweeting this? Come on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alizaslav @kaitlancollins DEMS IN DISARRAY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VeritasSola YEAH HA HA BURN IT!!!!!! TRUMP!!! AMERICA!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bencjacobs @maggieNYT We will run against you and WE WILL LOSE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fredosmithjr @joshtpm a generation of white 33 year old former interns will be inspired by jon ossoff's story]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fredosmithjr @joshtpm white privilege in action baby]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LarrySabato @joshtpm #ReleaseTheQuAcken #QuAckenCaucus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrandyZadrozny @maggieNYT @oneunderscore__ @janestreet #ReleaseTheQuAcken #QuAckenCaucus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mmcintire @maggieNYT Nah. You can punch a Nazi and you can mock Giuliani for getting COVID. Its really not that complicated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JennaEllisEsq Oh yeah? Your guy is a giant pussy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @gtconway3d ORIGINALISM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPCarney Im willing to own Bidens worst traits. Why wont you own Trumps?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPCarney Horrific? Youre so full of shit, Carney.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPCarney You serious bro?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DKThomp @chrislhayes CAN WE WAIT TIL AFTER THE ELECTION JESUS FUCKING CHRIST!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClydeHaberman @gtconway3d https://t.co/AvYrqfB4Hy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@freedlander @maggieNYT https://t.co/aburpBfwIO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelkruse @maggieNYT @AlexConant @bterris ...to be clear, the Iraq War is also our partys Iraq War]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hear Dems are planning to wear #MAGA hats to vote in swing states to avoid harassment at the polls. Smart! @gtconway3d @TheRickWilson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikkiMcR HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing https://t.co/EkxiAvMlOA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntiVaxxMom: @KimKardashian After 2 weeks of multiple health screens and asking everyone to quarantine, I surprised my closest inner ci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian After 2 weeks of multiple health screens and asking everyone to quarantine, I surprised my closest inner circle with a trip to a private island where we could pretend things were normal just for a brief moment in time. https://t.co/94KmWKy5Ox]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Babylon Bee succeeds at Fake News by being bad at comedy https://t.co/BQuL1rEVzR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisMegerian @gtconway3d Time zones]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dougmillsnyt @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/AajfpzpyJM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonfavs Rally theme is 'President Pelosi']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You didnt lose your hair because its attached with a fucking upholstery gun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adamgoldmanNYT @maggieNYT IF IT WERE POSSIBLE TO STEAL THE ELECTION TRUMP WOULDNT BE COMPLAINING ABOUT IT ***HE WOULD BE DOING IT***]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sifill_LDF Blue Lives Matter, bro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes HUMBLES: 1) Kid doesn't mention your TV show 2) And kinda slams you for not knowing Leslie Odom Jr. too well, but that might just be an embedded humble brag  either way, VERY IMPRESSIVE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes BRAGS:  1) You know Lin Manuel Miranda 2) Your kids knows American Historical Figures 3) And brags about you to adults]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes This is a the rare Triple-Double Humble Brag!  Three brags, two humbles]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill So... not very scary?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PONY_Official It = Covid   #MAGA #SuperSpreader]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WBAY @gtconway3d Remember the moment when then President George W. Bush delivered the "I Now Have The Tallest Building In Manhattan" remarks at Ground Zero. #NeverForget #BlamePataki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WBAY @gtconway3d Remember the moment when then President George W. Bush delivered the "Democrat Hoax" remarks at Ground Zero. #NeverForget #BlamePataki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WBAY @gtconway3d Remember the moment when then President George W. Bush delivered the "Not As Bad As The Flu" remarks at Ground Zero. #NeverForget #BlamePataki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WBAY @gtconway3d Remember the moment when then President George W. Bush delivered the "More People Die Each Year Choking On Meat" remarks at Ground Zero. #NeverForget #BlamePataki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d The day Bush became President of the United States https://t.co/SY73CBltWK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #BunkerBoy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Hed obviously like to win by cheating but hell buy the election if he has to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley @realDonaldTrump Sucker]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mj_lee New Trump Ad: "You know me, a radical socialist with a soft spot for rioters."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeschlossDC @maggieNYT @marycjordan IT'S A FUCKING CEMETERY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kyledcheney @maggieNYT Medal of Honor!! Featured speaker at RNC!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d Bloatilla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LibsInAmerica Bloat Parade]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepKatiePorter Dems should give their question time to @RepKatiePorter as they have given their time to staff attorneys in the past]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alanna3HR No, but withholding vaccines could teach a valuable lesson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alanna3HR I believe withholding vaccines is an effective punishment, and we should be able to punish our kids however we want. Sometimes kids need to get sick to learn a lesson.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @gtconway3d When he said he'd build a wall and Mexico would "pay" for it, I thought he meant as a promise of remuneration not what a Supervillain screams after he's been thwarted "You'll PAY for this, Mexico!!!"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rainmaker1973 @maggieNYT i blame don jr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Get real -- Herman Cain is just *one* person. Trump said a "very small percentage" would get sick and die in Tulsa and that's all Hermain Cain is -- a "very small percentage". This media hysteria is a democrat hoax to take down the president. https://t.co/mppjJrJ5hH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Live your life and remember that death comes for us all. This is Trumps plan WORKING]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer ARI FLEISCHER BECAME PRESIDENT *TODAY*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT HUMAN STOCK CAPITAL CAIN MAKE GREAT SACRIFICE FOR PREMIER TRUMP!!!! Texas Lt. Gov.: Grandparents aren't afraid to die for economy https://t.co/qe258DYjwx via @nbcnews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@McNaughtonArt @realDonaldTrump @EricTrump @TuckerCarlson @dbongino @LauraIngram @seanhannity Why is Frederick Douglass with the ghosts?? Hes still out there doing a great job!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump HERE'S HOW YOU KNOW THIS IS A LIE -- If you could actually rig an election with mail-in ballots Trump wouldn't be tweeting about it he'd be doing it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KMOV: Former Miss Kentucky sentenced to 2 years in prison for sending topless photos to a 15-year-old student https://t.co/EWOBVyeHmx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mike_Pence @WhiteHouse Mike Pence sure looks like #PresidentPence here. Has @realDonaldTrump resigned?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheSharpEdge1 The children are #immune! Send them to work! #jumpstarttheeconomy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheSharpEdge1 I am #AntiMask because it's my right to choose how I punish my children]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake @maggieNYT When people talk about how dark this campaign is going to get, this is just the beginning. Dead kids, dead wife... Trump will go after it all. This deleted post was no accident. They will make him relive every funeral before November. Does America want that level of depravity?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedcruz cut to- Goya sales spike in coveted 'giant piece of shit' demo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaggieAstor @maggieNYT who writes these fucking headlines?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MikeBalsamo1 @maggieNYT @JZBleiberg Pardon him Trump! Medal of Honor!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TPCarney black lives matter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jbarro my god. after all this time why does this point still need to be made??? it's like we can't take any action to fight the virus until the dumbest people in the country are made to understand what's going on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProjectLincoln Trump discovers if you stare at the word totalitarianism it starts to look like a long slippery ramp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProjectLincoln Trump staring at the word totalitarianism on the screen until it starts to look like a long slippery ramp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @AndrewRestuccia what a headline]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomgara CUT TO: Angry Lib at computer gouging own eyeballs out thinking: "I guarantee I hate that song more than those bitches love Trump"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seungminkim @maggieNYT Next up Trump Resigns In Protest, Inks Deal For Anti-Trump Tell All]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seungminkim @maggieNYT Should take more than resigning AT THIS POINT to scrub the stain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POLITICO_Steve @foxnewspoll SUE!!!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SharonLNYT @maggieNYT @anniekarni Hahahahahah- morale was low at the BEGINNING. Real wide eyed optimists ready to make a difference]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexburnsNYT @maggieNYT Lets fucking hope]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZekeJMiller @PressSec I stand with the 328,000,000 Americans choosing not to go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Politics_Polls @abacusdataca APOLOGIZE!!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billscher @atrupar Maybe he really does have bone spurs??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billscher @atrupar I would contribute to @ProjectLincoln running this footage in DC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClydeHaberman @JosephRappaport I totally agree with this point. Kamala Harris couldn't even explain it this morning on The View. "Defund the Police" doesn't mean what it sounds like -- and what it sounds like is idiotic. Pick a different slogan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TVietor08 @joshtpm @pourmecoffee @tedcruz at least he found one roll the exact shape of his butthole]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atrupar Liked it better in the original Comic Sans]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TropicaliJaye @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/wpkIrC67f3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan Jon Swan-- King of the "Cold Takes"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan "Final phase" doesn't mean the end of his power, it means we're finally at the version of a Trump presidency some anticipated/feared from the beginning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexburnsNYT @maggieNYT Teflon Don - - -&gt; Don T, Felon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wpcbevo @robbystarbuck @nedryun THANKS, BOT. SAY HI TO VLAD]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>