<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA["Our aim is that the WHO Hub will take this work to the next level, generating better data and better analytics for better decision-making and a safer world."-@DrTedros https://t.co/kNEO9GzkMC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Indeed, it was the EIOS [Epidemic Intelligence from Open Sources] system that picked up the first reports of a new virus in Wuhan, China, in the early hours of 31 December 2019."-@DrTedros  https://t.co/miBoXhonuD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["It builds on WHOs existing work through the @WHOGOARN and the Epidemic Intelligence from Open Sources initiative, which scans online news sources for reports of public health threats."-@DrTedros https://t.co/kNEO9GzkMC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The WHO Hub will be part of the WHO Health Emergencies Programme, and we expect it to play a vital role in the global health security ecosystem."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Hosted in Berlin, the WHO Hub will be a global centre that works with partners around the world to lead innovations in pandemic and epidemic intelligence, data, surveillance and analytics."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Modern technologies give us unprecedented tools for collecting, analysing and disseminating data in real time around the world. Thats what the WHO Hub for Pandemic and Epidemic Intelligence aims to do."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Viruses move fast, but data can move even faster. With the right information, countries and communities can stay one step of an emerging risk, and save lives."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The #COVID19 pandemic has exposed gaps in the global systems for pandemic and epidemic intelligence.  And its a fact of nature that there will more viruses will emerge with the potential of sparking epidemics or pandemics."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As  Minister @jensspahn said, rapid and reliable information is essential in every area of health, but especially when it comes to preparing for, detecting and responding to epidemics and pandemics."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["And were very grateful for #Germanys financial support for the WHO Hub, and for hosting it in Berlin, where it will benefit from being in an innovative environment."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Thank you so much, Minister @jensspahn, and please accept my deep personal appreciation for everything you have done over the past few years, and especially during the past difficult 12 months."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["@jensspahn, thank you so much once again for your leadership and partnership. You have the floor."-@DrTedros  https://t.co/9MmrNnIvDK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Of course, like every great leader, Chancellor Merkel is supported by a great team.  Even as he has led the response to #COVID19 at home, #Germanys Federal Minister of Health, @jensspahn , has played an essential leadership role on the global stage."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Once again, my deep gratitude to  Chancellor Merkel for her leadership and partnership."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["In October last year I was honoured to speak to  Chancellor Merkel, which is when we first discussed the idea for a new centre that would serve as a global platform to enhance global capacity for pandemic and epidemic intelligence."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As part of #Germanys G20 presidency, Chancellor Merkel also initiated the first ever meeting of #G20 health ministers, which included a health emergency simulation exercise."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["In my first week as Director-General in 2017, I had the honour of attending the #G20 Summit in Hamburg, where under Chancellor Merkels leadership, #Germany put a very strong emphasis on health and emergency preparedness, years before #COVID19."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["#Germany has been a steadfast partner to WHO for many years, but especially during the past year.  And I have personally appreciated the strong leadership of Her Excellency Angela Merkel, the Chancellor of Germany."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Live event on new WHO Global Hub for Pandemic  Epidemic Intelligence https://t.co/zE3PII7jSQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Increasing #midwife-led interventions could help reduce the number of abortions from 40 million to 25 million annually.  https://t.co/qxkv16SVxp #MidwivesDay #IDM2021 https://t.co/Xo0O0nHffH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HandHygiene is essential to beat #COVID19  support #InfectionPrevention: Regularly  thoroughly #CleanYourHands  with an alcohol-based hand rub  or wash them with soap   water.  Staying safe:  protects you  protects others  https://t.co/uIWpfKfrVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Access to inhalers for #asthma is a problem in many countries  In 2019, only 1 in 2 people with asthma had access to a bronchodilator and less than 1 in 5 had access to a steroid inhaler in public primary health-care facilities  in low-income countries. https://t.co/lg7GoVBvxw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Investing more in #midwives means we could avert  67% of maternal deaths 64% of neonatal deaths 65% of stillbirths  and save an estimated 4.3 million lives per year by 2035.  https://t.co/qxkv16SVxp #MidwivesDay #IDM2021 https://t.co/KvyfT62C8F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Asthma cannot be cured, but good management with inhaled medications can control the disease and enable people with asthma to enjoy a normal, active life.  For more info  https://t.co/epWqSxZWvh https://t.co/TpYmAQMce2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the joint virtual event with Chancellor Dr. Angela Merkel  Minister of Health @jensspahn of , and @DrTedros, on the establishment of the WHO Global Hub for Pandemic and Epidemic Intelligence.    Today at 1:30 - 2PM CET The event will be streamed here on @Twitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear vaccinators: Remember to always #CleanYourHands before every #COVID19  other vaccine you administer. Thorough #HandHygiene is  to #InfectionPrevention, helping you  your patients to stay safe.   https://t.co/POpWFoM0xz https://t.co/ejSyW3pJNF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Common symptoms of #asthma include  Breathlessness  Coughing  Wheezing  Chest tightness  During an asthma attack, these symptoms become much worse. Asthma attacks can be fatal but are largely preventable and manageable. https://t.co/Pq9yvwDxDD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During the COVID-19 pandemic, governments must ensure #midwives are protected with adequate personal protective equipment (PPE)  prioritized for #COVID19 vaccines.  https://t.co/qxkv16SVxp #MidwivesDay #VaccinEquity https://t.co/sNpk4Pi3Ua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The latest data from the State of Worlds Midwifery report shows the shortage of #midwives is most critical in 88 low-  middle- income countries where 95% of  maternal/newborn deaths  stillbirths occur.  https://t.co/qxkv16SVxp #MidwivesDay #IDM2021 https://t.co/7LIMmRgvYE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's #WorldAsthmaDay.   #Asthma is a common lung  condition that causes intermittent breathing difficulties. It often starts in childhood, although it can also develop in adults, and affects people of all ages. https://t.co/dpUYU6xtdE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's the International Day of the #Midwife!  Midwives are fundamental to ending preventable maternal  newborn deaths. But the world still needs 900000 more midwives to save lives of moms  and babies .  https://t.co/qxkv16SVxp #MidwivesDay #IDM2021 https://t.co/LNLp1KPXx7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear patients and families, #CleanYourHands to help save lives!  Good #HandHygiene  is a critical part of #InfectionPrevention. Do your part to keep others safe!    https://t.co/POpWFoM0xz https://t.co/xSgjsdeZOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's #HandHygiene day!  #CleanYourHands to save lives: EVERYONE has a role to play to ensure #InfectionPrevention and help stop the spread of #COVID19.  YES, this includes your  too!   https://t.co/POpWFoM0xz https://t.co/Euf3V0I8UW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's #HandHygiene Day!  Nurses, midwives, doctors  other #HealthWorkers hands  make all the difference for safe patient care  ensure #InfectionPrevention.  #CleanYourHands at the point-of-care when needed using the appropriate technique:  https://t.co/POpWFoM0xz https://t.co/TnFOXsclz3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Does that travel need to happen right now? In many parts of the world the answer is 'No'. We are working with our partners in the travel industry, hospitality industries, to ensure that when this does open up, it can open up as safely as possible." -@mvankerkhove   #COVID19 https://t.co/dqWp82XTrh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These  countries  are working with WHO to halve maternal/newborn deaths  stillbirths and improve quality care for pregnant women, mothers  their babies in .   WHO report shows their 5-year progress https://t.co/GD8F1eKZPJ https://t.co/UdipzHPro4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Healthcare systems must be   effective  safe  people-centred  timely  equitable  integrated  efficient  Achieving this could improve and save the lives of millions of pregnant women, mothers and their babies.https://t.co/GD8F1eKZPJ https://t.co/gS8DO9WZob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Too many mothers  and babies  die each year due to poor quality care especially in low- and middle-income countries.  Access to SAFE and EFFECTIVE healthcare services is key to change this. https://t.co/GD8F1eKZPJ https://t.co/YLEJql3JoB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE #AskWHO QA on World Hand Hygiene Day, 5 May now https://t.co/ib7al3JpRk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Third, Wednesday also marks the International Day of the #Midwife, an opportunity to celebrate the vital role that midwives play every day of every year, and especially during the past year."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Second, Wednesday marks World #HandHygiene Day, a reminder that clean hands save lives."-@DrTedros  https://t.co/GqCM3ReKm0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Finally, I would like to recognize three important days that we are observing this week. First, today is #WorldPressFreedomDay.  WHO values the role of a free and fair press in informing the public and in holding governments and institutions accountable."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Thank you Gordon, and thank you once again for your clear and powerful call to world leaders."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We now face an even more severe crisis, and we need the same kind of leadership.  Gordon, thank you so much for your leadership, and thank you for joining us today. You have the floor.-@DrTedros  #COVID19 https://t.co/SLV10sq9GT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As Prime Minister, @GordonBrown hosted the #G20 Summit in 2009, when under his leadership the G20 countries committed to making an additional USD1.1 trillion available to alleviate the most acute economic crisis since the Great Depression."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Today its my great honour to be joined by @GordonBrown, the former Prime Minister and Chancellor of the Exchequer of the United Kingdom."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We face a shared threat that we can only overcome with shared solutions:  Sharing financial resources;  Sharing vaccine doses and production capacity;  Sharing technology, know-how and waiving intellectual property."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The #G7 countries could mobilize a substantial portion of these funds themselves, and lead a global effort to accelerate #COVID19 vaccination around the world."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The Access to #COVID19 Tools Accelerator @ACTAccelerator currently faces a funding gap of USD19 billion, and we estimate that we will need a further USD35 to 45 billion next year to vaccinate most adults around the world."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will only solve the #COVID19 vaccine crisis with the leadership of these countries.-@DrTedros https://t.co/1bu5pRuDFF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Next month, leaders from the #G7 countries will gather for what may be the most significant meeting in its history. The G7 countries are the worlds economic and political leaders. They are also home to many of the worlds vaccine producers."-@DrTedros #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["#COVAX has now shipped almost 50 million doses of #COVID19 vaccine to 121 countries and economies, but we continue to face severe supply constraints. Solving this dilemma demands courageous leadership from the worlds largest economies."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We call on other countries to follow the example these countries have set, and donate through #COVAX to help accelerate equitable distribution and access.-@DrTedros  #COVID19 https://t.co/tn4v5y7Lwv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tack s mycket, #Sweden, for this donation, which follows similar donations by #France, #NewZealand and #Norway, with positive signs from some other countries.-@DrTedros  #COVID19 https://t.co/1bgciaPd1V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This morning I met with Swedens Minister for Development Coordination, Per Olsson Fridh @thinkper, who informed me that #Sweden will donate 1 million doses of AstraZeneca #COVID19 vaccines to #COVAX."-@DrTedros https://t.co/dGnAMh1TE2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Were pleased to note that @gavi has signed an agreement with Moderna for 500 million doses of #COVID19 vaccine on behalf of #COVAX"-@DrTedros https://t.co/sw0eLDVjb5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emergency Use Listing is one prerequisite for #COVID19 vaccines to be purchased and supplied through COVAX. It also allows countries to expedite their own regulatory approval and to import and administer a vaccine.-@DrTedros https://t.co/sw0eLDVjb5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["On Friday, WHO gave Emergency Use Listing to Modernas #COVID19 vaccine, making it the fifth to receive WHO validation."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["What is happening in #India and #Brazil could happen elsewhere unless we all take these public health precautions that WHO has been calling for since the beginning of the #COVID19 pandemic.  Vaccines are part of the answer, but they are not the only answer."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We call on everyone to continue to follow WHO  national advice on keeping safe: maintain physical distance, avoid crowds wear a well-fitted mask that covers the nose and mouth properly  open windows  cover coughs and sneezes   clean your hands" -@DrTedros #COVID19 https://t.co/C1YwgFwHa4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["WHO and @thewhof are raising funds to support the need for oxygen and related supplies globally."-@DrTedros   #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were also providing advice for people on how to provide care at home for families that are unable to find a hospital bed. For #COVID19 patient with severe or critical disease, WHO recommends treatment with dexamethasone.-@DrTedros https://t.co/UYdE8gQhX7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["In #India, WHO is providing critical equipment and supplies including oxygen concentrators, lab supplies and mobile field hospitals."-@DrTedros  #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["#India and #Brazil account for more than half of last weeks #COVID19 cases, but there are many other countries all over the world that face a very fragile situation"-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["More cases of #COVID19 have been reported globally in the past two weeks than during the first six months of the pandemic."-@DrTedros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 is a very different disease, but the approach is the same.  The absence of any one of these key measures presents a weakness that this virus will exploit, as we are seeing all over the world.-@DrTedros https://t.co/4HGkwnp7AJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This has only been possible thanks to a concerted, comprehensive and consistent approach, using vaccines and therapeutics alongside proven public health measures, with empowered and engaged communities.-@DrTedros   #Ebola #DRC https://t.co/GCPeMZiyF1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Earlier today, the government of the #DRC announced the end of the most recent #Ebola outbreak, three months after the first case was reported in North Kivu. I congratulate the govt, health workers, communities  all WHO staff who were involved in the response."-@DrTedros https://t.co/STJU9gK4bz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media briefing on #COVID19 with  @DrTedros https://t.co/gKyZgVmL7U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Handwashing is one of the  actions to fight #COVID19. Still, around 3 billion people worldwide cannot wash their hands with    at home.  WHO/@UNICEF report provides recommendations to ensure affordable access water, sanitation  hygiene. https://t.co/T6KWfXHIl6 https://t.co/rroyX3ggAw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The report provides insights into water, sanitation  hygiene (WASH) affordability including:   percentage of income spent on WASH  spending preferences  poverty status  existing measures  More info https://t.co/T6KWfXHIl6 https://t.co/XX7tE5LLhb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join today 16h00 CEST @UN Special Envoy for Global Education  former Prime Minister of the United Kingdom @GordonBrown  @DrTedros  Financing the fight to end the #COVID19 pandemic, with a focus on the #ACTAccelerator in the context of G7/G20 LIVE on WHO social media https://t.co/bdTLUhfHEk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When people struggle to access water supply, sanitation  hygiene (WASH) services, they incur health, time  social costs.   WHO/@UNICEF report explains how countries can achieve affordable WASH services for all https://t.co/T6KWfXHIl6 https://t.co/ZVY8bsG3eA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ WHO/@UNICEF report sets out monitoring recommendations to help billions of people around the  get access to affordable water supply, sanitation  hygiene (#WASH) services.  Read more https://t.co/T6KWfXHIl6 https://t.co/3jjZE99xgv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOAFRO: GOOD NEWS from #DRC!  @MinSanteRDC has just announced the end of the 12th #Ebola outbreak in DRC  just 3 months after the f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOAFRO: People with non-communicable disease have a higher risk of severe #COVID19. The main risks of #NCDs are:   Tobacco.  Alcohol.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19 - tip 5  Open windows to increase the amount of natural ventilation when indoors.  Staying safe: protects you protects others  https://t.co/k7eMk2yufy  https://t.co/zFJz3vx83m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19 - tip 4  Cover yourwith your bent elbow or tissue when you cough/sneeze. Then dispose of the tissue immediately into a closed bin  wash your hands.  Staying safe: protects you protects others  https://t.co/3LAiDYr5Ns]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19 - tip 3  Maintain at least a 1-metre distance between yourself  others. Maintain an even greater distance when indoors. The further away, the better.  Staying safe: protects you protects others  https://t.co/CY9LdTJaOI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When out  about, make hand sanitizer part of your maskwearing routine.  Clean your hands every time you: put on your mask adjust/touch your mask remove your mask  We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19  https://t.co/QX57ltMoFV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can only be free from #COVID19 when everyone is protected from it. That's why @thewhof launched the Go Give One campaign, which enables everyone, everywhere to donate to buy a vaccine, helping close the funding gap faced by COVAX.   https://t.co/3krknY0eGm  #VaccinEquity https://t.co/tu7UvxkFyy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19 tip 2  Make wearing a mask a normal part of being around other people.  Staying safe: protects you  protects others   https://t.co/k7eMk2yufy  https://t.co/gH58f0UR2Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The first international delivery of #COVID19 vaccines from #COVAX arrived in #Ghana  in February 2021, with essential workers  other at-risk groups prioritized in the roll-out. Worldwide, over 49 million doses have been distributed so far.   https://t.co/3krknY0eGm https://t.co/ftYlseohk4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19 - tip 1  Regularly  thoroughly clean your  with an alcohol-based hand rub  or wash them with soap  water.   Staying safe: protects you  protects others  https://t.co/k7eMk2yufy  https://t.co/uIWpfKfrVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19  Here are 5 tips that help you stay safe to protect yourself and others:  clean hands  wear a mask  stay distant  cough, sneeze safely  open windows   https://t.co/k7eMk2yufy  https://t.co/RIGoL5izxn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVAX is the vaccines pillar of the @ACTAccelerator. It is driving #VaccinEquity by working to deliver at least 2 billion doses in 2021, with a special mechanism to provide access to vaccines for lower income countries.     https://t.co/3krknY0eGm   #ACTogether https://t.co/4eVU7SZAjw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone, everywhere can support the vaccines initiative #COVAX to help:  vaccinate the world   achieve #VaccinEquity   end the #COVID19 pandemic    Find out how YOU can contribute:  https://t.co/3krknY0eGm https://t.co/vKAwqp0JZP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out this animation and see how location, proximity and time can help you make safer choices when you're in an area of widespread #COVID19 transmission.  https://t.co/8lAA9M4tOa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lower your risk from #COVID19 by combining these 5 precautions: 1 Wear a mask  2 Clean your hands 3 Keep physical distance  4 Cough/sneeze away into your elbow  5 Open windows as much as possible    We are #InThisTogether to beat #COVID19 https://t.co/eFRNDXc8Fc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Learn how you can stay safe from #COVID19 when going grocery shopping.   Know your risk. Lower your risk. https://t.co/QSYPBWZPN2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOEMRO: Lets keep safe, happy and healthy during #Easter, Sham El Nessim and #Ramadan.   Protect yourself and loved ones from #COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOWPRO: Studies showed a reduction in illness and death after being vaccinated against COVID19. Together with other preventive measure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOWPRO: You remember sitting down next to your best friend?  Sharing a quick meal? High fiving? Hugging?  #VaccinesWork to bring us an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you need to attend a medical appointment , heres how you can lower your risk of catching #COVID19.   Know your risk. Lower your risk. https://t.co/zhC3smCnir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you would like to pay a visit to family members in a care facility, heres how you can lower your risk of catching or spreading #COVID19.   Know your risk. Lower your risk. https://t.co/YklNiJBkjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How can you stay safe if someone from your household falls sick from #COVID19?   Know your risk. Lower your risk. https://t.co/ShS5NoJccb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are several things you can do to prepare in case someone in your household falls sick  from #COVID19.  Know your risk. Lower your risk. https://t.co/Dgdyzp5V7L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines protect against more than 20 diseases, from pneumonia to cervical cancer and Ebola, and now, #COVID19. Yes, #VaccinesWork to bring us closer. https://t.co/FybFf1OS6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are caring for yourself or a loved one at home, how can you keep everyone safe from #COVID19?   WHOs Dr April Baller explains in #ScienceIn5  https://t.co/O0UqyQmCr8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The full remarks by @DrTedros at the #COVID19 media briefing  https://t.co/1NMOtdeCP4]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>