<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Many patients and their families spend long hours in health care facilities  especially because of #COVID19.    Clean your hands! Make sure you wash your hands with soap and water or alcohol-based rub to keep infections at bay!    #WorldHandHygieneDay https://t.co/j4aBOdLrMq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Infection prevention  control (IPC) practitioners are experts on #HandHygiene and often teach techniques in health facilities! Be a role model for clean hands at point of care.   If you are an IPC practitioner, post photos of your commitment  tag us or your place of work. https://t.co/fPIwyPOQjx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its World #HandHygieneDay!   Make clean hands your habit! It protects all of us.   #HandHygieneis one of the most effective actions you can take to reduce the spread of pathogens and prevent infections including #COVID19. https://t.co/y6vdVccpkE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For countries and areas outside of the WHO Western Pacific Region, please visit: https://t.co/VY9fK0B4Wd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DOHgovph removed 15 cases previously included in total number of cases due to duplication. The total number of cases reported for 4 May 2021 has been corrected to 1,062,210.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Health, Labour, and Welfare of Japan updated the total number of deaths for 4 May 2021 to 10,420.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated the total number of cases for 4 May 2021 to 16,299.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/YiIGypt21R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Washing your hands frequently with soap  and running water  for at least 40-60 seconds can help stop the spread of infection.    Make it a habit!  Join the campaign here: https://t.co/x4tqt03Mgx  #WorldHandHygieneDay https://t.co/dCvLS4UoeI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make it easy to #CleanYourHands:   Make sure #HandHygiene supplies are available where they are needed  especially in health care facilities   Teach people the right way to clean their hands   https://t.co/x4tqt03Mgx https://t.co/L5LaT4jjYw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's World #HandHygiene Day! Are you a #healthworker looking to improve how you #CleanYourHands?   Take the #OpenWHO online course to support the #COVID19 response: learn how to prevent infections with good #HandHygiene   https://t.co/OMDb7ZqhM4 https://t.co/y7Ta1cbfxd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Risk factors for developing #asthma include   inhaling asthma triggers:   Allergens    Tobacco smoke   Chemical irritants   -#AirPollution https://t.co/2R9CY6r89y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medication is not the only way to control #asthma. It is also important to avoid asthma triggers - stimuli that irritate and inflame the airways. With medical support, each asthma patient must learn what triggers they should avoid. https://t.co/UqkmsvaCrk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Asthma can't be cured, but it can be managed. This includes:    short-term medication to relieve symptoms    use of medication daily to control inflammation  prevent symptoms    avoiding asthma triggers, like air pollution  allergens   https://t.co/KsWvINxsh8 https://t.co/dYS7nApojl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you have asthma? Does someone you love have #asthma? Learn more about the disease here: https://t.co/KsWvINfRpA https://t.co/dQbQWjW9T8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is #WorldAsthmaDay!   #Asthma is a chronic disease of the air passages of the lungs which inflames  narrows them. People with asthma experience recurrent attacks of breathlessness and wheezing, which vary in severity and frequency from person to person. https://t.co/RCE3S4s2jH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you have or do you know someone with asthma?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What are the differences between the various testing methods to diagnose #COVID19?   Watch this video! https://t.co/wJKIHHTBEk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To see #COVID19 case counts in countries and areas outside of the WHO Western Pacific Region, please visit: https://t.co/VY9fK0B4Wd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DOHgovph removed 13 cases previously included in total cases due to duplication. The total cases reported for 03 May 2021 has been corrected to 1,054,970 cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The National Department of Health of Papua New Guinea updated total cases for 02 May 2021 to 11,262 and for 03 May to 11,273 and total deaths to 121.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated total cases for 03 May 2021 to 15,361 and total deaths to 107.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/uRO3d49eCI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How do you ensure that you wash your hands for at least 40 seconds?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 moments for#HandHygiene:   Before touching a patient   Before a clean/aseptic procedure  After body fluid exposure risk  After touching a patient  After touching patient surroundings   #CleanHands Save Lives!  #CleanYourHands! https://t.co/kKvo1Eme6Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you a health care worker?   #CleanYourHands at the point of care. Now more than ever.    Protect yourself and othersfrom #COVID19 and other disease withproper#HandHygiene https://t.co/5Lm7njNsqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Washing your hands with soap  and running water for at least 40-60 sec or alcohol-based hand rub for 20-30 sec can prevent infection.    Clean hands save lives! We must provide the facilities to keep them clean.   https://t.co/x4tqt03Mgx https://t.co/KKtmiveI4O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its World #HandHygiene Day tomorrow!   712 M people worldwide  have no running water at their health care facility.   1 in 4 health care facilities  dont have basic water facilities.  Learn more:    https://t.co/x4tqt03Mgx https://t.co/nUNdhD5dZu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 transmission:    Transmission of some COVID-19 variants:    With these new variants, it's even more important to:     Stay at least 1 metre apart.   Limit time in or avoid enclosed/crowded spaces.   Wash our hands.    Wear masks. https://t.co/BoyOJRaknx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone should have a fair opportunity to attain good health.   Yet, the places where people live, work and play can make it harder for some to reach their full health potential, while others have the conditions to thrive.   Lets build a fairer, healthier world for everyone. https://t.co/mc4pJrsJz5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To see COVID-19 case counts in countries and areas outside of the WHO Western Pacific Region, please visit: https://t.co/VY9fK0B4Wd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated total cases for 02 May 2021 to 14,520 and total deaths to 103.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DOHgovph removed 16 cases previously included in total cases due to duplication. The total cases reported for 02 May 2021 has been corrected to 1,046,637 cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of New Zealand removed one case previously included in the total cases and have been reclassified. The total cases reported for 02 May 2021 has been corrected to 2,261.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/2oFWBlLpxt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sometimes, people may feel ill after receiving a vaccinebut that doesnt necessarily mean the illness is linked with the #COVID19 vaccine.   https://t.co/KvPL9INeRZ  #VaxFacts https://t.co/xj58BKwf1n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its very rare for serious side effects to be caused by a vaccine, including for #COVID19 vaccines. As with any vaccine, health authorities are continuing to carefully monitor the introduction of COVID-19 vaccines to ensure they are safe for everyone.  #VaxFacts https://t.co/JBt89hr20I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just like with other vaccines, experiencing mild side effects after receiving a #COVID19 vaccine is normal and is a signal that your body is building protection against #coronavirus.   Learn more: https://t.co/KvPL9INeRZ  #VaxFacts https://t.co/TCVX7NkYGi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Draw   Sing   Dance  Spend time in creative play with children at home.  #MentalHealth  #COVID19 https://t.co/tCar0JIJat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Practice proper #HandHygiene to help #StopTheSpread of #COVID19. https://t.co/i5VV8tNcBa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@WHO's regional logistics team in the Western Pacific plays a crucial role in making sure life-saving medical supplies and equipment are ready to be shipped wherever and whenever needed during the #COVID19 pandemic and other emergencies.  https://t.co/2IWpQY2kH7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Young and healthy? You are still at risk of #COVID19.   #WearAMask Wash your hands frequently with soap and  for at least 40-60 sec  Keep at least 1 m distance from others. Avoid crowds and enclosed spaces.   We are #InThisTogether. Help #StopTheSpread of COVID-19. https://t.co/ACFZLqtzT0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We continue to:   Keep 1 metre distance.   Avoid crowds and enclosed spaces.  Wash hands frequently.  #WearAMask   Get vaccinated when its our turn! #DoItAll   #InThisTogether against #COVID19 https://t.co/T02bZfbQPy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You remember sitting down next to your best friend?  Sharing a quick meal? High fiving? Hugging?  #VaccinesWork to bring us and our children closer to a normal we know.  Back to school.  Back to friends.  Back to childhood.  #WorldImmunizationWeek https://t.co/dVpXWHJ5dn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#VaccinesWork to bring us closer to a world where being healthy is for everyone.  #HealthForAll https://t.co/GjfZpUGiTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#VaccinesWork to bring us closer to #HealthForAll.  Immunization reaches more people than any other health service, connecting families with health care systems and ensuring everyone has access to the care they need.  #WorldImmunizationWeek https://t.co/CtukilUont]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the future, they will talk about #polio the way we talk about MySpace  (sorry #MySpace)  One day soon its going to be an archaic, foreign concept.  #VaccinesWork to bring us closer to a world without polio.   #EndPolio #WorldImmunizationWeek https://t.co/Qqrql33Kyw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#VaccinesWork to bring us closer to a  without:  Cervical #cancer #COVID19 Cholera Diphtheria Ebola Hep B Influenza Japanese encephalitis Measles Meningitis Mumps Pertussis Pneumonia Polio Rabies Rotavirus Rubella Tetanus Typhoid Varicella Yellow Fever  #WorldImmunizationWeek https://t.co/oSdRLVEpsQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Studies showed a reduction in illness and death after being vaccinated against COVID19. Together with other preventive measures, #COVID19 vaccines are important tools in bringing an end to the pandemic. Get vaccinated  when its your turn.   #VaccinesWork https://t.co/4AAbqsy6wG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read the statement from @WHOMalaysia on vaccines and #COVID19 here:    https://t.co/9Y8pHJXf7Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @takeshi_kasai: Rising #COVID19 cases in Mongolia  have been concerning. So its good that over 99% of the 56,000 targeted health work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To see COVID-19 case counts in countries and areas outside of the WHO Western Pacific Region, please visit: https://t.co/VY9fK0B4Wd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The total number of cases reported for 28 April has been corrected to 120,667 and for 29 April to 121,346.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Health and Welfare of Republic of Korea removed 4 cases from the total number of cases reported on 28 April 2021 and 1 case from the total number of cases reported on 29 April 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@DOHgovph  removed 33 cases previously included in the total number of cases due to duplication. The total number of cases reported for 29 April 2021 has been corrected to 1,020,462.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated the total number of cases for 29 April 2021 to 12,641 and total number of deaths to 91.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/ki2PpuncyJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its not just about going to work and doing your daily tasks.    Its about the connections.  Its about getting that thing just right.   Its about fulfillment.    #VaccinesWork to help us build back. Better. Healthier. https://t.co/hVI5SuV4UN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Young people can be more active     Limit screen time   Get out to play   Play active video games if you cant get outdoors   Indoor workouts work too!    #BeActive https://t.co/5fqY5MnGZL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In our unequal world, how does inequity impact our fight against #COVID19? How can we address it? WHOs @mariangelasimao explains in #ScienceIn5   #HealthEquity https://t.co/nLSDUp964w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you were a kid, vaccines meant needles, tears  a painful memory if you were lucky.  But innovations have brought new  improved vaccines that are easier to transport,  more readily available.  #VaccinesWork to Bring Us Closer to a healthier future!  #HealthForAll https://t.co/y6hT20Bmet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For countries and areas outside of the WHO Western Pacific Region, please visit: https://t.co/VY9fK0B4Wd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Health and Welfare of Republic of Korea removed 2 cases from the total number of cases reported on 28 April 2021. The total number of cases reported for 28 April has been corrected to 120,671.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@dohgovph removed 18 cases previously included in the total number of cases due to duplication. The total number of cases reported for 28 April has been corrected to 1,013,600.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The National Department of Health of Papua New Guinea updated the total number of cases for 28 April 2021 to 10,997 and total number of deaths to 107.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated the total number cases for 28 April 2021 to 11,761 and total number of deaths to 88.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/nbCCB6LS9l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@Freerice by the @WFP will keep your children entertained, informed, and part of a movement to end world hunger. Keep your children informed and empower them to fight fear with knowledge.  https://t.co/exkx65uoYF https://t.co/1fr68gTGUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HanlindK We also have specific information for COVID-19 vaccines here: https://t.co/b2pM2q2FoE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HanlindK Hi, thank you for you question. We have a lot of information on vaccines in the link below which you may find useful:  https://t.co/mR3vUZZkke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Continuing to exercise during the #COVID19 pandemic is good for your physical and mental health.   #StaySafe while working out indoors  follow these tips!  #BeActive https://t.co/gP6WiKvDWL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#VaccinesWork to bring children closer to a healthy start in life.    Over the years vaccines have protected children against  diseases that can leave them unhealthy or disabled for the rest of their lives   Like #polio. Like #measles. Like mumps.  https://t.co/MRvNF1Tj4T https://t.co/toEtDMvqRs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is #WorldDayforSafetyandHealthatWork!  Read a commentary from @WHOMalaysia and @ILOAsiaPacific on the importance of a healthy and safe work environment, especially during the #COVID19 pandemic here https://t.co/HnvLqQpY3A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@DOHgovph removed 14 cases previously included in the total number of cases due to duplication. The total number of cases reported for 27 April has been corrected to 1,006,414.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The National Department of Health of Papua New Guinea updated the total number of cases for 27 April 2021 to 10,915 and total number of deaths to 107.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@minhealthnz removed one case previously included in the total number of cases and have been reclassified. The total number of cases reported for 27 April 2021 have been corrected to 2,252.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated the total number of cases for 27 April 2021 to 11,063 and total deaths to 82.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/zsRgRVUfeQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today #Fiji  received more #COVID19 testing equipment, with support from @WHO @UNICEFPacific  @spc_cps.  Amid locally-transmitted cases last week, @MOHFiji Min @Nadokoulu says this will boost their work to identify  stop transmission. @FijianGovt https://t.co/3my923afyz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What criteria should be followed for health care workers to return to work after a confirmed exposure or contact with a case of #COVID19? https://t.co/pWKq8WGAUp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How can you #StaySafe during sohour, iftar or other social events during #Ramadan?   Follow these tips to keep friends, family and yourself safe! https://t.co/N9LN2UEgOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 pandemic is a challenging time, for children, parents and caregivers. Doing a few simple activities with your child can provide them with vital comfort and love during these uncertain times. https://t.co/Ve93aLfsB4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have sacrificed so much to keep our loved ones and community safe from #COVID19.   Now vaccines along with other preventive measures will help end the pandemic and bring us closer again.   #VaccinesWork to Bring Us Closer https://t.co/Jqw0aAEIP6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Health and Welfare of Republic of Korea removed 1 case from the total number of cases reported on 26 April 2021. The total number of cases reported for 26 April has been corrected to 119,386.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@DOHgovph removed 19 cases previously included in the total number of cases due to duplication. The total number of cases reported for 25 April has been corrected to 989,399.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated the total number of cases for 25 April 2021 to 9,975 and total deaths to 74.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L14iMqi https://t.co/HAwcLr5zWF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Vaccines save millions of lives each year. Before they are approved, #COVID19 vaccines must meet strenuous research and quality standards. The result: a safe and effective defense against severe illness and death from COVID-19. https://t.co/nedcJvXJd8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even if you take a #COVID19 test before traveling, its still possible to be in the early incubation stage of the illness. And traveling risks exposure to #coronavirus.   Maintain hand washing, mask wearing  physical distancing when traveling.  #InThisTogether https://t.co/6DTqZ3Rzc2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WearAMask while travelling, even if youve already been vaccinated. https://t.co/8lxWhg5ETh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are travelling, its important to continue practicing safety measures whether you have been vaccinated or not.   -Keep a distance of at least 1m from others -Wash your hands often for at least 40-60 seconds w/ soap and water or alcohol-based handrub -#WearAMask   #COVID19 https://t.co/Ko1tjdLfZW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@WHOPhilippines procured and delivered 50 Oxygen Concentrators and their accessories to @DOHgovph, aimed at increasing preparedness for #COVID19 in the country in coming weeks.  Read more: https://t.co/yyQfe5TQJK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@DOHgovph removed 19 cases previously included in the total number of cases due to duplication. The total number of cases reported for 25 April has been corrected to 989,399.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATES: The Ministry of Health of Cambodia updated the total number of cases for 25 April 2021 to 9,975 and total deaths to 74.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 confirmed cases and deaths reported by countries and areas in the @WHO Western Pacific Region over the past 24 hours.   For more info on #coronavirus cases in the Region, go to our dashboard: https://t.co/qQ2L141byK https://t.co/1rmcgcTK8X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quitting tobacco promotes physical and #MentalHealth and reduces your risk of #COVID19.  Get started:    set a quit date in the next week seek professional advice plan ahead to manage cravings ask for support from loved ones follow through with your plans  #NoTobacco https://t.co/COemHGrlIP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOWPRO: #China  drove down its indigenous #malaria cases from 30M a year in the 1940s to zero indigenous cases in 2017! The country]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#VaccinesWork to bring us one step closer to the people and moments we love.   Friends.   Family.   A long hug.    Support systems.    Birthday parties.   Game nights.   Dinner out.   Quote this tweet and let us know what youre looking forward to! https://t.co/0PMlNhz1DR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Successful surveillance, strong national plans and changes to how the programme worked during #COVID19 were among the strategies adapted by countries to help them reach their 2020 goals to #EndMalaria.  Read more: https://t.co/yaRR0gVe4q https://t.co/fxc1mj1dFY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WHO @APLMA_Malaria @takeshi_kasai @MalariaNoMore #Malaysias  national malaria plan has successfully eliminated a disease the country has been battling since the 1900s  maintaining zero indigenous cases even during the #COVID19 pandemic!   Read more: https://t.co/tkBf4Hpkdy https://t.co/KPdGMrIFMh]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>