<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[If you think this would be necessary in a real pandemic, idk what to tell you.  #Scamdemic https://t.co/kHQm4NwfLZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FNullifies: Another $45 BILLION needed next year to vaccinate most adults across the globe  World Health Organization  RT Business Ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Breaking911: JUST IN: Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine earned the company $3.5 billion in the first three months of this year, 25% of Pfizer's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BabyBlues2016: .@GovRonDeSantis Palm Beach county is still evading your orders  FL law by REQUIRING citizens wear masks in county buil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tickerguy: This is YOUR young adult or teen who some COLLEGE is "mandating" take the jab.  Do YOU, as their PARENT, consent to this mad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarlosGSmith: We're NO LONGER under a state of emergency," says @GovRonDeSantis as he justifies stripping local governments of emergen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*on July 1st https://t.co/8spZqzN8qg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flu season is officially over https://t.co/WTFhid2Zj9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BabyBlues2016: .@GovRonDeSantis #annegannonscandal happening in Palm Beach County FL.  Gannon previously targeted employees of color re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: Apparently the Florida legislature has taken the advice of FDOH that masks aren't necessary https://t.co/Q1fOMOZbaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: There's only one story that matters in 2021: America's government (at state  fed level) has now suspended public wors]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust the government*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: It's amazing that the CDC is JUST NOW acknowledging that a PCR positive test with a cycle threshold over 28 probably d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: I spoke too soon. @GovRonDeSantis just signed an extension to the emergency order even though Florida has no emergency.  The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And the mask finally drops. Figuratively. https://t.co/sX66ec1eyV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: Why did the Democrats send 73 lawyers to Arizona to stop an audit of the ballots?  You know why. You're just not allow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CelestineBee: At this point they should just change the PR slogan to Protect The Lie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @flcivilrights: Newly discovered evidence in the case against Palm Beach Countys unconstitutional mask mandate showing local officials]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: Nurses who speak out are a liability to any organization that has something to hide. They fire, coerce and threaten us.  We a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaraHillPhoto: People bragging about getting the vaccine is so bizarre to me. It's like, hello I have volunteered to be injected with e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GMOFreeUSA: The Florida Keys would become known as the "HOME OF GMO MOSQUITOES." The coronavirus pandemic has already hammered the Keys]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @foe_us: The EPA green-lighted @Oxitecs plan to release half a billion experimental mosquitos into the Florida Keys  without checking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine defeating your opponents through censorship, and still thinking you've won a debate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: I dont know who needs to hear this, but they are literally trying to take your guns while mandating an experimental vax as a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Appears legitimate https://t.co/uvyeJKMtPV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: 1.) Shut down society 2.) Lockdown citizens 3.) Limit travel 4.) Limit groceries 5.) Mass riots 6.) Take guns  How stu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome to Psyopland! https://t.co/HcA9ga8CSo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GarretKramer: So vaccine manufacturing keeps increasing and viruses keep increasing and we keep spending billions of dollars to increas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kavana Good for what ails ya! https://t.co/X6pom856o7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: JJ, the same company charged with concealing evidence of cancer-causing asbestos in their baby powder, paused" their experi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: When is  the JJ experimental jab going to be permanently recalled?  https://t.co/x33fOVkn1T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: It's amazing how many people think COVID is so dangerous to children (it's actually less dangerous than flu) that they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccine passport issue is turning into a power play between Tallahassee and Miami. https://t.co/O7CwAtn1Wl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drmelissasell: You will soon be vaccinated as often as your phone updates.   Please, wake up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Imagine if all of the billions of taxpayer dollars being wasted on PR campaigns by govts to keep us in a permanent state of i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: That's how you ACTUALLY give an intramuscular injection.  Why doesn't anything make sense anymore? #sos https://t.co/mRbsclPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Human experimentation should be voluntary, not mandatory, so that those of us who believe in our rights can safely monitor those who choose to get injected for any potential long-term side effects.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Southeastern University was desperate to bring mandatory vaccines to its campus by August 1st, but has apparently decided to hold off thanks to @GovRonDeSantis' Executive Order against vaccine passports, which is welcome news. https://t.co/xupTtTEqBH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are we really going to have to pass a trillion+ dollar bailout every time the media decides to fake a pandemic?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: From a doctor - not me! "Unmask children ASAP"  @GovRonDeSantis  @richardcorcoran]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: Mask mandates are dropping like flies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's estimated that 1.56 billion useless face masks have already made it to the ocean, but remember, Democrats are better on environmental issues. https://t.co/qe1hpxYFah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is welcome news. Now, why are the countywide mask mandates still in place since by now we all know they did nothing to cut transmission rates? We're weeks behind Texas already! https://t.co/DFLYRwquXp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CelestineBee: Truth always comes to light in the end. I hope those who've conspired to deceive the world are sweating  those who've bo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are experiencing a repeat of bird flu, swine flu, Zika, 9/11, and the Global Financial Crisis all rolled into one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have no confidence that this proposal has real teeth, but it's an important step in the right direction. https://t.co/1g9uFemewW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When the dollar loses it's purchasing power, remember everyone who lined up to get experimented on because they thought the shots were "free".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LouisLeoIV: If #vaccines are safe, why are those who profit from them awarded immunity from legal liability for harm caused by their ex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: Can we talk about the fact that literally any symptom someone had during the plandemic was diagnosed as COVID, but fast-forwa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've reached the "experimenting on children" phase of the Scamdemic. https://t.co/if38mLWllH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's about halting a deadly new wave.  Yeah. Right. https://t.co/4KmqIVDoLJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: Let's get masks off children!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's going on here https://t.co/sbrefA2paM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Dominion Voting Systems has filed a $1.6 billion defamation lawsuit against Fox News, arguing the cable news giant falsel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If @GovRonDeSantis had banned mask mandates from the beginning, Florida's numbers would prove how useless they've been.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's great but why are countywide mask mandates still in place around the state? https://t.co/emWhxjUi22]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: Those who choose the free donut a day are the same people who will carry vaccine cards as proof they are entitled to the free]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: They dont even care that we know.....  https://t.co/wudxtK2rVA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who's going to pay for it? https://t.co/aKdVGbJIyi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: .@fgcu is similarly saying "masks likely" for fall, but they are letting ScienceTM drive their decisions.   Right.  Ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SusieFrmSeattle: 1/  Covid-19 vaccines:   38,444 adverse reactions reported to VAERS thru 3/12/21   1739 DEATHS  3976 HOSPITALIZATION]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cynthiamckinney: https://t.co/obiJyZk6hE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that a billion genetically modified mosquitoes are about to be released in the Florida Keys? https://t.co/Kw8gayjQT8 https://t.co/a7OkSKQ72R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: Wondering why were on a flight that requires a negative COVID test to fly, but they still require all passengers to wear mas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: What are we doing to our kids??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Im not a slave so I dont wear a mask outdoors, at stores, while working or to sit down at a restaurant for five seco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looks like they're finally starting to get the message in Tallahassee. https://t.co/iW0ZMW1nyz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gummibear737: 365 days to stop the spread!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaraHillPhoto: I'm happy to launch my new campaign, #TellVAERS .   Tell VAERS is the public health campaign the government refuses to i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanStevens1103: The vaccine wasnt created to save us from the pandemic.  The pandemic was created so we would take the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LouisLeoIV: Great news...but why won't @GovRonDeSantis cancel the so-called "emergency" or continued abuses of power by local authoriti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida takes a big step in the right direction as @GovRonDeSantis finally issues an Executive Order ending the fining of businesses for violating mask mandates. https://t.co/fK2W2sNPr8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CelestineBee: This is a strange war. We're under attack but most are too comfortably numb to even notice it let alone think about ways]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gummibear737: Were a generation of pussies, raising our childrens as bigger pussies  We think that shielding them from danger protects]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure they can. They can just keep expanding suffrage like they've been doing for years.  It's the only way they can win elections nowadays. https://t.co/WLPCwAC6Ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are no longer living in a serious country. https://t.co/b1cgtfwTG9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cynthiamckinney: 460 Dead 243,612 Reported Injuries from COVID19 Vaccines Reported in the U.K.  https://t.co/UhQXUkABXl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erin_bsn: I don't know who needs to hear this, but Pelosi is trying to get Cuomo out quick on sexual harassment to avoid the unraveling]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AK4WA: Folks, you dont get it.  Im in WA State.  Once they have your elections, they have EVERYTHING.  You cant elect legislators to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for your permission, but also kindly GFY.    "Fully vaccinated people can gather indoors without masks, CDC says"  https://t.co/p4FMx7bn8x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rising_serpent: Anthony Fauci has done for science what James Comey and Andrew McCabe did for law enforcement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But wait I thought they just mobilized a massive voter turnout for The Most Popular President in U.S. history!?!?  https://t.co/tDEkrIZP7a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@manuelQ_22 Here I was referring to all the effusive praise for our heroic leadership.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congress is still more concerned about the Hong Kong Freedom Fighters than the assault on the First Amendment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Philly852: I'm still shocked so many people have no clue that health passports are being rolled out globally, and when they are told it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @covid_clarity: There are a total of 237 people in the hospital with covid-19 in Minnesota, a state of 5.6 million.  That's about 1% of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Floridians are currently experiencing a severe case of Stockholm's Syndrome, but they're not going to tell you that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CelestineBee: So its been about a year since we saw videos circulating of people dropping down in the middle of the street in Wuhan wit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianmSC: Has anyone asked Fauci why he was giving maskless press briefings to a maskless crowd, surrounded by maskless people all throug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IAmTheActualET: People with masks in their profile pics and bios are going to have to find other ways to broadcast their self-perceived]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh, really...?  Because all of the available science says they're lying. https://t.co/LZZ8PImTuw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gummibear737: Dr. Sucharit Bhakdi Interview Summary: -According to Oct 2020 WHO Bulletin, C-19 is about as deadly as the flu -Less leth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally, some good news. The mask mandates were never backed by science, and never should have been implemented.  Now it's time to start asking @GovRonDeSantis to follow suit and fully #ReOpenFL with no mask mandates and no restrictions! https://t.co/kjNhU2a3EV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: Texas now open 100%.  No masks.   Time for other Governors to do the same.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: For those who are fighting masks in schools:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drscott_atlanta: Can someone show me the study that shows wearing a mask made of any material from the front door of a restaurant to yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EWoodhouse7: Minos in Naples, Florida tells it like it is: we arent doing the mask thing or spacing tables far apart.   You dont lik]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KenMcCarthy: The amount of money the Feds spent to buy off NY CoVid victims families by paying for funerals $2 billion. The amount they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: A second @nytimes article quotes doctors who say the mRNA technology used in #COVID #vaccines may cause immune thrombo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccines are SO safe that you're not allowed to talk about how safe they are.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>