<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@haroldthimbleby @jljcolorado Make one for me? TY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shikta_das Of course. Am feeling rotten today but dm me your email and Ill send word doc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hssood: Webinar 2 of series - Hospital and ICU Management of COVID19 with leading experts - please share and help spread the word @Sona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Thatquaratined1 @MichaelPaulEdw1 @IndiaCOVIDSOS Dm me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @axelheitmueller: What exactly does this mean for gyms and cinemas @trishgreenhalgh ie they all claim to have enhanced cleaning of air c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really important thread. Why AGPs are not AGPs and some non AGPs are AGPs. https://t.co/hyJZ7EMadA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Study of children (&lt;20) and transmission, using data from Israel. All members of house tested (PCR).  --&gt; susceptibility of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/3OeFgjF1k7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FeelGoodPage11: "I'm not crying, you're crying."  https://t.co/8b8IsZHEwD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@doctorcaldwell @CarolynFahm @DrAnsuMRCGP @AliRacaniere @Aaliya_UK @Aaisha_Saqib @docwas @aayshacader @shahnaz_mh @shutcake @_araoof @sailor424 @griffglen @OpsProf @j59dd @BrennanSurgeon @RanaAwdish @DrUmeshPrabhu @PeteGordon68 @wolvesboy @vincentconnolly @ETSshow @DrGrumble @IamBonglie @JohnLauner @SafetyCarm @dr_shibley @AndrewElder @Trisha_the_doc Well there's the Summary Care Record...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@irenep671 no, shoudl I just send it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSelvarajah sourdough starter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfSarahCowley @Kaumee @DrDAHatfield Let me know who else needs unblocking!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolynFahm @doctorcaldwell @DrAnsuMRCGP @AliRacaniere @Aaliya_UK @Aaisha_Saqib @docwas @aayshacader @shahnaz_mh @shutcake @_araoof @sailor424 @griffglen @OpsProf @j59dd @BrennanSurgeon @RanaAwdish @DrUmeshPrabhu @PeteGordon68 @wolvesboy @vincentconnolly @ETSshow @DrGrumble @IamBonglie @JohnLauner @SafetyCarm @dr_shibley @AndrewElder @Trisha_the_doc ugh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People who said we should have put precise numbers on our #CovidRiskChart - we did, in this new paper. I played a very minor role, the aerosol experts led this.  https://t.co/qR3odzdvNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolynFahm @doctorcaldwell @DrAnsuMRCGP @AliRacaniere @Aaliya_UK @Aaisha_Saqib @docwas @aayshacader @shahnaz_mh @shutcake @_araoof @sailor424 @griffglen @OpsProf @j59dd @BrennanSurgeon @RanaAwdish @DrUmeshPrabhu @PeteGordon68 @wolvesboy @vincentconnolly @ETSshow @DrGrumble @IamBonglie @JohnLauner @SafetyCarm @dr_shibley @AndrewElder @Trisha_the_doc well I am stroppy, especially when septicaemic, but I didn't invent my ADR...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kaumee @ProfSarahCowley @DrDAHatfield done - sorry! following her now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@irenep671 He's busy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikkiKF: Can someone help me offer @trishgreenhalgh a #gujarati translation please?   #COVID19India https://t.co/Fbxb9OuBBl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Orla_Hegarty: #Covid19 Poorly ventilated, heavy exercise, high occupancy, no mask (such as a gym) ... the infection risk starts ~immed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SouthAsianHF: Join SAHF @AHSNNetwork @LWNurses for our first in a series of UK-India #COVID19 webinars, Wednesday 5th May 8:30 IST/4pm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GYamey @MartinStott65 this is the guy you need to do the foreword to your magnum opus on masks (if I wasn't already doing it)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Liz_ORiordan purple asparagus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actual science. https://t.co/1YOxIKevM7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SajaAlNahar We have Arabic thanks! May need more...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trishgreenhalgh: This is a humanitarian emergency. The Covid-19 pandemic is out of control in many countries. A key priority is PREVENT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone got the actual science on this? https://t.co/1DGnDeR6sq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive signed up. https://t.co/LzABC1OCAD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two languages from Philippines: CEBUANO (thanks @MichaelPaulEdw1 and partner) and TAGALOG https://t.co/q37k33qT8a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof Raina MacIntyre has done stunning work in this pandemic. Well done on the award!  https://t.co/QUDDM1AImK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mjhegde @pash22 @oncology_bg Do please DM me your email! THANKS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's the end of an auld sang: Farewell to the NHS market [in England]  Calum Paton (left-leaning professor of politics/policy) at his cantankerous best.  https://t.co/gGqciCQoe3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Orla_Hegarty We have Welsh! https://t.co/ppmFusISdV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Orla_Hegarty: #EdChatIE #Schools #GaelScoil #Covid19  an bhfuil aon mhinteoir /gaeilgeoir ann ar mhaith leis seo a aistri? https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TAMIL, thanks to @BasuNephro https://t.co/ye150KcH0o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @xkcd: Types of Scientific Paper https://t.co/crpSNv9Er5 https://t.co/ZOJYH6xyhF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hssood: Help us spread the word to colleagues in India - series of webinars for learning  sharing NHS experiences - first one on NHS C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @luxurygite: @trishgreenhalgh I imagine youve seen this but just in case its an excellent explainer for us non-doctor/scientists !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChitraEndocrine @parthaskar Always need to balance risks and benefits]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDlbcl: French health authorities formally issue advice about ventilating public indoor spaces (especially schools and universities) an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oiioxford: It's our 20th birthday today!   Find out more about our story so far:  https://t.co/X7jH2NueZK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FARSI https://t.co/WTUKu6dJJf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@salehpirouzi Someone got in first! THANKS https://t.co/zs9njbI95J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeremyFarrar May the fourth be with you and yours!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@axmthompson The trials were all same doses, but going by first principles any vaccine will do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mishkab risk outdoors is very low unless you INHALE air that someone else has EXHALED - hence rallies where poeple are chanting are risky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@somedayadoctor Excel is very draughty and high ceilings so I reckon you'll be OK. Good luck in exam!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aayshacader yes please - DM me your email (actually may have Bengali, will hunt)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@somedayadoctor Depends on ventilation and whether vaccinated but yeah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ARABIC [have had a request for a new translation into Urdu in Arabic script - anyone fancy doing that?] https://t.co/iZUbjX8RUf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatAdeney @AliRacaniere @parthaskar OK will try]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatAdeney No but I think most people who speak Urdu can read Punjabi. Need advice on this! @AliRacaniere @parthaskar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mishkab You're right, risk increases with inverse of distance. But the virus is airborne so after 20 minutes or so indoors in a small room, the physical distancing issue becomes less important than ventilation!  For fleeting contacts, distance is more key.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wirebird50 OW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PORTUGUESE (may need tweaking for S America - please let me know) https://t.co/M3z1OWYCHJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SPANISH https://t.co/eu59n2aOV3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ODIA https://t.co/zIwaKMXlhY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEPALI https://t.co/rYAcQx2I91]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MALAYALAM https://t.co/2VYdIHYkpE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PUNJABI https://t.co/uqOiJTwNgO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HINDI https://t.co/HZDewNpk09]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's our #CovidRiskChart in South Asian and South American languages: I will post English first then other versions in this thread. Track me down if you want to translate this. https://t.co/6PQW1pkXe8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgurdasani1: Our joint letter by &gt;20 scientists &gt;400 parents/students  Education unions to Gavin Williamson asking that govt follow da]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kit_Yates_Maths: Our open letter to Gavin Williamson asking for the government to continue to follow data and not dates with regards to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @martinmckee: Clinical outcomes and risk factors for COVID-19 among migrant populations in high-income countries - our new systematic re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfJuneG You don't fancy "mixed-sex" in that building?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK-India Covid-19 webinar  on home oxygen monitoring.  Wednesday 5th May 4-5pm UK time, 8.30-9.30 pm India Standard Time. Please disseminate this free webinar to your medical colleagues in India - it could be lifesaving at this dreadful time.  https://t.co/RKWKYfpMqO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoyceLauNews: More harassment of female academics like @MicrobiomDigest for calling out shoddy #research. Complete w/ childish taunts a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mzeetodd: VERY IMPORTANT THREAD.  I Cannot overemphasize how important this research is concerning the how the pandemic develops from h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NicKeaney: WHY COULDNT WE FEED THE SCHOOL CHILDREN THEN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LABailey: Please read this thread by @trishgreenhalgh on what we now *KNOW*  about how transmission of the COVID-19 virus SARS-CoV 2 do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Special issue of the Journal of Health Care for the Poor and Underserved on 'TechQuity' (equity in tech) - some interesting-looking papers  https://t.co/tpPrRBUVPG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoWolffBSG Langue... Parole]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ryoungprout PS It sounds warm(ish) but I got close to hypothermia in a full wetsuit a week ago (temp of water was 10.7 but air was 2 and wind was whipping - stayed in too long).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ryoungprout 10.1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: 1/ COVID-19 has "anisotropic" infection:   Despite 100 times LOWER dose, monkeys infected by SARS-CoV-2 thru aerosols deve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jacqui_gath Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfSomashekhar Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OrthopodReg: This is the best one yet. Hands down.   Because its funny.   And also true. So true it actually makes me really very angr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cdavidnaylor: Great thread by @trishgreenhalgh cf Lancet paper w/ @dfisman. Per (sorry for self-reference):  https://t.co/ZYeD8yR3px):]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Orla_Hegarty: @trishgreenhalgh here are 50 reported #COVID19 super-spread events, all plausibly explained by virus build-up in ~prevent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And my response to critics here: https://t.co/WcGZHW22mV  30/end  (PS at NO POINT in this thread have I said we should stop washing our hands).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our paper again here: https://t.co/ZOY0lXx2VJ  29/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally, if the virus is airborne, health and care workers in infectious settings should be supplied with higher-grade PPE including respirator masks for ALL activities. There are several ongoing court cases. I predict the HCWs will win.  28/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the virus is spread mainly by the airborne route, we need to -Encourage people to go outdoors -Pay attention to ventilation (dont use air-con) -Reduce time spent indoors -Avoid crowds -Keep physical distance -Wear well-fitting, high-quality masks whenever indoors 27/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have a humanitarian emergency. WHO is the leading international organisation for health. Its still pussyfooting on the question of airborne transmission. Based on current WHO guidance, many HCWs around the world are being denied high-grade PPE. 26/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People advising the WHO, and some who claim to speak for WHO, are saying this is all nuance, and we should stop fighting each other and that aerosol scientists are trying to further their own careers. This is gaslighting. 25/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World Health Organisation got it wrong back in March 2020. They rejected the advice of aerosol scientists offered a year ago. Theyre now saying that aerosol transmission can occur in certain situations, by which they mean (mostly) medical AGPs.  24/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smell the garlic on someones breath. You dont want to be close to them do you? But you can still smell it across the room. Washing your hands wont help here. Scrubbing surfaces wont help. But opening the window will. 23/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So talking about close-range transmission confuses two different modes of transmission. Yes, we need to keep physical distance. No, thats not only (or even mainly) to reduce droplet transmission, its to reduce AIRBORNE transmission. 22/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A key point: close-range is not a route of transmission. We all know the virus is transmitted mostly through close contact. AEROSOLS are transmitted mainly by close contact, but they ALSO travel longer distances in the air. 21/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres a previous thread by my co-author @jljcolorado which goes into more detail on some of the science: https://t.co/gGUFHqpt4C  20/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The signs all pointed to the virus being airborne right back in early 2020, but (perhaps because of a dire shortage of PPE), the World Health Organisation and other bodies confidently denied this. https://t.co/LQLsEvbpi0  19/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EVIDENCE #10: ABSENCE OF EVIDENCE THAT OTHER ROUTES OF TRANSMISSION ARE DOMINANT. The evidence for droplet or fomite transmission is weak. These routes likely occur but unlikely to be *dominant*. https://t.co/R3S69VaalZ 18/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EVIDENCE #9: ABSENCE OF DISCONFIRMING STUDIES. We looked hard, and we didnt find a SINGLE study which offered evidence against airborne transmission. If airborne transmission didnt happen, it would surely not be too hard to disprove it?  17/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EVIDENCE #8: TRANSMISSION BETWEEN CAGED FERRETS VIA AIR DUCTS. Yes I know, animal models. But this isnt a claim that human physiology is same as ferret physiology. Its saying *the only way this could have happened* is AIRBORNE. https://t.co/1yYHsKK857 16/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EVIDENCE #7: SARS-COV-2 FOUND IN AIR DUCTS. In a hospital, the virus is sucked out in the ventilation system and cultured from the ducts and filters. Theres only one way it could have got there: AIRBORNE.   https://t.co/VSUePK6dKI 15/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same team (Lednicky et althese people are the *world experts* on capturing airborne viruses) also isolated SARS-CoV-2 virus from clinic rooms: https://t.co/3I33Druq2V 14/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EVIDENCE #6: VIABLE VIRUS HAS BEEN FOUND IN AIR. Its hard to catch airborne virus so not all studies are positivebut the black swan has been seen, not once but several times. eg this study of virus in a CAR. https://t.co/9BqmryoVFH 13/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indeed, in that case, the judge accused the so-called expert of using "false arguments" and "fallacies", and another expert for being unaware of key scientific developments in his field when testifying.  12/]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>