<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndrewLawton @RachaelHarderMP @karen_vecchio Someone is losing his cool and control as people start to question his Bill- maybe he knows he has been caught lying and trying to shut down free speech?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ImDarrenDunn2: .@JustinTrudeau @fordnation @celliottability @Sflecce   Mortality in children aged 0-14 was 18.57% above the 5 yr averag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nationalpost What is wrong with people commenting on here saying that this is terrible messaging. You dont want a second, non-biased opinion? People need to calculate their risks and that means having all the information.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brianlilley @erdocAA Refreshing to see someone not parroting fox approved talking points. People need to be informed and gage their own risks, you might feel that a vaccine is needed for you but someone else has a low chance of dying from covid but a predisposition to blood clots.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: WHO is going to stop the @WHO?  Even a vaccinated population wouldn't get us back to "normal" as @DrTedros indicates in thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation Why dont you just kill us all to save us from getting covid and having a 99.7% chance of surviving it? Oh wait you are doing that- Do you ever think that locking us down for months has caused our immune systems to weaken thus more people are in the ICU? #covidiot #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferSey: And dont get me started on loss of life years due to lost education. How many tens of thousands wont graduate high schoo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferSey: "Severe disruptions in health services due to the COVID-19 pandemic may have resulted in an additional 239,000 child and m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rayargyle Not sure why you are tagging me on this but it seems like Alberta has quite a lot of smart people. Why dont you stay home Ray? You cant control anyone but yourself, others have different opinions and thats okay.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ddos1271 @Australia @ScottMorrisonMP Who is dying? The average death rate in the country is within a year of  the average age of death for covid. What about all the people dying due to missed diagnosis and mental health issues. Covid is not even a top ten killer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BarrettWilson6: Wow! https://t.co/05IeG9ccxu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@janephilpott @CANImmunize How do these types of people make it to be advisors? Do they lose their minds and souls once they get a taste of power and being able to control millions? I see a French Revolution type of thing happening in Canada if this path continues. Canadians are slow to anger but they will]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CTVKitchener Dont be #fakenews. Its not the pandemic but #governmentlockdowns that have caused this, which ironically further adds to the severity of covid since exercise is essential for reducing risk of contracting and dying from covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlobalNational @globalnews Hahaha who would have thought that these ridiculous non-laws wouldnt stand a chance in court. They gov doesnt even want to open the floodgates because once one goes through court and gets deemed an infringement of rights, imagine the 10000s additional cases and class actions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesManson6263: @janephilpott No. A yellow card stays in your wallet and cannot be hacked. A customs agent can glance at it and move o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WeHaveNoRights2 The vaccine resistant covid that Doug keeps blabbing about. Just in case that happens, you should let the government protect you by locking you in your home forever.  Also this allows rich people to travel in peace and we still reduce the overall carbon footprint. Yeyyy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CTBird6 @HeadSpaceSpace1 @BogochIsaac @rubiconcapital_ Do you know yellow fevers mortality rate? If you get a severe case its up to 50%, overall it is about 5% (and that is with current medical treatments). You are comparing that to 0.3% covid death rate. Plus only a handful of equatorial countries require it. Hope that helped!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdithyaR_YXE @digitaltincan @BogochIsaac @rubiconcapital_ I am pretty sure people illegally crossing the border to live here arent being asked for their vaccine papers before entering. Plus the vaccines required are usually for devastating diseases with mortality rates in double digits, not for 99.97% survival rate, flu like virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BogochIsaac @rubiconcapital_ What if they have immunity from previous infection as according to Nature, it actually produces an immune response even 6 months after infection and of note its due to non-S proteins, which could mean natural infection is superior to vaccines https://t.co/YUw7AGri6A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thealczervik1 @AlexBerenson Its like someone telling you to find a person by giving you a picture of their arm. vaccine only focuses on one protein of the virus (spike protein). Your immune system upon seeing the real virus, will remember and attack multiple proteins of the virus=better immune response]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also it clearly shows that people retain immunity to #covid even if they were asymptomatic. So this #vaccine is the only thing that gives #herdimmunity is an outright lie. #science #VaccinePassports @Milhouse_Van_Ho https://t.co/YUw7AGri6A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to this Nature paper that looked at immunity of naturally infected people 6 months after infection- the majority of CD4+ and CD8+ T cells were activated by non-S viral epitopes. That means that vaccines using S protein are not as potent as natural infection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Australia once again shows their love of authoritarian measures and lack of empathy. 5 years in jail for a citizen coming back from India? No one should look at that country and think of them as a success when it comes to #covid measures. #Australia @ScottMorrisonMP https://t.co/pJTcGUVSag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JPLuisi1: The Nazis came to power in Germany while holding only 230 out of 608 seats in the Reichstag.  The next time someone tells you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GoyerBarbara @Evan00167980 @globalnews Essential travel that doesnt require quarantining at all, happens far more so nothing is going to change even if you make non essential people quarantine for a month at a hotel. #think you #covidiot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@globalnews Essential travel with no quarantine necessary still persists by 1000s of truckloads and planes everyday. This hotel-pretend-we-are-doing-something quarantine thing is as useless as the last few brain cells #trudeau and some of the people on here have left]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@anthonyfurey @anthonyfurey On the bright side, once #BillC10 passes they wont have to put out these types of warnings since anyone speaking out publicly against government mandates will be shut down on social media. Canada is becoming a scary place. #canada #cdnpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oracle of Canada? #lockdown #Ontarioshutdown #cdnpoli #canada https://t.co/I0AlOzEcHY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@globalnews Funny how its happening more as more young people get vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Well as long as its not passports  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nationalpost They continue to uphold their promise to be the most transparent government (sarcasm)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FerretKeto @thegamedesigner @AlexBerenson @pfizer Actually you can still die from covid even if you tested negative twice  https://t.co/lLPOQGbqbV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: This weeks VAERS update also contains two reports of healthy teenagers who died after receiving the @pfizer vaccine - a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ONThealth @ONgov It was not rigorously tested, and it was rushed through by Helath Canada as the final clinical trials do not conclude until 2022/2023. By lying about this you are not allowing people to give informed consent to the vaccine. #COVID19 #COVID19Vaccine #ontario #onpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@constans @robinmonotti2 Why are you being such an anti-vaxxer Dean? If the vaccine works then the vaccinated will be fine and the un-vaccinated will die, right? But your fear of unvaccinated folk makes it seem like you think vaccines dont work....or you just like to discriminate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Boss_Hos @RoonilWazlib02 @constans @woman_phd @robinmonotti2 @EmmanuelMacron You stay current. That was never claimed by trials but by reducing severity of your symptoms it means that you are less likely to transmit it to others as you will be asymptomatic. However, that contradicts the lies about asymptomatic transmission being possible...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Roman_Baber @fordnation This is so insane. Covid is here to stay and variants will be around for a long time. Will @fordnation shut the airport down for 2 years? 5 years? When would it end?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: 22 UK Covid deaths in the past 24 hours (deaths for any reason within 28 days of a positive test). 450 UK cancer dea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is this amazing journalist? Can we get more of them?? #BillC10 https://t.co/blqtcPFMsJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cpso_ca This is a authoritarian, anti-science statement to make and all you did was cause further distrust in your guidelines. Forcing your physicians to be robots who parrot your stance or face disciplinary actions makes us think that you have something to hide. #canpoli #canada #COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@globalnews So if someone came to my house and went into my cabinets and chugged drano while I was in another room, it was my fault?? Or what if I accidentally startled them and they had a heart attack? Or I served them uncooked chicken from takeout and they died from salmonella infection?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope people start seeing #msm for the #fakenews that they are. She was negative for #covid but they are trying to really push the angle of that is the cause of death. Maybe if they run the test 50 more times they can finally get a false positive? #COVIDIOTS #COVID19 #canpoli https://t.co/RFI7vhmN5a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MattAgorist: And people wonder why questioning vaccine safety is met with such extreme censorship. $157 billion buys a lot of Facebook]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Translation@ "!!! The Ministry of Health in Sweden has officially declared the PCR test NOT SUITABLE for determining contam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeldersRoosje: @APosoukh @MooniShines @FatEmperor https://t.co/HypZlts06A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Wtf? "Covid-21" ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Roman_Baber: Hey Doug  Christine,  Stop pretending this isn't happening. We have a mental health pandemic. A pandemic you created with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#canada and #ontario are really lost. Drove through my suburb and everyone outside is wearing masks even though there is plenty of space. Kids walking around and cycling with masks everywhere #childabuse #covidiots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DiverFiji @henrymcmaster I dont know what world you live in, but here on earth we do still live with TB and polio. TB still kills- in 2019 it killed 1.4 million people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Golden_Pup: Ontario is reporting 27 deaths from COVID today.  Just 11 of the deaths reported today are linked to cases reported in the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kristen_lindop @bahaay81 @CTVNews My entire career is based on science and I wont be taking it. I have taken the time to read everything and have weighted my risks. Mumps/rubella.etc vaccinate me up but not for flu-like covid with an emergency use approved vaccine. But I also dont judge others for their choices]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This goes against science. So why should we believe anything that government and their agencies say? You have no one to blame but yourself for believing people who lie so obviously. Even the EU allows people who had covid or were vaccinated to get passports https://t.co/AQrKNMghOY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow @CPHO_Canada that is some authoritarian shit here. How did this woman ever make it as the head of public health?? @randyhillier @Milhouse_Van_Ho https://t.co/r3T5uwRR95]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashley88817465: 3 years ago before covid19 was on the planet, the seasonal flu overwhelmed hospitals and surgeries postponed. WOW. so c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @net_nuance: Do masks work? Viral immunologist Dr. Byram Bridle performs a simple experiment. #Masks #masking #Science #covid https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@friendlyinsc @AmericanMom4bz @brianuhlig @bethanyshondark @AlexBerenson Do you know how a stroke happens? One main reason is a blockage, like A CLOT! Vaccines can cause clots so there is no evidence that a vaccine didnt cause this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alisa252525: The benefit of lockdown, therefore, was the avoidance of this extra 22,333 years of lost life. However, the cost of lockd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Metabo_PhD: Presented without comment.  #cdnpoli #onpoli #Ontario #Canada #fraud #scam #news #Accountability https://t.co/p7j475bgpm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ha #BillGates now doesnt even want to pretend that he is doing this to help people. I respect him more for admitting it instead of acting like he is some good guy when he was in this for the money. https://t.co/VviyC1Rh9C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I only now understand why #HydroxyChloroquine and #Ivermectin are not being allowed for treatment. Emergency use approval for vaccines would be revoked because an alternative treatment would be available!!! #COVID19 #scamdemic  https://t.co/BMZEe1gmWm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Roman_Baber @celliottability @COVIDSciOntario @fordnation There should be a rule, if you dont answer the question-$1000 fine. This is beyond ridiculous. She might have as well just sang a Celine dion song because it would have answered as much as her answer did]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hillsje @JohnMcEwen21 @zchagla @BogochIsaac Natural infection is just as good as a vaccine. In fact with natural infection your body can produce antibodies/memory cells for several parts of the virus, the vaccine does it for just the spike protein. Seriously educate yourself]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@no_maiden @A1RON1R @LeslieYoung @DFisman @BogochIsaac Not true]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeslieYoung @DFisman @BogochIsaac Well yes it is. According to CDC 30k/200k cases die each year due to yellow fever. Covid is at 0.05%. Maybe we should have vaccine passports for every single strain of the flu and SARS virus? It is like saying wear a helmet while lying in your bed vs driving a motorcycle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BogochIsaac Ha each country will have its own rules so this is meaningless EU talk. Germany I can see being asses about this, but countries like Greece and Hungary will likely say no. Plus I can skip Europe for a summer and go somewhere more free like China]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WanderingGirl10 @LaymanKarla @Leesa64901807 @NightShiftMD @CTVNews Math isnt your strong suit either. There is also the chance of getting covid to factor in. It depends on where you are but out of the entire population of ON less than 1% are positive at any given time. Norway did the calcs, concluded covid over AZ vax for better outcomes &lt;65]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vitevoila @celliottability Thanks for not giving one fact about your claim of Sweden situation being debunked.  Enjoy the sunshine if you can :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GonzoPhil And you are a selfish turd for trying to control others lives. Stay home  and get everything delivered- if others choose not to, thats their prerogative. People can gage their own risks, like they do with driving and drinking sugary, unhealthy beverages (ur photo)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vitevoila @celliottability No please tell me what brainwashed people think about Sweden. What has been debunked? Swedens deaths in 2020 were 98k compared to year before in low 90s. Also Florida and Texas opened way before 1st doses were administered to even a quarter of the pop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepThomasMassie: NOTHING TO SEE HERE...  Former director of CDC is now CEO of the foundation that funds FACTCHECK. orgs vaccine fact c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seeing little kids on their bikes driving by on a mostly empty lane with masks almost covering their eyes. You know what has a higher chance of killing your child than covid? A car that they cant see #COVIDIOTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soshuldistansin: @jasonlietaer Very worrying but a complete outlier. https://t.co/xAmQiqyr1l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vitevoila @insoplido86 @celliottability And there are examples of fully open regions with no hospitals being overwhelmed- Florida, Sweden...etc. Whats your point? Even WHO doesnt recommends lockdowns.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation Stop it Doug-It has been over a year. You guys did nothing and now you want to shut down after the variant is already here? Where are the extra hospital beds? What is being done to promote healthy immune systems? you have made people more susceptible by stopping exercising]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BonnieLCarter @l_stone The only entitled person is you- Judging and controlling people on how they want to live their lives. Stay home for the next 20 years if thats what you choose but a person going to see their sick family member or just for their mental health should be able to travel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vitevoila @insoplido86 @celliottability Nothing that shows variants are deadlier. Who is to say that this is not happening due to prolonged lockdowns and peoples immune system being destroyed from stress and lack of activity? A lot of other countries have opened up we are postponing surgeries in Ottawa with icu at 66%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vitevoila @insoplido86 @celliottability Same can be said about dying from covid for healthy &lt;50 year olds.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@celliottability Norways public of health calculated risks with serious adverse reactions due to AZ vaccine and covid and have said it is greater for AZ vaccine in those under 65. Show us your data!! https://t.co/3uSu7pYRR6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NightShiftMD Any comment on Norway public health saying the risk is greater in getting the AZ shot for under 65 olds than it is from covid virus? https://t.co/3uSu7pYRR6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CanadianPM Norway feels different. They calculates the risks and stated that the risk to AZ vaccine is higher than covid disease in younger people (under 65). Has @CPHO_Canada calculated the risks? Can we see the data?  https://t.co/3uSu7pYRR6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@globalnews Norway public health had a different take. The risks for under 65 are greater with AstraZeneca vaccine than covid disease https://t.co/3uSu7pYRR6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VeraEtches Good for you. I am going to go with Norways public health who say that there is a Higher risk associated withAstraZeneca vaccine than from COVID-19 disease for younger people https://t.co/3uSu7pYRR6 @Milhouse_Van_Ho @randyhillier @drmikehart]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow #Norway take on #astrazenecavaccine #COVID19Vaccine https://t.co/oYzmX8FbdN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wilder_kali @GovGone @VeraEtches Probably starts with A and ends with mazon. They do have a huge warehouse in Ottawa and are expanding further. Where else would you buy things if you cant in the store or via curbside pick-up?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matthew_mclaugh @StephanieKusie My grocery bill has gone up 20-25% since 12 months ago. I keep a budget and havent changed my eating habits, and am definitely paying more. My tax returns have not increased by that much (if at all). Such an easy to prove lie. The cost of everything has skyrocketed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeanmarcBenoit: If overall, Ontario ICUs are not overrun, there must be *some* areas that are overrun, where ICU occupancy is at 100%..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IAmTheActualET: Patients with heart attack symptoms and spinal injuries are being forced to wait as long as 5 hours. Emergency departme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kishkitsch: As a morally superior mom, today I will proudly ensure that my daughter:  - wears her graphene mask - sanitizes her hands w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patrickbrownont @Transport_gc Covid has definitely helped people see how many government officials are genuine idiots or tyrants. Imagine if this was a more deadly virus with maybe 1% or 10% death rate instead of barely 0.3%. What would they do then? Kill anyone who dares to cough?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Radtheragirl @docbrandon12 @Suzy4242 @AlexBerenson Well 85% asymptomatic covid is also not a scary stat, at my age survival is 99.997%. So why get a vaccine? I agree with things being blown out of proportion for #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlobalBC @globalnews So is she saying the experts are wrong?? Lol. They have more medical education and hands on experience than @PattyHajdu @CPHO_Canada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sanl @GlobalBC @globalnews Hopefully one day one of them will tell you to f-off or worse, as you deserve. Some people cant wear masks or is your safety all that matters, queen of the world? Just stay 6 feet away from them instead of being a Karen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: VAERS reports a breastfeeding five-month old infant has died of TTP - a rare clotting disorder linked to, yes, low platel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PublicHealthSD @ONThealth There are actually worrying cases of women miscarrying after covid vaccine and this was not part of the clinical trial. how can you as a public health even advertise this? Shameful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RosieBarton Already talking about booster shots  for next year and year after...So you are saying covid is the flu and will need yearly shots??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarnfan @DestroWod @KevN95 @TorontoStar You can still get and transmit covid after the shot. The shot protects you from getting very ill so if this person chooses to not get vaccinated you should be fine. Or do you not trust the vaccine?? This virus is here to stay and versions of it have been around before 2019]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TorontoStar At least 75%? I know Canadians have a follower mentality but that seems like a very high expected volume, when there is so much hesitancy and children shouldnt be getting the vaccine so it. Also there arent enough vaccines so 75% seems unattainable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy78 This girl is on a ventilator but also is able to perfectly do her make up (better than most healthy people can)and has the cleanest, glossiest hair after being bedridden for over 2 weeks??? And dont come at me, professional hairstylists wouldnt have been allowed in a covid ward]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@globalnews Sophie had covid. She is already immune.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PattyHajdu please dont talk about science if you fail to believe in #vitaminD, known to help strengthen immune system. Why are we letting these people make decisions for us #canada? https://t.co/IqjBK1KXhj]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>