<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_evelynrae: The video that got banned.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetUpESPN: .@Espngreeny is calling it right now: Washington will run away with the NFC East.  @nfldraftscout: "If you wanna talk about]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Washington_Wire: One draft analyst says put your money on Jamin Davis for defensive rookie of theyear https://t.co/CtaJpTwJvC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[pay attention  https://t.co/olK7fcCv1T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm in that 8% https://t.co/2CFOqtxFgO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mamabear_jones: Follow the money]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASimplePatriot: Black man brutally  attacks 2 Korean woman store owners in West Baltimore. https://t.co/haQe9Z6UKu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/XFN1Y1DMoY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gr33nbot: https://t.co/Om2esL9wrK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maybe60794885: And the SHAMING begins,.. That ain't LEADERSHIP,.. this is M4$$MURDR!  Biden Says People Unwilling to Get Covid Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CardinalConserv https://t.co/szhyczxTty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hell yeah we knew all along or at least since all 5 swing states stopped counting Ballots in the middle of the night but really didn't. https://t.co/aUtv70NcqR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheShuffleCast: Just so everyone is up to speed. We kick off tomorrow. And done in 30 is on the Julian calendar . So roughly still anot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wtf ? https://t.co/BxljG0PYPs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SebGorka: Does anyone know what Kamala does?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kshadyacct4:  FREEDOM!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We knew all along he told us about being president from his basement... https://t.co/rP9kfsamjy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MJGospel: https://t.co/iuUYWz0FZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KymC1019: There is Science and then theres that bullshit liberals make up and claim is science   -There are 2 genders -The flu didnt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thorsome1: Maricopa ballot audit is ESTIMATED to be approximately 15% complete. https://t.co/UCyEKQroZA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/cHGzyo4fcL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecryptob0t: https://t.co/sr0lpDFxtY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealTina40: Im in !!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: What if we find fraud so massive that we have no choice but to audit every county?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/nliHP9q7EX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today marks my 60th time around the SUN MAY THE 4TH BE WITH YOU..HOPE EVWRYONE IS HAVING A GREAT DAY https://t.co/rSymj0auvs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASoftstar: If someone is still judging you by your past  Then they aren't able to move forward with you  And it's time to move on witho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: Just in case other news distracted anybody last week  They dont plan on pricking kids though...right?  https://t.co/k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottAdamsSays: I cant stop looking at this picture.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ilSharko: Buenas Noches to the most amazing Patriotos in the world. I LOVE YOU WITH ALL OF MI HEARTO. Love and hug that beautiful Famil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArizonaAudit: This is the most comprehensive forensic election audit in the history of our galaxy! Everything from voter history and vo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If your alone tonight and don't have anything else to so ....GFY ....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dukewells: @GretchenInOK The DOJ has degenerated into a criminal organization, much like the CIA and the FBI.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatSecCNN: The Biden admin is considering using outside firms to track extremist chatter by Americans online, an effort that would expa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh I know he's going to be in TROUBLE for that saying... totally opposite of what it really is...the pattern has been set. https://t.co/hzvMvPhK0l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Own it, if your a lier your a lier ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArizonaAudit: THE AUDIT CONTINUES!! WE ARE GOING TO COUNT EVERY DAMN BALLOT!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sometimes a bitch ...welll just got to be a bitch. It's all good. https://t.co/vz5eaUR0wv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NewDayForNJ: Hey Barack @BarackObama STOP TRYING TO COERCE MY MINOR CHILDREN.  Its MY Right to choose what, when  if to discuss vacc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TPUSA: Wow if only someone had been saying this for OVER A YEAR...  #BigGovSucks #COVID19 #Lockdown https://t.co/SH4S0l2GwI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@citizenkawala @ButtercupThang 20 years old.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SexCounseling: The Big Lie and we all know it, they know it. https://t.co/Qr5BBySLe5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BOOM https://t.co/l5QXbN3hYK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @clking61: Hey tomorrow is May the 4th be with you...and it is my 60th time around thw SUN...may God be with you throughout your journey]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey tomorrow is May the 4th be with you...and it is my 60th time around thw SUN...may God be with you throughout your journeys  and I hope you wake up to all the lies and madness that you have been taught, QUESTION EVERTHING YOU HAVE BEEN TAUGHT. https://t.co/CldivTZ5cd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wa_kin_gup: https://t.co/1z8vjUlnub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brandy1024: I ended up with two heads and four arms after my vaccines. Is that normal?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eb454: The real story: 77% of Americans are still divided.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bullshit .....#TheBigLie https://t.co/ZHkhaWnDOC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BitcoinMagazine: BREAKING: EBAY INC CEO LOOKING INTO BITCOIN AS A PAYMENT OPTION - CNBC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: Who is the greatest President of your lifetime?  Mine is Donald J Trump.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDrGina: I saw 45 this weekend  he stated that he doesnt want to talk about 22 or 24 until 2020 is resolved TO THE SATISFACTION]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So what's the latest flag at the CIA building.....?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EscanorThe2nd: #TheBigLie https://t.co/GfgFXEzQMZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fortunately I have yet to have a covid swab a covid test and a covid vaccine and I'm doing just fine been all up and down the east coast so I don't wear mask now either they do not work..  SCIENCE proven, I am sick of their BullShit.... I sure hope you guys are waking up ....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DarrenPlymouth: Like everything else we are told to believe, it makes zero sense. https://t.co/R9RLgTSMhx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrMichaelBurkes: MAGA isn't dead.   MAGA is forever.   President Trump is the most influential President EVER!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CawthornforNC: We now know the CDC colluded with special interests to keep our children out of the classroom.   Swamp politicians don't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carolyn2813928: BOOM BOOMBOOMBOOMWelcome To Your New World....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gregkellyusa: WHATS GOING ON ?! BILL AND MELINDA GATES ARE GETTING A DIVORCE ?  WOW!!!!  Bezos RUINED it for all the other Billionaire]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/2EHZbYoFCy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @youngbiafra: I love it when Candace Owens triggers the left ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yeah and guess what ....YOU AINT and NEVER will be in the BIG CLUB.. personnelly I hope they all rot in HELL  https://t.co/qEQoueoZj0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck UNMASK EVERYBODY ....MASK DO NOT WORK ...SCIENCE PROVEN FACTS. https://t.co/HcbqoLfOmY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASoftstar Hell yeah but it's funny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SebGorka: Something happening at the CIA.   Road outside Langley entrance has been closed for at least 4 hours.   Local police divertin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RaheemKassam: She left him for his best friend  https://t.co/k53Miq8Y5f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeresaFreeThink: 1 Year Delta - Currently in Process.  https://t.co/9QseLeQFMS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @disclosetv: JUST IN - Now we have "bangs" and an ambulance arriving at the CIA HQ in McLean, Virginia.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolutely  https://t.co/wgdxxBobQw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: Catturd is CONFIRMED for Faith and Freedoms Conference in Dallas, Texas May 13-16!   GET YOUR TICKETS and as CATTURD Tak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So it seems things seem to be going all south for the Deep State Dems and all their agenda....Pay Attention to Maricopa County]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: WOW!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/1XP0JokBtI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: Why isn't anyone in sports media talking about DeShaun Watson and the 22 women who have accused him of sexual assault or h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RN_Destiny: ABC shows full support of dictatorship!  We need to shun those that refuse to get vaccinated   Shes an psycho-path that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: Is the UK going to ACCEPT lockdown 2021? It might go like this:  COVID21 turns up vaccine-resistant, a mutant hybrid sup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreitbartNews: Trashing AmericaTHATs the Democrat Party way! https://t.co/aDspKGuFrj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASimplePatriot: Officer Who Shot Ashli Babbitt On Jan. 6 Didn't Issue Warning First https://t.co/f6nGe9g3ks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaCherner: Ambulance arriving on the scene at CIA Headquarters after we heard 13 loud bangs that sounded like gunshots. https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kshadyacct4: Shots fired?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: We have it all!  Lets see what happens!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kshadyacct4: https://t.co/4toscMIWNi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They cheated and they KNOW they are caught they caught them all and they can not stop what's coming seems everything they try and do now BSCFIRED on them they are playing Chess by not like us we are 5D CHESS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BarnettforAZ: #TheBigLie and Maricopa County will be providing the proof very soon https://t.co/J0tMgAeldq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden stands with the DEVIL https://t.co/OPIZGSZFPG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRightMelissa: Bill  Melinda Gates are getting a divorce but the bigger news is what their foundation is being accused of around t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jmbenson1491: Running the same Joe ballots through the scanner, dead/illegal people voting, ballot harvesting, no signature verificatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sahouraxo: How are these two war criminals still walking free, but Julian Assange is languishing in prison for exposing their war crime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @The_Wizard_Me: @jmbenson1491 The comeback didn't happen until they halted counting in 5 states so that they could truck in enough fraud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @truths4_u: @jmbenson1491 https://t.co/BlPYpuJkIj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Thomas1774Paine: There Is No Shortage? Train Loads Of Lumber Stacked As Far As The Eye Can See https://t.co/ptftZuo2oP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArizonaAudit: Thanks for following the audit and helping us hit 30k. -AZ Audit Comms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bennyjohnson: BREAKING: Trump statement on Mitt Romney getting booed at the Utah Republican State Convention this weekend https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good Luck both should be seeing prison time for Crimes against Humanity at the very least also Mads Murder....#TheBigLie https://t.co/pwGVQN2zrO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SexCounseling: Wow, the trolls are coming out against President Trump and his supporters BIG TIME, we must be over the target!  #TheBig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who does this to children  Mr.Biden dies this  https://t.co/xAuAWVytXQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WTF...#TheBigLie and still spreading it.  https://t.co/lkjeyghAsC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emaysway: Derek Alexander May 2, 2021  5:38pm 8 lbs 5 oz  20 inches https://t.co/r5pSRnZkv8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CG__I7: Wake up America  https://t.co/TNfBn3i72q]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>