<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@rileydfarrar My Condolences to his Family! and I thank him for his service! God Bless!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader I want the President 80 Plus Million Voted for! President Donald Trump! Not this sham of a President! just saying that makes me throw up in my mouth! https://t.co/HpbBIBen7n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrissaccoccia1 Thank you Chris Sky for all you do ! and for being a Patriot and standing up for our Canadian Brothers and Sisters!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLeoTerrell That's OK Leo, Were gonna Replace all of them! with real Republicans!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@awarrior828 Yes that has been happening to me for the last 2 weeks! waking up way earlier than is even close to normal for me! and going to bed at say 1am. Something BIG is Coming! Praise God!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch "4.22.21 Scott McKay "Patriot Streetfighter"'s Interview w/ Dr. Sherry Tenpenny" on YouTube https://t.co/XLyCR2vI7t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WE all need to call the Legislatures and Tell them that's NOT Acceptable! #MattGaetz #lDonaldoTrumpo #AndyBiggs #LaurenBoebert  Please Help! Oregon Govoner Kate Brown Vetos Enough Votes to Recall her???????????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So Update from the DARK BLUE  State of Oregon, So We got Enough Signatures to Recall Our China Loving Govenor Kate Brown. So Guess What she does? She Veto's it? What? She can't do that right? But because she is Kate Brown She thinks she can do anything? Opinions?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Makes U wonder Dosen't it? lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Bitch is trying to cause more Riots!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jpgftw U only flipped it cheating! Well flip it back!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CollinYourbs @scdlcaramia @ArizonaAudit @MaricopaGOP @MaricopaDems @AZGOP @azdemparty @Arizona_LP @AZGreenParty Yes u?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oregon  Yes health care workers,  should be more supported! We all get less pay,  than a Bank manager! When we take care of people loved ones,  their comfort,  Giving Love,  Support,  and Happiness,  in their late years!. And it's just i unconcienable!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Folks don't give up! It's not even close to being over! This is a war! Good virses Evil! And God Always Wins! https://t.co/7HlPlVWvsH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@redpack57 @CortesSteve No Honey the fat lady hasn't sung yet! God always wins!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Yes We MAGA Nation will always have your back Matt Gaetz! We love you! Your a Patriot! Were still fighting right behind you! Always!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXPOSING THE GLOBAL LUCIFERIAN ORDER (Special Guest - Ms. Jessie Czebotar) https://t.co/tpQzO0blxn via @YouTube                       A Must see! Save our Children!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mel K, Ann Vandersteel, and Dr. Sharnael Shine Light on the Darkness  Humor on Chaos 3-28-2021 https://t.co/n6dqDC7aZV via @BitChute]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TXGXR @mikepompeo BS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Godschi04935684 @mikepompeo God has this Pray!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraScheetz1 @mikepompeo Your an idiot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@niawag1 @mikepompeo NO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FrankAmari2 @mikepompeo Really then why did God Choose Donald Trump For President? He's a Republican? Hmmmmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure so u say, you are all still in Office,  cheating is that how,  i didn't vote for  Any of you! https://t.co/70pn18T6gW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See my review of The Autosmith @SureCritic https://t.co/kHvb7qefpq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FantauzziRuben @ilDonaldoTrumpo Love this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo And We LOVE you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch "You'll Never Look At Your Pants The Same Way After This Tiktok: Officialmikehammer" on YouTube https://t.co/BCFlDA4mO1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CAFinUS https://t.co/LYRQlMqq6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Good Karma! That's what Woke gets u!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch "Lol our President Donald J Trump he is really good at dance lol    " on YouTube https://t.co/8HZK6rHnDq ilDonaldo Trumpo still dancing after a long night of Fiesta!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz We will all be fighting together again soon Matt Gaetz! Still Holding the Forkin Line here in Oregon! God always Wins We love you Patriot!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JennaEllisEsq Us Patriots are still Strong Jenna! still holding the Forkin Line here in Oregon Waiting! All is Well! Have faith, God Always wins!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez Are all you Dems Scared of the Boogie Man? Maybe if you quite Screwing people you wouldn't always think someone was after you? Just a thought! Wouldn't worry so much about us Patriots, we are pretty Peaceful Spirits. But now God and Judgment day, is another?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeaderMcConnell A bit late McConnell to convince us that you give a Crap, unless it fits your China Agenda!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley Merkley your a Blooming Idiot! Whats the matter, Pissed off cause requiring ID for Voting make it too hard for you Cheating Democrats to Win?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 @13AliWeatherton Oh my gosh another False Flag! when will this STOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OOOOOO I drove thru town this evening, here in Oregon, finally a beautiful day no Cem Trails! and Guess whata? Everyone wasa Maska Freeo! YUUUUPPPPPEEEEEE Are the Sheepe finally wakin up? OOMYGOSH! I was hollering out my windows thanking everyone for NOT wearing the CRAZIO Masko https://t.co/gXVcnYNozH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LandRoverUSA @JohnMayer @TheAtlantic OOOOOOO I want ONE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An animated GIF https://t.co/AQ5Q4yFtf9 via @imgflip ilDonaldo Trumpo Hope you like my Wino Glass! want a Sipo?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TONYMAC55208788 @ilDonaldoTrumpo 3 of my favorite Patriots! Fiesta! Cheers! https://t.co/DZG6lKjtYF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo That Pelosio makes me throw upo in my moutho! https://t.co/Ff4LYhWnVo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo @Stephan05593081 Never have I ever Turned my back on a Wonderful President Like our President Trump, like so many of our Damn Rino's have!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo @MrsDelgado2U oh yea their Crunchy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[lol I have peeedo undero a Semio Trailero Whileo my CoDrivero waso asjustingo the Brakeso, Guesso Where my peeo wento? lol He holleredo! Hey U justo got meo Weto! it waso Warmo! https://t.co/4e5yDz8but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo @Lonewolfy777 jjjjaaaaaaa that will buurnnno  thhhe eyeso righto outo youro heado!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo I Love and MISS you ilDonaldo Trumpo! We'll all be back together soon! Lets go have a Festive time! https://t.co/M58pDwbkfv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No Oregon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ltdp22 @NRA Research your facts, before you start spouting on her to people, its not law abiding citizens who shoot people on the streets, its Criminals, and the Government, those 3 letter agencies know one wants to talk about.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NRA Some BS More Biden tearing down of our Constitution! It begins! its not us Law abiding citizens that shoots people in Walmart, folks, 1 by one they are gonna start taking away our rights!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernardKerik @VP What a Disrespectful Bitch!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArmyChiefStaff Semper Fi Soldier!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Lock her up! They all need to be in jail!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo @JennaEllisEsq @realDonaldTrump We Love you Donaldo Trumpo!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CortesSteve Pushed by your Leftwing Agenda! 1 World Order, the more Chaos the better! right? Close down the Economy, Small businesses, shut down, never to reopen, a virus, no worse than a common cold, then the Killer Vax. Steal the Election. but guess what GOD ALWAYS WINS!! BYE! BYE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MamaFisher1920 @mikepompeo So much BS Stop  listening the the Lie news! Pull your head out of the Sand, Turn to God, and away from the Evil Luciferian Left, which is obviously who you r listening to! We'll all Pray for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CindyKendrick11 Shes in gitmo Singing like a Canary!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TracieLVaughn Another RINO to jail you should go!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: PRESIDENT DONALD J. TRUMP delivers remarks at CPAC 2021. https://t.co/fF59WsCaUU via @YouTube    Starting soon!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KHOUmelissa Way to support The real President MAGA Trump! Thank YOU Patriots!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please help if you can! https://t.co/uPVlTdTBLT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fired for my Belief in God over not wearing a Mask https://t.co/1YaCl0vtER]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill Ty Senator Josh Hawley!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hollyjayewiley @TrumpWarRoom @DonaldJTrumpJr lol Is She Fing Nuts?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise thank you Mr. Scalice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MIGOP To Jail she goes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanScavino Dosen't look like President Trump does it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2.24.21 Patriot Streetfighter POST ELECTION UPDATE #56: Alliance moves o... https://t.co/ld6xqxcLkF via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EYE OF THE STORM. Juan O Savin teams up with Navy Seal Michael Jaco. Mil... https://t.co/62HRe5qEYG via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2.23.21 Patriot Streetfighter POST ELECTION UPDATE #54: Moves and Counte... https://t.co/7soXbf3wHV via @YouTube                                                                                 A Must LIsten!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mel K  Rob Really Back From LV Share Thoughts on The Sound of Freedom 2-23-2021 https://t.co/IkBREJJqDn via @BitChute  Please Watch and SHARE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr Thank you Justice Thomas! We understand you can't fight the fight alone!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OANN We Love you President Donald J Trump! and what the Left dosen't seem to understand is the more they try and Fight against us the stronger it makes us! We are still holding the line! and we will never back Down!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden  Happy  Birthday: President Donald John Trump! We Love you! See you for good soon! https://t.co/UEwATxkkAC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#silversqueeze I now have a total of 100 Ozs!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ROB ANDERSON DISCUSSES LATEST UPDATES WITH NICHOLAS VENIAMIN [mirrored] https://t.co/QHUOFSvTtl via @BitChute]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenboebert Idiots!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/EhuzaV8gRJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Ya Think?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays Kiss Our Deplorable ASSES! He was AQUITTED AGAIN  IDIOT! Its not Trumpsters that Riot, and Burn down Cities! that is your friends Antifa, and BLM!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2.18.21 Scott McKay'S Powerful Interview of Former CIA Clandestine Ops O... https://t.co/MeVIZtlo9Y via @YouTube A Must Listen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@trish_regan I disagree he needs to go to Jail!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Thank you Mr. Vanderveen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ilDonaldoTrumpo lol! Too Funny! Just Sitting back enjoying the show!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/c5rrKCtycg    A   must read!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/c5rrKCtycg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PKcVMGme8K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@upington5 @DanScavino LOL Cry me a River!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanScavino Thank you Dan! Love you!  Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rothschildmd Are you related to the Rothschild  family involved in Banking?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/th8rbkrYuA Wake up! This is really going on! These are Babies!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenBobCasey ANTIFA! NOT TRUMP SUPPORTERS!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Definitely right! They all need to be replaced!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLeoTerrell True,  but time for President Trump to drop some Truth  Bombs!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/F4e6jM06qv                                                   This is not OK! Boycott ALL of these STORES!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/085qSoyGDv                                                  Everyone WAKE up! Get Mad! This is not OK! we all need to do something!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley Merkley you are gonna be Primaryed! you ARE NOT FOR THE PROPLE! YOU NEED TO GO!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bLjKYXb15A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ohv1qSV2k4  This Criminal needs to be Arrested  for Murder!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>