<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: 500% increase in COVID diagnoses on vaccination.   https://t.co/Ir3ub2y3FQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A safe vaccine does NOT kill people. Products which kill people are called POISONS. https://t.co/eQ8yLadKJG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Bill Gates UK rep wants Step 4 of the Road Map delayed. Oh, what a surprise.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: It breaks my heart to see that our governments are systematically abusing our children. Those responsible will hopefully be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am not "anti-vaxx" I am pro-treatment  anti-fear. https://t.co/jAfH9jYDrG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If we don't stop them they will stop us. https://t.co/5yeIHf5jSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: WHO is going to stop the @WHO?  Even a vaccinated population wouldn't get us back to "normal" as @DrTedros indicates in thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UsforThemUK: This week, we've seen in technicolour the utter disregard those in power have for children.   @phe_uk have admitted they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Monotti Protocol. Includes the Nobel Peace Prize nominated Zelenko Protocol https://t.co/jAfH9jH236]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Nobel Peace Prize Nominated Zelenko Protocol (linked to in the Monotti Protocol) https://t.co/gJtEx3tUrK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Cinema reopening dates around the world: latest updates Russia - OPEN At the beginning of 2021 97% of Russian cinemas had reopened, in 83 of the countrys 85 regions. There are still capacity restrictions ranging from 70% to 15% in half of open cinemas." https://t.co/QPv57KpjIv https://t.co/CRJow7vnFZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am not "anti-vaxx", I am pro-treatment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jack Last: 27-year-old British engineer dead 21 days after experimental AstraZeneca viral vector shot https://t.co/UuXvXZvBsn https://t.co/SgOTbXTCAw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Proud to call Dr Zelenko a friend. Banned from twitter. Think abt it. https://t.co/W92lfPdQHh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@headqueries Agreed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @leoniedelt: @Francis_Hoar Primary duty of all educators is safeguarding of the children. Not the staff. Not their coworkers or staff. T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drsimonegold: Dr. Vladimir Zelenko, an early adaptor and pioneer of the HCQ protocol, has been nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize.  This]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They don't work. Because they target 1 SARSCoV2 protein instead of 29, they don't target the protein responsible for replication, N protein. They increase severity of disease in an estimated 10% of recipients through ANTIBODY DEPENDENT ENHANCEMENT or ADE. https://t.co/AGHbSrfiwu https://t.co/gEcEM3yHrh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cordeliers: Prior to the coronafascist takeover, these exceptionally dangerous vaccines would long since have been banned in the US.  h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I even think I caught that Swine Flu. It was not much different to Covid19 to be honest: very high temperature, then you recover. Let the body do its work. Trust your body. Help it with nutrition  supplements. Antibiotics if need be. The right ones always cure pneumonia.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was around in 1976. Listen to the elders who remember. Share. https://t.co/a7M7KHGSTN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Mr Hoar [@Francis_Hoar] accepted that the girl did not have to wear a mask at school, but added that she was faced with a school environment in which the wearing of masks was enforced "aggressively". https://t.co/ZHxwk6i9BT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schoolgirl sues Sheffield school trust over mask-wearing https://t.co/ZHxwk6i9BT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANTIBODY DEPENDENT ENHANCEMENT or ADE 43,000 people Pfizer study.  At 0.1% prevalence, if the risk of ADE was 5% you would only see it in 2 patients in their study.... That risk would be presented as 2/43,000 and the vaccine would be considered "safe" https://t.co/zJssGJKoqW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This weeks data included three reports of deaths among teens under age 18, including two 15-year-olds and one 16-year-old who died unexpectedly from a blood clot 11 days after receiving her first Pfizer dose." https://t.co/2Scd5hA7RE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/779CQDzIwa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/X078ccwrFa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/T8hwEG3wYR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9pokgrG7tA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JnsP2iP8M2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/f9qbjSDrow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YNrdjrwDP7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jWXaRkf5YT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RN8dtgu5KT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YdGz9Bb45L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6wFdRsaorj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OPEN LETTER TO THE WHO "Dr. Shi Zhengli has stated that Wuhan Institute of Virology virus databases were taken  offline during the pandemic. However the key bat virus database was taken offline in  September 2019, three months before the official start" https://t.co/Wfgvrbz4oU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is Bill Gates trying to hide from the Indian people? https://t.co/0QpnUEaXxb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[INDIA: "a reportlisting a litany of quality problems with Bharat Biotechs manufacturing plant for its inactivated COVID vaccine, Covaxin. These problems included insufficient measures to ensure that the SARS-COV-2 virus was completely killed".. https://t.co/H5rC0JdN4N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: The reality of #lockdown in #Bengaluru. Is "lockdown" just for TV  news fear factor?  https://t.co/6C5GS8gzWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are newspapers in India pushing this implausible narrative of mutants evading PCR tests? What illnesses may they be covering up by calling them "negative Covid"? What did they roll out in last few months? Mystery.. https://t.co/UggNa9lyNN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are doctors in India pushing this implausible narrative of mutants evading PCR tests? What illnesses they be covering up by calling them negative Covid? What did they roll out in last few months? Mystery.. https://t.co/xFrQcsv6Jx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are they pushing this narrative of mutants evading PCR tests? What could they be covering up? What did they roll out in last few months? Mystery.. https://t.co/SdP86eii3y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["#Florida will fine any business or school $5,000 each time it requires a vaccine passport, or proof of COVID-19 vaccination, for entry or participation"  https://t.co/slVc7UAV54]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Didier Raoult: "The chance that a vaccine for an emerging disease will become a public health tool is close to zero. There may be surprises, but I'm skeptical." https://t.co/hFoLjxv80a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreedomIsrael_: The same fucking embarrassments the world over.  https://t.co/J2lvgF9dF0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's nothing nuts about vaxxing kids, it's the necessary step to implement the vaxx IDs. They could not care less if yours and other hundreds die. It's up to you to protect them and say NO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karma44921039: Reason for your next lockdown..wake up https://t.co/5fNNUjkum7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karma44921039:  https://t.co/OStNWtLvZ9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yogurt. Not gene modifications. https://t.co/0N3f0b8MDN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What have they done to us.. #NeverForget. https://t.co/7BddgcNdoa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wakeupfromcovid: The narrative of "the next one" is being manufactured in media as of NOW: same tactics as with "the previous one".  I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laworfiction =PULMONARY FIBROSIS https://t.co/sQ25zpKJl6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laworfiction: Revealed IN COURT:  neither school nor govt conducted ANY assessment of the risk to children of harms of masks  unchall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The entire planet has lost it. This woman has kept it together. https://t.co/ToKVW5IPLy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you believe the double triple mutant Indian variant that magically evades the PCR test scare story, rather than a wave of adenovirus jab adverse reactions, then I have a bridge in London I want to sell you. Good price.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[INDIA EXPLAINED IN TWO IMAGES. THE MUTANT IS THE ASTRAZENECA "COVISHIELD" ADENOVIRUS VECTOR + SPIKE https://t.co/f2AdMgyzMi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indian "third wave" solved. Next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: CONCLUSIVE PROOF THAT IT IS THE JAB. (A MUTANT WOULD TEST +) https://t.co/a67BIWs2T5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[INDIA: CONCLUSIVE PROOF THAT IT IS THE JAB. (A MUTANT WOULD TEST +) https://t.co/H5BiHHrC4j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[INDIA EXPLAINED IN TWO IMAGES. THE MUTANT IS THE ASTRAZENECA "COVISHIELD" ADENOVIRUS VECTOR + SPIKE https://t.co/f2AdMgyzMi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: The "mutant" isolated! https://t.co/2inl1RgVYG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check for yourself: https://t.co/zr8ZCUPiFF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: The mutant is "Covishield" (Astrazeneca): https://t.co/VnQeAK7quG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kevin_McKernan @prof_shahar "As the N protein sequence is much more stable than the spike, vaccines that include a component targeting the N protein are likely to be effective for longer." https://t.co/IFAdYl6eoj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As the N protein sequence is much more stable than the spike, vaccines that include a component targeting the N protein are likely to be effective for longer." https://t.co/IFAdYl6eoj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kevin_McKernan @prof_shahar "patients (n=23) who recovered from SARS possess long-lasting memory T cells that are reactive to the N protein of SARS-CoV 17years after the outbreak of SARS in 2003; these T cells displayed robust cross-reactivity to the N protein of SARS-CoV-2." https://t.co/yNVIllFBB2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kevin_McKernan @prof_shahar "The spike-based vaccine conferred acute protection in the brain only if combined with the nucleocapsid-based vaccine. https://t.co/ccdl2h246L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Didier Raoult, the worlds most cited infectious disease specialist says that the Pfizer vaccine has around 70% secondary effects, "never seen in before in a "vac_ine." https://t.co/fvrEp6MQOQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: #FarmersProtest rep: "Even if you say there is Corona, its not a pandemic. Because the govt stats that are coming, and the international stats that are coming,dont add up to what would or should be called a pandemic. In a pandemic [almost] everyone would have died" https://t.co/QPTJysIctu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: #FarmersProtest rep: "Even if you say there is Corona, its not a pandemic. Because the govt stats that are coming, and the international stats that are coming,dont add up to what would or should be called a pandemic. In a pandemic [almost] everyone would have died " https://t.co/iOQEvlx2lB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India: Whistleblower actor arrested for "vaccine misinformation". High court sets bail. https://t.co/1JxZlBZAUv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: In late 2020 a leader of the #FarmersProtest indicated the pandemic is being used to stop them. Now FF to April 2021. https://t.co/NfRJXneSrG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#INDIA: In late 2020 a leader of the #FarmersProtest indicated the pandemic is being used to stop them. Now FF to April 2021. https://t.co/NfRJXneSrG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One person's "misinformation" is another person's unshakeable truth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @elleprovocateur: In addition to "Bill  Melinda Gates revealed as largest private #farmland owners in US", #Microsoft "has launched a n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD  https://t.co/onBqEDidkK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mamasaurusMeg @threadreaderapp pls unroll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GreatGameIndia: THIS IS BIG  Officers from Epidemic Intelligence Service, a programme of US CDC will reach India soon for #COVID19 help]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cordeliers: From the memory hole: CDC censured by Indian government for funding bioweapons research on Indian soil without approval. ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cordeliers: "CDC was caught funding Karnatakas Manipal Center for Virus Research (MCVR) for secretly carrying out research on the leth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India: Whistleblower actor arrested for "vaccine misinformation". High court sets bail. https://t.co/1JxZlBZAUv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020: "India pulls up US agency for doing unauthorized Nipah virus research" https://t.co/ZzG9bS0sSD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2015: "To examine the emergence potential (the potential to infect humans) of circulating batCoVs,webuiltachimericvirusencodinganovel,zoonoticCoVspikeprotein -fromtheRsSHC014-CoVsequencethat was isolated from Chinese horseshoe bats" https://t.co/68MlUjJRD9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["SARS-CoV-2 spike protein alone may cause lung damage" https://t.co/C3yeHd5yUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2007: "Intravenous (i.v.) delivery of recombinant adenovirus serotype 5 (Ad5) vectors for gene therapy is hindered by safety and efficacy problems." https://t.co/DXgcXSHmMx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["SARS-CoV-2 spike protein alone may cause lung damage" https://t.co/C3yeHd5yUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The spike-based vaccine conferred acute protection in the brain only if combined with the nucleocapsid-based vaccine. https://t.co/ccdl2h246L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The N protein is only found inside the virus particle, wrapped around the RNA. Therefore, N protein antibodies cannot block virus entry, will not be measured in neutralisation assays that test for this in the lab, and so have largely been overlooked."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Following SARS-CoV-2 infection, researchers have discovered that we actuallymake the most antibodies to the N protein not the spike protein. This is the same for many different viruses that also have N proteins."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["SARS-CoV-2 virus is more complicated than just a spike protein. There are 4 different proteins that form the overall structure of the virus particle: spike, envelope (E), membrane (M) nucleocapsid (N). In a natural infection, our immune system recognises all of these proteins" https://t.co/1hICu8Ur7D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The SARS-CoV-2 spike protein produced by the new COVID-19 vaccines triggers cell signaling events that promote PULMONARY ARTERIAL HYPERTENSION, other cardiovascular complications, and/or complications in other tissues/organs in certain individuals" https://t.co/thwZubN6Bn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["SARS-CoV-2 spike protein binds to bacterial lipopolysaccharide and boosts proinflammatory activity" https://t.co/xN0F8NSPQC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, you don't need boosters. https://t.co/wUr7EmuD47]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We found that SARS survivors all have significant levels of antibodies remaining in their blood 17 years after infection. Anti-N antibodies waned more than anti-RBD antibodies, and the latter is known to play a more important role." https://t.co/RtDQwVf4Jg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The spike-based vaccine conferred acute protection in the brain only if combined with the nucleocapsid-based vaccine. https://t.co/ccdl2h246L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Neither CoVs nor their spikes enter blood in uncomplicated infections. In more than 90% of all corona-infections immune barriers in the upper respiratory tract or local mucosa immunity will prevent this. This is the result of T-cell driven cross-immunity" https://t.co/owOoqzRbXL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GarretKramer: If youre not called to challenge the elements of indoctrination thrust upon us since childhood (vaccines are a savior,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alex_on_A14 Yes. Approx 40 million. Check the column on the right. https://t.co/9nzPQCsbxE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's not Covid. It's governments. https://t.co/ROpn1xlvUO]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>