<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Can they just stop?  Allow people to speak https://t.co/UBsTJjPa4O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See what I'm really sharing these days. Join me on MeWe - the social network with privacy! https://t.co/R65OkO23A2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @willchamberlain: We're not talking enough about Facebook banning the PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES from its platform  The left is comp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emrata: Anyone else feel like proper amount of capital police being absent/letting Trump people in/providing insane visuals of MAGA dud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy Have you seen the bill the NY is trying push through? https://t.co/NgbC2zq4PB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VOX, ladies and gentlemen  https://t.co/kySI0m3Gr9 via @Not_the_Bee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @starchildsf: #DonaldTrump is far from the only #authoritarian threat to the #republic. The #NewYork legislature's #AssemblyBillA416 wou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Fauci #newyork #AssemblyBillA416 #sayno]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NY wants to right to detain you for "health" reasons.  https://t.co/e8KZ36iwK9.kidding?!   Absolutely not!  Stand up.. Say no.  If you are in NY, vote against this. https://t.co/wUEh56Eul6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats Up with the Great Reset? https://t.co/mv1viYR2eY via @aier]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ugh.. people that liked the disgusting comment...who does that?   #covid19az #offensive https://t.co/jghCeiRTzA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Names removed... Yikes.. Offensive much Gabriel? Ugh  https://t.co/rSzJIMDAHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Theyve purposely lied  misled people all year to push an agenda of control. Its so obvious. They dont follow scien]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Trump did not do enough to stop or end these lockdowns. But he did a lot to bring them here. I dont care how much you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why won't Fauci retire?  The dude is 80. Enough already.  #Nocovidvaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thegrandtour: Because Epic didn't really work. The Grand Tour Presents: #AMassiveHunt. Launches 18 December only on Prime Video. https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tedcruz: https://t.co/HSCSdXkst9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ofctimallen: My new mask is how I feel: Angry for those who've died. Worried for the sick. Sad for those in fear. Exhausted by homescho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovPhilScott You lost 2.  What is the Vermont population?  Stop using fear to control the population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovPhilScott @VTEducation Pretty sure you're an asshat.  Tyrannical dictator in training. I do hope you are voted out in the next election.  How dare you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is a political statement. Biden's first manipulation in his new position https://t.co/Pd3weN7mJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have to laugh at the media interviewing Hillary Clinton like she even matters.  She is a murdering criminal that is still under investigation for basically EVERYTHING.  Clinton needs to disappear.  #HillaryClinton]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stop supporting Biden!  Stop censorship! https://t.co/lCJsmS220Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whether you are a Trump fan or not... Everyone should be furious with Clinton, Obama and all that were involved in their schemes.  They lied to American citizens.  #Obama #Clinton #democrats]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oJbBUgcjng]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hollywood- Posting declarations like anyone cares.   #reallife #weareyourpaycheck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: There is only one side that believes in God.  The atheist Left were always fighting a losing battle.  No one has ever gon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ITGuy1959: Whichever RNC staffer did this deserves a promotion    https://t.co/IkNUnJXpKm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's funny that celebrities demand things as if their opinion matters over the general population. Last time I checked, they need a fan base in order to be successful so they depend on us.  I'm anti-hate groups and anti-celebrity demands. #selenagomez #facebook]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finishing up a custom order. https://t.co/gWkfTGH6hn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: The 1st Amendment doesnt give you the right to burn down police precincts, federal buildings, small businesses  thre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: You have famous journalists  personalities on social media calling for terrorism. By definition. Whats wrong with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4DaCI76WB3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes please! https://t.co/zppOsKkK26]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/bfu8ozIt5y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[School in action!! . OG homeschoolers. They sat down after a day out setting up children's church and running errands. Personal responsibility baby! . P.S. it's not always like this...  . . . #farmhousefixers https://t.co/UAzMtJHPs5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When my "work" collides on the kitchen table. . History test. Paint waiting for pickup.  Planning the new theme for children's church.  . I  it.  . . #farmhousefixers #momlife #smallbusiness #mombusiness https://t.co/TQEfG6vCf1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@engadget  bias and nasty as ever. https://t.co/kpkLImMlyA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ . . . #farmhousefixers #swim #dontconform #justjesus https://t.co/X1lg2f7Y4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The second half of this secretary desk is in.  Not gonna lie, it's been a challenge. At least 3 different coats of paint. Dried stripper is hard to get off. But I think we made it to the paint https://t.co/HVObvTDuY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The husband made the nightstands.. woodworking and welding. I painted in blended Dixie Belle colors. We make a good team.  . . #farmhousefixers #dixiebellepaint #handmade #husbandwifeteam #furniture #antebellumblue https://t.co/2kzxBjMu9d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#amazon - we are still paying a premium price for basically nothing. Shipping is over 2 weeks for basic items. Not items that are hard to find. eBay has become our go to.  . #AmazonPrime #shiptime #primecustomer #overpriced]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A first! My husband made the nightstand and I painted it.   Painted in Dixie Belle antebellum blue, french linen and midnight sky. Accented with black and clear wax.  Now on to the next one.  . . . #farmhousefixers https://t.co/b0KKN5QPAq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While we are pointing out what a disgusting pig Bill Clinton is let's remember his wife knew all about it.   She is just as guilty as he is...and people wanted her in the White House.  . #billclinton #hillaryclinton #guilty #Epstein]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hmm...  Stop ignoring this! #TomHanks #Hollywood #pizzagate #coronavirus #COVID19 #ChrissyTeigen #theyareguilty https://t.co/WtYJbm5Kmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Working on projects together.  I'm working on a pair of nightstands during my custom order dry times.  Today I'm blending Antebellum blue, french linen and midnight sky . . . #farmhousefixers #saturday #kids #paint https://t.co/JgbRtDyr4w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thebradfordfile: How the hell is "Bill Clinton was at Jeffrey Epstein's private island with young girls" NOT the lead story on every ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Waxing my legs  . . #farmhousefixers #customorder #legs #tablelegs #dixiebellepaint #bestdangwax #furniture #smallbusiness #womanowned #chinovalleyaz #prescottvalleyaz #prescottaz #arizona https://t.co/0Q64j9EgY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix Peace out McDonald's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disneyplus Nope. She is not to be praised. Watch Out of the Shadows]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#hollywood #RISEUPFORCHILDREN  #ignoremedia https://t.co/EI0kyzvse8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix What? So ridiculous.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Accurate https://t.co/KZ4TNPnaJS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix Nope. Not interested in her opinion. Part of the Hollywood elite turning a blind eye to pedophile and human trafficking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntonioSabatoJr Ummm masks? Isn't that what his party is all about?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealDeanCain @jack You're not spreading their propaganda so they block you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are the Emmys still happening? Why are we celebrating a group of people that either hurt children or knew about it and did nothing.  They don't deserve awards for being monsters. #Emmys2020 #boycottEmmys #HumanTrafficking #emmys #Hollywood]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeanCain: Well this certainly raises some questions...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you haven't read her resignation letter, you need to.  We need to wake up and see beyond what those that "have a voice" are pushing.  https://t.co/2RYTikV6eJ  #newyorktimes #bariweiss #nyt https://t.co/h1HLdFnDgr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Playing with green metallic . . . #farmhousefixers #dixiebellepaint #green #dresser #furnitureartist #furniture #smallbusiness #gold #chinovalleyaz #prescottaz https://t.co/fF9f811qjN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perfect morning for a walk.  . . . #farmhousefixers #chinovalleyaz #morningwalk #monsoonseason https://t.co/3YGkpJTYmG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qMkl2qWKPp  I hope local retailers are fined.  @FrysFoodStores @Walmart #nocashless]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NYTimes  Despicable. Murderous https://t.co/b2rRZhcGqw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My reality right now https://t.co/guNqBPCPmY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@azfamily Ridiculous.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JLemon66: Once you exit the simulation its hard to go back into it. Pizzagate, James Alefantis, Epstein, the Clintons, Tom Hanks, Ell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix Isn't she still on trial for leaking emails? How many times has she been on trial now. Honestly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@azfamily NO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix Oh give me a break. I wish the media would stop controlling the narrative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Deniseotten1: Award winning journalist, Liz Crokin was very successful until she researched Marina Abramovic and pedophilia and cannaba]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix Nope. Corrupt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why #tomhanks opinion and anything Hollywood is complete nonsense.  https://t.co/53VmRlcqAQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She's coming together.  . . . #farmhousefixers #vintage #antique #furnitureartist #furnituredesign #wood #bleachedwood #diy #diydecor #homedecor #fresh #chinovalleyaz #prescottaz #prescottvalleyaz https://t.co/AVocWCaA5t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not really romance. This can and does  apply to family... In the link below... . https://t.co/rsa5TrmeRL . . #farmhousefixers #article #toxicpeople https://t.co/S8dTj859ZJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It always looks worse before it looks better. . Prep is serious.  . . #farmhousefixers #dresser #prep #fixing #antique #vintage #lotsofwork #lovewhatyoudo #homedecor #decor #furnitureartist #serious #smallbusiness https://t.co/fwzpgZm4eu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got paint? I do! . Don't be fooled by the price point at Home Depot or Lowe's.. there is a difference! Dixie Belle is easily used and corrected. The choices at the big box stores are not!  . So if you are looking at https://t.co/eAjYlNEY0v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone one a brie fan?! This is my reward snack for making it through the crowds! . Anyone else space the fact Christmas is Wednesday. I mean I knew but it just didn't click.  I had my regular shopping today and https://t.co/cxZxKcxsVP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tea. Multi-vitamin. Echinacea. Ibuprofen. . Praying that I didn't catch the head cold that's zooming around out here.  . P.S. Sporting my hubby's 20 year old #GAP sweatshirt..One of my faves.  . . #farmhousefixers https://t.co/idT4Z7cDmc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Snow mountain cornholes. 130.00 for the set. . Handmade and handpainted. . . . #farmhousefixers #cornhole #forsale #diy #mountains #handmade #handpainted #dixiebellepaint #fluff #games #fun #christmas #family https://t.co/ojeE4Amtxq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ So cute! . Can't wait for the wine and signs class tonight.  . . . #farmhousefixers #signclass #socute #lovethem #farmfreshtrees #christmastime #christmasparty #dixiebellepaint #wood #smallbusiness #wahm https://t.co/8cjlCxXhxW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Squeezing in a little work before our Star Wars evening. . ....And listening to Stranger Things with my boys.  . . . #farmhousefixers #stockingholder #sawmillgravy #bestdangwax #wahm #lovewhatyoudo #strangerthings https://t.co/xqvQ37UXGB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now available. 130.00 for the set. . Solid wood. Handmade and handpainted. Sealed  Ombre finish  . . Shipping not available . #farmhousefixers #diy #cornhole #artist #ombre #unique #games #handpainted https://t.co/7dwZ7mXZmz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chino Valley sunrise.   . . . #farmhousefixers #sunrise #colors #earlymorning #morning #arizona #northernaz #chinovalleyaz # https://t.co/gxPsyEzXhz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cornholes!  Handmade and handpainted... Fluff, Mermaid tail, Bunker Hill Blue, Midnight Sky and Coffee Bean. . Available in Chino Valley, AZ. . . . #farmhousefixers #cornhole #forsale #solidwood #blues https://t.co/jG1xMM2U3I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Something new for this cornhole set.  . . . #farmhousefixers #cornhole #colors #blues #midnightsky #pureocean #coffeebean #bunkerhillblue #diy #smallbusiness #paint #painting #artist #games #fun #chinovalleyaz https://t.co/m2cFgaAn09]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cornholes taking up the living room! . Blending one (beginning stages) and changing the other.  . . . #farmhousefixers #bestpaintonplanetearth #cornhole #diy #dixiebellepaint #painting #artist #forsale https://t.co/KByWWCLSzW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My husband built me a new project! Time to paint!  . Do you know what it is?  . We may make more for purchase if the want is there! . . . #farmhousefixers #project #handyhusband #handmade #solidwood #christmastime https://t.co/nS7t95ldMz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sold  . . . #farmhousefixers #dresser #furnitureartist #sold #smallbusiness #prescottaz #prescottvalleyaz https://t.co/dbxtLH2p6M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yup...that's a lot of batter at 1030am and I gave it to my boys to eat.  . I'm baking cookies for my kiddos history class party and decided we were done with school for December.  . Too many events, errands, friends https://t.co/IqZMOkwdDU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ . . . #farmhousefixers #adventcalendar #justkidding #eatallthechocolate #nomnom #mom #chinovalleyaz https://t.co/XJm09paPC9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stencils arrived for wine and signs night!  . Pink dresser is getting the wax accents and it's on track to be finished by Thursday. . Fun information- I did a little research for the approximate age of the dresser https://t.co/ldrypcJCIy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoying the square after rushing to get out of the rain and cold. . At least it was fun with friends! . . . #farmhousefixers #friends #cold #wet #kids #prescottaz #downtown https://t.co/oINIufpvPB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mrs. Maisel- best show ever! Orange Daisy dress... Good.. hat...bad ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Paris Geller in Mrs.Maisel! Yes!! Season 3- so far the best #MrsMaisel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The snow is one basset deep.  . . . #farmhousefixers #snow #thicksnow #snowapocalypse2019 #chinovalleyaz #prescottaz #snowedin #familyday https://t.co/5Lvy5MbVhd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Making an early dinner for the kiddos (they have youth group tonight) and representin' Farmhouse Fixers.   How is your Wednesday night?? . . . #farmhousefixers #wednesday https://t.co/wNyBCmG8Wl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Friday nights in my 20s started at 9pm and ended at 3am Friday nights in my late 30s start at 6 and end at 1030pm. Commonality-both have wine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LurkAtHomeMom: 8yo: How come you only cook food that I hate? Me: Well, for starters, I keep a secret recipe book called Meals Kids Hat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KateWhineHall: Your metabolism after age 40 is like, "Nah, I like you fat."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealJamesWoods: Just brilliant. https://t.co/NJY4f5fyun]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>