<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelPSenger: Regardless of one's views on lockdowns, EVERYONE should be outraged by the excessive ventilator guidance from China tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NEUnion @GavinWilliamson Pathetic lying. How dare you muzzle up children?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti3: How does this relate to "Covid deaths" in the elderly? -28,186 people euthanised in care homes and hospitals. -38,000 do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thelaymanstake: @gummibear737 I made a video showing the cost of lockdown.   It goes through  Economic  Mental health Physical health D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GHS @WHO @doctorsoumya Everything needs to be done to stop mad nonsense transmissions from corrupt WHO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: Its the passports and vaccination of healthy children we must now all focus on...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hughosmond: News: after unexplained 2 week delay, Court ruled our claim "academic" as would not be heard before 17th May. After the rul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy10: Watch this reporter get owned by a member of the public https://t.co/rRQNfxv7Mj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No masks helps a lot. https://t.co/U0PSmmPjXK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil https://t.co/UkV0BWkbRi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef You are the main reason why.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil Why you lie?  Asymptomatic spread in nonexistent.   How much  council gets per test flogged?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRustler83: 1047 deaths following the now reported in the UK(as 21/4/21)  #ASTRAZENECA Reactions 573,650  Deaths 685 (+58) Blood c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FIDE_chess Who is the muzzled one?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil Do not take deadly untested vaccine. Many people die after second dose.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @deeksj: The 1st 2 weeks of school testing did find MORE FALSE POSITIVES than TRUE POSITIVES - data are finally public.  Proportion fals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil Tests are absolutely useless. Do not get tested.  Healthy people are healthy people. Stop twisting reality. https://t.co/3L4W4rzekJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TiceRichard: HORROR: On @talkRADIO @JuliaHB1    vaccine minister @nadhimzahawi confirms vaccine passports likely despite his previous p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Psychological warfare tactics have been deployed against the home population - that's why some people's behaviour appe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YardleyShooting Freemasonry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Whenever I watch this again I get the creeps and wonder what it all represents and why it should celebrate the opening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BorisJohnson Do not take deadly and untested covid vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @blackswan_t2: There will be a 'Third Wave' as without emergency corona legislation, the 'emergency vaccines' cannot be rolled out. Ther]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter in covid Nazi scum.   Censoring truth. https://t.co/lIlFdXQHPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rezhgjis @Astalbergs @Prusis Izsldz TV. Varbt pamodsies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: 1/  Hello, my name is Gal,  I am an Israeli citizen, and I want to convey this urgent message to the world: Contrary to what y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timfprice Please point me to wheel's falling off.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alasdair_Lord @9thfloor https://t.co/s3IfST2luC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YardleyShooting Yes. It's still there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nickynoble: Thank you to everyone that reached out with help and advice, for a young lady who had her baby refused an emergency op beca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @celebrityradio: SHARE    Suspended @YouTube violation of medical-misinformation quoting Chris Whitty DIRECTLY.   Curious conincide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnMappin: BUT what if this lady is RIGHT?    I am personally aware of three women in Cornwall who have had extreme periods and one is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peterrowen_: I now know of two people personally who have had the AZ vaccine and arent doing well.. be very careful folks, your govern]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Rasists gonna rasist.  Virtue signaling tossers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YardleyShooting 100% https://t.co/UuByVxnTk0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SchmittNYC Truth is out there. Most of them are paedophiles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLongerGame: Just spoken to two nurses at City hospitals who inform me blood clots have risen exponentially and many of the elderly ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilClark66 #DefundTheBBC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: The job of BBC reporters should be to report objectively  neutrally on large public demonstrations in the UK  not to see]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@doctor_oxford You are sick in the head.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil 49 out of 50 positive tests will be false positives.  You want 49 to imprison themselves.   You are criminal Covid Nazi scum.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil Why are peddling this scam so relentlessly?  How much are you getting paid?  Tests are worse than useless.   You desperately want to keep this scam going.  Shame on you.   Good thing that elections are soon. https://t.co/yjGpNlfC33]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SKMorefield: What an amazing example of eloquent courage and speaking truth to power from Georgia mother Courtney Ann Taylor. We need a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock https://t.co/u5013xnqVZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cKRK8eYwkq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Let them in and keep covid Nazis out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @amazonpyjamason: Future prediction: the unvaxxed will be sought for plasma, sperm, ova, stem cells, breast milk and cordblood.  Healthy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LukeJohnsonRCP: DAN WOOTTON: Raise a glass to Rod, the landlord who spoke for millions https://t.co/W6SO60dOlU via @MailOnline]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VernersViews: GPs in England that are only dishing out AstraZeneca's Covid vaccine are told to CANCEL planned appointments for pregnant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLongerGame: Hes turned down the cycles on the PCR test from the negligent level of 45 to under 35. There never was a pandemic it was]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef @thisisinsider @ProfKlausSchwab @Deloitte @Unilever The best thing for planet would be if all criminals connected with WEF got arrested today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomhfh Kier Starmer is finished. So are you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YardleyShooting It's because you appear very naive. "Long covid"? Give me a break.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@udumpis Tu nolptais masu slepkava!  Varbtba nomirt no AZ covid "vakcnas" ir lielka nek no svt Covida!  https://t.co/QGXuJ4S8hY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@angelofmercy911 @JamesMelville Brainwashed to the bone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: Any school teacher who punishes children on face masks is violating the child's human rights  we will name them  shame]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil @activesefton Gyms should have never been closed.   You are a disgrace and will go down in history as covid Nazis for playing your part in this scam.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Excellent and detailed article from Professor Simon Wood of Edinburgh University  - books were cooked by Imperial, spurious]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IlzeJaunberga @Dzintarz Aitas uz nokauanu.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: Be wary of taking 'health advice' from people who believe the world is overpopulated...   I shouldn't have to explain this o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Telegraph I would say that more like 90%.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Last summer, without a vaccine, we could travel freely; masks were not mandated for shops until late July and guess what:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLongerGame @SkyNews So obvious and was easy to see many months ago. PCR tests are key to it all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamNeary: @johnestevens @FatEmperor Governments and the pharma industry do NOT want you to see this table.  HCoV = human coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Stratford_: Just taken my wife to hospital - suspected collapsed lung. She cant breath properly as she is only able to take short]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gillsdenam @AndyBird21 @GFL9112 Fat brain dead moron you are.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do not get deadly covid vaccine! https://t.co/cshiGIxSak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jay_Azeltine Great. Thanks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jay_Azeltine How do you get your ice?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TVNET_zinas Ir gan taisnba.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laworfiction: MASKS IN SCHOOLS UPDATE: experts confirm masks in schools are causing immediate risk to our children of the most serious]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassports   https://t.co/6DrgJdt6g9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikolovScience: New information has surfaced, which may explain today's odd decision by the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) to ru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mikosoph: @RealJoelSmalley @peterktodd https://t.co/4aMubuC0pP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Covid passports must be ruled out full stop.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Crusher: Ivermectin was approved in Panam on January 15.  "Against complications"  What has happened since? https://t.co/F8yfZ5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLongerGame: If this was on your CV you wouldnt get a job in Mickey D's let alone the job as Health Secretary. Matt Hancock is a time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Based on my own experience  that of many who have contacted me I would not have the AZ vaccine, I believe that there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBGRichie: "A mild respiratory infection (covid) is being used as the excuse to bring in a long-planned mass vaccination programme, whi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LongCovidKids @kidsCovidGamble @FieryredheadHan @FrancesorFran @C4Dispatches @BBCPanorama @PandasPans @Parents_Utd @SafeEdForAll_UK @fhcappg @march_change Nasty propoganda to force children take experimental vaccines. Criminal lying scum!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLongerGame: Why is Matt Hancock still in Govt? https://t.co/WbXZWKQLRj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bej62: step daughter is in hospital on the stroke ward. she's had the AZ vaccine. she's 25 years old I'm beside myself]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeahButlerSmith: Refusing him essential treatment because he wont accept the heavily flawed often wrong test?    Which every NHS staff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JurgisLiepnieks Uk no covid vakcnm nomirui vairk k 500 cilvki. Ir jatcers, cik ctgi tiek skaittas covid nves, un cik ktri vakcnu.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JurgisLiepnieks Slimam 80 gadgam - j, veselam 50 gadgam - n. Nemaz nerunjot par vism blaknm.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: The frightened masses call the unvaccinated "spreaders of disease" - Hitler said the same about the Jews.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/e6BpJC4CFi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrSepah: Impressive  @jerryteixeira https://t.co/ILEOKA5x1D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seftoncouncil Close those evil places down. And open facilities as designed.  #Scamdemic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LukeJohnsonRCP Unless we stand up for ourselves and drag the lying criminals out of number 10.  Relentless mass protests is our way out of this hell.   Raise up people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LozzaFox: I will end lockdowns, now and permanently, and get London moving again with free bus and tube travel for six months.  Your Lo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@richardgaisford @waitrose Bedwetting moron.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nadhimzahawi Covid Nazi criminal.  #Scamdemic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BigBrotherWatch: NEWS: We've launched a crowdfunder to grow the greatest possible fight against Covid passes - including a legal chall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@udumpis Tu esi nolojams noziedznieks. Meliem sas kjas. oti drz cietum sdsi.  https://t.co/l7S2SsDs1b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@udumpis @GuntaSloga https://t.co/rF3m9rftGj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@udumpis @GuntaSloga Cietums tevi gaida. Masu slepkava.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: You really can't watch or listen to mainstream media anymore, it's constant propaganda and social engineering. I monit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrenpjones @KerryMP @Steph_Peacock @PaulWilliamsLAB @UKLabour Muzzled sheep.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Critical: **** BREAKTHROUGH*** A settlement regarding #ivermectin in South Africa is now an order of the SA court. IVM can now b]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>