<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[we need someone like him in #australia https://t.co/3M48rndgxs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[oh look, the communists are simping for the oligarchy. how original https://t.co/w7ekeifsia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElijahSchaffer divide and conquer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv Imagine still thinking this hasn't been part of an ongoing effort to eradicate the middle class]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@loganclarkhall https://t.co/UnIFMQ5idn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SydneyLWatson: Free people don't need permission.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VoteArjay @coinspotau coinspot's spreads are fucking awful, i'm glad there's finally some competitors to it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DickPower369 does she know she'll be going back for another in 6 months?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DitchTwitch use https://t.co/trXk06LFuj #censorship]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[60-70% of worlds attention focused on just 10 online domains, according to latest research  RT World News https://t.co/uhddIK5iWx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Authoritarians often confuse a mandate or ban of something with the thing itself. Why? Because living in an echo chamber makes you retarded https://t.co/zBe9R809BQ via @TheBabylonBee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4zu9QgplOb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Totusporcus @masks_more @femalecynic @DickPower369 You think the government has any intention of ending this? how naive. Government NEVER gives up power.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[many thousands march against #SCAMDEMIC2021 in #londonprotest. Media silent except to pretend it was only a few people and demand that anyone they don't like be sent to gulag https://t.co/4q0cgkrEod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government has absolutely no intention to ever return to normal. #SCAMDEMIC2021 #Totalitarianism https://t.co/y1f3Uv8e2r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AZGOP are you sure you have every ballot? I wouldn't be surprised if the demoncrats have already destroyed many of them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ELECTIONS MUST BE COMPLETELY TRANSPARENT https://t.co/8emgRnNObA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Better4Hughes @10NewsFirst @CraigKellyMP We will be watching every table in the electorate to make sure you don't try anything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@10NewsFirst @CraigKellyMP What a vile, defamatory statement from a smear merchant with deep ties to big pharma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CraigKellyMP The reason they insisted on using hotels is so that they could bankrupt people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigKellyMP: This is one of my posts Facebook has permanently removed. Its a proposed bill to Ban Domestic Vaccine Passports within A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBrandonMorse: #Oscars https://t.co/Br9LbgKuj9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElijahSchaffer In Australia, you'd pay $6 for that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's easy to be a marxist lunatic when you never have to experience the consequences of your own actions #Hollywood #elitism https://t.co/CFVfYI0spY https://t.co/GzyXGiNDSP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the #democrats are so confident there was no #electionfraud then why are they using every dirty trick in the book to obstruct this audit? https://t.co/t5vZmnvREN via @gatewaypundit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hsjajnds @POTUS The people preventing you from doing that are the government. They have blackmailed you. Why are you allowing yourself to be bullied into submission?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GravesWilliams6 @ManBehindCurta1 I'll take that as an admission that she got the saline.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shoe0nhead &gt;chad richison come on this has gotta be a joke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@benshapiro: *buys a plank* MSM: https://t.co/2rCj2PYkCH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a fucking authoritarian child https://t.co/ff523XT2P5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Took you long enough @tedwheeler  Everyone else knew these were rabid religious extremist totalitarians as soon as they began burning small businesses #antifaterrorists https://t.co/Fq4ri7e69r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: Difficult to trust doctors about vaccines when they repeatedly lied about: Tabacco, Thalidomide, asbestos, mercury fulling, op]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: What the large protest in London shows is that there isn't a small minority of fanatic and selfish 'anti-vaxxers' with lively]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hey, didn't we tell you those saline vials were for the rich and powerful only? https://t.co/jnypaflHA5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the fucking post office is spying on citizens for political purposes, imagine what they did with mail-in votes. We already know they destroyed evidence that @FoxNews was silly enough to entrust them with. REJECT AUTHORITARIANISM. https://t.co/Rbzwe8IAXG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leftist academics say BMI is fat-shaming and suggest we stick people in water to determine between fat and muscle mass, a legitimate downside of BMI is that it can't distinguish between the two. Perhaps we could call such a device a whale tank? #FatShaming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Swagaliciousnss synthwave]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/SZHqvS2drA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OregonGovBrown I'm so upset by this that I'm going to smash the windows of a liquor store and steal 2 bottles of whisky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The globalist cabal are just flat out stealing elections and no one seems to care. https://t.co/HzSkHRezBd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CraigKellyMP They will try to pull some sneaky electoral fraud this election to kick you out of your seat. If you haven't already done so, make everything completely transparent in polling places so that they won't be able to kick out observers (like what happened in QLD state elections)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What exactly is the point of it then? https://t.co/U6sObMV64m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jennyleong but can racism stop westconnex?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jennyleong One Nation led the effort to trash the cash ban. I think that outweighs Pauline being a xenophobe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jennyleong I stubbed my toe today, the white man is to blame]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrueBardsley @CraigKellyMP He tweeted about a local playground not 6 hours ago. You're full of shit mate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@logicsayz @CraigKellyMP You tell them to get fucked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrueBardsley @CraigKellyMP Okay, now hold all other politicians to that standard. The fact is, this is a crucial moment in determining whether our human rights are restored or we become #China]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@truthful_100 @CraigKellyMP Generally, yes. But totalitarianism must be opposed no matter what. #VaccinePassport is #totalitarisme.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CraigKellyMP https://t.co/XEZltA9pbN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BASED CRAIG STRIKES AGAIN #VaccinePassport #totalitarisme #auspol https://t.co/lHB2X5Yhm8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not even fentanyl makes you have a stroke or be infertile. Don't take the #vaccine. https://t.co/vreH55zkGc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#RINOs backstab and slander Trump, and then use his image for fundraising. lol get bent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What, did they actually think @amazon wasn't going to rig the vote? https://t.co/4Q2YQG3iMh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Chipman, Biden's gun-grabber in chief, defended the #waco massacre and thinks the feds did nothing wrong.  What a fucking scumbag. Don't trust any politician.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHY HASN'T @JoeBiden STOPPED #Westconnex @jennyleong]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Speaking at a press briefing on Tuesday, @WHO  spokesperson Margaret Harris ruled out supporting the use of #VaccinePassports  due to the question of discrimination and because they are not certain at this stage that the vaccine prevents transmission. #covidcult fucking BTFO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZachandMattShow Hmm, almost like millions of people are useful idiots.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your god has spoken, #COVID19 cultists. WHAT SAY YOU NOW? #VaccinePassports https://t.co/WCL16yB2Pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 is the new #suicide #EpsteinDidntKillHimself https://t.co/uaRq7MqvW0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#authoritarians have no values, no principles, no moral compass. They have no problems using whatever filthy tactics necessary to get their way. It's hard to see them as deserving of the human rights that the rest of us fight so hard for.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aus_spirit People like this deserve the #totalitarianism they shill for. When you have to live under a regime that will be literally WORSE than communist #China, maybe then you will repent for your statism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS IS WHAT FEARMONGERING DOES TO WEAK AUTHORITARIANS #scamdemic https://t.co/akUl55A8fs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dogecoinww @safemoon if you want an actual shitcoin check out $SHT - backed by IRL toilet paper (project is dead lol, shitposters never commit)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrewPavlou I just like to point and laugh from across the river]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliBard Beheading all of Rockefeller's servants in government]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CraigKellyMP A lot of naive, ignorant statists in these comments. Grow a brain, bootlickers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#statism is cancer https://t.co/OKYvvkl0tv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BridgetPhetasy: I don't care about your arguments for the vaxport. They don't matter to me. Because the question is, "Do I trust the go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@achooproducts @MerriamWebster @WHO Or you could just not take the vaccine, then you won't have to rely on some dubious-sounding herbalist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["your crying says more than real evidence ever could" - The Simpsons, making a joke at the expense of idiots like @voxdotcom who literally and unironically make this argument. Also, media in general is straight up making shit up about #ChauvinTrial. USE PRIMARY SOURCES.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanielAndrewsMP Back again to break your own rules and stick your brown-shirts on anyone who dares question, huh? I wish you were in jail for life, it's what you deserve.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliBard fuck he didn't actually die]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He's absolutely right. Keep the proletariat (for lack of a better term) fighting amongst themselves, that's how you get away with #totalitarianism. Don't listen to the media, all they do is incite hatred. https://t.co/3Jd7N3ogyU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[London and Finland are now POSTPONING ELECTIONS INDEFINITELY. DO YOU UNDERSTAND NOW, NORMIES?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just a reminder that @JoeBiden was the one who removed the White House petitions website and disabled comments on all White House channels]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: Federal income taxes paid last year:  Nike: $0  FedEx: $0  Zoom: $0  Dish Network: $0  Salesforce: $0  Hewlett-Packard: $0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PetiteNicoco @Lauren_Southern statists deserve prison for putting everyone's rights at risk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny how @YouTube want to remove dislikes when Rewind 2019 is the most disliked video on the platform and Biden isn't far behind. hmmm, really gets the noggin joggin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheQuartering what a fucking fascist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinDaubney: I dont trust anything this government says anymore  I dont trust them on COVID passports. I dont trust them on no mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidgokhshtein Retards Finance cap of about 50k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[said the quiet part out again did we @CNN  #ResistTotalitarianism https://t.co/rLUA0eNKYu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zerohedge https://t.co/EBMII3URpI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RedEaglePatriot: Will Delta, who has condemned Voter ID Laws, serve alcohol to anyone on their flights without an ID?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RandPaul: Your sports league might be a little too woke if it will freely do business with Communists in China and Cuba, but boycotts a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmazonFCBean wow, i never thought @amazon would consider me a threat, i'm honoured. I wonder if they paid for the stock photo this time after getting exposed by @RT_com for using the face of @DudePerfect]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Children cannot consent to the irreversible procedures of hormone replacement therapy, puberty blockers, and genital surgery.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BridgetPhetasy: So many liberals telling me privately they hate the idea of a vaccine passport but theyre afraid to voice it and right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sickening. https://t.co/2B7GDEbPcE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People who simp for #Totalitarianism sicken me https://t.co/bL3AowrMxH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JayTrdr @Rasmussen_Poll looks like you have no principles]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We CAN'T sit this one out. FIGHT FOR YOUR RIGHTS #VaccinePassports #Totalitarianism #Tyranny #medicalapartheid https://t.co/kyRKYRZG3W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepJeffDuncan: An overwhelming bipartisan majority of Americans support requiring an ID to vote, and any organization that abuses its p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why the fuck was that a thing in the first place? Good on you anyway #VoterID #ElectionIntegrity https://t.co/LBa6zvVxPg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The "conspiracy theorists" fucking warned you this would happen, people https://t.co/X9aFsf70pS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RegionEquality @goodfoodgal @MillyMolly300 haha react]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@oldm8onthaloose @goodfoodgal Sorry, corporate media doesn't get to decide what reality is. Go back to licking boot, statist]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>