<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Today we welcomed seven doctors and nurses from @GovNL to Ontario. They join the incredible team who arrived last week.  Thank you for continuing to support our province as we respond to the third wave of #COVID19. We are grateful for your selflessness, courage and compassion. https://t.co/te3xXMDMSG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.  Stay home, stay safe, save lives.  Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/ZLTXgJGIiY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 5,467,120 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.  Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 2,791 cases of #COVID19 and over 33,700 tests completed. Locally, there are 931 new cases in Toronto, 653 in Peel, 275 in York Region, 147 in Durham and 128 in Hamilton.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/4bAAnWIwoI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 5,378,249 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,436 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 33,200 tests completed. Locally, there are 985 new cases in Toronto, 714 in Peel, 351 in York Region, 271 in Durham and 194 in Hamilton.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting today, individuals 18+ in hot spot communities are now eligible to book a #COVID19 vaccine appointment at a mass immunization clinic through the provincial online booking system or through public health units that use their own booking system.   https://t.co/vOAx29BA8s https://t.co/RfobQpoKtd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy #Easter to Orthodox Christians across the province. May your day be filled with love and hope, as you welcome spring and celebrate life.    Please remember to celebrate safely at home with your household. https://t.co/N451H3bJbv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting May 6 at 8:00 a.m., individuals ages 50+ in 2021 will be eligible to book a #COVID19 vaccine appointment through the provincial online booking system and call centre or through public health units that use their own booking system. https://t.co/vOAx29BA8s https://t.co/t07BDBBt45]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting May 3 at 8:00 a.m., individuals 18+ in 2021 who live in hot spot communities will be eligible to book a #COVID19 vaccine appointment through the provincial online booking system or through public health units that use their own booking system. https://t.co/vOAx29BA8s https://t.co/3JRS5GCACT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During the weeks of May 3 and May 10, Ontario will allocate 50% of upcoming vaccines shipments to hot spot communities - an increase of over one million doses  as a targeted, time-limited measure. Allocations in other public health units remain the same. https://t.co/yG6Wh0Jcwk https://t.co/DM1NetbJEW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/Rc13uvl5nx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 5,324,369 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,732 cases of #COVID19 and over 45,300 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,198 new cases in Toronto, 797 in Peel, 306 in York Region, 237 in Hamilton and 232 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today on #FirstRespondersDay, we honour our courageous first responder professionals and volunteers who answer the call to protect Ontarians and save lives.  Thank you for your incredible service and unwavering commitment to being there in our time of need. https://t.co/ce7HopPkmM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/JN7DPlcCJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 5,247,684 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,369 cases of #COVID19 and over 46,800 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,050 new cases in Toronto, 819 in Peel, 286 in York Region, 158 in Ottawa and 157 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is #DoctorsDay and #NationalPhysiciansDay.  Throughout the pandemic, Ontario's 30,000+ doctors have worked tirelessly to be there when we need them the most, making a difference in countless lives every day.  Thank you for your incredible service. You truly are our heroes. https://t.co/JktBZsx70M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rigorously tested and approved by Health Canada, the #COVID19 vaccine is the best way to protect you and those around you.    Everyone is strongly encouraged to sign up to get vaccinated as soon as you are eligible. Learn more: https://t.co/aj03EIiNcr https://t.co/sDH6LYHvF8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario has now administered at least one dose of the #COVID19 vaccine to 40% of Ontarians aged 18+.    With a steady supply of vaccines expected, the province is preparing to ramp up its vaccine rollout and expand booking eligibility across the province. https://t.co/7XnXQs5HZw https://t.co/Zhmmu7uouv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RudyCuzzetto: Thanks to @THP_hospital for my first dose of the #COVID19ON vaccine today. Grateful for all your hard work throughout thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TobyBarrettHN: Bears repeating ... Ontario has administered over 5 million #COVID19 vaccinations, and the supply from the federal gover]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ONThealth: This Patient Experience Week join us in thanking health care staff across Ontario for giving patients positive #HealthCare e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week for #NationalImmunizationAwarenessWeek, we encourage all Ontarians to book your vaccine appointment as soon as you're eligible  All Health Canada approved #COVID19 vaccines are safe and effective at protecting you and your loved ones. Learn more: https://t.co/aj03EIiNcr https://t.co/3Rf0eIN7fF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Town_of_Aurora: The following services are available to York Region seniors in need of transport to a vaccination clinic:  @YRTViva- M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/xeBdVsTdmr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 5,139,984 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.  Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,887 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 53,100 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,331 new cases in Toronto, 871 in Peel, 267 in York Region, 208 in Durham and 204 in Hamilton.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting today, individuals aged 55+ are eligible to book a vaccine appointment through the provincial booking system at https://t.co/pxlgLpkLxR or through their public health units booking system. https://t.co/NX7iNCipAk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @normmillerpc: Today I was thrilled to join the almost one third of Ontarians who have received the first dose of the #COVID19 vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With a stable supply of vaccines, we will continue expanding access across Ontario, including to our hit hardest communities.  As we accelerate our rollout, adults 18+ across Ontario will be eligible to book an appointment as early as the week of May 24: https://t.co/yG6Wh0Jcwk https://t.co/LSPcR2ONGY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ORCRoseAnne: 1/ Grateful to receive my #seconddose of #Moderna #vaccine today. My first dose on April 1, was easy and I had no side eff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/foQCbgiI0C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 5,027,770 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.  Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,871 cases of #COVID19 and over 56,900 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,172 new cases in Toronto, 901 in Peel, 392 in York Region, 292 in Durham and 147 in Ottawa.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario has administered over 5 million #COVID19 vaccine doses!   We continue to work with all our partners to ramp up the pace of our vaccine rollout and get needles into arms as quickly and safely as possible. #TeamVaccine https://t.co/m7ebiozLV8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NANComms: As we continue to do our part to end the COVID-19 pandemic, lets celebrate the success of #OpRemoteImmunity. Over 25,000 dos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/tKEWMFEOeq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The case counts for some public health units in the Central West Region may be higher today due to a data catch-up process.  Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,480 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 50,200 tests completed. Locally, there are 961 new cases in Toronto, 589 in Peel, 341 in Niagara and 290 in York Region.   As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,907,203 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our government is working with public health units and businesses to set up workplace vaccination clinics in hot spot communities.  These clinics will vaccinate essential workers aged 18+ and members of the surrounding community.  Learn more: https://t.co/IxfJE5iYgT https://t.co/HFsjmhdTMk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobinMartinPC: Im honoured to greet the health heroes from @GovNL who just arrived in Ontario to help support our health care system.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to the courageous volunteers, @PremierofNL and @GovNL for supporting Ontarios response to the third wave of #COVID19 driven by variants.  The selflessness of these nurses and doctors is nothing short of remarkable and heroic. We are truly grateful. https://t.co/4NLaLesEr0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CAPAACAM: Thank you to @celliottability and @FordNation for prioritizing the regulation of Physician Assistants. We look forward to wor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OntarioPSWAssoc: After advocating for the professional recognition of Ontario's PSWs for over a decade, OPSWA welcomes this historic de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OCSAtweets: Today's announcement about a new Authority for the registration of PSWs will continue to bolster the public's confidence in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KKOVe0 https://t.co/QSIxcSXTTT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZcdsmV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,265 cases of #COVID19 and 34,000 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,044 new cases in Toronto, 673 in Peel, 452 in York Region, 171 in Durham and 150 in Ottawa.   As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,791,030 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LoganKanapathi: Today I added a layer of protection against this virus with my first COVID-19 vaccine! Im keeping myself, my loved one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting April 27, individuals 45+ in hot spot communities will be eligible to book a #COVID19 vaccine appointment at a mass immunization clinic through the provincial online booking system or through public health units that use their own booking system.  https://t.co/PcYNS9A41F https://t.co/eooeigQRl5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was pleased to join @C_Mulroney and Chairman Emmerson to announce our government is supporting a pilot for select 9-1-1 patients in @YorkRegionGovt  This pilot will allow @YorkParamedics to provide treatment in the community and protect hospital capacity https://t.co/XPMTa4kCkO https://t.co/cvmNpmy5lR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YorkParamedics: We are taking great steps to improving care for our patients when and where they need it most by launching the Paramedi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PBethlenfalvy: Ontarios Action Plan: Protecting Peoples Health and Our Economy has passed in the Ontario Legislature.  Ontarios #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffYurekMPP: Today I administered vaccines at the Indigenous vaccination clinic located at the N'Amerind Friendship Centre in London.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/lrxWdSDT9i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,696,211 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,510 cases of #COVID19 and over 33,800 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,015 new cases in Toronto, 909 in Peel, 391 in York Region, 244 in Durham and 206 in Ottawa.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/tZ7NTK1lk4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,626,903 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZcdsmV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,947 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 46,700 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,136 new cases in Toronto, 901 in Peel, 406 in York Region, 209 in Ottawa and 207 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ONThealth: #WorldMeningitisDay is Saturday, April 24. #Meningitis is the inflammation of the lining around the brain and spinal cord. V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,527,368 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 4,094 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 52,200 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,191 new cases in Toronto, 1,014 in Peel, 406 in York Region, 226 in Niagara and 199 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fordnation: Thank you Premier @premierbhiggs and all the volunteers for offering your support to Ontario.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @THP_hospital: : I'm pregnant. Should I get the #COVID19vaccine?  : Yes. We still recommend that you speak to your physician, but it i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StanChoMPP: The best #COVID19 vaccine is the first one to go in your arm! Yesterday I received my first dose of AstraZeneca - I encoura]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/hCXnYwXmhN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,400,674 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 4,505 cases of #COVID19 and over 56,200 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,257 new cases in Toronto, 1,232 in Peel, 412 in York Region, 247 in Ottawa and 224 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @OCSAtweets for inviting me to yesterday's Town Hall to speak with our heroic home and community care support services professionals.  We continue to work closely with our home and community care partners to deliver better connected care for patients and caregivers. https://t.co/iDWRyogDU9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pregnant individuals who are in a public health unit not using the provincial booking system should contact their local public health unit to book an appointment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pregnant individuals living in a public health unit using the provincial booking system can call the provincial call centre at 1-888-999-6488 to book their appointment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 23, all pregnant individuals can register for #COVID19 vaccination appointments under the highest risk health conditions in Phase Two of the provinces vaccine rollout. https://t.co/hS6jL4E84y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/yPvn7DfoPK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,266,802 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,682 cases of #COVID19 and over 54,200 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,131 new cases in Toronto, 507 in Peel, 436 in York Region, 279 in Ottawa and 200 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rigorously tested and approved by Health Canada, the #COVID19 vaccine is the best way to protect you and those around you.   Everyone is strongly encouraged to sign up to get vaccinated as soon as you are eligible. Learn more: https://t.co/aj03EIiNcr https://t.co/ZTN2H2FgDi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All Health Canada approved vaccines available in Ontario are safe and effective at protecting you and your loved ones from #COVID19. The best vaccine for you is the one that is offered to you first.   Learn more: https://t.co/aj03EIiNcr https://t.co/E9cuMUDxHX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobinMartinPC: Got my first dose of #AstraZeneca last week and I feel great!   The most effective vaccine is the one available for YOU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/2ujMZfzZ8M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 4,131,882 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 4,212 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 51,900 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,249 new cases in Toronto, 771 in Peel, 386 in York Region, 276 in Hamilton and 214 in Durham.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RandyPettapiece: Today I received my first dose of the COVID-19 vaccine in Stratford. Thank you to everyone working at vaccination site]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario continues to expand the number of sites that can administer vaccines. Over 1,400 pharmacies are offering the AstraZeneca #COVID19 vaccine to those aged 40+.   You can find a pharmacy in your community and book your appointment directly at https://t.co/emPnyQfI5t https://t.co/3gwm7O456n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beginning as early as April 21, Ontario, in collaboration with Shoppers Drug Mart, will begin offering 24/7 #COVID19 vaccinations for Ontarians aged 40+ at 20 pharmacy locations, with the majority located in hot spot communities. https://t.co/8RmWaMF4kB https://t.co/GIInTzkm2d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KL6wCA https://t.co/UmEEksEPQc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 3,995,187 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZbVRvn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 3,469 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 40,600 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,074 new cases in Toronto, 775 in Peel, 406 in York Region, 256 in Durham and 197 in Ottawa.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ONThealth: April is #WorldAutismMonth. #DYK children and youth who have been diagnosed with #autism spectrum disorder by a qualified pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteveClarkPC: A big thank you to Dave and the @RexallDrugstore Brockville team, one of the 22 area pharmacies now with the Astra Zene]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ONThealth: April 18-24 is National Organ and Tissue Donation Awareness Week. #DYK one organ donor can save up to eight lives and enhanc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KKOVe0 https://t.co/zyocRb3vwV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of 8:00 p.m. yesterday, 3,904,778 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been administered.   Todays numbers will be available at 10:30 a.m. at https://t.co/ypmgZcdsmV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is reporting 4,447 cases of #COVID19 and nearly 42,900 tests completed. Locally, there are 1,299 new cases in Toronto, 926 in Peel, 577 in York Region, 233 in Ottawa and 227 in Hamilton.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 20, Ontarians aged 40+ can receive the AstraZeneca #COVID19 vaccine at pharmacy or primary care settings. All Health Canada approved vaccines are safe, effective and the best way to protect you and your loved ones.  Sign up when it's your turn! https://t.co/FAYpWphFDs https://t.co/c2wIxWkHw0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stay-at-home order is currently in effect for all of Ontario. Only leave home for essential purposes such as food, health care, exercise or work. Its the law.   Stay home, stay safe, save lives.   Learn more about this and other #PublicHealth measures: https://t.co/9ta1KKOVe0 https://t.co/tCfvYwJxVU]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>