<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  LIVE NOW:  Media briefing by @MoHFW_INDIA on the current #COVID19 situation in the country  #Unit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  #COVID19Vaccination registrations have begun for those above 18 years of age.   Get yourself re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBMumbai: 11 districts in Maharashtra showing continuous decline in #COVID cases since last 14 days   - JS, @MoHFW_INDIA   Live Now ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Steps taken by Indian Customs for expeditious clearance of #COVID relief related imports:  High]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Union Minister @DrJitendraSingh today said that Government has decided to extend the payment of provisional pension up to a period of one year from the date of retirement in view of the #COVID19Pandemic situation.  Details: https://t.co/0rKE4419J6 https://t.co/sqUUDtPjDf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs, chaired by Prime Minister @narendramodi, has given its in-principle approval for strategic disinvestment along with transfer of management control in #IDBIBank Ltd.  Details: https://t.co/Vra3nyVEqA  #CabinetDecisions https://t.co/7rwygR1XM5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIB_India: LIVE NOW  Media briefing by @MoHFW_INDIA on the current #COVID19 situation in the country  #Unite2FightCorona   Watch on P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Are steroids advisable in mild #COVID19 cases  Taking high dose steroids in mild cases may lead]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona  Is CT scan required in mild #COVID19 cases  If you are asymptomatic, have mild illness  oxygen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:   Availability of #COVID19Vaccine doses (As on 5th May, 2021 till 08:00 AM)   Follow #COVIDAppro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DPD_India: The May 2021 issue of #Yojana is focused upon our federal structure of governance. Besides this, read views on the need of o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDNewslive: Watch the LIVE discussion on Treatment Protocols by a panel of top doctors. Ask your queries on 011-23387031  #DoctorsSpeak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Fake news around #COVID19 is as harmful as the virus itself.   Think before believing  Think]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Key decisions for boosting medical staff availability, as announced by PM @narendramodi:  Medic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NFAIOfficial: #PosterOfTheWeek: Our pick is this poster for the historical drama Oru Vadakkan Veeragatha (1989). #Mammootty received wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  @IITKanpur decides to produce around 30000 oxygen concentrators by June. It has invited industries]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rashtriya Ayurveda Vidyapeeth, an autonomous organisation under the @moayush is commencing a series on Exploring the Facts  #AYUSH64 in combating #COVID19. The first webinar of the series will be telecast live today at 2 pm onwards.  Details: https://t.co/33CZd7665o https://t.co/axEMVzBlrK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@IndiaCoastGuard has apprehended 4 Myanmarese poachers fishing illegally in Indian waters off Barren Island.  Details: https://t.co/2avDB10hC0 https://t.co/Qf7IYl7k7r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mayank23Agrawal: "Oxygen Therapy for COVID patients": Live Webinar with senior doctors from AIIMS. Must watch at 3 PM today on DD News]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: Ministry of Home Affairs draws attention of States/UTs on need to have plan of action to ensure no fire incidents occur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   What is Ayush-64   Ayush-64 is an Ayurvedic formulation d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Cabinet gives ex-post facto approval to MoU between India and UK on Global Innovation Partnership.  Details: https://t.co/R1H8JSqJTH  @PMOIndia @DrSJaishankar @MEAIndia @HCI_London   #CabinetDecisions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NFAIOfficial: The first film in #FaceOfTheWeek #SatyajitRays #Calcutta Trilogy #Pratidwandi depicts urban angst through the eyes of an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Cabinet approves MoU between India  United Kingdom of Great Britain  Northern Island on Migration  Mobility Partnership.  Details: https://t.co/DeqDCLsykg  @PMOIndia @MEAIndia @DrSJaishankar @HCI_London   #CabinetDecisions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Ministry of Corporate Affairs clarifies that spending of CSR funds directly or through pooling of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Government of India has so far provided more than 17.02 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Cabinet approves allocation of additional #foodgrain to NFSA Beneficiaries under #PradhanMantriGaribKalyanAnnaYojana (Phase III) for another period of two months  May and June, 2021.  Details: https://t.co/K6kYgBpQKi  @fooddeptgoi @CimGOI @PiyushGoyal @PiyushGoyalOffc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@MoCA_GoI has granted conditional exemption from Unmanned Aircraft System {UAS) Rules, 2021 to 20 entities to conduct Beyond Visual Line of Sight (BVLOS) experimental flights of drones.  Details: https://t.co/2vQga3ZGde https://t.co/1mE4Sv5iwb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  India becomes the fastest country to exceed 16 Crore cumulative vaccinations as the Nationwide Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Twelve states cumulatively account for 81.25% of Indias total Active Cases.  #Unite2FightCorona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Installation of 2 high capacity Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) completed at #AIIMS, Ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Highest number of daily #NewCases in several states of India (as on 05th May, 2021 till 08:00 AM)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Do's  Don'ts to be safe while in indoor settings  Do's Wear mask Maintain 6 feet distance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  India registered more than 3 lakh (3,38,439) #COVID19 recoveries in the last 24 hours.   Togeth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Are steroids advisable in mild #COVID19 cases  Taking high dose steroids in mild cases may lead]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Govt. of India has so far provided more than 17.02 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of Cost]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaVirusUpdates:   State-wise details of Total Confirmed #COVID19 cases (till 05 May, 2021, 8 AM)   States with 1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  These Medical #OxygenPlants are designed for a flow rate of 1000 liters per minute.   These will o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Installation of 2 high capacity Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) completed at #AIIMS, N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIB_India: In our fight against second wave of #COVID19, we propose to take further measures:  Term Liquidity facility of Rs 50,000 cr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIB_India: High Frequency Food Prices Data for April 2021 from @jagograhakjago suggest:   Further softening of prices of cereals  key]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIB_India: LIVE Now: Address by #RBI Governor   Watch: https://t.co/8jb1ZmwW4X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaVirusUpdates:  #COVID19 India Tracker (As on 5 May, 2021, 08:00 AM)  Confirmed cases: 2,06,65,148 Recovered]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  #COVID19Vaccination Status (As on 5th May, 2021, 7:00 AM)  Total vaccine doses administered (so f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDIndialive: The UK has been a solid friend. Were getting oxygen plants, oxygen concentrators, cylinders to address the oxygen challen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoHFW_INDIA: #Unite2FightCorona  India registered more than 3 lakh #COVID19 recoveries in the last 24 hours. Together, we can win the b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaVirusUpdates:   Total #COVID19 Cases in India (as on May 5, 2021)  82.03% Cured/Discharged/Migrated (1,69,51,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  India's Cumulative Vaccination Coverage (As on 05th May, 2021, 08:00 am)   More than 16.04 cror]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoHFW_INDIA: Your hands may carry the virus. Wash them frequently and thoroughly with soap and water to protect yourself. Remember, Saf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Know the fundamentals before using a #PulseOximeter    Have a look to this video  #Unite2Fight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaVirusUpdates:  #COVID19 testing status update:  @ICMRDELHI stated that 29,48,52,078 samples tested upto May 04,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:   #COVID19Vaccination Status (As on 04th May, 2021, 8:00 PM)  India's Cumulative Vaccination Cove]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona  Is CT scan required in mild #COVID19 cases  There is no use of a CT scan if you have mild #Covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:      #COVID19        .  #Unite2FightCo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Union Minister @prahladspatel virtually participates in #G20 Tourism Ministers' Meeting held in Italy today.  Details: https://t.co/iEDTuDQXNb  @g20org  #G20Italy https://t.co/B0eyWFYK8j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrakashJavdekar: Some facts related to Doses of #Covishield and #Covaxin ordered by GoI.  #LargestVaccineDrive https://t.co/6eN16ZbMbT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona   India's Cumulative Vaccination Coverage: (As on 04th May, 2021, 08:00 am)   More than 15.89 cror]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDIndialive: World Exclusive | DD DIALOGUE : THE MASTER CRAFTSMAN on Filmaker Extraordinaire #SatyajitRay with @BhatSakal   Ex Preside]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona   Government of India has so far provided more than 16.69 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona  #COVID19 Vaccination   I have recovered from #COVID19, when can I get vaccinated  A recovered #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDNewslive: As the third phase of #COVID19 vaccination began on May 1, here is everything you need to know about registering yourself f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[About 65% more wheat procured during the current Rabi Marketing Season in comparison to the corresponding period last year.  The government through its Nodal Agencies procured 6,27,276.56 MT of Pulses and Oilseeds.  Details: https://t.co/Y8BwTFV8RO https://t.co/0buIz6VRPU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MEAIndia:  PM @narendramodi and the PM of UK @BorisJohnson held a Virtual Summit today.  Leaders discussed Covid19 situation  ongo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IAF_MCC: #IndiaFightsCorona  An IAF C-17 flew in oxygen cylinder units to Chennai from @RAFBrizeNorton, UK.  The aircraft had earlier t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona   Installation of 2 Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) has begun at war-footing at #AIIMS an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona   Prime Minister @narendramodi and the PM of UK @BorisJohnson held a Virtual Summit today.  Leaders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona   @DRDO_India to install five medical #oxygen plants in Delhi  Haryana  Equipment arrives at AIIMS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona  The tankers from #UAE with 140MT #LiquidMedicalOxygen transported from Gujarat via #OxygenExpress w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona   Union Government did not waste time in effective allocation  distribution of #COVID19 relief mate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBFactCheck: A message claims that people can register for #COVID19Vaccination by downloading a mobile application through the given l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Union Minister @DrJitendraSingh appeals to all Central Government Employees aged 18 years and above to get themselves vaccinated at the earliest.  Details: https://t.co/qq3Q5eLTl3  #We4Vaccine #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/i9i5A9jyHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Union Minister @nstomar releases a new framework for implementation of #SVAMITVA Scheme  Coffee Table book to mark the nationwide roll-out of the #SVAMITVA Scheme.  Details: https://t.co/zyWbNhwPIb https://t.co/udHJeo7IfX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[28 States/ UTs start lifting food grains from @FCI_India  depots for distribution under #PMGKAY-III.  5.88 LMT food grains supplied for further distribution to more than 80 crore beneficiaries.  Details: https://t.co/bnFRzYZ7qN https://t.co/NHwZZhGyaz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NFAIOfficial: Poovinu Manamilla  PriyaManasa, producer rejected both songs. Thikkurissi said he wouldnt do the film if songs are rem]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Indian customs is sensitive to the need for availability of #COVID related imports including #Oxy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Telecom Department gives go-ahead for #5G Technology and Spectrum Trials.  Telecom Service Providers to start 5G trials in different locations across India.  Details: https://t.co/hTNe4jQrpB  @rsprasad https://t.co/EROeYsOEWj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Benefiting the tribal livelihoods of Odisha through the @VanDhanSeVikas.  The visits are taking place across the country and have helped Team #TRIFED to oversee the ground-level implementation.  Details: https://t.co/54UNw0l9HI  #VanDhan https://t.co/6DddgHOV02]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDNewslive: The Indian Railways Oxygen Expresses have delivered approx. 1125 MT Liquid Medical Oxygen to various States as the country]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaFacts:  Can Thermal Scanners detect #COVID19 infected people   No, thermal scanners don't detect #COVID in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#AsiaticLions housed in #HyderabadZoo infected with SARS-COV2 recovering well.  Analysis of samples reveals infection not caused by any variant of concern.  Details: https://t.co/gA4wqrF2XD  @moefcc @PrakashJavdekar @SuPriyoBabul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaFacts:  Myth:- It is not safe to take #COVID19Vaccine during menstruation   Fact:- Menstruation has no effe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Union Minister @dpradhanbjp off 1stsupply of Used Cooking Oil-based Biodiesel from IndianOils Tikrikalan Terminal.  A landmark in Indias pursuance of Biofuels which will have a positive impact on the environment.  Details: https://t.co/ravhI6xJSD  @PetroleumMin @IndianOilcl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Effective Allocation by Govt of India of #COVID19 supplies received from Global Community for figh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Threefold increase in production of #Remdesivir in the country  will soon be able to meet growing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Hum paanch bachayen #COVID se   Wearing mask  Physical distance  Staying at home  Washi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nfdcindia: National Award Winning (1985), NFDC #GhareBaire is a 1984 Indian Bengali drama directed by #SatyajitRay, based upon the 1916]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDNewslive: PM @narendramodi speaks with Governor of #WestBengal over the political violence in the state and deteriorating law and ord]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Maintain #COVID Appropriate Behaviour  Do Not lower your guard!  Wear Double Masks Wash Hands]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Steady Reduction in Daily New Cases (As on 4th May, 2021, till 8:00 AM)  #Unite2FightCorona  #Sta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biodegradable #Yoga mat developed by 6 young girls from #Assam may save lakes from water hyacinth menace.  The mat called Moorhen Yoga Mat will soon be introduced to the world market as a unique product.  Details: https://t.co/7FokwnwKQR https://t.co/CA2jRiiy0n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nineteen companies filed their applications under the PLI scheme for IT Hardware.  Production of Rs. 1.60 lakh crore and Exports of Rs. 60 thousand crore expected over next 4 years.  Details: https://t.co/MlpwhGT70L  #AatmaNirbharBharat #MakeInIndia   @rsprasad @makeinindia https://t.co/xI19f1yLOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NFAIOfficial: On the birth anniversary of filmmaker #DasariNarayanaRao, revisit his acclaimed melodrama #MeghaSandesam (1982). The film]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:   Follow #COVIDAppropriateBehaviour to #StaySafe    Always wear face mask Properly   Maintain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  #COVID19 Labs in India (As on May 03, 2021)  #StaySafe #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/I4lHnouMyU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #CoronaVirusUpdates:   State-wise details of Total Confirmed #COVID19 cases (till 04 May, 2021, 8 AM)   States with 1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:   Highest number of daily #NewCases in several states of India (as on 04th May, 2021 till 08:00 AM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@moayush and @IndiaSports join hands to promote #Yoga in the run up to the International Day of Yoga 2021.  The International Day of Yoga (#IDY) 2021 is coming up in less than two months from now.  Details: https://t.co/XVIHv5h2CS  @KirenRijiju @RijijuOffice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:   Increasing gap between #COVID19 Recovered  Active cases of India (June 01, 2020 to May 04, 2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @official_dff: #Tuesdaymotivations  #KASTOORI, a powerful story of a 14-year-old boy who manages to study along with assisting his fathe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona:  Govt. of India has so far provided more than 16.69 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of Cost]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>