<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KismetandHope: I've suspected for a while now all the covid vaccines are deadly but the public are only getting 10-20% real ones, the r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ojbollinger: @Breaking911 Breaking!!  People die every damn day, vaccinated or not. Nobody is getting out of here alive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealLathan Im right there with you. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nb0816Bishop @ShivversLaw More like what are they doing underground in their dark tunnels or DUMBS?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Adam_Penning @Jaye1222 @ShivversLaw Like mask wearing. Its symbolism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DioneJoe: @DjstannyG @ShivversLaw There's the full interview available online, it says a lot. https://t.co/q2ZJADuZXJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeanFulce2040 @JoeBiden I hope the answer in none.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@divinedre11 28+2=30 30+45=75]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissDeNovo @Sadblueplanet @DailyCaller They most certainly do. I have experienced this in surgery twice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NattyEyece No, you have more than half your life left on average (as long as you didnt take that jab). There are plenty of broken relationships that can lead to Heaven on earth in these last days. I say go for it, but watch out for the wolves.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex lame]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I hope our Heavenly Father has mercy on your soul for pretending to be a man of God and not a troll. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Thanks for clarifying who you are.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex So do you really live in the Vatican city or do you live in China?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I just stated my opinion based on Twitters recommendations.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Hahaha ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex So youre the troll. Bingo, over the target ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Hey lets face it, you were the one who told me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex So according to this Internet troll definition, you just defined yourself.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I disagree. It gives them a chance to respond. How come he has not responded?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Nope trolling is when you seek out to follow someone. I did not seek out to follow the pope. Twitter recommended his post to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I only aim to seek the truth and let the truth of our Heavenly Father be seen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Commenting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Thats called responding.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex On the contrary sir, I like my line to be yanked because I call them as I see them and I think you are fake.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Because trolls ask and answer questions like you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex You lead me to believe you are a troll. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Because what I see is not representation of a serpents head?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex The definition of mediating is being the in between person.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Its called questioning him.  Calling him out. Why is he not the one answering my question, but rather you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex True, and I do believe that we should look to many outside sources coupled with prayer to seek the truth, as Satan has many deceptions, like your mass gathering hall and its serpent satanic symbolism. https://t.co/V166BIGGEG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I do agree with you in this. I love to listen and I should learn to listen more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Nope, not trying to mediate. You asked a question and I am simply just trying to answer it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex What I believe is totally relevant to the final destination of my soul.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Dont you know? For it is written, I am a woman and the head of a woman is a man and the head of a man is Christ and the head of Christ as God, according to Paul.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Never will I claim to be the Messiah, nor will I claim to be a mediator between man and our Father.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I do believe there have been some changes made to that book by men, who think they have the authority that they so claim, when really they dont.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex OK to answer your question, it is the whole book and nothing but everything thats in that book.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I disagree. It is my soul purpose to seek out the truth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex We all know the story of people assuming the Messiah could not possibly be.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Dont assume that the Most High cannot use anyone, even the lowest among men.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex https://t.co/7xA3OvbAaH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex So that is how you direct others to the truth?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I can agree with you on this, assuredly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I also never claimed to be right, as per my statement prove me wrong. I also said I would humbly apologize for my stupidity when you could show my ignorance backed by scripture. But you say scripture should not be repeated or cited.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I never claimed that church as being established by the Son.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Let me ask you, what verse says the pope is granted any authority, or acts as a mediator between us and the Most High?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katstillhere: I saw a lady wearing a mask today that said - Ive been vaccinated ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marklutchman  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marklutchman: Liz Cheney and Mitt Romney are TransRepublicans.  They say they're Republicans, but they're really Democrats.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @End_TheFederalR: This is mass Genocide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrWillis23: The day i became a racist is when i said All Lives Matter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickAdamsinUSA: Why are Democrats so against God?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theHetal Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 He must have a magic wand.  #IllegitimateBS #IllegitimateBiden #TheGreatReset]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Thank our Heavenly Father for the disciples and all His messengers. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Are you having a bad day? Is there anything I can do to cheer you up?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex You are obviously talking to a mirror.  That makes two of us dear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Do you hold the book of life?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I stand in the line of following the teachings of our Savior.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex The Messiah granted authority for us all to share the gospel. Go, be fishers of men.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex If you truly are a bishop, you already know the verses well. No sense in citing it, as per your words.  The church you speak of has a terrible long history of overstepping the authority granted to them, and granted only by Father I Am, who granted it all to the one true Son.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Nonsense.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seagrlutwrld @DavidHarrisAJC No, it must be you. You are the brightest.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seagrlutwrld @leahcrosta @YourDailyRemin6 @Raisin13674217 @DavidHarrisAJC You can use Duck Duck Go if you prefer. I dont watch the fake news, even Fox News (All China owned and operated). Im not trying to attack anyone for their beliefs, but you are. Just trying to keep an open mind that those in power are lying like the Bible says.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jsmith4966: Whos ready for President Trumps return? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Recited. It must be read out loud and shared. Should it not?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex That means all His people. All who believe in the Son are His people. Meaning we are granted authority from the Most High through the blood of the Christ. All authority belongs to Him. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Eyes of the Devil: A Documentary Film About Child Trafficking For Child Sex Slaves Or Organ Harvesting by Patryk Vega.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Dozier School for Boys.  Young Boys were raped, tortured and beaten to death at a facility in Florida that lasted from]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Michael Aquino, Satanic pedo involved in ritual abuse sacrifices, heads the NSA. He was an army general, specialty was]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Johnny Gosch was a 12 year old paperboy in West Des Moines, Iowa, was kidnapped on Sept 5, 1982.  He was kidnapped by a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Conspiracy of Silence: The Franklin Cover Up, a documentary listed for viewing in TV Guide was to be aired on Discovery]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Photographer Rusty Nelson shares his personal experience witnessing high level people in our government, entertainment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Doug Millar has been an investigator for 21 years for violent crimes against children in 20 states.  In this interview]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Michael Aquino, satanic pedo involved in ritual abuse sacrifices, heads the NSA. He was an army general, specialty was]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mononoke__Hime: Mouthy Buddha's PedoGate 2020 Documentary.  This documentary looks deeper into the evidence of an organized pedophilia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bennyjohnson Keeping it weird ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My guess...its in Austin?  https://t.co/b8R8IMoXfJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex So you are trying to claim to be my authority in our Heavenly Fathers headship? Who gives you that authority?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Answer this, if you truly are a bishop then how come you have not mentioned even one scripture nor shared one scripture with me?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Undoubtedly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex What qualifies a person? You mean like people who accused Jesus as not qualifying to be the son of God?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: BACK THE BLUE!    https://t.co/lInNE0x2Dl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @agvBruceAdams: Who would think this display is from God?  Resurrection Hall of the Vatican is Satanic. https://t.co/F1lFkO7Ljh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Soultry4: Satanic Vatican had to silence a few. Remember Leonardo servers in Vatican was part Election fraud.  I love to connect dots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bradley93038424: Are they hooves?? https://t.co/glyAgiboo1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kabamur_Taygeta: The Vatican didn't become satanic. It was always that way.  It's now just becoming obvious.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @End_TheFederalR: The Simpsons did it again https://t.co/CYbfa6Gxi0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@End_TheFederalR That is the alter of the Antichrist. No doubt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex The pope did change the Lords Prayer. There are many, many articles about it. https://t.co/RrWuaxOong]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NotAlexSheppard I agree. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Democrats are turning America into a shithole country!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex I am not afraid to expose darkness. I do admit when I am wrong. Prove me wrong with scripture and I will humbly apologize for my accusations of the pope. Tell me...should a pope have Jesuit ties? Or should he humbly not take the position because of his ties with the Jesuits?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex The real church is not found in a building.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex You are clearly offended. You have done nothing, but try to label me with harsh words when all I did was call the pope out as being the false prophet, because he is surrounded by satanic symbolism and serpents. Are you one of them? Only the Most High knows.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Hahaha ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Any educator in a school system. Myself included.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Our fathers word is very clear the Sabbathday is the last day and you should rest on it and keep it holy. The first day was the day that are Messiah was resurrected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeotheGreat19 @Pontifex Of course anybody knows that. But it does tell us the first day and the last day.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>