<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arktinentuuli: China's New Nuclear Submarine Missiles Expand Range in US  China's newly commissioned nuclear-powered submarine is armed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InCytometry I doubt you would be interested, but this account is taken from work of Wolfgang Wodarg, MD, specialist for internal medicine and pulmonology. He together with people like Mike Yeadon   Sucharit Bhakdi wrote to the European Medicines Agency about their worries  w/r mRNA jabs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jayne_puligan @SwaledaleMutton And what makes you think this is nonsense?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 12. ...and of serious complications reported in the literature following COVID-19 is a molecular mimicry mechanism, i.e. of sequence homology (similarity) between Spike proteins and human proteins from various tissues." This must be a surprise for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 11. There could be over 100 citations of medical research articles. I noticed this comment on page 6: "It would appear that the source of this adverse vaccine reaction, which has already been encountered among people vaccinated with Pfizer vaccine...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 10. The mRNA jab make your own body attack itself, an autoimmune reaction. This is rather well known. I suggest you get a copy of this  have a good read: https://t.co/hioskCYXWU I consists of 34 pages of various mechanisms by which COVID-19 vaccines can induce immunopathologies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 9. So the killer T cells will attack your own cells, immune cells, endothelial cells, muscle cells, etc, any cell which has taken up the lipid nanoparticles which contain the mRNA instructions for creating a spike protein like the protein on the Covid-19 virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 8.  It has been proved that killer T cells developed by people who lived through the SARS-CoV2 infection are also effective against Covid-19. The pathological priming is the previous exposure to a coronavirus which develops killer T cells that will attack anything similar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 7. This is not possible without the immune system having been prepared for the virus. This suggests a continuous development up to SARS-CoV2 (and its many variants)." (War against a joker, https://t.co/vUOfl5Syku)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 6. It has been proved that killer T cells developed by people who lived through the SARS-CoV2 infection.  "A very large number of SARS-CoV2 positive people show no or only mild symptoms. The proportion of asymptomatic people who do not show symptoms is said to be 50 - 70%."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 5. We must assume that these lymphocytes will mount an attack on the respective cells.  The lymphocytes discussed are killer T cells which WILL recognize the spike protein on the surface of an immune cell or any other cell AND ATTACK/DESTROY IT. .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 4. Many healthy individuals have CD8-lymphocytes that recognize such peptides, which may be due to prior COVID infection, but also to cross-reactions with other types of Coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 3. It must be expected that during expression of the vaccines nucleic acids, peptides derived from the spike protein will be presented via the MHC I  pathway at the luminal surface of the cells.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 2. Following intramuscular injection, it must be expected that the gene-based vaccines will reach the bloodstream and disseminate throughout the body.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwaledaleMutton 1. I am not sure you really understand pathogenic priming. This discussion of mRNA vaccines comes from a letter doctyors4covidethics sent to the European Medicines Agency.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arkmedic: People need to understand that this represents a hospital FIGHTING TO WITHHOLD A SAFE TREATMENT that has been shown effective]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heather74299543 They are approved for EXPERIMENTAL purposes only.   With no "Covid Emergency" they would be illegal!  #auspol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @artycrafty232: Nope, I eat a ketogenic diet so consume quite a lot of beef  no way am I going to stop. https://t.co/3alV0stwNh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Virgini86646075: @1BJDJ @NotTheNewz Certain groups will never see it that way until all that they have worked hard for has been taken a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We deal with reality, not with rubbish other countries (or their conspiracy theorists) are trying to concoct."  I am confident you will understand eventually when the reality you speak of destroys your life.  I can wait to see what you think then.....  #auspol  @Heather74299543 https://t.co/cCkHsEtRbE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Reasons to abstain from emergency CVID-19 jabs  1 Experimental 2 Long term safety unknown 3 Effective treatments available 4 New genetic engineering jab 5 Not a aine: does not prevent infection  transmission.. #auspol  #CovidVaccine  @CraigKellyMP  https://t.co/1fqXSscnHt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sucharit Bhakdi Interview  COVID Vaccine Blood Clot Risk Was Known, Ignored  Buried  We must understand what Cerebral Venous Thrombosis and why its symptoms seem to be identical to some adverse events from Covid19 jabs  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF   https://t.co/h8UlLIP52j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eddiec_tweets2: @hapyhusbandwife @arkmedic Thanks. I am just mostly summarizing Prof Sucharit Bhakdi's view on the jabs: https://t.co/N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eddiec_tweets2: 5. IF too many blood vessel walls damaged  not enough clotting material #Thrombocytopenia v low platelet count in blo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eddiec_tweets2: 4. #Thrombosis (cont'd)  b. If in the Leg/Thigh/Pelvis/Arm#DVT  If DVT clot breaks of  travels to  clogs the lung:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eddiec_tweets2: 4. To stop bleeding from the damaged blood vessel wall cells, blood clots form#Thrombosis  a. If in the Brain#CVT or]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eddiec_tweets2: From Jab to Adverse Effects 1. The blood stream would carry the injected mRNA/DNA 2. Where the mRNA/DNA end up, the end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angelovalidiya: If there is no deferral period after #vaccination how do we know blood donation by #COVID19  vaxxed doesn't harm the re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Experimental COVID Post-Vaccination Adverse Events  Deaths. Coincidences?  This is just one of MANY, MANY reports of adverse events listed in this post!  A gold mine!  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF  @CraigKellyMP  @normanswan   https://t.co/52uyHHA8bB https://t.co/LbNfmyJLew]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigJo37661463: Ardrossan South beach was adorned with support for Assange today, You can  just make out the isle of Arran in the back]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: Isnt it amazing how so many people are waking up to the corrupt institution that is @BBCNews  We are onto you. We are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @darthhatter00: 747 days ago, the UK illegally arrested Political Prisoner #JulianAssange.  He is still facing 175 years in prison for m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Professor in epidemiology from US shows 830 post-vaccine deaths in Israel happened mainly within 4 days after jab. #auspol  vaxhttp://www.nakim.org/israel-forums/viewtopic.php?t=270873s=Exposing_distortions_in_the_NEJM_scientific_publication_on_the_efficiency_of_Pfizer%27s_vax https://t.co/bh8cO7hw7i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Censorship of Professors, Medical Doctors, Scientists  Data Analysts re. COVID-19 Info  MANY MANY censored articles can be found here!  Monopoly: An overview of the Great Reset  Follow the Money  Forbidden Knowledge TV  and more #auspol  #CovidVaccine   https://t.co/remvSguBnH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 Information  The Experimental COVID Vaccines The Experimental PCR Tests Non-Medical and Medical Experimental Mandates Censorship of Medical Doctors  Scientists re. COVID-19 Information....  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF  https://t.co/K8oTwuxnLz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VerumBellator1:  NEVER BEEN ISOLATED https://t.co/TtU9Ot5zO0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCPEREZCODEX: Indias Health Ambassador Dies One Day After Taking COVID-19 Vaccine https://t.co/xm3y3KgxQe via @DailyExposeNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jasonpillifeant: So, with Covid escaping Perth, coming to Vic, and Captain Gold Standard swinging into action and testing hundreds of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: A vintage photo of how people socialised in 2019. https://t.co/V2ps7XM34g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilipSoos: What's unforgivable are the so-called 'progressive' groups in the country such as the Greens, Labor, ABC, SBS, union leader]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilipSoos: Even when skill shortages were affecting only a fraction of occupations in the post-GFC era, the establishment lied incessa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilipSoos: Translation: we need more obedient, exploitable immigrants we can treat like trash, instead of doing what's necessary, like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Schmiddddy: The secret meeting that exposes the true origin of gangsta rap in the mid 1980s, destroying a generation? https://t.co/MPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Yeadon vs Dr Vanden Bossche  Bossche and Yeadon disagree as to: (1) abilities of the innate human immune system (2) likelihood of asymptomatic spread (3) likelihood of mutations of SARS-COV-2 to defeat immune systems #auspol  @arkmedic  https://t.co/6fQybYBOhN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["When vaccine passports come a large number of people not vaccinated will rush to get vaccinated because they will see their horizons shrink, they simply wont realise they are being herded like cattle into a pen."  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  @normanswan  https://t.co/PZ1jIBv8PG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BusyDrT, DrMadej and more prominent Doctors speak out on the huge amounts of injuries, due to the people who have taken the COVID19 vaccine - Having an impact on those who have not! A must watch  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF  https://t.co/okGQ5tdjee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@normanswan   Since you are so interested in these jabs, have a look at this leaked document from the NHS explaining some of the well-recognized results of your favourite jabs.  (Original tweet coming shortly.)  #auspol  #CovidVaccine https://t.co/lJX0xWhC9F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Albion_Rover: laughing emoji mocking vaccine concerns - then dead within 48 hours:  Another proof that informed consent is not happenin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CelestineBee: Society tries to program you to condemn those who commit small scale crimes but condone those who commit major crimes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: The gaslighting has been off the scale these last 48 hours hasnt it? If you protest against lockdowns  the introduction]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigKellyMP: FACEBOOK ATTACKS FREEDOM OF POLITICAL SPEECH  It's wrong to censor the free speech of elected officials as it threatens o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@normanswan   JAB DEATHS COVERED UP  Report from Israeli People Committee - leading Israeli health experts:  288 deaths reported following jab  According to the Ministry of Health, only 45 deaths in Israel were vaccine related." #auspol  #CovidVaccine   https://t.co/W8vNbwiEx2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most frightening epidemics in Congo, Afghanistan, and the Philippines, are all linked to vaccines. In fact, by 2018, 70% of global polio cases were vaccine strain. #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF   https://t.co/KQa30vmDB8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is the "PROGRESSIVE" and "INCLUSIVE" ALP.  Tanya DIVIDES "coloured" diggers from the rest of us!  "Coloured" ANZAC ceremony  "Non-coloured" ANZAC ceremony  HOW IS THIS DIFFERENT FROM HAVING SEPARATE TOILETS FOR "COLOURED" AND "NON-COLOURED"?  Is this progress???  #auspol https://t.co/qCe1cqOuVY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OMGTheMess: Diggers only have one colour Tanya. The ADF colour. Ive served with many ethnicities, genders, sexualities and religions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cagsil: Want to really see what pharma does?  https://t.co/ws9CgKfa6g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: If you dont understand that our right to freedoms has been fought for, many times over thousands of years to maintain that righ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jules31415: .@catturd2 Congratulations on 500,000 followersagain!!!  Id say aim for a million next, but if we know Twitter, they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LockdownLazarus: This is the protest the BBC has ignored entirely. If that doesnt worry you, then you have no idea what democracy actu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maytham956: Kurdish militias slaughter the Syrian army's First Lieutenant Saeed Hilala, Qamishli https://t.co/Y0Oe7NFxRO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2:  https://t.co/dBmXDsp2Ic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FluorescentGrey: I feel like we need to have a new category besides anti vaxxer and pro vaxxer where its kinda like lets talk openly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CanuckDefiant: @StoneSculptorJN @surveyorX @GlobalNational Im making a list of every cheerleader for the NWO I come across. We can hel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThomasConnors Fantastic find! Can you please supply the source? Thanks....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Carmilla5: Woman lies paralyzed in Nashville hospital, says it happened after she received Pfizer vaccine | News | https://t.co/G3M2tDT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrumpyOLSoldier: So the Outcome of Bidens Climate Conference is that IF ALL the nations including China  Russia do whats promised it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GoddoG_668: @GrumpyOLSoldier "Chinese power industry has proposed 40.8 gigawatts of new coal plants  an amount comparable to the entir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThomasConnors: Vaccines have been shown to cause side effects https://t.co/OP7vv7u5Z5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LouisLeoIV: Who is Fakebook truly protecting by censoring the truth about the experimental products it promotes? https://t.co/Iu2HgIEKUG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[STUDY AND DISTRIBUTE THE ARTICLES!  AN INVALUABLE Compilation of Scientific Research, Data,  Reports.  This compilation contains OVER 50 ARTICLES  VIDEOS!  Scientists  Doctors Warn Against COVID-19 Vaccines  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF  @CraigKellyMP  https://t.co/ClkflZRFQe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You don't need prove youre not a health risk.  PEOPLE WITHOUT SYMPTOMS ARE NEVER A HEALTH RISK.  Once people concerned about Covid-19 are vaccinated, there is NO ARGUMENT for anyone else needing the jab.  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @craigphase8: Wheres Daniel Andrews?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANYONE SEEN THIS ON THE 5pm NEWS?  The Great Reset promises to 'build back better' by reinventing capitalism and solving climate change through REDUCED BEEF CONSUMPTION.  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF   https://t.co/e0pxFpLi2J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JumboJones56: @NotTheNewz @Heather74299543 @LesserMegadeath I was responding to Heathers comment about No mandating of  in NZ but tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heather74299543  "OK - so a conspiracy theory."  Think about this:  IF what I and the article suggests is happening, do you really think you would see it on the 5pm news?  So NOT SEEING IT ON THE NEWS is not evidence it won't happen.  You have NO REASON to believe it is false. https://t.co/MkmMcuA9ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@damiendubsy "a mostly cowardly citizenry"  I'm not sure most are cowards. I think they would fight IF THEY KNEW THE COST OF NOT FIGHTING. The cost of not fighting is the imposition of the Great Reset, total surveillance, loss of all property, freedom and dangerous jabs as long as you live]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Evidence of vaccination has been part of recruitment for certain jobs in Australia. Eg cleaners in hospitals in Qld  have to have certain vaccines to be eligible for employment." This jab is DIFFERENT. It is  EXPERIMENTAL, NOT FINALLY APPROVED, not tested on animals. #auspol https://t.co/LZ8dFD16mg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ablebodied777: Praying for this. https://t.co/ftlxtdPuUN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @umasrikanthk: @NotTheNewz This should be implemented all around the world. No New World Order-Humanity is the only world order forever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JumboJones56 @Heather74299543 @LesserMegadeath "so what's this about in NZ?"  NZ is down the road to the Great Reset. I doubt a court would make the same judgment due to political pressure. In fact the decision in Canada is a surprise as Covid Emergency seems to override all laws  court decisions. Emergency could be illegal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carm138: Amazing !!! #RemoveThePM https://t.co/dkG18BgmSn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Yeadon has emerged as a very important expert voice with a penetrating interpretation of the dangers entailed in the COVID jabs.   With his impeccable credentials, the WHISTLEBLOWER Dr. Yeadon  is now near the center of the COVID crisis.  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF https://t.co/0rbNE54q2J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DR MICHAEL YEADON SPEAKS  Has all humanity been put in a vast  unimaginably dangerous phase-three clinical trial without our informed consent?  NOTE: The video has a warning attached SO USING CENSORSHIP LOGIC IT IS PROBABLY TRUE.  #auspol  #CovidVaccine   https://t.co/ZZwb8zjMeS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JAB DEATHS COVERED UP  Report from Israeli People Committee (leading Israeli health experts:  288 deaths reported following vaccination  According to the Ministry of Health, only 45 deaths in Israel were vaccine related."  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF https://t.co/W8vNbwiEx2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heather74299543   This is for you.   The argument is:  How else can we explain all that has happened EXCEPT by assuming there is a world-wide conspiracy to take control of our future?  THINK ABOUT IT.  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF  https://t.co/CYsBzVp0EB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Or are you trying to push some kind of scare campaign?"  I am MOST DEFINITELY pushing a scare campaign.  If you hadn't noticed ALL WESTERN COUNTRIES are following the same plan.  WHY IS THAT?  'No jab, no job' policy MAKES JABS MANDATORY.  #auspol  #CovidVaccine https://t.co/gYUrkdEpno]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THE FIGHT FOR FREEDOM IS NOT OVER!  Are you happy with the ILLEGAL RESTRICTIONS ON YOUR FREEDOM  since the start of the Covid-19 Emergency?  If you want to get your freedom back  THAT FIGHT FOR FREEDOM WILL HAVE COSTS.  ARE YOU READY TO PAY THE COSTS YET?  #auspol  #CovidVaccine https://t.co/gBRc5QnLw5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While the pro-mask, pro-lockdown people are often quite free with their insults and abuse of those of us they disagree with, we should simply IGNORE THE NOISE and get on with the job. We fight for them too!  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF https://t.co/9Gd0BklHde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rob_Ruadh: We Will Remember Them. https://t.co/4Kd7EHd8IY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOW FOR SOMETHING COMPLETELY DIFFERENT!  "In reality, all viruses are exosomes. Stated another way, scientists are discovering that all of these viruses originate in our own tissuesthey dont attack us from the outside."  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF  https://t.co/0G9u53Cq7d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lionnoise: @ZNeveri Cest magnifique! Prenons exemple! https://t.co/cg1ZdRywmv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: Surprise, Surprise?  They are all riding the gravy train   MPs and Scientific Advisors are heavily invested in Vaccine Indust]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS ADDS INSULT TO INJURY!  In addition to taking away our FREEDOM and pushing DANGEROUS and unnecessary jabs these BASTARDS fill their pockets with MONEY from their ILLEGAL activities!  #auspol  #CovidVaccine  #KBF https://t.co/t5o1lESPGC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: "They all are in this together"   The Covid Contracts UK https://t.co/fcBK41WK46]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS IS PRICELESS!  WATCH UK POLICE ON THE RUN!  Note some of the crowd are trying to protect them as they perform a "strategic retreat".  #auspol  #CovidVaccine https://t.co/AxHbnG04Vw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: Part 2 https://t.co/thikkmXYCm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: Police try to end party in Hyde Park and it backfires  People just had enough... https://t.co/pXXI2AJ9Ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LekkaMercedez: Look at what our disgusting governments have done, they caused this, the police need to join the ppl, they will always b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mariusknulst: DO YOU REMEMBER THIS  https://t.co/7jDeLfGvTJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Valkyrie20201: We owned Oxford Street  #uniteforfreedom https://t.co/XM01uj2y32]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>