<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@BDUTT Please message your contact number and location.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@anish_krishnan @CMOKerala We have informed the authorities. Thank you for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AAPKA_BAJRANGI @HemantSorenJMM @jharkhand181 @JharkhandPolice @CMOKerala @TheKeralaPolice @BJPKerala1 Have informed the authorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmitabhSanyal6 @CMOKerala @dpcknr @SPC_Kerala @KannurPolice @CMOfficeWB @COVResponseRNC Noted. Have informed the authorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nair_299 @timesofindia @CMOKerala @KeralaGovernor @chennaicorp @albyjohnV @chennithala @mathrubhuminews Can you please send us more details? Thank you for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SNavatar @MithileshKuma43 @JharkhandCMO @DalitRights @LateharDistrict @vijayanpinarayi @shailajateacher @dpcmpm @CMOKerala Have informed the authorities. Thank you for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AadilHasanAdv1 @PathakAmritaJNU @NitishKumar @DrMdJawaid1 @DKishanganj @vijayanpinarayi @CMOKerala @cpimspeak @INCKerala Have informed the authorities. Thank you for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RajnalkarSuhas @DgpKarnataka @DIPR_COVID19 Noted. Will inform the concerned authorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CMOKerala: Press Meet on #COVID19. Live from Kerala Government Secretariat. https://t.co/kKdU0Z6kMh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kadakampalli: 267 international tourists returned to London from Trivandrum/Kochi today.7 of the tourists were earlier tested positive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StrandedinIndia @PayalChaddha3 @UKinIndia @JanThompsonFCO @Kieran_drake We are sorry to hear about the situation. As we are in a nation-wide lockdown, there are some restrictions on inter-state travel. Can you provide us more details about the affected persons. We will try to help them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PayalChaddha3 @UKinIndia @JanThompsonFCO We can provide them assistance. Can you please message us more details?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NavakkuruchiDMK @CMOKerala @vijayanpinarayi We have the informed the authorities. Thank You for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AICCTUhq @vijayanpinarayi @CMOKerala We have the informed the authorities. They will contact these workers. Thank You for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PTTVOnlineNews Noted. We will inform the concerned authorities. Thank You for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeemanOfficial @CMOKerala Noted. We will inform the concerned authorities. Thank You for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tamilanntk @SeemanOfficial @CMOKerala Noted. We will inform the concerned authorities. Thank You for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sruthipillai19 Have informed the authorities. Thank you for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PradyotManikya We can provide them assistance. Can you please message us more details?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GokulRa69976626 @vijayanpinarayi We are sorry to hear about your situation. We will discuss your case with the authorities and will get back to you soon. If possible, can you message us the details? Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VismayaVinod10 @vijayanpinarayi We are sorry to hear about your situation. We will discuss your case with the authorities and will get back to you soon. If possible, can you message us the details? Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SomenMitraINC @vijayanpinarayi @CMOKerala @BPSinghINC_ @chennithala @IYC @INCIndia @RahulGandhi @priyankagandhi @ShashiTharoor @MamataOfficial @AITCofficial @PMOIndia @narendramodi @GauravGogoiAsm Have informed the authorities. Thank you for reporting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RJDforIndia @PKKunhalikutty @CMOKerala @vijayanpinarayi @ShashiTharoor @TheKeralaPolice @rojimjohn @yadavtejashwi We have forwarded this request to authorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ds_nice2 Connect with https://t.co/WEhnsdtksm for all requests related to Guest Workers in Kerala. This is the dedicated support channel for tracking requests related to those workers in Kerala who are from other Indian states. #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Connect with https://t.co/WEhnsdbJ3M for all requests related to Guest Workers in Kerala. This is the dedicated support channel for tracking requests related to those workers in Kerala who are from other Indian states. #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vijayanpinarayi: #COVID19 UPDATE | April 5 2020   8 new cases reported in the State, which include 6 imports  2 contact cases.  6 have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sri. Balram Kumar Upadhyay IPS, IGP  Commissioner of Police, TVM City @cptvmcity  interacted with more than 100 residents associations over video conferencing. He discussed issues related to enforcement, awareness, preparedness and confidence building measures.  #COVID19 https://t.co/lDaDnzocFl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are a guest worker in Kerala and in need of assistance or support, please contact the Toll-free Numbers given below. #COVID19 #BetterWorkingLives https://t.co/1jlEiHJSFm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kerala Government Opens Call Centre to receive Complaints from the Guest Workers. Government Officials fluent in Hindi, Bengali, Assamese, Oriya languages  have been appointed to attend the calls.    Toll Free NO :18004255214, 155214 #Covid19 #HelpLine https://t.co/1iLLr1znN5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dipdas1979 Noted, and handed over to respective authorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RinzuRajan Could you please provide the address and a phone number to contact?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mudassirmjs @CMOKerala We will pass this information to district authorities. Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*CMO Kerala COVID19 Centre*   CMO Kerala has started a COVID19 Centre on Twitter. You can connect with us here. We will listen and respond to your SOS messages and requests. Please tags us in your messages.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vijayanpinarayi: We must address the aspect of a probable "Response Fatigue" to lockdown | #COVID19  A society-level behavior change, e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vijayanpinarayi: Care For Guest Workers | #COVID19  Kerala hosts a large number of workers from other Indian States; the State consider]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/yZfZ79Dcg1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine. Fasting. https://t.co/wUxojcXt2U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Neurophysik What is wrong having studied from madrasa. They are like older form of schools. https://t.co/KKek0LW7dC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. He can take the vaccine.  Hope he is doing well after TACE procedure. https://t.co/lOSTzYyiGD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. Vaccine is safe in this . https://t.co/zKQcHEKloC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Camphor, clove, carom. DO NOT INCREASE BLOOD OXYGEN   Important thread  https://t.co/XOedC4Bq46]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Completely unnecessary and stigmatising. Please stop this. https://t.co/CEqB5Fn7tw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sro_kashmir: This Oxygen Concentrator we used to get for 42-45K inclusive of GST last year. Now the price being quoted is 69K+  12% G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[                     https://t.co/tNkh32z8Tc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Helplessness all around.  At times patients plead before doctors for help but to whom will doctors plead to??  RIP sir.  https://t.co/V3t8oaQgpw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@islahmufti Do you think anyone can tell the unwanted facts and still continue on the chair?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @juneymb: Jugaad, in my opinion, is a deadly sin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I fear it might not be far when the whole blame is put on hospitals and doctors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/doc6dmx7Ck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bismahmalik Heartfelt condolences. May Allah reward the departed soul.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SOSbanglore https://t.co/ttIIfVCf4n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rj_vijdan   Do you know the name of the legendary news reader we have grown listening to this accent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pandemic or no pandemic, we need a robust healthcare system.   Not just temporary stadiums turned hospitals, but permanent hospitals. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*or NO pand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pandemic or on pandemic, we need a robust healthcare system.   Not just temporary stadiums turned hospitals, but permanent hospitals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every single death is painful.  Every single soul deserves mourning.  People are not just digits in a chart.  Fatality is low or notThe families left behind are devastated.  Rest in peaceall the COVID victims.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrKaloo: Dont wait for RT-PCR results!  If you have symptoms and think you might have COVID, measure Oxygen saturation (SpO2).   If Sp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ManzoorWagay2 Perception management]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/JzJc6UbAc2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indias fatality rate is the lowest in the world: Dr Harsh Vardhan, Union Health Minister https://t.co/tBY2t0RKVg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thewire_in: Former Indian ambassador to Brunei, Mozambique and Algeria, Ashok Amrohi, passed away after midnight on April 27 while wait]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SOSDelhi  @jaynavin_15 https://t.co/pW96MyctHJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Verified.  Many vaccine centres are running out of stock. https://t.co/8ekuwwi4sP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: Heart-wrenchingA mother in her 50s dies of #COVID19 after she had low oxygen. But theres no ambulance, so her dead body i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Salute to all the nurses, medical staff and volunteers for braving this pandemic.   https://t.co/juUeJn24D3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@juneymb ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now working again. Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AliyaNazki Same here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whenever I try to join @TwitterSpaces, my @Twitter app is crashes.  Does iOS14.5 have to do anything with this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/qBzHOPFHSR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@syedzakiahmed_ https://t.co/U6sc4nsSsG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrKaloo: Best vitamins https://t.co/bjyErEbiA2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No.  Allergy to vaccine components is a contraindication for vaccination. Other allergies are not. https://t.co/GZl97269VA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@burgerrkhan Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AruViva I am here in my personal capacity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/zrYcKl8WYO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best wishes https://t.co/WJKFQhZcwO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/hHzABc5gMD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isolation for symptomatic https://t.co/qSrI8XsoKv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Symptoms https://t.co/VD0KjxUTsH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/SNcMsu1yz0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Self medication https://t.co/UbYZxWRhsw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best vitamins https://t.co/bjyErEbiA2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/9Tt0Sj7fGS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/3SpoYsk40n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/Rehl7yEsDx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine https://t.co/AT7nA7YmqZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyderabad https://t.co/aj5XgHVVL8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[M. Tariq Jamil  https://t.co/BGhm4lgLii]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pick up your phone-  Call   /  Text   /  Video Chat    with your family  friends. They need you as much you need someone right now!  Retweet  #Anxiety #depression #Covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Zebaism: Still looking for this. #SOSDelhi #COVIDEmergency2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#sosDelhi @syedzakiahmed_ https://t.co/C1VbSlk6rg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wish same firm rules applied to OTHERS which apply to ordinary man. https://t.co/w74c0VEQbg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrKaloo: If you have any ONE or more symptoms (cough, fever, sore throat, severe headache, diarrhoea, body pain)  Do these steps in ord]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every 1 minute = more than 2 deaths   #COVIDSecondWave https://t.co/7IdCKBvnzq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Srinagar https://t.co/L4e3Lmddyu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ye gai trath https://t.co/AshSTr6191]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@keithppereira Yes. Most private hospitals and many private practitioners provide virtual consultation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have any ONE or more symptoms (cough, fever, sore throat, severe headache, diarrhoea, body pain)  Do these steps in order  1. Isolate 2. Measure temperature  Oxygen  3. Seek telephonic consultation 4. Discuss with doctor if you need COVID test  Remember 1 is Isolate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@juneymb ...and conclude by deciding the date for next such meeting]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>