<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do people turn a blind eye to the downsides of vaccines?! A close friend of mine got the COVID vaccine and died in a plane crash a week later. That cant be a coincidence! Wake up sheeple! #Antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Awithonelison: #Antivaxers/#COVIDIOTS : "You've been brainwashed by mainstream media!"  ...links to YouTube video.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@akedpa Ive been busy killing children through neglect! Its exhausting!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that vaccines kill 200% of people they are given to? #AntiVaxx #StayWoke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anti-Vaxx parenting tip: Count your childs age in dog years to increase their life expectancy to a normal amount!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rsb366 @pfizer Lies! You dont look dead!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Justsomekidhah1 @AntiVaxxed365 Enjoy your long life, moron!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SciencePharmer I have Bing search results, will that suffice?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@puretruthcouk @gluhwein11 My children wont be getting vaccines either! You can take that shit to the bank too! Well, that or the funeral home...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shellity Admittedly, logical thoughts are not one of our strengths.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SciencePharmer Hey! Alta Vista is cutting edge for an antivaxxer such as myself!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SciencePharmer No I dont! I simply need to search it in Alta Vista!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ENirenberg But I dont like that the answer doesnt reinforce what I already believe!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @The_Ohioan_: https://t.co/wVL92IB3Zj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ENirenberg What if youre antivaxx solely because you hate your kids and need a way out? Asking for a friend...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/22X0i7I6Mv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If someone like @elonmusk doesnt vaccinate, thats should be all the rest of us need to know! Its not like his behavior over the past few years should make us question his competency.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ytho59725771 Something something conspiracy theory.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BadHealthAdvice: Breathe more easily by cutting a hole in your mask https://t.co/GY5X45zpaN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone tried telling me about all the benefits of vaccines while I was on my smoke break earlier. Dont they know how many chemicals are in those things! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Christi77069937 Words cannot even begin to explain what is wrong with my kind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that 100% of people who are vaccinated eventually die?! #AntiVaxx #FactsMatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3KLwKyvTaH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TCS_helloanddie @myunclesmemes We are a pretty dumb bunch. Its an easy way to make money off of us!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YoniFreedhoff If she lived that long, it means you vaccinated her. Im disappointed in you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schools had better open back up this Fall! I dont want these little shits around me anymore! If I wanted them around long term, I would have gotten them vaccinated!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Nr3NVFMz8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Or should I say, lack thereof.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interestingly enough, the fact that Im letting my child play with dangerous explosives today isnt the worst thing about my parenting abilities!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wYrg9R2gVh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Fathers Day to the man who gave me the children I use as pawns in my misguided ill conceived cause! #AntiVaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0obFtG5cj2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden No way! Daddy Trump told me to do it, so Im gonna do it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ActingTheGom Such an adorable little girl. I wonder if her mother has picked out her coffin yet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blainetilley Thats cause theyre dead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ash_OLeary: Anti-vaxxers: Im not injecting myself with some #BillGates poison.  #Trump: I see the disinfectant that knocks it out in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@limolnar @AutistTrainGuy Wait, so I shouldnt have injected Clorox into my son?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crumbfollower_Q I know! Big pharma only wants to make money so we cant trust them! Big automotive also only wants to make money, so Im not driving anymore either. Big housing is the same, so Ive decided to be homeless. #antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is great advice! Break your arm? Just drink some water!  Does your ear hurt? Just order some garlic knots from favorite restaurant! https://t.co/QwQ1tqX9UY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MsTrixter @provaxtexan https://t.co/Voc5DN3EF5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@provaxtexan @MsTrixter Why is she taking such offense? Its a badge I wear with pride!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I went to my states capital to protest this draconian lockdown! I mean, I waited in the car and made my kids go outside to hold the signs. You didnt think Id actually stand by my convictions, did you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@luthra_anita @ProAntiVaxxer Oh so very!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neiltyson I am smart! Ive done all the research I need to using Google!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@creature4hire @ProAntiVaxxer @Autism @AutismSociety @NationalAutism I knew it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im quarantining from my children. No one in the household is sick, I just hate those little shits.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mcgrathew33 The solution is clearly more vagina scented candles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mcgrathew33: Has anyone asked Gwyneth Paltrow what we should be doing about all of this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@provaxtexan To be fair, we do all of our research with Google, and he uses Bing! Its like comparing apples and oranges!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After I inevitably and inexplicably survive this pandemic, I will self-righteously proclaim how unnessecery vaccines are, all while ignoring the massive amount of people who perished from it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@manzoni77441525 https://t.co/EMru4a9jL2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZosKiaCultus666 Way ahead of you! My treatment method involves drinking a cup of bleach with a few drops of lavender essential oil!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CaraMia200 Most of us are dead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was able to cure my sons Coronavirus without the help of Big Pharma! I just had him drink a cup of bleach! I mean, hes dead now, but he doesnt have Coronavirus anymore! #Antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is all the death and dispair from this pandemic making anyone else really horny, or is it just me?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TeddyFreddy11 @ryarmst @TeddyFreddy11 is right! Childrens lives are at stake and we must do all we can to extinguish them! #Antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You dont have to vaccinate all of your children, just the ones you want to keep! #Antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fiski70 Dammit!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fiski70 Thank you. Its hard to find time for Twitter when your kids are always sick. I dont get how they can get so many sicknesses when Ive given them so many essential oils!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wait, isnt that the point of what us antivaxxers are doing? Harming our children while maintaining the illusion that we care about them? https://t.co/3Qd1zKmYNY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BadHealthAdvice: It's 2020.   Just tell the disease that you do not consent to it being in you, and you'll be alright.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines cause the gay! Ive been saying this for years! https://t.co/6408PFDqwM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally! https://t.co/NRJiHVq6jm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Totally not true! My parents had me vaccinated so I have nothing to worry about. Its my children who will pay the price for my stupidity, and frankly, its a price worth paying! https://t.co/7ptbnP0HVV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check and mate! https://t.co/IqzAGmuBjB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rex_gw @Kim_Wiggins Antivaxx, anti-living. Call it what you will.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that vaccines contain dihydrogen monoxide? What kind of parent would let their child near such a substance! #DoYourResearch #AntiVaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Reeeeee37097151 I need to see if I can get a punch card for child deaths!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My son stepped on a rusty nail and the doctor said the only thing that could help him was a tetanus shot. So yeah... hes dead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmykims33 You clearly did not use the appropriate essential oils.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SciencePharmer No, its not sleep, its silent autism!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My son wanted to go trick-or-treating, but his polio makes it difficult. If only this could have been prevented! I cant help but feel like this is everyone elses fault but mine!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most people go to cemeteries on Halloween to be spooky. Us anti-vaxxers go to visit our children. #antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Costume? This is reality! https://t.co/cifO9GuWCx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is so me! https://t.co/F0R3rS2mRh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notfromseattle Amen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedwheeler Has the autism set in yet?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@XC_Enel So true. Most of my kids havent lived into their double-digits!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are completely unnecessary. Ive never vaccinated my children and the one who lived turned out fine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My son has skin cancer. The doctors recommended a number of treatments, but I know the the only real cure is to put him in direct sunlight and let it burn the cancer out of him. Its the only all natural cure! #antivaxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@s8n Better they be your problem, not mine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My son used to fall asleep at 9 every night. On the night he got vaccinated, he wasnt able to fall asleep until 9:30. The vaccine clearly has destroyed his sleep schedule for life!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ugh, sometimes I just want to pack up what's left of my family and move to a 3rd world country!   #AntiVaxxNations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obtained the results of a groundbreaking study on https://t.co/bQUkH5L77S before it's official release! Apparently 99% of children under 5 are way too reliant on Oxygen. Unless you reside in Tajikistan, practicing breathing deprivation is strongly advised. #AttackWithFacts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@4256Apple @RepMaryFranson @kristinsullivan @delbigtree Ill have to check these out! It will take awhile to get through them all, but what else am I going to do with my time? Not care for my children, thats for sure!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Williesillie2 Yes! Soon you wont have a personality at all because youll be dead from a preventable disease!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SciencePharmer Dont argue with this. 20 hours of research is far superior to years of medical school!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoqueteLove @SimonGr41594862 Im going to pass. While us antivaxxers are capable of reading, we seem to lack basic comprehensive abilities. Im afraid it would just be lost on me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Science doesnt lie! https://t.co/0ifDkTwkjN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Andree1990 Never. We dont admit fault for anything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jameshamblin Ridiculous! I treat all my childrens sicknesses with my own brand of lavender essential oils and some of them are still alive!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MAhealthforkids @TheKidKidDoc But what if you dont care about your kids like us antivaxxers?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@avoiceforchoice @MinnReb Yes, VictoriaAdvocate! Everyone knows shes more reputable than the CDC!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TeddyFreddy11 @AmandaPinkley1 Ah yes, Gibiru! Everyone knows of this highly reputable website!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarenMccartny @KarenWachowski Because I read it somewhere on a Facebook post so it must be true!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pediatricskc @TheKidKidDoc But they dont work to protect my ego from being proven wrong! I wont ever admit wrongdoing, even if it means putting my childs health at risk!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just traded in my pediatrician for a mortician! #AntiVaxxMomLife]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jake_mcclure @drfixus Its almost worse!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmandaPinkley1 Same]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BigBoyOlimario Shhhh! Dont let our secret out!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>