<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: Citizen committees and citizen  common law courts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ukboffin1 just what i thought]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Neely1717 @antilockdownTT Count politicians walking through the door of the ICC. https://t.co/nAKWyE2NdH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VanessaGray158 Totally agree, it is quite incredible.  And the house of commons just allows it all to happen they are all complicit and should be ashamed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VanessaGray158: Every Govt directive since March 2020 has made people sicker. Every single one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is amazing how much crap people are taking. Unreal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/ykua66guBh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Globalist hell on earth https://t.co/M7ZnOnvDTf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You've taken our freedoms, the fun out of life, isolated us, psychologically attacked us. Used of coercive tactics to  -create billions for the pharmaceutical industry  -get us under your control -create huge debts You've caused immeasurable suffering You want us to vote for you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I thought there was no magic money tree?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville It should be stopped.  Absolutely unjustifed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: If furlough was stopped, i suspect the majority of the country would suddenly hate lockdowns.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Iromg  @ToniaBuxton talking real sense just now on @talkRADIO 175 lost to sucide A WEEK in the UK. Why the HELL are we talking about covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love this  https://t.co/gioMzDVidt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Johan12216: @AI_Clayton I would def support the military taking over at this point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/DECA7zPbUm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Your lives, livelihood, civil liberties, freedoms are currently  in the hands of a tiny few career politicians and bure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @In_Hope_: @AI_Clayton A non violent approach is essential. 'They' want riots, violence, to justify bringing in their forces. We must ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abi__bee: @AI_Clayton Where are you @BritishArmy? We need you!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: No tyranical government anywhere should be allowed to remain in power - they should be ousted by citizens and replaced. Thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ITS A START  https://t.co/IkBO34T1JY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Coercion in any facet for anything at all is NOT consent.  Simple fact....and there seems to be an awful lot of judgeme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What **** has it got to do with an ice cream maker? https://t.co/6XNH4N4BCz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@a5a2a335e2fa44e This is unreal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NHSuk A change in strategy? Less nasty advertising? Less evil? Hmmm ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Farinances: 'Essential' workers - You survived the deadly plague for a whole year without a 'vaccine'  What makes you think you need on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020's Communist Party Leader. Hijacker of the "Conservatives" Don't vote communist next week. Vote INDEPENDENT https://t.co/IP7vDv8mFp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HughJardon70 My thoughts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/7ZUEXtm0Fg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Vicster82: Liar!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/Kvtq9lu9tb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDelingpole: 10 per cent of Italians had CV antibodies in Sept 19 https://t.co/HC2ws8MOjQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serious question.  Will OAPs have a flu jab AND a covid jab in 2021?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DominicFrisby: Parliament last night https://t.co/j5nZraKGMi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Politicians pretend to care.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A group of researchers from Norway have filed a lawsuit against the corona policy. https://t.co/85ee3Y96BB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brothrstrawbrry: @Demo2020cracy Would someone please explain how denying people access to food, healthcare, public spaces or social gat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SharpieDj: High court judgement today on wearing masks in school...  Do we know when we are likely to hear the judgement?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LozzaFox: Seeing as Im trending, Id like to reiterate that the people of this country have bent over backwards to protect the @NHSuk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[G7. Elected dictatorship,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Government is NOT for the people. It's for the ELITE!!!!!!!!  They HATE the rest of us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ricky58766053: @Demo2020cracy It's starting..we must stop this nonsense now...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK wake the **** up already  https://t.co/NQXSqh0vYs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HumanRights4UK: Our purpose is to inform EVERY citizen of the UK of their fundamental Human Rights. If these were taught in every schoo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: NOT ON BBC 'NEWS': BELGIAN POLICE TRAMPLE PROTESTORS (It's for your safety!)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ella32823623 How much longer ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WAKE UP https://t.co/d5CNwgApPh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: How the UK's Covid reopening has proved Imperial's pessimistic modelling wrong   https://t.co/rV1XmktAgH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: #ToryCorruption #BorisJohnsonOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: Of course the real irony is that we are "protecting the NHS" as they continue to decimate it. #ResignHancock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Green swastika, a new tory party logo.?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Masks are fascistic symbology on kids faces.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democracy was FAUX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deeply evil government.  Tell me you can see too. https://t.co/SwkZKOYqt8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock You are an evil man, high on a sick power trip.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarieDBaker: Very good point. Where is the current emergency in the U.K.? https://t.co/bPPg3oQV2b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jimac111: PMs brother becomes director of Dyson the week after they ask their tax problems to be fixed. Coincidence obviously. Voting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidKe52871220: Liz truss pushing vaccinations and new global world order shocking and scary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Just heard from a friend who like me has been ill for 2 months since having the AZ vax. He also noted a friend who had]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: A vaccinated person is still at risk of getting Covid (but are likely to have reduced symptoms because of the vaccine).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOT ON BBC 'NEWS': BELGIAN POLICE TRAMPLE PROTESTORS (It's for your safety!) https://t.co/wVM8pT04fg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: My crystal ball tells me we need to open up this country NOW before it is too late.   Well, it is actually already too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FunTimeFred1: Your chances of winning the U.K. Lotto:  One in 45 million   Your chances of dying with Covid:  One in 67 million]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/6ZVifGMYUk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SimonPearson961: Liz Truss gave the entire game away. They are not stopping with restrictions until they have jabbed everyone on the pl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SassyCoopster: @Sacha_Lord Roll on Nuremberg....  https://t.co/AtSSPi4WTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angiebUK: @Sacha_Lord It makes perfect sense as this is all about digital ID now which is why the vaccine is being rolled out to those]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: Theres a reason youve not seen your GP recently  and frankly its a scandal by the excellent @allisonpearson   https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GoodLawProject: NEW: Cross-party group calls for action against the Prime Minister for misleading Parliament over multibillion pound Co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrunoAm05317727: Poll: Has Boris Johnson done a good job during the pandemic? Vote and retweet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GroundedGoddess: I'll just leave this here.... https://t.co/VgNoSkdIk6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bradley31761624: @Demo2020cracy Democracies? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernieSpofforth 6uild 6ack 6etter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chunkymark: Unfcknbelievable!!!  https://t.co/C1RailmgtQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How dark  sinister do they look? https://t.co/v5X12YGD7S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kmacbean123: Looking for a UK based psychologist who is currently deeply concerned about the current status quo and would be keen to jo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Freedom49503795: Have people started to put vaccinated against covid on their CV yet?   I'm vaccinated against BS does that count for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#endLockdowns https://t.co/qSBjCU7VPw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The reason you cannot drink indoors at your local is that you are under the tyrannical rule of the elite. They are laughing at us meet mortals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @__ItisWritten__: Just wondering who still thinks their government cares about them? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lorobawa: @chrissaccoccia1 @Demo2020cracy So sad to see Canada fall to tyranny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: If someone has a different opinion, dont be a twat by trying to undermine or mock them. Try and get to know them, liste]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrissaccoccia1: Just a crazy conspriacy theory...  https://t.co/v6MmQjD5v8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrissaccoccia1: So I just spent 3 weeks, barely sleeping and eating as we were driving upwards of 12 hours per day. Spent countless ho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy10: Moderna plans to produce up to 3 billion COVID-19 vaccine doses next year, citing a 'significant need' for shots and b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy10: Woman arguing for mask mandates almost passes out from lack of oxygen https://t.co/JEGHIfq5XW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/sPLp21Mou6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOT ON BBC NEWS: GO! #NAPLES!! https://t.co/b8wDJhsTkO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: I was told travel bans were racist and xenophobic... What changed??? https://t.co/6GXQomnhu9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy10: Whoopi Goldberg: I'm not going outside until I know everybody outside has had the shot... https://t.co/1Ml7i9lJuh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SuzanneEvans1: Oh do shut up. You don't give a damn about kids.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeeHurstComic: NZ just missing the A and I now to finish the rebranding. https://t.co/mA2SxnOhMQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Oh yes, please do respect their privacy as they continue their 'mission' to utterly deprive you of yours.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamgarriereal: One of @bobscartoons's best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abiroberts @JamesDelingpole @naomirwolf Really a very good interview. Delingpods should be available on prescription.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abiroberts: This is one of the best things Ive ever watched. When this time in history is written about, fearless journalists like @Ja]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @siana7772: @Demo2020cracy Similar to whats happening in India with the mass protest by farmers against the governments new agricultur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: https://t.co/oIpCleaqwI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: when big corporations are off the leash and in tandem with govt thats fascism or corporatism as mussolini termed it. CORPORAT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ COME ON, ITS TIME TO SPEAK UP! SNAP OUT OF THE FEAR https://t.co/LasIC751m2]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>