<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are so many #dems so full of #hate, Always nasty, disrespectful in debate? They never seem to have an open mind. In disagreement they're very cruel, unkind. It's to the point that one can tell One's a dem very well By their nasty remarks alone Because of bitterness they hone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip70932970 @wef Yeah  #communists r in power right now many don't realize. Both gates  China r buying up our farmland at alarming rates. U can't wake ppl up tho 2 see the big picture 2 see what #BidenAdmin's doing is inching us 2 the #GreatReset of #NWO. The #BuildBackBetter slogan confirms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[B/c #integrity  #principles can keep the wallet lean Those who can't b bought r few  far between. Those who stand on #MoralGround, answer not 2 greed R extremely rare altho more of them we need. When ppl lust 4 money, power  control They'll forfeit anything along w/their soul. https://t.co/u98jAT75Ci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CRRJA5 @jjauthor @RealDrGina @KristySwansonXO @atensnut @DFBHarvard @BernardKerik @tomborelli @SandraSentinel @SaraCarterDC @catturd2 B/c #integrity  #principles can keep the wallet lean Those who can't b bought r few  far between. Those who stand on #MoralGround, answer not 2 greed R extremely rare altho more of them we need. When ppl lust 4 money, power  control They'll forfeit anything along w/their soul.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip70932970 @wef Yep. Pushing #NWO agenda, force us all in2 cities, packed in gov housing like sardines, they take all the land, control food  they can take millions of us out at a time. #InfrastructureBill'll mandate #GND upgrades most can't afford = gov seizure of homes/property. Ppl r blind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wanna know why.. lumber prices are so high? I wonder who is getting paid to leave HUGE amounts of lumber piled and not delivered? #LumberEmbargo Make it unaffordable to have/build a home. #GreatReset plan to take everything from us as the @wef is saying. https://t.co/fcf3EhcGGr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@JoeBiden @BarackObama @HillaryClinton @JohnBrennan IF EVERY American knew the #truth of ur WICKED deeds u wouldn't dare 2 walk outside ur homes! #Benghazi #SEALTeam6 murdered #Iran #blackmail deal #BinLaden decoy = obama's #TrophyKill #epstein #pedoring https://t.co/4jmZNiU6qH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not disclosing vital info so ppl can know how 2 protect themselves  using #censorship 2 w/hold vital info is absolutely CRIMINAL. 1000s have died b/c of this. All guilty should b held accountable 4 murder/accessories 2 murder. This is worldwide #genocide! https://t.co/W55nD8vsxU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Out of sight, out of mind An easy cop out 2 stay blind. Willful #ignorance is no excuse 2 treat 1's #oath w/abuse. When serving the ppl is ur job But u serve not, then u rob We, the ppl  our nation. Ur position calls 4 termination. @Liz_Cheney #election #fraud coverup w/#BigLie https://t.co/gzIVKHCpNY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernardKerik Out of sight, out of mind An easy cop out 2 stay blind. Willful #ignorance is no excuse 2 treat 1's #oath w/abuse. When serving the ppl is ur job But u serve not, then u rob We, the ppl  our nation. Ur position calls 4 termination. @Liz_Cheney #election #fraud coverup w/#BigLie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When we learn extreme approaches don't bring solutions 2 either right or left in seeking resolutions But somewhere in the middle there can b found A place where we all can find #CommonGround. Extremes r never good either left or right  egos keep solutions always out of sight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Progressive #democrats r #communists 4 real Who plotted WICKED schemes 2, our #election, steal. Then there r the #RINOs who share the same Who in name only #republican they claim. From the same mold they r all made. #NWO #globalists 4 greed, America they'll trade. #BigLie coverup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well now, IF it wasn't stolen, what's the harm in PROVING it wasn't? It's pretty hard 2 dispute MOUNTAINS of #evidence that CLEARLY shows there was all sorts of #cheating, #fraud  #ForeignInterference caught in realtime by top cyber experts. All #globalists protect the BIG Lie! https://t.co/xR1jTFD53E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney Well now, IF it wasn't stolen, what's the harm in PROVING it wasn't? It's pretty hard 2 dispute MOUNTAINS of #evidence that CLEARLY shows there was all sorts of #cheating, #fraud  #ForeignInterference caught in realtime by top cyber experts. All #globalists protect the BIG Lie!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #1619Project is all about indoctrinating our children 2 hate America so they'll b willing 2 accept the fall of America 2 the #NWO, a one totalitarian gov ruling the entire world, run by the #GlobalElite, the most WICKED beings on the planet who plan 2 take EVERYTHING -&gt; @wef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck The CIA has a number of #MindControl operations. They program selected individuals to carry out WICKED deeds for them, like #shooters in #MassShootings to help push #Biden's #GunControl agenda. #WakeUp people! https://t.co/iozGCNAbKW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CIA has a number of #MindControl operations. They program selected individuals to carry out WICKED deeds for them, like #shooters in #MassShootings to help push #Biden's #GunControl agenda. #WakeUp people! https://t.co/iozGCNAbKW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Eugenics under hitler = atrocious horrendously cruel experiments on humans/murder of deemed 'inferior' (99.9%) by the elite (.1%) who believe they're 'superior' race, ONLY should procreate -&gt; to U.S. =&gt; #ReproductiveHealthcare =&gt; #PlannedParenthood by gates father =&gt; @BillGates https://t.co/zP7bHdsQLy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksorbs #Eugenics under hitler = atrocious horrendously cruel experiments on humans/murder of deemed 'inferior' (99.9%) by the elite (.1%) who believe they're 'superior' race, ONLY should procreate -&gt; to U.S. =&gt; #ReproductiveHealthcare =&gt; #PlannedParenthood by gates father =&gt; @BillGates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loss of freedom and rights #SocialismIn5Words  Wealthy few, the rest poor. Widespread persecution, slaughter of people. Government owns and controls EVERYthing. Citizens are turned into subjects. Destroys incentive, innovation and creativity. Subjects must worship the government.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why r they all still wearing #masks  staying 6 feet apart, when they've all been "supposedly" #vaccinated? Either, they know the shot doesn't actually work -or- they know the shot is dangerous  "pretended" 2 get it -or- both. Regardless which, they're LYING! #Coverup #SOTU https://t.co/9pdNbVQhcN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The EVIL intention behind #VaxPassports is to gain FULL control over the world's population. It's the agenda of the @wef and the #NWO's #GreatReset for #WorldDomination by the most WICKED beings on the planet! #Virus =&gt; #panDEMic =&gt; global tyranny. https://t.co/WcpHa3u3P0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kenkircher1 @NRA @wef Wow, such an important point to make that's totally irrelevant that I doubt you'd understand or care if I explained  to explain would take more than a tweet. Whether someone ELSE likes what I tweet or not is not important to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kenkircher1 @NRA Stay asleep. Wallow in ignorance. It's the easiest path to follow but the cost is going to be astronomical and the @wef has it all planned out w/their #BuildBackBetter slogan that #Biden FULLY supports.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For those who aren't paying attention 2 the @wef's agenda, w/its goal 2 take everything leaving us w/nothing  #biden supports, the #InfrastructureBill is 2 start the seizing of property, etc  is why they aim 2 disarm us. See the bigger picture! #2A  https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9 https://t.co/I3L7uzM8k1 https://t.co/9dPwgeZO1Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NRA For those who aren't paying attention 2 the @wef's agenda, w/its goal 2 take everything leaving us w/nothing  #biden supports, the #InfrastructureBill is 2 start the seizing of property, etc  is why they aim 2 disarm us. See the bigger picture! #2A https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kenkircher1 @NRA It's explained in the beginning part of this video. https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Those who think it's ok 2 take away our guns, I wonder how they'll take Biden  commie dems w/their #GND taking away our homes, property  cars? This is the plan tucked in the #InfrastructureBill. When they come 4 ur home  everything else they plan 2 take u'll wish u had a gun. https://t.co/I3L7uzM8k1 https://t.co/cLPMV80yHv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Those who think it's ok 2 take away our guns, I wonder how they'll take Biden  commie dems w/their #GND taking away our homes, property  cars? This is the plan tucked in the #InfrastructureBill. When they come 4 ur home  everything else they plan 2 take u'll wish u had a gun. https://t.co/I3L7uzM8k1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NRA Those who think it's ok 2 take away our guns, I wonder how they'll take Biden  commie dems w/their #GND taking away our homes, property  cars? This is the plan tucked in the #InfrastructureBill. When they come 4 ur home  everything else they plan 2 take u'll wish u had a gun. https://t.co/q8YVbQsSYg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #hellywood elite's favorite cuisine Is human flesh young, tender  lean. At the #CannibalClub they like to dine And drink children's blood as their wine. ALL must awaken to what doesn't show. Their #WICKED deeds the world must know. #oscars #satanic #baal #SaveTheChildren]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Hellywood's carpet on which celebrities stroll Is BLOOD RED SHED from the lives they stole Of innocent children who couldn't escape Their acts of abuse of torture and rape And they've sacrificed to/for baal, To harvest #adrenochrome, their drug  ale. #oscars #luciferians #EVIL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If everyone KNEW what they do with/to innocent babies  children, everyone except the #pedos  #cannibals like the #hellywood elite would never watch what the WICKED do. In fact the participators in their WICKED acts would be forced to hide from sight. #BloodStainedCarpet #oscars https://t.co/ghoj1NwyuM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JennaEllisEsq If everyone KNEW what they do with/to innocent babies  children, everyone except the #pedos  #cannibals like the #hellywood elite would never watch what the WICKED do. In fact the participators in their WICKED acts would be forced to hide from sight. #BloodStainedCarpet #oscars]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stained w/blood, the carpet of RED They parade on from children dead Who've they've tortured, raped, killed 4 sadistic pleasures they've filled. #Pedophiles, #cannibals, 4 satan's glee Parade in #hellywood as a celebrity On satan's stage of WICKED sin The #oscars honor yet again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a perfect example of #DemLogic. But don't think they're really stupid or crazy. They want us to think so, so we'll dismiss the idiotic things they do. What @TheDemocrats are doing is DELIBERATE to destroy our country. #MAGA #SaveAmerica from WICKED #communist #globalists! https://t.co/8eqmzfkjY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanScavino This is a perfect example of #DemLogic. But don't think they're really stupid or crazy. They want us to think so, so we'll dismiss the idiotic things they do. What the democrats are doing is DELIBERATE to destroy our country.#MAGA #SaveAmerica from WICKED #communist #globalists!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Used as #pawns unwittingly #Brainwashed by lies extensively With #ignorance bred Drilled in their head Many comply as they aid Unaware of being played Against themselves, against us ALL By #globalists serving a WICKED cabal. We awake try to warn But very thick is embedded scorn. https://t.co/BwPYZD0Wgc https://t.co/FwXb6qVrLj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnnyO74614472 @DanScavino Used as #pawns unwittingly #Brainwashed by lies extensively With #ignorance bred Drilled in their head Many comply as they aid Unaware of being played Against themselves, against us ALL By #globalists serving a WICKED cabal. We awake try to warn But very thick is embedded scorn. https://t.co/wkWTfnemKn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The more @TheDemocrats resist transparency the more transparent is their guilt. If they've nothing 2 hide, they'd want 2 prove the true outcome of #election2020. Elementary. It's THEIR actions that spotlights THEIR guilt of #fraud. They're #Globalists  cheated 4 #NWO's fruition. https://t.co/GSzpjxqREy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler The more @TheDemocrats resist transparency the more transparent is their guilt. If they've nothing 2 hide, they'd want 2 prove the true outcome of #election2020. Elementary. It's THEIR actions that spotlights THEIR guilt of #fraud. They're #Globalists  cheated 4 #NWO's fruition.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@Twitter has deactivated #SaveTheChildren hashtag? Twitter doesn't want children 2 b saved from being raped, tortured, sacrificed 4 sadistic pleasure  their blood harvested 4 the elite's #adrenochrome fix? Does raising awareness of #pedophilia go against #CommunityStandards?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These same WICKED #globalist beings who rape, torture  kill innocent children FOR PLEASURE are the same ones responsible for unleashing covid as a strategy to gain complete control of the world, #NWO. #SaveTheChildren from #adrenochrome harvesting! https://t.co/XBxrE7kQs4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They're so blatantly arrogant they can't see the more they work 2 prevent #truth the more guilty they PROVE themselves 2 b. Only liars  cheaters r afraid of the truth. In their opposition 2 transparency, the more transparent THEY r. If they didn't cheat they'd want it proven. https://t.co/q2OZjGpYn8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KerryPetrauskas @NickAdamsinUSA They're so blatantly arrogant they can't see the more they work 2 prevent #truth the more guilty they PROVE themselves 2 b. Only liars  cheaters r afraid of the truth. In their opposition 2 transparency, the more transparent THEY r. If they didn't cheat they'd want it proven.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ClimateCrisis is the polluting of earth w/#ToxicChemicals by #globalists. If they REALLY cared about our planet they'd stop polluting our air/water/ground (that's producing toxic food) w/toxic chemicals. Why save a planet that'll b 2 toxic 2 live on? #NWO #scam 4 world control. https://t.co/PdnB6FvVDs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@JoeBiden @SpeakerPelosi @JohnKerry @RepAOC and all the rest of you devil worshipers with satanic #NWO agenda, baby killers, trans-sterilizing of children, criminal praisers, liars, cheats  thieves who stole #election2020, hell awaits your arrival! https://t.co/jy81UQYLrU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The #EmperorsNewClothes, in #truth he was bare, But 2 say truth, he was naked, no 1 would dare." ~ #Artsieladie #quote This fable surely fits the theme in America now. @RealCandaceO tells it like it is which we should all b doing, calling out the BS. https://t.co/kzOqvng7EQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Candace Owens: 'Systemic oppression' in America is mass producing 'failures' |  https://t.co/yr7SwG0vpL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bulletin: COVID Vaccines Could Cause Irreversible Harm! CDC NOT Telling You  Ledger Report 1113! | Frank Speech the https://t.co/kGbcfLCRTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When a jury's faced w/coming 2 a just verdict -OR- keeping themselves/loved 1s safe, which will most select? #BLM  #antifa mobs have replaced our justice system, making themselves judge  jury. The root cause is drugs which the EVIL #CIA puts on our streets. #DerekChauvinTrial]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DerekChauvin: The true verdict we'll never know because the #terroristmobs have become the judge and jury in this country which are encouraged by the left for their #communist agenda and #MSM FULLY supports. Hell awaits for ALL the disgusting and despicable complicit traitors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If u'r believing all the lies said By #MSM  the fed  r obeying, going along W/it all altho it's wrong, U'r a #sheep, dumb  blind, 2 lazy 2 bother 2 look 4, find, The #truth  u'r benefiting Corruption  2 fear, submitting, Risking rights of every1 B/c #research u haven't done.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When all ppl believe all the lies 2 b #truth  truth they believe 2 b the lies, the human race will b primed  ready 2 b fully subservient  then led 2 its demise. Only truth will keep us free  ultimately save humanity. Lies: #CovidVax #planDEMic #ClimateCrisis #GunControl https://t.co/MzIpHQRcs7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ez_dee When all ppl believe all the lies 2 b #truth  truth they believe 2 b the lies, the human race will b primed  ready 2 b fully subservient  then led 2 its demise. Only truth will keep us free  ultimately save humanity. Lies: #CovidVax #planDEMic #ClimateCrisis #GunControl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FreeSpeech #AmericaFirst #Patriots #SavingAmerica  #PatriotsDay Live stream now! https://t.co/DyhFX42Swm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CHIZMAGA #FreeSpeech #AmericaFirst #Patriots #SavingAmerica  #PatriotsDay Live stream now! https://t.co/DyhFX42Swm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes! Fight for Freedom! https://t.co/DyhFX42Swm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're 2 believe this whole #covid fiasco happened by accident, when the wealthiest control freaks  puppets have milked it 4 all it's worth every which way but loose. If u'r still in a #woke stupor u'll believe this but if awakened, u know it's all a scam. https://t.co/iE3ZLclybq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@madrasvinod This is a good article on the #NWO...  https://t.co/KGCFrTslzV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Way to go, Lin Wood! You led the left like blind sheep and they fell for it! So predictable they are! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebias_news If you know Lin Wood, you understand what he's actually doing and it's not what the left thinks but the left will insist they know and that they're right, of course. ..And then we, who understand, get to chuckle at the left's nonsense that perceive to be intelligence. HaHa ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wonder why all these #MassShootings and now as they're pushing for #GunControl legislation and Biden with his unconstitutional EO? Read this article and you'll wonder no more! They aren't random shooters. They're #MindControlled shooters. https://t.co/iozGCNRMCu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Focus not on 'what' but on 'who' Who's timing the shootings; 'why' they do. Suddenly many incidents, All r coincidence? If u'r blinded w/lies  U'll b the fool who buys The con they're selling W/lies they're telling Risking ALL rights of every1 If we lose the right 2 own a gun.#2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The shootings are deliberate with a sinister aim To push the dems agenda to justify and claim That more stringent laws, pushing #GunControl Are needed as they inch towards their end goal, Which is to disarm us so we cannot fight Against their intent to take our every right. #2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Silencing the #truth that exposes lies Has become the norm, a #nazi enterprise, Because the dicktators know if the truth comes out, They'll lose over the people all their power, clout."  "Truth keeps the people free, While lies chain the people to tyranny." ~#Artsieladie #quotes https://t.co/boQWxD5dqY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CovidVaccines are NOT safety tested  long term effects are NOT, have NOT even been considered. "They haven't been honest with #covid facts, So, why should we trust the covid vax?" ~ #Artsieladie #quotes  #experimental #HumanGuineaPigs https://t.co/9UE7APZQD9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #CIA uses mind control Programs shooters 2 play a role Of convincing us, every 1 The problem is owning a gun. When ppl c all the shooting B/c of fear they'll b rooting 4 #GunControlNow  say "Stop the killing now, 2day!" As criminals r left armed More ppl keep getting harmed. https://t.co/4DPLEtYtBd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["If the #fraud's not righted, there'll never be Another #election done honestly." ~ #Artsieladie #quotes https://t.co/rNOZqIh7Ej]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now we have evidence the #media deliberately spikes #covid death #'s 2 cause #fear  panic. But the media doesn't report the many deaths caused by the #CovidVaccine nor the ways 2 protect from  treat covid 'safely'. R u getting the picture, yet? https://t.co/qUj7xRiKy6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow! Another #mafia in control? Or a re-emergence of the #gestapo? #MarxistMobs get 'protected'? But #LawAbiding 'citizens' must be disarmed? #Illegals welcomed, get paid w/citizens' tax money, housed, fed, get medical, covid+ can do/go where they want? https://t.co/9hV6kUToL2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, hell no, does #BLM want anyone investigating its finances. We all know by now or should, that transparency is taboo here in America. Crimes and criminals must be protected at all cost, while law abiding folks are under attack. #DemLogic  https://t.co/9Xnt016zCI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what all the mainstream media sources do, manipulate their viewers' thinking. They don't report the #truth OR the actual news. They 'report to distort'. #MSM #propaganda #CNN https://t.co/vnzV2TQ4YL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#911Attack #DirectEnergyWeapons #ColdFusionEnergy #Tesla #FreeEnergy #SAIC #MediaCoverUp #censorship #Wikipedia #DrJudyWood #NASA #CIA #FalseFlags #PsychologicalWarfare #ClimateCrisis #WeatherManipulation #BiologicalWeapon #covid #CovidJab #ConnectTheDots! https://t.co/z1lLkruijf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ALL need 2 pay attention! Look closely at the #InfrastructureBill 4 #GND  how they plan 2 seize our homes/properties from us, both Dem  Rep supporters. 4 the #GreatReset/#NWO. "Only a government with sinister plans Will plot to disarm law abiding hands." https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9 https://t.co/WQslpqtHwI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ALL need 2 pay attention! Look closely at the #InfrastructureBill 4 #GND  how they plan 2 seize our homes/properties from us, both Dem  Rep supporters. 4 the #GreatReset/#NWO. "Only a government with sinister plans Will plot to disarm law abiding hands." https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9 https://t.co/qjo3qEwS7d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @JackPosobiec ALL need 2 pay attention! Look closely at the #InfrastructureBill 4 #GND  how they plan 2 seize our homes/properties from us, both Dem  Rep supporters. 4 the #GreatReset/#NWO. "Only a government with sinister plans Will plot to disarm law abiding hands." https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec ALL need 2 pay attention! Look closely at the #InfrastructureBill 4 #GND  how they plan 2 seize our homes/properties from us, both Dem  Rep supporters. 4 the #GreatReset/#NWO. "Only a government with sinister plans Will plot to disarm law abiding hands." https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How long before EVERYONE wakes up  realizes everything we've been  are being subjected to is nothing more than #PsychologicalWarfare that's been drastically upticked against us with their #covid #BiologicalWeapon. WICKED people like Fauci are playing us all. #resist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U'r a wolf in sheep's clothing; betrayed the flock. So in ur mouth now just put a fat sock. U serve urself, ur own ambition. U'r a #globalist pushing 4 fruition Of the #NWO meant 2 destroy America 2 launch  deploy Worldwide a 1 #communist regime U r part of this WICKED scheme. https://t.co/RqltyIrQWH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MittRomney U'r a wolf in sheep's clothing; betrayed the flock. So in ur mouth now just put a fat sock. U serve urself, ur own ambition. U'r a #globalist pushing 4 fruition Of the #NWO meant 2 destroy America 2 launch  deploy Worldwide a 1 #communist regime U r part of this WICKED scheme.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looting, burning, destroying, killing, The commie dems find this thrilling, As they encourage  support, Make no attempt to such, thwart. Law abiding must disarmed, be, To ensure criminals the liberty To prey on Americans at leisure Once from law abiding there's gun seizure. #2A https://t.co/PiuHtEY2Sf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrAndyNgo @ICEgov Looting, burning, destroying, killing, The commie dems find this thrilling, As they encourage  support, Make no attempt to such, thwart. Law abiding must disarmed, be, To ensure criminals the liberty To prey on Americans at leisure Once from law abiding there's gun seizure. #2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter, right or left, Against us all is planned a theft Of all we own, our rights  properties, Our health, country  liberties. 2 grab from us til we have none 1st they must take our every gun. If we don't wake up, c behind the plot, We're going 2 lose ALL we've got!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone who doesn't like or agree w/Tucker Carlson or anyone else, then simple, "DON'T LISTEN!" He  all of us have the right 2 #FreeSpeech. We all have the right 2 agree or disagree but none of us has the right 2 infringe on another's right 2 voice their thoughts  opinions. #1A https://t.co/ElCVUr1PN1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goal = 2 not 'take' our guns but make impossible 2 own. #InfrastructureBill = same, make impossible 2 keep our homes/property  ban private owned cars. See beginning of video. #WakeUp! "Only a gov w/sinister plans Will plot 2 disarm law abiding hands." https://t.co/vteWKSj3N9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Personally I'd like to see that the Black Communities in America ACTUALLY being helped with jobs  opportunities, nice homes  neighborhoods to live in  family values taught  encouraged by #BLM not destruction by hateful mobs. #Racism ends when NO group is targeted. https://t.co/1yOUTGAI0b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Personally I'd like to see that the Black Communities in America ACTUALLY being helped with jobs  opportunities, nice homes  neighborhoods to live in  family values taught  encouraged by #BLM not destruction by hateful mobs. #Racism ends when NO group is targeted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No surprise really about #CocaCola siding with the enemy. The company supplied Coke to the #nazis in #WWII. https://t.co/WVIfDu0ykk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #communist demonrats r hellbent on disarming us, b/c they plan on taking our homes, properties, cars  everything else from us =&gt; #GND #InfrastructureBill They have 2 get our guns so we can't defend ourselves, property  country from their takeover.#2A https://t.co/cnUO1m11rp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Typical #leftist BS. When someone isn't pandering  kowtowing 2 their crazy, psychotic ideologies, attack w/false accusations  labels, which they, themselves, r the ones guilty of. #projection Tucker Carlson says what he thinks  has the right 2 whether the left likes it or not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Infringement = encroachment: intrusion on one's territory/rights/etc What's being done 2 keep criminals from getting guns? ZERO Taking guns from the law abiding  not criminals makes us all easy prey 4 criminals as @JoeBiden lets more in our country. https://t.co/kCLujGvq3M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where's the #ExecutiveOrder that takes guns out of criminals' hands, @JoeBiden, ummm... like your criminal son, #Hunter's? *waiting* Taking our guns will force law abiding citizens to exercise our #2ndAmendment rights. https://t.co/D6YYpm8sTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You know 'law abiding' Americans practicing #2A rights aren't going to willingly give up guns. So, you're aiming to make it impossible to have a gun, just as you're going to make it impossible to afford having a home with your #InfrastructureBill. You're a satanic #globalist. https://t.co/g44HEeyF2Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS You know 'law abiding' Americans practicing #2A rights aren't going to willingly give up guns. So, you're aiming to make it impossible to have a gun, just as you're going to make it impossible to afford having a home with your #InfrastructureBill. You're a satanic #globalist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How about tackling the 'law breakers', @JoeBiden  start with your law breaking son, #Hunter?  Why not tell the American ppl how the #CIA uses #MindControl to create #scapegoat shooters to brainwash ppl into believing we need more #GunControl? All need to #WakeUp to the #truth! https://t.co/g44HEeyF2Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS How about tackling the 'law breakers', @JoeBiden  start with your law breaking son, #Hunter?  Why not tell the American ppl how the #CIA uses #MindControl to create #scapegoat shooters to brainwash ppl into believing we need more #GunControl? All need to #WakeUp to the #truth!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How about tackling the 'law breakers', @JoeBiden  start with your law breaking son, #Hunter?  Why not tell the American ppl how the #CIA uses #MindControl to create #scapegoat shooters to brainwash ppl into believing we need more #GunControl? All need to #WakeUp to the #truth! https://t.co/hWazhu6UcW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld How about tackling the 'law breakers', @JoeBiden  start with your law breaking son, #Hunter?  Why not tell the American ppl how the #CIA uses #MindControl to create #scapegoat shooters to brainwash ppl into believing we need more #GunControl? All need to #WakeUp to the #truth!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seabiscutt77 @TheRightMelissa Read the PDF link of it spelled out: https://t.co/IvFRtD6Rjz]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>