<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 These things make someone seriously contemplate leaving clinical medicine. Even someone who really enjoys taking care of pts.  A metric that has zero bearing on true quality of care received by the pt.  Everyone needs to stop talking about burnout until this crap is fixed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PergamIC: Still argue that the immunosuppressed should continue to be more cautious even if vaccinated as early data ( data from other]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BioAscend: Ahead of #IUCLS21's kickoff tomorrow, meet your #lymphoma experts! Co-chairs @SoniSmithMD @DrAEvens @bpromd and keynote spea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MediHumdani: Great to see this CD19 ADC getting accelerated approval! #lymsm  A detailed tweetorial to come after the manuscript is pub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 Brown Recluse only an issue in certain parts of the US]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 Novel MOA Fixed duration A new treatment option]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mkraju: Marjorie Taylor Greene and Lauren Boebert were the lone two members to vote against a bill that would reauthorize the National]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan @Patriots @TomBrady @Buccaneers @daviesbj @skathire @WilliamDale_MD @barttels2 @sethmhardy @SMImmunology @PatsMilitia @BoucherMitch @GIcancerDoc @Rfonsi1 @VincentRK @DrChoueiri @NarjustDumaMD @DavidSteensma @cancerassassin1 @weldeiry @DrSarcoma @7RingsTommy @CityofTampa No comment... hey at least us @packers fans are getting to enjoy @AaronRodgers12 guest hosting @Jeopardy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@concernecus Onion powder]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sophpacz: Impact of Previously Unrecognized HLA Mismatches Using Ultrahigh Resolution Typing in Unrelated Donor Hematopoietic Cell Tran]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sanamloghavi: How long has this #pandemic been going on for??? This neutrophil has an answer for you. #hemepath https://t.co/3OR86GVhEO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASkarbnik @KrishPatelMD @DrLizBrem @GuiperiniMD @LoriLeslieMD @tobyeyre82 @graham74GC @JohnPLeonardMD @mshadman @bpromd @AaronGoodman33 @DrAEvens @DrAnasYounes @UjjaniC @JmPagelMD would be very helpful to have a way to reliably measure resid CART cells and track whether they expanded w PD-1 therapy.  we can with our own investigational CART but difficult to do with commercial CART.  And yes I would be concerned about GVHD esp if &lt;2-3 mo post PD-1 Rx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AaronGoodman33: The majority of my time spent as a clinical investigator for trials is reseting passwords I forget and docusigning.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@anthonymatomd @MCThompsonMD @sloan_kettering @LRoekerMD Agree although once Loxo-305 (pirtobrutinib) is available this may not be an issue... extremely well tolerated, once a day, and no PPI interaction]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnnKumfer The first year or two as an attending are hard that way - you will get there.  Suddenly one day you realize you are there :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AaronGoodman33: Happy Saint Patrick's Day https://t.co/acgkSnZgju]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mtmdphd Bigger question is, how often did genomic profile lead to an actionable mutation, which  produced an outcome better than whatever the oncologist would have done?  Im a science guy but havent sent one of these broad fishing panels on a lymphoma patient in years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MediHumdani @Phari @BldCancerDoc @sairah__ahmed @Transplant_Doc @szusmani From the same debate (Does allo still play a signif role in HL?  Mehdi yes, me no).  I looked at our HL Allo data, tried to explain the trends. RIC, Bv, Haplo, Checkpoint inhibitors . . . or, the Hamadani effect?  Also, fyi, "Fancy" Fenske hasn't worn a suit for a year... https://t.co/J8iG34UJ2u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 @EphraimFuchs I have had a few amazing responses with duvelisib - one is AITL.  Old guy, 4th line, still in CR 8-10 months.  Brentuximab, or Aza also good sometimes. However if transplant candidate would try to get to low-ish disease burden and then go to RIC allo.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 AITL is probably the lymphoma for which the GVL effect is most robust.  Registry studies in NHL in general do not support use of ablative conditioning - no benefit, just more tox.  In our program we rarely if ever use MA conditioning for lymphoma Allos.  I can pull a few refs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mtmdphd @HaydayLab @SheebaIrshad @CR_UK @KateYandell @Ecquis Really fascinating data - although need more patients to be further out for full interpretation.  However suggests that, while 1 injection may be sufficient for healthy controls, solid Ca (and esp heme Ca) pts really need the 2nd dose]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this one immune suppressed patient is a playground for the virus to try out different mutations; and some of these same mutations keep independently arising all over the world.  Shows how we really need better understanding of how the virus behaves in our cancer patients]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fascinating podcast on how SARS-CoV-2 mutations can be tracked as arising within one lymphoma patient over time, and how those same mutants grow out after conv plasma, and reflect similar mutations arising worldwide. https://t.co/B1wpRE7K6a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gary_lyman @NicoleKuderer @ADesaiMD @double_whammied What is the % forming antibody after 2 doses...? The story is unclear in this regard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gary_lyman @NicoleKuderer @ADesaiMD @double_whammied Wow - confirms what many of us have suspected.  Although even some protection is better than zero.  Will be interesting to tease out who responds better (on chemo vs 2 months or 6 months post chemo; those with B cell or T cell depletion, etc)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Moving piece that reminds us that we all need to look out for each other, and continue to make systemic changes in our training programs.  The stress that house staff (and attendings) endure at times is very real. Thank you @releiter for sharing   https://t.co/7oaZcuhq8U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BioAscend: Featured topics on aggressive #lymphoma will be presented by @StefanoLuminari, @MediHumdani, Frederick Locke, MD of @Moffitt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CARTTherapy @i_yakoub_agha @GruppSteve @ASTCT @DrMiguelPerales @ProfBMT @MediHumdani @Phari @niravshahmd @aljurf100 @kenderian_ss Please do not give bendamustine if you have any real intention of trying to make a CAR-T product! Benda causes serious depletion of T cells -can make a CAR-T production impossible.  We have had patients like this referred to us who ended up dying with no real chance for CAR-T.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NPR: There's not much difference between white and Black Americans on reluctance to take the COVID-19 vaccine, a new poll finds, despit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important to encourage / reassure our hematologic malignancy patients to get vaccinated.  Results of this recent LLS survey are concerning.  https://t.co/5EAXHAD1X8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very cool https://t.co/acSqXAjqVZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tobyeyre82: Umbralisib, a Dual PI3K/CK1 Inhibitor in Patients With Relapsed or Refractory Indolent Lymphoma https://t.co/5WvsdCDOWd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The phase 1/2 BRUIN trial of pirtobrutinib (Loxo-305) is now published in Lancet.  Very active in CLL and MCL (even C481 mutated) with VERY favorable tox profile, QD dosing.  Very excited about this drug   https://t.co/LMBSyub4qi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 Is there a cheat code for closing all my open Epic encounters?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesFanWu: Milwaukee, WI residents, please help amplify #COVID19Vaccine WALK-IN clinic information. PLEASE SHARE  Tag others in #MKE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HemSandoval I vividly remember, as intern at UW Madison in early 2000, hearing Brad Kahl (a heme fellow at the time!) present the ABC vs GCB study from the NCI.  I thought this would change how we treat DLBCL.  Still 20+ later we do not treat based on cell of origin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MungeBM @VincentRK What does that function do?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VincentRK Drone photography ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Epic nonsense.  What does this even mean?  Its an actual billable diagnosis / encounter https://t.co/ZkQ5dFay7F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[States Must Include Patients with Cancer on COVID-19 Vaccine Priority List  https://t.co/5jEmcK3iEe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drkevinknopf I have a patient still on oxygen 3 months later... may take a lot longer than a week]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drkomanduri May I please get 2 followers to copy and re-post this tweet? I'm trying to demonstrate that someone is always listening.  #SuicidePrevention   1-800-273-8255  Just two. Any two. Copy, not retweet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VincentRK What a great story - thank you for sharing!  I love examples of simple studies of cheap interventions that have a huge impact on patients (e.g. ice chips during high dose melphalan...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crisp winter day (zero degrees F!) https://t.co/CTRDOnzcgA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StefanoLuminari Nice work - pulls together diff pieces of info into easy to use assessment tool.  Will be helpful in identifying high risk pts for trials for elderly/frail.  However in practice,  doubt many high risk patients/ families will forgo treatment if predicted 3 yr OS is still 42%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 1 week Otherwise I find it too hard to slow down clinic and other stuff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndreWi54721839: Today is the International Day of Women and Girls in Science. I want to honor all the women of @ASTCT. There is no bet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan Insomnia ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @niravshahmd: Strong Work from our fellow @jzurkomd presenting cytokine data from IL-2 vs IL-7/15 expanded LV20.19 CAR T-cells #TCTM21 h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Subzero drone shots over Beaver Lake.  Pine Lake in background https://t.co/LBYLpDOseN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrAEvens: Kudos to @BrownUniversity @RIHospital Adam  Adam (@lymphomatic) on detailed #RWE analysis of CNS involvement in Burkitt #lym]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WWW = Wisconsin Winter Wonderland.  First pic is right out my front door https://t.co/cGLSpiF2gW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jmarksloan @cedittus @AaronGoodman33 I had a patient who called it Polar Bear ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 Agree with goal of RIC Allo. Can use various salvage regimens though - pola+BR, Tafa/Len, GDP, trials.  BiTEs in theory may get residual CART to expand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HowellJollyBody: (My) #CovidVaccine response on Rituximab - look! Blue means antibodies to RBD (Spike data similar). Encouraging datapo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HemSandoval @chadinabhan @graham74GC @DrRaulCordoba @AaronGoodman33 ECOG 1411 should help answer this question https://t.co/ivLuuOsdhd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WilliamDale_MD @chadinabhan @TomBrady @uroegg @daviesbj @skathire @barttels2 @JBMatthews @CMShannon_ @tbima68 I think overall Matt Lafleur has done an amazing job in his time with the @packers.  That call made no sense to me though and right when it happened I felt like the game was lost.  Of course there were many other lost opportunities along the way... but overall great season!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SueEvansMDMPH: this is a lovely bit of storytelling.   and a lovely reminder that hearts filled with hate can become hearts filled with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan @TomBrady @uroegg @daviesbj @skathire @barttels2 @WilliamDale_MD @JBMatthews @CMShannon_ @tbima68 Cant believe the Packers didnt go for the TD on 4th down, when down by 8 with just over 2 min left.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AgrimaMianMD @BMTjunkie @BrianHill_MDPhD @brad_pohlman @CCF_IMCHIEFS @BldCancerDoc @jamecancerdoc Ive had 2 develop therapy-related MDS as well.  Flu/Cy probably doesnt help in that regard...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ouholter She was pretty amazing   https://t.co/FerSJxAMR6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronGoodman33 Ofatumomab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrAnasYounes Seriously]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NigelCornelius: @PackersForTheWn Elgton Jenkins making Aaron Donald his son]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PackersForTheWn ZaDarius Smith is a BEAST !!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chanyooncheah Little different situation here in Wisconsin.  This is what my pool looks like right now https://t.co/SYVryavcuF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HannaSorensen Even if you hobble across that finish line, having that MD will open many doors later.  Very few MDs on unemployment and you can go in many different directions.  Stay strong, reach out to your circle of friends, they may be struggling as well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrAEvens BEAM/ auto for a younger patient is low risk and can be done outpt (our center TRM for younger HL patients close to zero). But agree better risk prediction needed and would welcome alternative escalation strategies, eg Bv-AVD. (Note in Echelon-1, 61% 5y PFS in PET2+ patients)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocHutchings @hematologo @periniheme @graham74GC @MarcAndre64 @DrAEvens @bpromd @ASkarbnik And SEER data shows continued improved OS in HL patients as time goes on (despite extremely little use of escBEACOPP in the U.S.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocHutchings @hematologo @periniheme @graham74GC @MarcAndre64 @DrAEvens @bpromd @ASkarbnik I have not had a young HL patient die in about 6-7 years (and I used to have at least 1-2 every year).  There could be many factors there but I really believe we can fix those who fail 1st line therapy with subsequent Rx, and spare the others unnecessarily intense treatment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MediHumdani: Proudly making Physician  Provider part of my @twitter profile. @sghmd @timfenske @DrDanPersky @szusmani #doctor Privileg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sghmd 100% agree it is a term that minimizes us as physicians, turns us more into a commodity. I dont think patients (or APPs) are particularly fond of it either.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @graham74GC: Oberic et al  R-miniCHOP v R2-miniCHOP &gt; 80y  subcut R  frontline DLBCL  249 pts, med 83y  2y OS 66% both arms  No ben]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrAEvens I would also say that not all PET-2 positives are equal.  Some are barely positive (90+ % improved) and others much more strongly positive.  I cant point to a study that has dissected that, but likely different outcomes in those two scenarios.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@periniheme @graham74GC @MarcAndre64 @DrAEvens @bpromd @ASkarbnik @hematologo @DocHutchings would not escalate to BEACOPP b/c (1) many false+ PETs (2) barely PET+, (3) no OS benefit, so ok to not esc and if still persist dz, Rx 4 cure in 2nd line; (4) tox of escBEACOPP signif (infertility, second malig).  need data on other less tox escalations (e.g. add Bv, PD-1, etc)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jersey_Craig: This is why being a nation of immigrants is what makes our country great.  Different experiences that come together to te]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ottoadelheid @graham74GC @tobyeyre82 @StefanoLuminari Agree mini RCHOP reasonable starting point.  We actually prefer split dose RCHOP (very well tolerated - half doses Q14d) although there are many ways to attenuate RCHOP.    https://t.co/sdsLnsKIDT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hematologo Thank you - yes these were with my drone ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DBelardoMD OMG hilarious...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @packers: A historic year for Davante.   With 18 TD receptions, @tae15adams tied Sterling Sharpe's single-season #Packers record fro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MediHumdani DJI Mavic Air 2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@niravshahmd Yes, in the first pic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Took the drone up in my neighborhood - great shots of Nagawicka Lake https://t.co/w2fosQn0Ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brgridiron: Packers officially clinch the No. 1 seed in the NFC  https://t.co/vx8okHsL19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MediHumdani this is horrible news. Hopefully Turner or Wagner can step up at left tackle...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonathan W. Friedberg Named Next Editor-in-Chief | Journal of Clinical Oncology  Congrats @DrJFriedberg and well deserved! https://t.co/CYmcNkGM1B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid science news from 2020, #15, NEOWISE comet.  One of my own pics (below).  If you missed it, you'll have to wait 6,800 years . . .   Please post other cool science/medicine stories from 2020 that I may have missed! https://t.co/vgAAmZWq0k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid science news from 2020, #14.  Highest-Resolution Solar Telescope Ever Releases Incredible First Images of the Sun.  Really cool video.  https://t.co/Ezb5YZxAPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid science news from 2020, #13.  Chinas Change 5 mission put a robotic lander on the Moon and marked the first time in 44 years that a spacecraft had delivered lunar material to Earth.  https://t.co/ppkczaUhBF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid news from 2020, #12.  The OSIRIS-Rex spacecraft, recovered samples from the asteroid Bennu, and is returning these to earth.  Really cool video.  https://t.co/UQUMRM1Dha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid scientific news from 2020, #11.    SpaceX launch !  https://t.co/25ucLL8So8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid science/ medicine news of 2020, #10.  2nd largest Ebola outbreak in history contained (Congo), with a WHO-led vaccination campaign.  https://t.co/bkBftfOvw4)%20outbreak%20in%20Equateur%20Province.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-covid science news of 2020, #9.  There is water (ice) all over the moon.  https://t.co/okZVTHu5Re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-COVID science news of 2020, #8.  Murder hornets, of course !  https://t.co/mdVLJUJhV5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool scientific discoveries/ advances in 2020, #7.  So this was ingenuity driven by covid but not really covid research.   Moving the research lab home (into the laundry room).  https://t.co/k9Z6bYbgjr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-COVID scientific discoveries of 2020, #6.  Decrease in limb transplant rejection by recruitment of Tregs.  https://t.co/5kFtZCBylG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-COVID scientific/medical discoveries of 2020.  First Alzheimer's blood test approved in the U.S.  https://t.co/XialTbXHlj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-COVID scientific discovery of 2020, #4: The fabella (tiny bone behind the knee) is making a comeback.   https://t.co/AHRiPI5L6U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-COVID scientific discovery of 2020, #3: New human salivary glands.  https://t.co/tLdGhDoXO8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool non-COVID scientific discoveries of 2020. #2: There are lymphatics in human meninges.  https://t.co/oNvlCQ3bJ4]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>