<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Women who are breastfeeding can now receive the COVID-19 vaccine when it is offered to them.   If you have any concerns, speak to a healthcare professional before having the vaccination. More info: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/57EJAhwZBl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worrying too much can have a big impact on the way we feel. Visit #EveryMindMatters for a range of specific tips and expert advice to help you manage feelings of anxiety: https://t.co/cUgudRCBI9 https://t.co/mz57aFIT2M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pregnancy can impact your mental health in many ways, even if this isn't your first time. You are not alone and support is available. Find advice about how to look after your mental health in pregnancy: https://t.co/2HRtaRFMom #WorldMaternalMentalHealthDay #WMMHDay #MMHWeek https://t.co/DseTQyupL0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember F.A.S.T for the signs someone might be having a stroke. Face  has their face fallen on one side? Can they smile? Arms  can they raise both arms and keep them there? Speech  is it slurred? Time  its time to call 999. When stroke strikes remember to Act F.A.S.T. https://t.co/O8ODTeZgVu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine has already saved thousands of lives. Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Find out more    https://t.co/ATVQU3x9J3 https://t.co/FeEDT3yCYE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The second dose of the COVID-19 vaccine helps to provide longer-term protection.  Don't delay in getting your second dose when it is offered to you: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/GBY64bmXdM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHS_Parents: It's important for everyone to protect their skin from sunburn, especially children and babies as their skin is much more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS is sending texts to some people to invite them to book a COVID-19 vaccine appointment. These may come from a local NHS service, or from NHSvaccine.  Remember the NHS will never ask for payment details. Find out more about how we may contact you. https://t.co/x1F0rO37r6 https://t.co/6C0U7ctKIj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you've had the COVID-19 vaccine, it's vital that you continue to follow social distancing guidance.  Read the latest guidance here: https://t.co/pC1m3uw2zj https://t.co/zFXrqTIwWv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women who are breastfeeding can now receive the COVID-19 vaccine when it is offered to them.   If you have any concerns, speak to a healthcare professional before having the vaccination. More info: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/ayZQfzL9h1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine is safe and effective. It gives you the best protection against coronavirus.  Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Join the millions already vaccinated: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/zu7zty7V94]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This bank holiday, find out which pharmacies are open near you  so you can get the medicines and advice you need:  https://t.co/LAMyUuxExK https://t.co/CM2fm1ZkAk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoy the Bank Holiday safely. If youre meeting others outdoors, keep to a group of 6 or two households. https://t.co/kAn6xSHrcR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fifi_Borgia (2/2) The COVID-19 vaccines were only approved once they met robust standards of effectiveness, safety and quality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fifi_Borgia (1/2) The safety of the public will always come first. The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) is the UKs independent regulator, their role is to ensure medicines, devices and vaccines work and are safe for use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TBlighe @thedartswidow (2/2)  The COVID-19 vaccines were only approved once they met robust standards of effectiveness, safety and quality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TBlighe @thedartswidow (1/2) The safety of the public will always come first. The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) is the UKs independent regulator, their role is to ensure medicines, devices and vaccines work and are safe for use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiki123_o @thedartswidow (2/2) The COVID-19 vaccines were only approved once they met robust standards of effectiveness, safety and quality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiki123_o @thedartswidow (1/2) The safety of the public will always come first. The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) is the UKs independent regulator, their role is to ensure medicines, devices and vaccines work and are safe for use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@S__KETC (4/4) The data looked at includes all the results from lab studies, clinical trials, manufacturing and quality controls and testing the product. The public can be very confident that all those tests are done to the very highest standards.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@S__KETC (3/4) Right through the tests and the trials, teams of scientists and clinicians carefully, methodically, scientifically and rigorously review all data on safety, effectiveness and quality as soon as they become available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@S__KETC (2/4) The COVID-19 vaccines were only approved once they met robust standards of effectiveness, safety and quality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@S__KETC (1/4) The safety of the public will always come first. The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) is the UKs independent regulator, their role is to ensure medicines, devices and vaccines work and are safe for use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TinaBr2 (4/4) The data looked at includes all the results from lab studies, clinical trials, manufacturing and quality controls and testing the product. The public can be very confident that all those tests are done to the very highest standards.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TinaBr2 (3/4) Right through the tests and the trials, teams of scientists and clinicians carefully, methodically, scientifically and rigorously review all data on safety, effectiveness and quality as soon as they become available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TinaBr2 (2/4) The COVID-19 vaccines were only approved once they met robust standards of effectiveness, safety and quality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TinaBr2 (1/4) The safety of the public will always come first. The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) is the UKs independent regulator, their role is to ensure medicines, devices and vaccines work and are safe for use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you've had the COVID-19 vaccine, it's vital that you continue to follow social distancing guidance.  Read the latest guidance here: https://t.co/pC1m3uw2zj https://t.co/GPiWgf0HVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you need urgent dental treatment this bank holiday  the NHS is here for you. Call your dentist, or use the NHS 111 online service. They will be able to arrange an appointment if it's necessary: https://t.co/8VfK81f9u3 https://t.co/6qLoAteG8f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine has already saved thousands of lives. Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Find out more    https://t.co/ATVQU3x9J3 https://t.co/lPR3Rt7WJg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine is safe and effective. It gives you the best protection against coronavirus.  Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Join the millions already vaccinated: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/innufb7SNu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoy the Bank Holiday safely. If youre meeting others outdoors, keep to a group of 6 or two households. https://t.co/0F7g7kJ9jj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davepoflynn ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davepoflynn How did you book - on the NHS website? If so you should be able to manage your booking through the site.  Details are here   https://t.co/TDhqQk4otX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some GP services will be available this bank holiday. If you have a health concern, contact your GP practice or use the NHS 111 online service for quick health advice: https://t.co/8VfK81f9u3 https://t.co/rZzIJJM4za]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women who are breastfeeding can now receive the COVID-19 vaccine when it is offered to them.   If you have any concerns, speak to a healthcare professional before having the vaccination. More info: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/Q8l6asCq4g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The second dose of the COVID-19 vaccine helps to provide longer-term protection.  Don't delay in getting your second dose when it is offered to you: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/H2kAcZyEkr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS is sending texts to some people to invite them to book a COVID-19 vaccine appointment. These may come from a local NHS service, or from NHSvaccine.  Remember the NHS will never ask for payment details. Find out more about how we may contact you. https://t.co/x1F0rO37r6 https://t.co/l09mVBXmUT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccines have met strict standards of safety, quality and effectiveness set out by the independent Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA).  Read more about the COVID-19 vaccine: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/xZ9qzBUz5m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With thanks to @LennyHenry, Lydia West, @davidwalliams, Navin Chowdhry, @ElizabethHurley and of course, @eltonofficial   ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A quick reminder about some of the science behind the Covid-19 vaccine  and that it is safe and effective.  More info  https://t.co/MPCevFV6SM  https://t.co/1Dl3NxO57o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This bank holiday, find out which pharmacies are open near you  so you can get the medicines and advice you need:  https://t.co/LAMyUuxExK https://t.co/emTL1V4VyQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine is safe and effective. It gives you the best protection against coronavirus.  Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Join the millions already vaccinated: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/QAdziR081X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WinnyWaggles You are eligible now that anyone over 40 can book. Go online at https://t.co/95odTgmvQS or call 119 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pterjan @jiggott Let's see if we can get this sorted. Can you drop us a quick DM and we'll go from there. Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoy the Bank Holiday safely. If youre meeting others outdoors, keep to a group of 6 or two households. https://t.co/tprbUrfbNI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sassy_social If you book via https://t.co/c1P11eNyw5 then you can book an appointment anywhere. Appointments made locally via a GP will be local to their address.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're aged 40 or over, or if you turn 40 before 1 July 2021, you can now book your COVID-19 vaccine.   https://t.co/95odTgmvQS https://t.co/k8glGyKXhA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you sleeping well? If you're not getting good sleep it can start to affect your mental wellbeing. Luckily there are easy changes you can make for more restful sleep.   Visit #EveryMindMatters for advice on getting to sleep and sleeping better: https://t.co/MIZ77qUcYf https://t.co/73cBuS6ktO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bekip1010 @jiggott Hey Beki - let's see how we can get this sorted for you. Can you DM us and we'll go from there?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine is safe and effective. It gives you the best protection against coronavirus.  Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/Ydgj6P6MVN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS is sending texts to some people to invite them to book a COVID-19 vaccine appointment. These may come from a local NHS service, or from NHSvaccine.  Remember the NHS will never ask for payment details. Find out more about how we may contact you. https://t.co/x1F0rO37r6 https://t.co/4NmNJ6yqLy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccines have met strict standards of safety, quality and effectiveness set out by the independent Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA).  Read more about the COVID-19 vaccine: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/Z1tzV24K7a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GoonerRichB The UK operates a system of informed consent for vaccinations. Vaccines are the most effective way to prevent infectious diseases; however, it is up to individuals to decide whether they want to receive a vaccine or not. There's more info here:  https://t.co/jKMHsJHocp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@B93972428 The Oxford/AstraZeneca vaccine is safe, effective, and has already saved thousands of lives. The UKs independent regulator, the MHRA, and the JCVI have both said that the benefits of the vaccine far outweigh the risks for the vast majority of adults.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nikkijfox Hi Nikki. We're working on providing people with the ability to show their Covid-status through digital and non-digital routes, with security and privacy at the core of this approach. Use of the NHS App is being considered as part of the digital route.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PHE_uk: NEW: Our new research shows that one dose of #COVID19 vaccine can cut household transmission by up to half.  Read more here: ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine, just like any other vaccine, works by teaching your immune system how to defend itself against attack from the virus. https://t.co/MPCevFV6SM https://t.co/q41LjZDqbJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jo624288 @amandafclark @lindaarella @SkyNews Indeed. This is the app, if helpful for anyone  https://t.co/WD9Ky0xec7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women who are breastfeeding can now receive the COVID-19 vaccine when it is offered to them.   If you have any concerns, speak to a healthcare professional before having the vaccination. More info: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/7ffKuAoqnz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEngland: If you're pregnant, you should be offered the COVID-19 vaccine when you're eligible.  You'll be offered the Pfizer/BioNTech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS will never ask you to share bank details or pay for a vaccine.  Report anything you receive that looks suspicious to: https://t.co/qqDOj6xrRN https://t.co/ITe7lcfzyB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine has already saved thousands of lives. Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Find out more    https://t.co/ATVQU3x9J3 https://t.co/KEw7P48WGo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RagnarBelial @guardian    https://t.co/WD9Ky0xec7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Airwatcher773 In case it's useful, this has some more accurate information about the NHS App  https://t.co/WD9Ky0xec7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bmsplit You should be able to download it.   Is this info about Google Play store country setting any help for you?   https://t.co/fbq1UCWeIj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bmsplit Should be fine. Worth checking the country settings on your Google Play account?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wilkina50 You can tell us if it's any good, or if there's anything we could do to make it work better or make it easier for others to use. Gathering feedback from people who will use something is incredibly valuable as it'll make a service better and more useful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay safe this Ramadan by following COVID-19 guidelines. For more information, please visit https://t.co/oYuvskwCxB https://t.co/F85L1EM2jV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wilkina50 To help us make sure it still works as people expect, and that they can still use it easily. All the feedback is useful to help us design a service that works for as many people as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@peteduncanson @fatwelshbloke What Pete said.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two households or a group of up to six people can now meet outdoors.  Remember to always keep a safe distance from those not in your household or bubble.    More info: https://t.co/pT134S8T9K https://t.co/MdSUVk6IHr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS is sending texts to some people to invite them to book a COVID-19 vaccine appointment. These may come from a local NHS service, or from NHSvaccine.  Remember the NHS will never ask for payment details. Find out more about how we may contact you. https://t.co/x1F0rO37r6 https://t.co/nNaABcMBVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women who are breastfeeding can now receive the COVID-19 vaccine when it is offered to them.   If you have any concerns, speak to a healthcare professional before having the vaccination. More info: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/9TO8vdiJU3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrumLeader It's actually 42 and over now! https://t.co/VjeTVqlcNc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If youre aged 42 or over, or if youll turn 42 before 1 July 2021, you can now book your Covid-19 vaccine.   Book online  https://t.co/95odTgmvQS https://t.co/f4t0nw3RlN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@honeybouboule Hello Antoine.  We are working as hard as we can to get through everyone.  You will be invited for the vaccine  Keep up to date with the roll out on our website : htti://www.nhs.uk/conditions/coronavirus-covid19/coronavirus-vaccination/coronavirus-vaccine/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mandm280511 Hello MM. COVID-19 vaccines were tested on 30,000 people from all walks of life and have been part of the trials. The Government has accepted the recommendation from the independent Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) to approve the COVID-19 vaccinations.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine is safe and effective. It gives you the best protection against coronavirus.  Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Join the millions already vaccinated: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/n3jbc2ttXp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worrying too much can have a big impact on the way we feel. Visit #EveryMindMatters for a range of specific tips and expert advice to help you manage feelings of anxiety: https://t.co/cUgudRCBI9 https://t.co/lplm9fwRmV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NoelLakshman Vaccination is the most important thing we can do to protect against ill health. It's much safer for your immune system to learn this through vaccination than by catching the diseases and treating them and can often protect you for many years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People aged 44 or over in England can now book their COVID-19 vaccine.  Get started here: https://t.co/tUlUhVwE5e https://t.co/4LRCEaNzUg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every vaccination gives us hope. https://t.co/4ds9mv6Wru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSuk: Every vaccination gives us hope.  Join the millions already vaccinated, to protect yourself and others.  Find out more about the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every vaccination gives us hope.  Join the millions already vaccinated, to protect yourself and others.  Find out more about the Covid-19 vaccine at https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/kowye8WbpK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@louisehallbooks Hi Louise. We have some information on our site about how you will be contacted and how to book your coronavirus vaccination appointments online - https://t.co/RZnFznhXUs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're invited to get your vaccine, or you have a second dose booked this #Ramadan, please take it. https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/WKq3mkjH9e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Oxford/AstraZeneca COVID-19 vaccine has already saved thousands of lives.   The UK's Independent regulator has said that the benefits of the vaccine far outweigh the risks for the vast majority of adults.   Info: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/Rs5y863nQe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This series of images celebrates the monumental and collective effort of the Covid-19 vaccine programme so far across the UK.  Every vaccination gives us hope. https://t.co/TKlvcQ11gJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every day is a good day to do something positive for your mental health. Visit Every Mind Matters and take the Mind Plan Quiz for your own personalised mental wellbeing action plan: https://t.co/D0gs8lxYvT https://t.co/99jj2gwRqj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The second dose of the COVID-19 vaccine helps to provide longer-term protection.  Don't delay in getting your second dose when it is offered to you: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/IwVvVeOoyL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Please, hear us. And when your turn comes, take the jab."   Find out more about the Covid-19 vaccine: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/3fqS3MKFSp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 1st dose of the COVID-19 vaccine should give you good protection from coronavirus from 3 or 4 weeks after you've had it. But you need to have the 2 doses of the vaccine to give you longer lasting protection.  Read more: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/AcEmvGV7ap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS is sending texts to some people to invite them to book a COVID-19 vaccine appointment. These may come from a local NHS service, or from NHSvaccine.  Remember the NHS will never ask for payment details. Find out more about how we may contact you. https://t.co/x1F0rO37r6 https://t.co/qj20Yqub1C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The second dose of the COVID-19 vaccine helps to provide longer-term protection.  Don't delay in getting your second dose when it is offered to you: https://t.co/qAOGzpWMu6 https://t.co/mZa1IV99Ih]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic has had a devastating impact on ethnic minority communities. Thats why its so important that to get the vaccine when it's offered. For the facts on the COVID-19 vaccine, visit https://t.co/SkCoecbJWC https://t.co/0uoVFQOJT8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you sleeping well? If you're not getting good sleep it can start to affect your mental wellbeing. Luckily there are easy changes you can make for more restful sleep.   Visit #EveryMindMatters for advice on getting to sleep and sleeping better: https://t.co/MIZ77qUcYf https://t.co/u7Mj62J7Eb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you've had the COVID-19 vaccine, it's vital that you continue to follow social distancing guidance.  Read the latest guidance here: https://t.co/pC1m3uw2zj https://t.co/hhqvzVRasR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS is sending texts to some people to invite them to book a COVID-19 vaccine appointment. These may come from a local NHS service, or from NHSvaccine.  Remember the NHS will never ask for payment details. Find out more about how we may contact you. https://t.co/x1F0rO37r6 https://t.co/fakfnFIVFX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the millions across the UK who have safely received the COVID-19 vaccination. Don't delay in getting your vaccine when it's offered to you.   Find out more    https://t.co/ATVQU3x9J3 https://t.co/Bpq2497F3A]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>