<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@jkenney What's disturbing is your opposition to people's God given rights. Conservatism is dead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Charliefox1984 @VancouverPD Depends on the scenario. A bunch of activists blocking a road for an afternoon isn't a violation. But if the government uses the police to restrict your ability to travel say throughout the province, well the that certainly would be a violation of your rights.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LafyLarry @LeonardRoxon Who gives a shit when the entirety of our government is run by criminals?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonardRoxon The the conservative party is beyond useless at this point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRealMkA20 https://t.co/HIrtLm38GH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheoFleury14 Who would have ever thought that future dictatorships would be hostile toward the domestic population and traditionalism. While promoting foreigners and degeneracy? It truly is clown world. https://t.co/YHoiSH3P9n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Openly Progressives: "The America is racist, misogynist and transphobic!"  Also progressives: "Why can't the fake women fight and die to protect America?"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD "After allowing the group to peacefully assemble and express themselves for several hours"  Not your place to 'allow' citizens to exercise their God given rights.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@panagis21 @mjc383 @WHO @NIH @CDCgov Still not worth it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheoFleury14 @TrueNorthCentre @AndrewLawton Based Theo. Just waiting for your PM run.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@opitersia Easy, just keep her away from any communication devices and chained to kitchen sink.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Huh, I've been doing that all along.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IntellectEmbarg @stone_toss https://t.co/5cCS9aPn7I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeMoreAlpha @OrwellNGoode And in 10 years she will be depressed, childless and no man will want her. Shame.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dxxnya Maybe just stop being a slut.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@XtofMyself @ghinsenk @stone_toss Can you mods stop banning me for random posts I never made?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Forge_rhys @L0m3z We all are friend. We all are.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Apaukolypse @stone_toss It's more like Stoneroll really.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stone_toss i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickiclyne Make his own TV channel or something.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sp4h @nickiclyne That's because social media is a social cancer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeshmatAlavi This has been happening to Western countries for generations now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ATurtleApprover @NickJFuentes You forgot pederast.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CTVNews tfw Alex Jones was right all along. https://t.co/XI57jEzRMM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier @Caitlyn_Jenner @JoyVBehar https://t.co/j9RiNxuOmQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VinTag10 @NickJFuentes Unless they're 400 years old they aren't responsible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichaelSiscoWV Doubtful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drex It really is amazing just how blindly obedient you people are when the corporate-state super structure tells you to do something. I bet if the media started broadcasting that killing your own pets to help *insert manufactured social cause here* that you would gleefully comply. https://t.co/zV6pyQLCxI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lollardfish @chloe_adlestone lol jews btfo with a single symbol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tbzill @Chesschick01 Nothing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau So, all these lockdowns and restrictions on our freedoms is going to go on into 2023?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickJFuentes Too late. Time to jump ship and hop onto the #NationalJusticeParty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLevineNYC Make sure to get the vaccine goyim. It's for your own good.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @DrKarlynB Debate him and find out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 https://t.co/xkjQNAKJXA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CBCAlerts Uh huh...  https://t.co/DkWJcODlWR https://t.co/ejFWiN0oWF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jadapsmith https://t.co/M5WD460zO6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau Doubt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews I remember the days when anonymous was cool and mysterious. Now it's just cucked and gay.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timcast Why is 50% of Biden's cabinet Jewish?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GaryTurner007 @Timcast Pretty sure blacks just aren't interested in playing hockey.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheBelaaz Huh, it's almost as though forcibly removing people from their land and then keeping it for yourself will cause a bit of resentment from those same people. Who would have thought?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NHL I just want to watch hockey. https://t.co/Qxtrf6stAO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmyBeePhoenix "This is just the voice of the oppressed fighting against white supremacy."  Same as always.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blacks are still going to riot anyway. #Chauvin #GeorgeFloyd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MadBerserker22 Yeah, I only noticed that after I posted it. An unfortunate oversight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timjacobwise I would like preserve these traditions. https://t.co/u0sjBGssSm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bIuebirdIake Yeah, a #BlackBoySummer would involve burn that McDonald's to the ground.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DGlassbrook You must be jewish.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZackyKaye @IlhanMN Oy vey!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hahmad1996 @GeorgetownLaw Oh no! We can't let here tell the truth now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NalyDelRey Excuse me but I'm actually a valid #SS human being and trying to invalidate me like that is bigoted and very #superphobic.You don't know the lived experience of we that identity as #superstraight. #superstraightpride #superstraightrightsarehumanrights #superstraightrepresentation https://t.co/oQhrQ1eeNv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VaushV #SuperStraightRightsNow https://t.co/bquwW4h9Jr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmyBeePhoenix End clown world. Embrace the third position.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gigadgets_ Live in the pod. Eat the bugs. Transition your child. Wear the nose.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BLivesMatterMS God damn that's funny.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ban_0525 @lisasrina Are you sure they aren't jewish?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lisasrina I am white. And it's great.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@onlyfanjessford Wow. That's disgusting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrKarlynB https://t.co/lOYCb0OA71]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atomicwick I'm more looking forward to the new #MartinLutherKing film. https://t.co/dku44TCUxY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelgalassi @theslowfactory @barnor_hesse Dear God you are brainwashed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theslowfactory @barnor_hesse I stand with Whites.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eurojewcong What about jewish extremism?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@koocites Ooga booga https://t.co/JuG6GlICt5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm done with this platform. App will be deleted. P.S. The MAGA supporters should have occupied the Capitol Building and barricaded the entrances. The Congress was more representative of the people for those two hours than it has been the last 40 years. #TrumpWon #DCRIOTS Capitol https://t.co/eiZPzpmApu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This "art" is considered acceptable in the modern day. Our people need to push back on this clear incitement to violence.  #waronwhites  #hatespeech  #stopwhitehate  #whitelivesmatter https://t.co/1C2PPZXNeA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Whiteness", as the the hateful left likes to call it, is portrayed as an obstacle to be overcome. It's is a convenient scapegoat on which they blame all the world's ills. Instead, it should be something that is celebrated.  #waronwhites  #whiteness  #racism  #whitelivesmatter https://t.co/OWsRBgFx5p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the only future white people can look forward to if we continue stand idle against our enemies. At present our only choice is to organize and fight back, or stay atomized and become slaves.  #waronwhites  #slavery  #antiwhiteracism   #blm https://t.co/YHILIEW9aO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a continual push to destroy the integrity and cohesion of white families. Huffington Post seems to thinks preserving the innocence of our children is a form of "white supremacy".  #waronwhites  #huffingtonpost  #savewhitefamily  #saveourchildren https://t.co/PMIOs0wUkM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how the media portrays whites. The very people who discovered, founded, and settled America.  #waronwhites  #USElection2020  #Americans #AmericansFirst https://t.co/5gAKrFzuf6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The mainstream left isn't trying to undermine whites by using just the tactic of demonization in the media. They are also actively indoctrinating our children to become transgender aberrations.  #waronwhites  #transgender  #transkids  #saveourchildren https://t.co/Th5iMFcZwe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human facefor ever."  - George Orwell  #waronwhites  #preserveourpeople  #wakeupamerica  #takebackourcountry https://t.co/4HH1zg5gRs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anti-White hate is inescapable. Even something as innocuous as hiking is now "unbearably white".   #waronwhites  #hiking  #takebackcontrol  #whitelivesmatter https://t.co/fAgeSOl10f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This the world in which we live. The totality of the system (media, corporations, judicial system, etc.) is against whites. All the while we are flooded with messages of "POC" oppression.  #waronwhites  #takebackcontrol  #nojusticenopeace  #silentnomore https://t.co/d9OJj7Frsw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It should be understood as such by the European people, and dealt with by their government's idle militaries. Or well shall merely become another conquered people.  #wakeupeurope  #europeforeuropeans]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Europe, our indigenous homeland, is being flooded with both legal and illegal migrants from Africa and the Middle-East. This sort of mass migration has been used as a form of warfare throughout human history.  #waronwhites  #stopmassmigration https://t.co/dnf2QF5zIe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/2 Europe, our indigenous homeland, is being flooded with both legal and illegal migrants from Africa and the Middle-East. This sort of mass migration has been used as a form of warfare throughout human history.  #waronwhites  #stopmassmigration https://t.co/jDQNBU3reO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is exactly what is needed in Western nations. We need to preserve the family and natural gender roles. Something the left is doing is best to destroy.  #waronwhites  #familyvalues  #hungary  #onlytwogenders https://t.co/lkZLMZkLvN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SwipeWright: 1/ The Dalton School in Manhattan is having a race meltdown. It's absolutely insane. Teachers are holding the school for r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how we are thought of in modern day. Merely a genetic abomination that needs to delt with. This sort of hatred is pervasive throughout our very own societies, societies built by the ancestors of our people.  #waronwhites  #racism  #hatred  #whitelivesmatter https://t.co/j2PHFwubV7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whites are a completely atomized people with virtually no senseif common identity. If we are to succeed as a people through this century then we must come together as one people.  #waronwhites  #whitelivesmatter  #generationidentitaire  #wakeupeurope https://t.co/qh6pssIQoW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whites are in the midst of a generational struggle for the very survival of our people. Most don't even know it or refuse to acknowledge it. Organize and fight back.  #waronwhites  #racism  #thegreatreplacement  #antiwhiteracism https://t.co/x2LiOD4uhp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The indigenous peoples of Europe are being replaced by foreign invasion. If we continue to do nothing our people will only exist in special reservations within just a few generations.  #waronwhites  #muslimsareinvaders  #thegreatreplacement  #saveourpeople https://t.co/MAO2DfOur2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The media is in an all out war against white people. They do everything they can to incite hatred towards us.  #waronwhites  #fakenewsmedia  #mainstreammedia  #whitelivesmatter https://t.co/HagpVX56Xr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...totally-not-totalitarian sounding Cornell Compact Compliance Team, while failure to get tested for Covid-19 will see them locked out of libraries and campus buildings."  #waronwhites  #covid19  #nocovidvaccine  #pfizervaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just don't take the vaccine. Even Pfizer's CEO and President Trump aren't going to take it.  "For Cornells privileged whites, who make up 40 percent of the student body at the university, failure to get vaccinated will earn them a visit from the... https://t.co/g4dXeqzJKe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our people are being replaced at an alarming rate. Any other time in history such large scale migration would be met with war by the native population. Today European people sit idle while their homelands are being overrun.  #waronwhites #stopmassmigration  #saveamerica https://t.co/dfH37GeWbK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White men are builders, inventors, organizers and conquerors. Never let them shame you because of our heritage.  #waronwhites  #mediocre  #whitelivesmatter  #stopwhitegenocide  #havechildren https://t.co/qgRhQcK5wW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stillgray @Timcast But it is the return brought about by Muslims.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UN @antonioguterres Get fucked. #AbolishTheUN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Education? https://t.co/FFZNZapkxm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaporiser? https://t.co/ZE6kiIKgu0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Public Service Announcement? https://t.co/lr47U7KcjZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicken? https://t.co/ofQFTfNtsy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Music? https://t.co/4DDlKYC5ZA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[News? https://t.co/lVpMrBNLLd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beer? https://t.co/w3Ao23kgz9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[History? https://t.co/kHJFioIHbI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vodka? https://t.co/yr0gRd16JD]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>