<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Unless you plan to shut down international travel without mandatory quarantine, the COVID crisis in India is everyone's problem.   With &gt;350,000 confirmed cases a day, odds of a lightning striking twice event of a mutant variant that is more lethal AND more contagious increases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrNeilStone For USA the last stretch is harder due to vaccine hesitancy. Rates of vaccination are dropping. I'm just making the point for some reason or the other it's hard to get where we need to be.   With the variants in India I'm not sure even 80% total population is sufficient for herd. https://t.co/zLxhKz9T7h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrNeilStone What Israel has done is amazing. Vaccinating 80-85% of those eligible for vaccine. Given the age distribution, to reach herd immunity (at least 80 % of total population) Israel needs to get over 90% of eligible population. USA needs to get over 80%. The last stretch is hard.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trishgreenhalgh: Here's our #CovidRiskChart in South Asian and South American languages: I will post English first then other versions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VincentRK: Vaccines work: Starting one month after first COVID vaccine approval, cases and deaths have come down greatly.  After a brie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VincentRK: Vaccines are highly effective and safe, and they are working in the real world just like they worked in the clinical trials.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are highly effective and safe, and they are working in the real world just like they worked in the clinical trials. Keep delivering this message. https://t.co/ntXnbzDFZw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: 11) that said, its hard to get past 65% Israel having trouble now too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing Yes! And we have to. I'm willing to speak to anyone and explain. But the people who are hesitant need to hear it from people they trust. Leaders they trust.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joaquinlife I agree with you. If you notice I said my target is 80% of adults. Because I think 70% of adults (the target announced today) is not enough for herd immunity.   80% may not be enough. Especially with variants. Consider it "at least 80%".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How hard is it going to be to get to true herd immunity? HARD.   To get 70% of population immune we need to vaccinate 80% of adults (ideal). Note how Israel plateaus at 60%. The last mile is the hardest and will take a lot of effort from all of us to overcome vaccine hesitancy. https://t.co/uZmQrnUrZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: Its gonna be a slow crawl to 70% vaccinated. But we can get there. Lets do this.  #COVID19 #vaccinate https://t.co/bfcW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ruchitgarg: If you are sending medical supplies to India for covid emergency, we can get it cleared faster from the custom and possibly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skarlamangla Awesome!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @skarlamangla: I'm so honored to have been selected as a Livingston Award finalist, alongside so many talented journalists whose work I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SajalTanna @ashan @Nightline @NoopurRajeMD @JagSinghMD   Thanks @ashan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SajalTanna: I have been caring for COVID-19 patients for over a year in Chicago.  COVID-19 in India is beyond my worst nightmares. Like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@umasudhir @ndtv @ndtvindia Heartbreaking video. Words fail me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Isabel84436966 @TheLancetOncol @mvmateos @myelomaMD @ArjunLakshman This is what we use still. First tweet is on MGUS. There is a small effect of cytogenetics. But most risk of progression is driven by these 3 simple factors. https://t.co/cJivoNNWdz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: INCREASE QUARANTINES? A study suggests that #B117 UK variant may remain in human hosts nearly 2x as long as non-B.1.1.7 #SA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing Totally agree Eric.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: @VincentRK Im hopeful. But still nail biting until its much lower. We know the virus has a tendency to superspread if giv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NamanJain0918 @DrEricDing Are you in India? Yes. India vaccine supplies are not enough and need to increase.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines work: Starting one month after first COVID vaccine approval, cases and deaths have come down greatly.  After a brief plateau, cases have started to decrease again. Based on this I expect deaths to resume a downward trend soon.  Ask your hesitant friends to get vaccinated https://t.co/KQ5nyeyQnm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AashimaTweets Best wishes. Let us know if you need any help in Delhi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[News from UK on B.1.617 in community. And a good summary of our hopes right now. @chrischirp https://t.co/eN6jy3sX5Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vaibhav330 @aparanjape If there is no pulse oximetry available, at least go by the middle column (respiratory rate) or shortness of breath.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vaibhav330 @aparanjape It's does recommend as shown below at home. And the original tweet raised the concern that it's quite easy for patients to be treated with steroids without hypoxia. COVID symptoms can go on for 2 weeks. People can call docs  if they say they are still having fever and cough... https://t.co/7hZSk0tvZW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aparanjape I'm not sure what's going on if AIIMS is recommending before hypoxia. Im not in favor of giving steroids unless patient is hypoxic. That's what the data say. And early use can be harmful. https://t.co/xetcEfGA5G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aparanjape See below. https://t.co/hFCvdNYf54]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus *steroids]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnooBhu @DrSidMukherjee @ICMRDELHI Will reach out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@radheshwar @aiims_nd @rishika625 @ndtv Sorry for the typo. I deleted and reposted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14/ Dr Randeep Guleria, Director, AIIMS on the need for lockdowns in places where the test positivity is &gt;10% in India.  @aiims_nd @rishika625 @ndtv https://t.co/kF0XQZOOiM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Zathras3: Thread.  @VincentRK is a Mayo Clinic doctor, here pleading with the Indian government to respond to the gravest emergency in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ddiamond Important article. Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ddiamond: NEW: Meet the vaccine skeptics who changed their minds. (And why they did it.)  Public health experts and White House offic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PSampathkumarMD: We are overwhelmed by the generosity and kindness of people who want to help with the COVID crisis in India. Whether y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13/ Here are similar views from members of the governments COVID India task force. @kaunain_s @IndianExpress https://t.co/T3TV6vg1le]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12/ Here is Dr. Fauci. https://t.co/EfXNB6ZXZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11/ Control in daily new cases is essential for a safe and effective vaccination campaign.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GaviSeth: Delighted to announce that we have put pen to paper on a deal with @Moderna that will make up to half a billion doses of thei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GaviSeth @Moderna Great news. Thanks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMiguelPerales: Experts agree US wont achieve herd  immunity d/t vaccine hesitancy. Our most vulnerable patients need herd immunity t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrMiguelPerales We need to reach people who are hesitant through voices they trust. Each demographic where there is hesitancy needs a different approach. @jennfranconews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@moricemdphd @mnwild Have fun Bill. Stay safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nishit24 @hasanminhaj It's in my thread. We are part of @IndiaCOVIDSOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JulieNelsonKARE Wow!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrSidMukherjee: 14/n So overall suggestions 1. Release data or appoint from a clinical body to assess the reality of viral breakthrough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrSidMukherjee: 1/n The anecdotal stories about the number of people in India getting COVID after AZ or Covaxin need to be addressed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sharmasupriya: 25 flights have landed at Delhi airport in five days  Bringing 300 tonnes of emergency Covid supplies  5,500 oxygen conc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hasanminhaj: See below. Good collection of resources and places to donate to! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vaibhav330 @EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus See guideline from @ASH_hematology https://t.co/W18oALrJlV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vaibhav330 @EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus Blood thinner data is complicated. But basically mild patients don't need them. If they need steroids they also need blood thinners. There is disagreement on dose. Prophylactic dose vs treatment dose. If patients are severely ill  in ICU then prophylactic  dose is recommended.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vaibhav330 @EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus This is based on the evidence. People can follow anecdote or experience recognizing that they can be causing harm. And it's ok for their own practice. But when you put out a guideline I'd be careful with this drug, a drug I know all too well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vaibhav330 @EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus Dexamethasone is not an antiviral. It suppresses the immune system. You don't want it when the virus is dividing. That's why giving it early can be counter productive. I recommend Dex the moment you see hypoxia. Or if you don't have a pulse ox when someone has shortness of breath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus But when using a potentially harmful med, the onus of proving benefit is on us. We can't say there is no data that it won't help. We can't do by anecdote or hope. This is a risky med that I won't recommend outside of whats been shown in an RCT.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus The use of lsteroids, antibiotics,   several other unproven drugs seems to be quite common. It is causing harm. We need docs in India to promote what's important: Stay home, take paracetamol for fever,  don't go to hospital or take meds unless oxygen &lt;92% or are short of breath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EshaKaul1 @amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus Unfortunately that was tested in the RECOVERY trial. Benefit was only seen in hypoxic patients. None of us are saying don't give it if mild patients develop hypoxia, or if patients are hypoxic when you first see them.   There was trend to harm in patients who were not hypoxic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @DoriToribio Has to be done. Sadly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @haleemak_: If there's one thread you read today, let it be this one!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["About 2.7 million Americans age 55 or older are contemplating retirement years earlier than theyd imagined because of the pandemic" according to the article. Most are probably the "square root" type.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hasanminhaj: For those of you whove been asking how to support the countless lives impacted by Indias second COVID wave, @GiveIndia h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is one more. @GiveIndia https://t.co/Ldlzm4yizd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus @PSampathkumarMD is working on a website with guidelines for India. Will be out soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: WHERE ARE THE AID? Despite 25 flights loaded with 300 tonnes of emergency #COVID19 relief supplies landing in Delhi  (55]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarunaSagili @DrSidMukherjee As I mentioned, cases occurring shortly after 1st dose are considered as occurring in unvaccinated.   The trials didn't include immunosuppressed. So it's possible that we find cases if someone has leukemia or significant immunosuppression from cancer or chemo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarunaSagili @DrSidMukherjee Can you post link to data. Or report. How many were in fully vaccinated (2 weeks after 2nd dose)? What is the denominator? All of the people vaccinated in India?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amitguptabliss @AnantBhan @ashishkjha @DrLahariya @netshrink @ProfBhargava @FaheemYounus No there isn't. Can be harmful if that's the case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSidMukherjee Clarification  https://t.co/bisdU4B9sP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSidMukherjee Also to clarify, there are many people who have become critically ill shortly after first dose, before the immune response can set in. I'm not including those.   And have not heard personally of critically ill or dying after full vaccination (2 weeks after 2 doses).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrSidMukherjee: I got a thousand replies to my questions, but not any that I needed/wanted. 1. I know the lab data... do we have HUMAN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSidMukherjee With high enough viral dose, people are going to fall ill even if they have protective immunity. I hope for India and the world that protection from ICU admission and death holds to a large extent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSidMukherjee Also as you hypothesized last year, some of these breakthrough infections are likely related to high viral dose/multiple simultaneous exposure settings which have become unavoidable in the current crisis there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSidMukherjee Although anecdotal I have no doubt that the variants in India, whatever they are are capable of causing reinfection after COVID or the 2 COVID vaccines available there. Would be important to get the data you want in preprint or peer reviewed literature. We have no idea of scale.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSidMukherjee We have numerous reports and calls from people in India who are getting COVID after 1 dose or even 2 doses of Covaxin or Covishield. Some of these have been ill with fever for many days. So far we have not heard of anyone critically ill or dying.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chadinabhan: This is a good thread that underscores all the tough choices; no choice is perfect. Ill add that all unused vaccines in t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many comments that the lockdown or shelter in place will be difficult. But no one is providing an alternative.   I know that national shelter in place or stay home orders cause severe hardship. That's why I said no easy choices. But you cannot treat your way out of COVID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JasmineDivekar What's your alternative solution? https://t.co/HXxr0g8CED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArunKrishnan_ Please check out what is being proposed. https://t.co/AL6xhJ4v6o  You have to look at what the alternative is: do u think a shelter I place will cost 15,000-30,000 deaths a day. Coz that's the current reality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SonaliVaid Do you think a humane shelter in place will lead to 3000 confirmed deaths a day (in truth 15,000 to 30,000 deaths a day given the breakdown in testing and counting). Cause that's the current situation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JasmineDivekar Unlike the first lockdown you have a reasonable endgame. Let the cases come down. Simultaneously Vaccinate fast. Focus on one dose. It will reduce disease severity and keep people alive. Reopen in places gradually.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rfonsi1 @chadinabhan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID and early retirement. Price's law (50% of work is done by square root of the total people who work) is going to amplify the pain. The "square root" (people who are most successful or most burnt out) are the ones who may quit early. @atanzi @msasso https://t.co/085CFhJNMw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The crisis in India affects all of us.   More infections = more mutations More mutations = more infections. Vicious cycle.   With 400,000 new cases a day in India, we need to be concerned about variants arising that are more contagious and more virulent. @michaelmina_lab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See more here on the rationale and details on the way to do a humane shelter in place that avoids the mistakes of the first lockdown. https://t.co/LaEEVPclPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A nationally coordinated and implemented shelter in place will buy time for vaccines. It will flatten the curve, reduce stress on healthcare system, and reduce case fatality rate.   I don't see an alternative solution that will be associated with lesser loss of life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All the choices are bad.  But only one is even feasible in current situation: a nationwide lockdown (with protections for the poor). With proper notice,   provision of supplies  money to workers and poor people, the economic pain can be reduced. Will save huge number of lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India's choices:  Wait it out--&gt; Will cause massive loss of life   Vaccinate quickly--&gt; Not enough vaccines  Treat COVID effectively--&gt; Shortage of oxygen/beds/HCWs  Voluntary precautions--&gt; Low compliance   A nationwide shelter at home order--&gt; Feasible. Can work if done right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: Most SARS-CoV2 infections produces billions/trillions of virions inside the person.   Every day, there are Quadrillion]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PSampathkumarMD @UpToDate And I'm reminded that we sadly lost Dr. Rose who founded UpToDate to COVID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PSampathkumarMD: This is huge!!!    Easily the best source for the most updated, unbiased information on #COVID19   Burton Rose the fou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prar_s @PrakashLab @paimadhu @PSampathkumarMD @KrutikaKuppalli @FutureDocs Done.  I reviewed the site. You have done an excellent job.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @prar_s: I created "COVID Resources India" as a comprehensive list of COVID resources across India. For starters, it also has a subpage]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VincentRK: To control the crisis and limit further new mutants India needs a combination of 1) massive vaccination and 2) nationwide sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aakritipandita: India gets free access to UptoDate Articles  Great initiative by @GautamSikka @IndiaCOVIDSOS  @paimadhu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @calamur: I write on the Misplaced Priorities and Squandered opportunities by the Government, in the fight against COVID  https://t.co/I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kenjeong:  Californias secret weapon in COVID-19 success: Embracing the vaccine by @latimes https://t.co/6YhKssCLuQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaxAustin @lolacoaster Don't know about about the sense of smell. But many news reports of patients with long haul symptoms having relief of symptoms after vaccination. Vaccination is recommended anyway for patients who have had COVID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FixedPoint10 Yes. We are hearing of many such cases. And after AZ Covishield almost all cases we have heard are mild and keeping patients out of the hospital.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>