<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@J13mad Hi there, you will be contacted regarding this as soon as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @saoltagroup: Thinking about your future career, or even a new career, then think about #midwifery. Tracy Sugre, CMM, #UHG explains ho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BookNanny1 GPs will begin vaccinating those who are high risk with the specific conditions in Group 4 and will run seamlessly to vaccinate Group 7  there will be no pause and the timeline will depend on each GP and their patient group and profiles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@edep6 @CcoHse Dia Duit. Is fidir clr don vacsan as Gaeilge. Glaoigh ar HSELive ag 1850241850 agus cuirfear ar aghaidh t chuig Gnomhaire le Gaeilge a chabhridh leat le do chlr.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BookNanny1 Hi there, GPs will vaccinate people aged 59 and under in group 7. It will take some time for GPs to identify and invite everyone. GPs will contact their patients when its their turn to be vaccinated. Patients can also register online when their age group is being called.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@keltoi13 Hi there, unfortunately, we cannot provide clinical advice here. You should contact your medical team to discuss this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Edenderry, R45X951 Clonminch Castlerea, F45PX84 Nenagh, E45TY0 Kilcohan, X91EY73 Mullingar, N91X36E Ballina, F26E622  You will need photo ID and a mobile phone number at the test centre.  Find out more about walk-in test centres here: https://t.co/WwgEwshpXO  (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here are today's open #COVID19 walk-in test centres: Youghal, P36TX68 Dunmanway, P47CK70 Letterkenny, F92TD92 Blanchardstown, D15YV78 Ballymun, D11DK40 Tralee, V92C996 Newbridge  (1/2) https://t.co/NF0M9nzVuc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@steve7158 Hi Steve, could you please DM us regarding this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roinnslainte: An update on the National Clinical Programme on Eating Disorders, from Minister @MaryButlerTD.   @HSELive https://t.co/4X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IDM2021 #InternationalDayoftheMidwife]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch video messages to midwives and student midwives from: Rachel Kenna Chief Nursing Officer @roinnslainte- https://t.co/pQFhPaj54e @GSGerShaw Nursing  Midwifery Services Director @NurMidONMSD - https://t.co/cukSV2jNUn Sheila McClelland CEO NMBI https://t.co/T20Y6oH5uQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today, May 5th, we celebrate #InternationalMidwivesDay. We would like to thank all our midwife and student midwife colleagues for the fantastic work they do and the wonderful care they give to women, babies and families. https://t.co/eYaKJCyqTf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kerrywoman1 Hi Mary, could you please DM us regarding this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Emmas04716187 Hi Emma, could you please DM us regarding this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FeFeB15 Hi Aoife, yes this is a legitimate text. You will be contacted regarding your rescheduled appointment as quickly as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you need help registering online for your #COVIDVaccine, we have information on our website that may be useful: https://t.co/nTNxEKexNZ  You can also call us on 1850241850 https://t.co/yt1fD85PIk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is #WorldHandHygieneDay. Cleaning your hands is the easiest way to avoid infections including #COVID19. Watch our video to learn how to clean your hands properly.  https://t.co/xX7zmPQurQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@apjbrett Hi Andrew, could you please DM us regarding this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaeveOBrien5 Hi Maeve, those who registered will receive a message with details of their vaccination appointment within 3 weeks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today were inviting people aged 58 to register for their #COVIDVaccine. The quickest and easiest way to register is online. You'll need:  PPSN Eircode mobile number Email address Register: https://t.co/nTNxEKexNZ https://t.co/5T7hHWqMP5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulieRossi Hi Rossi, all individuals in the 50-69 age cohort attending mass vaccination centres will be receiving the AstraZeneca vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrsBBarry Hi Brd, you can see information on when the second dose of AstraZeneca will be administered here - https://t.co/CkoM2cwmRD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ever wonder what a #DayintheLife of a Consultant Respiratory Physician is like? Check out this @irishexaminer article for an hour by hour account of a working day in the life of Dr Desmond Murphy. https://t.co/keFD5K4Abt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaeveOBrien5 Hi Maeve, this will depend on the age group you fall into. If you want to DM us some more information I can help you with this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MariaRushe_ Thanks Maria, I have flagged this to be updated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have any symptoms of #COVID19, don't delay. Call your GP and they will arrange a test for you if you need it. Symptoms include: fever cough shortness of breath loss or change to your sense of smell or taste Learn more by watching our video.  #StaySafe #HoldFirm https://t.co/LC4CBiDDT2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@noelj5138 Our Medical Card team will be able to help you out with this. They can be reached by Telephone: 1890 252 919 (LoCall) or 01 8647100. Or you can email: clientregistration@hse.ie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marina23337990 Hi there, can you drop us a DM with some more information please?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder: if your child has any symptoms of #COVID19, they need to stay home from school  isolate from other people. Phone your GP if you think your child has symptoms. Children must also stay at home if a member of their household has tested positive. https://t.co/IlYpTmtWT8 https://t.co/5IWrB9a451]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GuyltyPleasure Hi Sonja, can you please send us a DM with some more information?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nithiarnaigh Hi Marie, can you send us a DM with some more information please?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BridDunneOT Hi Brid, can you drop us a DM with some more information please?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anna35290593 Hi Anna, can you drop us a DM with some more information please?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ktd_01 Hi Cit, can you drop us a DM with some more information please?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A cautious and gradual reopening of society and the economy will start from today. Please remember to keep following public health guidelines including hand hygiene, social distancing, and wearing a face covering. We can do this - better days are coming. #HoldFirm  https://t.co/VpXQSd0L5N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MindaugasLaban1 Hi there, if you have recently travelled to Ireland you can call a GP to book a free Covid 19 test on Day 5 after arriving. You can see a list of GP contact details in the area here - https://t.co/WDFOUpjPCK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BineTheBee Have you been in touch with your hospital team / consultant? Either they or your GP will need to refer for the vaccine if in one of the high risk groups.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVIDVaccine registration is open for people aged 59. The quickest  easiest way to register is online. You'll need your PPSN, Eircode, mobile phone number  email address. Don't worry if you can't register today, registration will stay openhttps://t.co/nTNxEJWWWr https://t.co/YLdE4e14IQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danielhayes_1 Hi Daniel, can you please DM us with some more information?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarenNiDhulain Hi Karen, those who registered should receive a message with their appointment details within 3 weeks of registering.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonomahony Hi Jason, could you please DM us some more information?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Midwife of the Year, Clare Kennedy would support anyone in their decision to become a midwife. I think it is a wonderful profession. We are encouraging anyone thinking about their future or a new career to think about midwifery. Learn more: https://t.co/1u678qd0iJ https://t.co/GZOZS7sUDg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sullymam Hi Stella, your appointment will be automatically rescheduled, you do not need to register. You will be contacted regarding your rescheduled appointment as soon as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sultanmk925 Hi Sultan, do not get your COVID-19 vaccine if you currently have COVID-19  wait until it has been 4 weeks since you first tested positive. If you have any other queries, please DM us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jpwright17 Hi there, could you please DM us some more information regarding your query?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@D8Boi Hi Deryck, thank you for letting us know.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UltravioletHilI Hi Adam, we will send you text messages with your vaccination appointment details 3 to 7 days before your appointments.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new video-based Pulmonary Rehabilitation Education support programme is now freely accessible on our website. Access the 14 videos and discover a range of topics herehttps://t.co/E8Dk9X1tD0 https://t.co/ZdILqBxL8f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you cleaning your hands correctly? Cleaning your hands is the easiest way to avoid infections including #COVID19. Protect yourself, protect your family, keep your hands clean #HandHygiene https://t.co/O5eIyNdVNJ https://t.co/mKDnghwGUC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mparlion @LiamTwomey9999 Hi Max, only those who will be 50 on or before May 13th can register.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenHi88873227 Hi Helen, could you please DM us regarding this query?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nicky82725490 Hi Nicky, they do not change every day, you can find details here: https://t.co/dC5Bb1pG0B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our helpline is busy as people aged 59 register for their #COVIDVaccine. You can:    Call in the afternoon when the lines are less busy on 1850241850   Register online at https://t.co/nTNxEJWWWr https://t.co/rw4No3ARlc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RachAnnFagan @DonnellyStephen Hi Rachael, we are waiting on guidance regarding this. We will update as soon as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@witchgirl26 Hi Susan, could you please DM us regarding this query?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@witchgirl26 Hi Susan, could you please DM us regarding this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lismcb23 Hi Lisa, could you please DM us regarding this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clonminch Edenderry, R45X951 Castlerea, F45PX84 Nenagh, E45TY04 Kilcohan, X91EY73 Mullingar, N91X36E  You will need photo ID and a mobile phone number at the test centre.   Find out more about walk-in test centres here: https://t.co/WwgEwshpXO   (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here are today's open #COVID19 walk-in test centres:  Youghal, P36TX68 Dunmanway, P47CK70 Letterkenny, F92TD92 Blanchardstown, D15YV78 Ballymun, D11DK40 Tralee, V92C996 Newbridge   (1/2) https://t.co/xDEAPIMz4Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mise_Smurph Hi Sarah, we are currently waiting on guidance for this. We will update as soon as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MjoconorMary Hi Mary, GPs will vaccinate people aged 59 and under in group 7. It will take some time for GPs to identify and invite everyone. GPs will contact many of their patients when its their turn to be vaccinated. Patients can also register online when their age group is being called.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shiels_bernie @notblondnow Hi Bernie, Thanks for contacting us, we are going to look into this. Would you mind sending us a DM with your phone number, the time you registered and if you requested a resend code?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fitztalty Hi Niamh, we are going to look into this. Would you mind sending us a DM with your phone number, the time you registered and if you requested a resend code?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Loulou3Kenny Hi Louise, unfortunately, there are currently no walk-in Covid-19 testing centres in Wexford. You can see the walk-in testing centres that will soon be opening in the 'coming soon' section here: https://t.co/dC5Bb1pG0B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TaylorStewart45 Hi Taylor, if you are aged 50-59 in Cohort 7, you can register online. If you are under 59, your GP will contact you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@creed_lorraine Hi Lorraine, as per the NIAC recommendations you can still have the vaccine if you have recently had a blood clot or are on blood-thinning treatments. There is no reason to delay vaccination. Like everyone who gets the vaccine, you should be aware of the symptoms to look out for.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leinsterwhite @careexperience Hi there, you can see details of updated walk-in test centres on our website here: https://t.co/dC5Bb1pG0B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scudkelly @andylampy Hi Sean, were asking people to register on specific days to help us manage the demand. This will make it easier for everyone to register. People aged 50 to 54 will be invited to register from Sunday 9 May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@One2One9020121 Hi Daibhid, those who registered will receive a message with their appointment details within 3 weeks of registering.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NiRiain28 Hi there, this may be due to capacity in the local vaccination centre. Those who registered will receive a message with their appointment details within 3 weeks of registering.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brennan2703 Hi Andrew, you will be able to register to receive your vaccine when registration opens for your age group. We do not yet have confirmation of when registration will open for those in your age group. We will update as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theresaryan Hi Theresa, we are waiting for guidance on this, we will update as soon as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sarahc74740912 Hi Sarah, we are waiting on guidance for this but we will update as soon as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important to hear feedback on your experiences of care in order to improve the quality of health and social care services in Ireland. We encourage anyone invited to participate to complete this important survey. @careexperience https://t.co/oIw8Qipf4J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Megan_1200 Hi Marjorie, a home vaccination can be arranged for people who cannot leave home for medical reasons. Your GP can refer you to the National Ambulance Service (NAS) for home vaccination. A NAS team member will contact you to schedule your appointment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sarahc74740912 Apologies Sarah, https://t.co/DusXXNA5yN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notblondnow Hi there, if you are having trouble registering online you can register by calling 1850 24 1850.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrRobertOConnor Hi there, were asking people to register on specific days to help us manage the demand. This will make it easier for everyone to register.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At The Helix in Dublin, staff are working hard to continue the rollout of the #COVID19Vaccines. Watch our video from The Helix to learn more about this vaccine centre and the people who work there #OurHealthService https://t.co/evNjlCQmqD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wallywalsh70 Hi Tony, when you receive a text message regarding your vaccine appointment, it will include details of the time and location.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Princessflash21 Hi there, unfortunately, as he is 49 he cannot yet register.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theresaryan Hi Theresa, you can find more information about pregnancy and the Covid-19 vaccine here: https://t.co/DusXXNA5yN - we will update as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Adi64194039 Hi Adi, if you are not in Ireland when it is your turn to register, you can register from abroad. If you are not in Ireland when your vaccine is scheduled, you can reschedule it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leonore25870915 Hi Leonore, if you are in the 50-69 age group you can register online.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You may not need to visit the Emergency Department for your injury. Injury Units treat broken bones, strains, burns and more. Find your local Injury Unit here: https://t.co/QXyBrPNRTO https://t.co/RFBmYzeZzb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brendandav1 Hi Brendan, you can register online here https://t.co/t0mwVg2ptG or by phoning 1850 24 1850.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rushig @paulreiddublin Hi Rushikesh, we will let these groups know when they can register through the HSE website, news or public advertising.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Aras80321462 Hi there, could you please DM us regarding this query?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sarahc74740912 Hi Sarah, you can find information on COVID-19 vaccines and pregnancy here: https://t.co/jgqcYKVfBd We will update as more information becomes available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andylampy Hi Andy, those who are high-risk aged 50-69 can register online or by phoning 1850 24 1850.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MargaretMcMen19 Hi there, you can register for the vaccine online or by phoning 1850 24 1850.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deere_pat Hi Pat, you will receive a message with your appointment details within 3 weeks of registering.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@steve7158 Hi Steve, you will receive a message with your appointment details within 3 weeks of registering.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BQurek Hi there, we will let you know when you can register for the vaccine through the HSE website, news or public advertising.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DaggaDigga Hi there, we will let you know when this group can register through the HSE website, news or public advertising.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Unkhkr1 Hi there, your mum can register for the vaccine, those who register will be contacted in the coming weeks. If your mum receives an appointment she is unable to attend, she can reschedule it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maduncjoe1 Hi Joe, could you please DM us regarding this query?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BineTheBee Hi there, we are currently vaccinating Group 4. Those in Group 4 will be contacted by their hospital team, disability services or GP when it is their turn to be vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeanKennedy51 @TerryEltel @paulreiddublin Hi Jean, this person will receive their appointment details within 3 weeks of registering.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>