<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[FDA announcement about new faster process for authorizing pooled testing, which increases options for school screening programs and others  https://t.co/PwJ0lG7dvJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Landmark day: all adults eligible. For those fortunate enough to have been vaccinated, talk to your family+ friends about it. Help them find vax appointments. Drive them to get vaccinated. Keep up the momentum to help get this pandemic under control   https://t.co/ZbYBHVdj3G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cyrusshahpar46: Amazing Saturday! +4.63M doses administered over total yesterday, a new record! More than 500K higher than old record l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see so many educators and school staff vaccinated, one more big step in making schools safer to return https://t.co/nHhf20JEwo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great new program in Boston to encourage vaccination.  We need these kinds of local programs across the country https://t.co/sNiNy9Epsw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID continues to devastate Brazil, in large part because of the actions and decisions of its leaders who need to change course https://t.co/WgfrWamcST]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gayle Smith will be a force for good in helping the US to assist other countries respond to COVID https://t.co/87rqOhOqZZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7pVGabu7da]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Collins' outreach to the faith community on the important of COVID vaccine https://t.co/a9fb3qGRzw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news as production of Moderna to expand https://t.co/9tstZIEk2H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lXr7wW45aZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/H3DngsXEYE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/UM6E1RSEVB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Launch of new @HHSGov COVID-19 public education campaign - a national initiative to increase public confidence in and uptake of COVID-19 vaccines while reinforcing basic prevention measures such as mask wearing and social distancing https://t.co/N3SZUJersb https://t.co/HskOex39nt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Consistent, clear guidance overall: get vaccinated when you are eligible, wear a mask, avoid crowds, socially distance, dont travel unless its essential. Need to keep up the collective work to bring this pandemic under control.  7/end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New data also shows how vaccination protects against wild type and variants. People should get vaccinated to protect themselves and their families and communities. 6/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New data shows that COVID was the cause of 11% of all US deaths in 2020, quite disproportionately affecting people of color.  Focus on reaching vulnerable populations with vaccine, testing, interventions more important than ever 5/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID cases increased by 12% in last week, hospitalizations increasing, with number of people dying continuing to be about 900 people, every day. Need to strengthen our response and slow the spread. 4/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 more federally run mass vax sites coming, which each will be able to vaccinate 3000 people a day.  Comes on top of 25 fed mass vax sites that together vaccinate 95,000 people a day.  3/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are more than 50,000 vaccine sites now across the country.  Within 3 weeks, there will be ~70,000 locations, as the number of pharmacies that are vaccinating doubles. 2/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White House COVID briefing today.  Significant news and developments starting with: by April 19th 90% of adult Americans will be eligible for a vaccine, 90% of Americans will live within 5 miles of vaccination site. 1/x https://t.co/cbD9IgabMJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reasons why testing for COVID is still so pivotal for bringing this pandemic under control https://t.co/W1Vj6aSnxu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RhGrgMev3L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yjaDIEA1dE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stunning collapse of a health system where people are dying because they can't get basic medical care, precipitated by stunning collapse of political leadership in epidemic crisis.  https://t.co/RhGrgMev3L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @EllenJMacKenzie and incredible @JohnsHopkinsSPH community for another year of critical contributions to public health in the US and the world https://t.co/NVxlAh7Kty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clear advice from health leaders across government and in public health community outside government: don't change course on masks and social distancing, cases and hospitalizations now on the rise  https://t.co/1k7TIQEl2b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Evidence continues to roll in regarding the amazing effectiveness of mRNA vaccines. Another study showing how effective they are in real world conditions.  https://t.co/hvUt0hD4ql]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is Paris right now. They are, again, on edge of not being able to care for pts in ICUS. Worse than their prior COVID peaks. We could get there again if we stop doing what we know works to slow spread.  https://t.co/zZz41qF2AD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lifting masking restrictions, reducing social distancing when the country still has 65,000 cases a day is wrong path and will lead to unnecessary critical illnesses and death. Vaccination will work but we need more time, need to reach many more people https://t.co/1sQ9C1ROiS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good development for COVID test developers //  FDA takes steps to streamline path for COVID-19 screening tools, provides information to help groups establishing testing programs  https://t.co/nIRjAM2zR1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Helix dashboard: shows steadily rising numbers of B.1.1.7 cases in US, most concentrated in CA and Florida https://t.co/QsgXab3lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @polsiewski: Good news @CDCgov now has excellent guidance on increasing ventilation  filtration to reduce risk of #covid19 in schools -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCDirector: We are on track to get 100 million #COVID19 vaccines into arms in the first 100 days of the Biden-Harris administration. A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @selenasd: NEW   If you feel like youre clicking around randomly to try to find a #COVIDVaccine appointment   I present to you an @NP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: For a window to the pandemic in Israel, and unique perspective, you may find our new podcast (+ transcript) with @segal_eran]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drJoshS: The enormous increase in the life expectancy gap reflects the staggering disparity in *age-adjusted* mortality by race and eth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterHorby: RECOVERY trial goes international.   Wonderful to welcome our colleagues in Nepal and Indonesia to the RECOVERY trial of CO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From WH briefing yesterday:  vaccine allotment to states increased to 13M week, +2M week to pharmacies; 1200 national guard, 1000 members of the military, and 1700 federal personnel now deployed to support vaccination; $3B in fed funding for the effort https://t.co/Ek9rznpeM5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[$200M in new @CDCgov funding to increase the capacity to screen genomes for variants.  Will increase screening capability from 9,000/week to 25,000/week https://t.co/asZeSFCrqS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to have started as Senior Advisor for COVID Response @HHSGov and eager to contribute here to all the good work being done to control this pandemic in the time ahead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinLandray: RECOVERY Result for Tocilizumab For patients with COVID-19, hypoxia  inflammation: - reduces mortality - shortens time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important to see @DrTedros convey that the @WHO led mission on the origins of COVID-19 will continue and that "all hypotheses remain open and require further study." It will be critical to analyze + present all salient data before making judgments https://t.co/d9sBjG6x0o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @invadingpirate: REACT study calls for increase in symptoms suggestive of covid.  We've been testing staff with myalgia, headache, sore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excited to share @JHSPH_CHSs newly launched COVID-19 Testing Toolkit, a one-stop shop for info about specific tests + testing services and guidance for organizations seeking to develop their own testing strategies: https://t.co/gBKjoWZNky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reichlab: I appreciate that @UMassAmherst is taking its recent spike in #COVID19 cases seriously. However, the prohibition of any outdo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarionKoopmans: preprint: single dose mRNA in prior COVID cases gives high titers of antibodies against variants even if the levels are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JHSPH_CHS: Today weve launched a new resource, The COVID-19 Testing Toolkit, a one-stop shop for organizations seeking to engage in CO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New report from #CommuniVax -led by @MSchochSpana + colleagues, informed by amazing stakeholder group-      provides steps local policymakers can take to work w/ hard-hit communities to ensure they receive the benefits of #COVID19 vaccination efforts: https://t.co/A8xpum2l0t https://t.co/TvOMgQpIGx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Given the consequences of this pandemic, it is essential to have thorough independent investigation of the potential origins of this pandemic https://t.co/6xbA3ANUi5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A mistake for Gov Reynolds (and other Govs) to end their mask requirements w/ rising numbers of more transmissible variant cases in US. We need masks, social distancing to stay in place as vaccination moves out to prevent resurgent pandemic https://t.co/wn0yyOwpbp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2ff4arlcqw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrRichBesser: Let us make the COVID-19 vaccine program something we can all be proud of. @DrJulieMorita and I share a few ideas in toda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/UfWL0fQdDA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many in @CDCgov, US pharmacies, health depts and public health community have long seen the promise of utilizing pharmacies as part of a national mass vaccination program. It's terrific  important that the program is getting started. 8/end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[... stores around country, a sizable portion of which are in underrepresented zip codes; ability to manage the cold chain required;  ability to move vaccine around w/ their distribution systems to try to match demand with supply.  7/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fed pharm program takes advantage of capabilities pharmacies already have in place: administrative, logistical and vaccination workforce house; IT systems that can schedule 1st and 2nd appts; tech to communicate by text w/ pts; ability to give epi for allergies, ... 6/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quite distinct from long term care pharmacy COVID program. In that program, pharmacies had to schedule visits to facilities, and were challenged by that, by holidays, by low sign-up in many places. The new program will happen in stores, less barriers to success and speed. 5/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Overall it has 21 chain + independent pharmacies representing &gt; 40K locations  with more getting vaccine as supply and success allow. A key factor considered in selection of the pharmacies in each state is their ability to reach populations most at risk for severe illness. 4/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These pharmacies are the same that people use daily for  the country, where many people already get their flu shots.  The number of stores having COVID vaccine will be limited to start, but with time and as they show success, the number will grow.  3/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will create additional new path for people to get vaccinated around country. Direct pharmacy allocation will be in addition to the 10.5M doses being delivered weekly that states will administer (this is a dose number which has increased some since end of last week.) 2/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big announcement about the vaccine roll out today is the start of the Fed retail pharmacy partnership for COVID vaccination. Excited to see this program get started Feb 11 and think it has high potential. 1/x https://t.co/gglFmzNaro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: We're so indebted to this team for all they've done, hundreds of volunteers, leaders including @kissane, @alexismadrigal, an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTedros: Encouraging news: for the 3rd week in a row, the number of new #COVID19 cases reported globally fell. This trend shows we can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Admin encouraging physicians and states to not hold back vaccine at this point because vaccine delivery now more consistent and holding back not necessary.  If this happens, then daily vax rate will go up.  6/end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of a couple weeks ago, less than 50% of vaccine delivered to states had been administered, now it is up to 62% and Admin will continue to monitor this number daily; 5/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1.3M vaccinations being administered a day; 25M have gotten a first dose, 31M doses delivered all together; Means 1/10 US adults have gotten at least first dose 4/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DOD/HHS announced $230M to ELLUME to make first OTC COVID test that is done at home and then available in 15 minutes. Will result in delivery 8.5M tests/month (would be 100,000 doses per month prior to that contract) 3/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Race/ethnicity data missing for 47% of vaccinations. @cdcgov and Admin working to change that and strongly encouraging the full reporting of that data 2/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From White House COVID response conference:  Will soon be ~7,000 viruses sequenced per week to look for variants 1/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WmBrangham: Fauci: if we want to stop more variants, we must deny the virus an "open playing field." Unchecked replication will create]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Live COVID press briefing now. This is the kind of briefing that the country needs on regular basis to be informed.  The more the public knows and understands the better the country will do https://t.co/UwQTDds80S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVID19Tracking: More Black Americans have died of COVID-19 than there are names on the Vietnam Memorial. More Black or Latinx people h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is sadly so clear now (and was so clear then) that states needed funding to plan for and execute the biggest, most urgent, most complicated mass vaccination effort in US history. https://t.co/PODkqqCcoU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you Andy Brooks for what you did to help the country's COVID response   https://t.co/z7KNpmAMCr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One in every 440 people living in Laredo has died from COVID so far, probably an undercount, and no signs of slowing. Highest respect for people like Dr Cigarroa trying to slow spread, to change policies, inform people about risks, care for people there  https://t.co/zADoKKbDVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congress should pass the American Rescue Plan to provide funding to accelerate and strengthen the vaccination program (community vax clinics, mobile clinics, free vaccine etc) and expand genomic surveillance for variants, and accelerate other COVID relief efforts. 13/end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As long as the virus thrives, evolves, mutates anywhere in the world, it will be a threat to everywhere in the world. 12/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very important to vaccinate the US population given the terrible illness and mortality from this disease in our country.  But we have to be big donor and part of the global vaccination effort too. 11/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Discovery of variants and clear evolution of this virus around the world means that there will continue to be major threat posed by this virus until there is successful global vaccination effort everywhere. 10/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JJ promises 100M doses to US by June (which could hugely accelerate US vaccination effort) as well as 1B doses for world in 2021 (which will hugely accelerate global vaccination effort).  9/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Terrific press release on JJ vax  85% efficacy in protecting against severe COVID at 28 days in wildtype, UK and S. African strains, and no deaths after 49 days. One dose will make administration faster + easier. Need to see data, and FDA to review, but great news so far. 8/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important to see all of Pfizer shipments now coming with syringe that allows use of that 6th dose  thats one more dose with every single vial (of previously 5 doses.) 7/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great development that US Public Health Service Commissioned Corps officers being activated to assist on the ground vaccination efforts. And that FEMA giving out $1B in assistance to states and to have 200 FEMA officials on the ground now helping with state vax efforts. 6/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very good to see that HHS revised the Prep Act to increase the number of vaccinators around the country by allowing retired nurses and doctors to do COVID vaccination. 5/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still wide range of coverage across US. Some states have given 6 doses per 100 people, others 13. Overall nearly 50M doses have been delivered to states, and about 31M have been administered. Hopefully states will be able to continue to close the gap. 4/x https://t.co/wXcqSHvS60]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are now stable dose projections for next 3 weeks  10M doses to be distributed nationally per week -a 16% increase. States have been asking for this stability, and it should help them in their planning efforts. 3/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will need to accelerate vaccination numbers further as soon as vaccine production allows, but the numbers of daily vaccinations moving in right direction. Now is the time to be rapidly scaling up capacity to administer in all states. 2/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very encouraged by the moves forward this week in the US vaccination effort. An average of 1.2-1.3M doses a day being administered across the country now (up from 700k-800K 2 wks ago). 1/x https://t.co/GYhUH4abqK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally - Congress should pass the American Rescue Plan  to fund these programs to slow this pandemic down, increase funding to make schools a lot safer, expand testing + PPE and other important COVID efforts. 14/end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And of course its critical for people to get vaccinated when they get the opportunity. 13/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you work or go to a school in an indoor place outside the home, then do what you can to improve ventilation and air filtration. We also should have paid leave in place to make sure people who are sick or exposed can stay home without losing their paychecks.  12/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dangers posed by the ongoing pandemic in the US and the spread of variants here also mean we should physically distance, avoid large gatherings, stay home when sick and get tested, remain isolated after exposure. And it means 11/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Masks should be 2 or 3 ply woven fabric, as per CDC,  should fit snugly over nose/on cheeks and under chin so that air goes through the mask, not around the edges.  Hold your mask up to the light and it should block the light out (or its too thin). 10/x https://t.co/EeqvjXUnxD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[University of Washington study this week concluded that we would save more than 30,000 lives in next 3 months if 95% of us wore masks consistently.  (That would mean hundreds of thousands of hospitalizations and millions of infections avoided too) 9/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To start, this means we should all be wearing masks when out of our houses and near any other people.  Even now just 75% of country wears masks consistently, and some states it's as low as 50% 8/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its also very clear the virus is evolving and may continue to do so in dangerous ways, and the best way to stop new mutations from appearing is to diminish the number of people who get infected. 7/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While tests done show far show vaccines seem to continue to provide strong protection against variants, the variants accelerate transmissibility (which will lead to more people dying), and the UK strain may also directly increase mortality risk in an individual who gets it 6/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Given the minimal surveillance in US, we need to presume that our number are much higher for all the variants of concern, and act accordingly. 5/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very low level of genomic surveillance in US up until now (though that is starting to change) compared to the UK which does genomic surveillance on 5-10% of every COVID case. 4/x]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>