<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Utter stupidity    https://t.co/dxCnqZJAyQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: No testing, No lockdowns, No face coverings,  No mandatory vaccines -- Thats ALL folks https://t.co/IOwJxnBljv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: Anyone can look at these numbers  reach the same conclusions!  So where is this so called pandemic that we are all supposed t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: IF you are not yet a member of our online community (apart from social media), please take 2 minutes and lets get that taken]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegalizeitLala: I cannot stand you fkn mask people. You make others life hell. Stay at home!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@john17_clark @Thesearethedamn @thedoctorxxx You should go back to sleep ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMadej: Avoid getting a nasal swab if you MUST get tested- blood test or cheek swab is safer. for Nasal Covid-19 vaccine - Game change]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMadej: https://t.co/07z3HVTwas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: WATCH + RT my interview with @drvandanashiva as she warns that if we dont fight back against #Gates and his empire, ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMadej: Make no mistake. You are the lab rat, you are the guinea pig when you consent to this CV injection. https://t.co/DB3Jr7kv4W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2LarryJohnson7 That red jacket The Weekend was wearing had 40lbs of rubies sewn into it. Ezekiel 28:13-15 - The word Sardius in that first verse is translated to Ruby in Strong's Concordance (H124). #Satanic #Ritual]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's not normal to grope children...@JoeBiden  #PedoJoeBiden #pedofiliaecrime https://t.co/8tkc2ByjOs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikepompeo: Censorship, wokeness, political correctness, it all points in one direction  authoritarianism, cloaked as moral righteousn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Using his #Drama teacher skill set to the utmost !! #Drama #DramaAlert https://t.co/DktbjEmxXk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Because politicians have forgotten what these documents stand for: https://t.co/oHSCKA2rOs https://t.co/FUy0ibfS77]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TruthMatters https://t.co/MxhTQvgCDm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good on you @Roman_Baber for standing against #Tyranny and @fordnation - The truth of this #covid #lie must be exposed. %99 recovery rate does not a #pandemic make! Glad you are standing against #NoMoreLockdowns like @randyhillier https://t.co/G1S7Tz7x06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The day of reckoning is coming... #TruthWillPrevail #TreasonAgainstAmerica https://t.co/HEFMkjhsyJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cangal21 They will actually be up and running by Tuesday noon according to John Matze.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi just resign now and prepare for #GITMO  #Traitor #Italygate #StopTheSteaI2020 https://t.co/erWPmqloCg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ill mix all I want! https://t.co/0ionkWw3QE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JacobIsrael71 Move to @parler_app]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just threw up in my mouth, I foresee a #curfew in #Ontario coming.... #NoMoreLockdowns https://t.co/ygJYGbkWPT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AbbyJohnson: Turn off the television and pick up your Bible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, like a #curfew on tap for #Quebec Jan 9th, but let's make it 24 hours for a week or two, hell how about a month so you bureaucrats can completely finish off the middle class, and obliterate #SmallBusiness     #sarcasm #NoMoreLockdowns https://t.co/tSzdOJjyp1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes I wonder why? Maybe @JustinTrudeau has the answer with more #lockdowns and #communist measures. The middle class and economy are being decimated by design. Welcome to #Chinada https://t.co/Fcb5CaLkLk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More #tyranny unfolding by #lockdown2021 https://t.co/ByylBUi6zd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticalOrgasm @deceptive_donny That's because he is a coward of a man, and can't stand like a man and defend his narrative. #Leftist spineless #communist thug he is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deceptive_donny @PoliticalOrgasm Guess when you kneel before #Jesus the King of Kings you will whistle a different tune... Must be a #CCP lover]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CapitolHill murder footage - Again no need for #capitolhill police to murder #AshliBabbitt in cold blood, she wasn't a threat. Hope she is in the presence of #Jesus now. #Tyranny #JusticeForAshliBabbit https://t.co/ZBeMPEm0XL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: Before Covid an Englishman's home was his castle. Not any longer! Our liberties are being destroyed.   https://t.co/FNNjk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jack @twitter I wonder at what point do you cease the technocratic #censorship of individuals because you dont like what they tweet!? That is anything but democracy and freedom, but #tyranny and #communism]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LLinWood @realDonaldTrump  @ezralevant  Woman Trump supporter that was shot by #CapitolHill police... https://t.co/rqnBKXabx8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LLinWood @realDonaldTrump  violent protests? More like murder of an innocent peaceful #Trump protester... https://t.co/vaPx85OAG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier @TPSBoard @TPAca Why are citizens being treated like this? Did you forget you took an oath to uphold the #Charter ? You pulled that crap with me you'd have a  lawsuit on your hands! #Tyranny #wearelivingalie   https://t.co/ZN05Hpdww3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drsimonegold: Lies  science are like oil  water; they dont mix.  When bureaucrats make life  death decisions based on critical race]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Milhouse_Van_Ho: Here we have the total number of deaths in Canada over the past five years. The most recent 12 months of data do not s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LawScribes: Re requiring negative #covid19 test before boarding airline to Canada: Charter of Rights 'mobility rights' section 6(1) "Ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: But its not that rare, is it? https://t.co/kEcb3fRW13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMadej: https://t.co/3QBtrZ3Hqc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LLinWood Hope #Epstein sings like a mockingbird]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @monicaonairtalk: Have it on good authority, we need to pray fervently for protection of @LLinWood family. Thank you. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And the inflated #Covid numbers continue when people die from pre-existing core morbidities. #nolockdown #Agenda2030 https://t.co/RkOGX6X9Aj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ezralevant https://t.co/kvQG4FVwNt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chucktodd so how much are you getting from #CCP ? This is laughable journalism at best. https://t.co/V2x3zlvQde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what Americans have to look forward to @JustinTrudeau and his #CCP coming to the #USA via @JoeBiden and @KamalaHarris if they get away with the fraud. Communist traitors they are. All of them!! #StopTheSteaI2021 https://t.co/7RUHQ9A3SV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Because being outside in the fresh air is dangerous now, especially if you dont wear a #mask outside! #stopthelockdown #covidisalie #LiveYourLife https://t.co/J2ap19sjq8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JB56748641: @GovCanHealth Traveling is perfectly safe right now. And not a crime. As demonstrated by SEVERAL Canadian politicians jetti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Only thing #Canadians are being exposed to is #CCP Bravo Sierra fomented by @JustinTrudeau and his sellout to #Communism  #StopTheLies #stopthelockdown https://t.co/AWkv3xCp6d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SKeshel: Carissa is a nurse. She sympathizes with those who have lost loved ones to this virus.  But here in the US on Month 10 of 15 d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is in Quebec. How long before this starts occurring in #Ont https://t.co/dKW5MBsAC6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier Hope you had an excellent Christmas Randy with your family! Thank you for standing up for our freedoms! Guess this Doc has been removed from #twitter for outing the #lie about our hospitals being overrun! https://t.co/2l3cM6uy6S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: The lies and deceptions of covid are over. How  why so many allowed themselves to be deceived will take years to to unco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: #onpoli #wearelivingalie #nomorelockdowns merry Christmas. Peace  goodwill to all https://t.co/wgyk9ftHEN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMadej: Lies, lies, and more lies. #whathappenedtomyprofession. https://t.co/XBPAdVWmK6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LauraLynnTT: I am grateful for @JustinTrudeau's incompetence. No proper testing and no knowledge about what is actually in the Vaccine,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Tyranny #NoVaccine #NoVaccineForMe https://t.co/CZEBmQSGqL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just do as you are told and dont question our authority! We know whats best for you!! https://t.co/CI5pD6Mrwc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And the media continue their blatant lie that the hospitals are overwhelmed and in dire straits! We are at the tipping point they say! I call #BravoSierra https://t.co/FBzxigVfJf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really, who cares @JustinTrudeau can have my doses. #NoVaccineForMe #mRNA https://t.co/nOVE15znww]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happening all over, nothing different here across the pond in #Ontario  Politicians continue the #fear #narrative unabated! https://t.co/48MPWkL4ti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SydneyLWatson: How did we go from "flatten the curve" to "stay home until you accept communism"?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TaylorMadeYYC Yes stay home and surrender your Charter of rights!?? This is not about black or white. I was born free in this country and resent globalists trying to instill their socialist communist agenda here thanks to bought and sold out @JustinTrudeau to the #CCP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Please read this. And stop and think. We all need to think this through right now. Because what is happening right now i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Milhouse_Van_Ho: https://t.co/TRS09HGFwl https://t.co/k9zeleikxt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TerryPolevoy @roccogalatilaw Must be a doctor of proctology cause you're an ass to not understand that what Rocco is fighting for is more than not wanting to wear a mask, or take a poisonous vaccine. Boys skating at an outdoor rink constitutes @CalgaryPolice overreach assaulting  arresting a boy #dumbass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gbrowning101: As Ontario prepares for the news of a total lockdown, lets not forget our politicians making the decisions for our lives]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it" - George Santayana - Life of Reason, Reason in Common Sense 1905 #Truth https://t.co/q42Xlgst56]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MachadoRedacted @stephiq06 @TheRealKeean @surveyorX @CalgaryPolice  couldnt have said it any more succinctly myself! Well done! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRealKeean @Jessie42292067 @WiesblattOcean Completely unacceptable behaviour by @CalgaryPolice You took an oath and you are infringing on the rights of these boys just participating in our Canadian pastime, over what a fake pandemic - loosing respect for #police #covidhoax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jessie42292067 @SianMorris20 @randyhillier @fordnation So many doctors are being threatened and bought off probably by the #CCP  Canadians need to take back our country!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pbmoreau @randyhillier @fordnation Full on ! Go back to sleep!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There you go, what Ive heard from some health care workers, there is no crisis, no strain on the system! It is all a lie and fear mongering! Stop the #tyranny #EnoughIsEnough https://t.co/8Ic7qT1pFX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: I was interviewed today about the new Tier 4 in parts of England. https://t.co/nZlp1bJqFH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes #WHO can trust them now? https://t.co/PFB4SHPQkM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@of_oide @Crucified316 Does this answer your query!? https://t.co/9VycOBU9Fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wear your #mask or we will infringe upon your Charter of rights!  #Tyranny #covidisascam https://t.co/R6vdkSHLcd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticalOrgasm: Seeing all these sheeple getting vaxxed up with some unproven elixir that is 95% effective against "something" that is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FarbridgeXBT @zerohedge Thats what its going to be called..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump tick tock tick tock.... 37 days sir... #InsurrectionAct]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Truth https://t.co/wu4mTsCLev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau @OurCommons @HoCCommittees @RebelNewsOnline @thelinecanada @truenorth  and don't forget the #CCP troops on Canadian soil!!  https://t.co/Npn2J0aNXF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BogochIsaac @tsnjamesduthie Yep, @JustinTrudeau  can stick it in his butt first!  #nocovidvaccine #Agenda2030 #Agenda21  #Eugenics #TheGreatReset]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@epdevilla @JohnTory @fordnation @JustinTrudeau  https://t.co/xBkswxciTL  #nocovidvaccine #TheGreatReset #Agenda2030 #Agenda21 #Genocide #Eugenics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Truth #nocovidvaccine #TheGreatReset #Agenda2030 https://t.co/Vo5PvjqTOX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMadej: https://t.co/xDhIevZkS0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticalOrgasm: An animal was secured by a chain that was shortened one link at a time, every couple days, until the chain was so shor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: Can we clone @GovRonDeSantis ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@epdevilla @JohnTory @fordnation  @RebelNewsOnline @thelinecanada   How is this store an essential service but you shutdown @adamsonbarbecue  @adamskely for providing for his family? #DoubleStandards #Tyranny https://t.co/Xu2OEwIDvi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will anyone standup and fight!? Will anyone stand for #righteousness https://t.co/xM81GNxL57]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julie_bertoia @CrasTalk @fordnation @celliottability @MariannMeedWard @RegionofHalton Actually governments made sure #BigPharma had indemnity in inoculating those who voluntarilytake the vaxx!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#truth https://t.co/HsWXbedS2s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @punditclass: Anguish and tears from a man who lost his business to the lockdown, and was then arrested for the thoughtcrime of complain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NoLockdowns1: People are dying from suicides  overdoses in record numbers. Join us now to demand  #NoMoreLockdowns (.Org) ! #cdnpoli #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NULOOKREFINISH https://t.co/dYhJBn34Dl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier @nomorelockdowns1  Simply wonderful more and more people are waking up! #Nolockdown #NoNewnormal  #Agenda2030 #Agenda21 #TheGreatReset https://t.co/tJ5IbEPBEK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Reuters Just the beginning of the #earth changes....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And the lies and hoax continue in this #Scamdemic - Its a #Casedemic now!  #TheGreatReset  #Agenda21 #Agenda2030  #NoLockDowns #nolockdown https://t.co/Xt4ljbwqaP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CheriDiNovo @fordnation But people can shop at big box Costco and thats okay? The leftists are killing this country led by the communist traitor @JustinTrudeau  #TheGreatReset #Agenda21  #Agenda2030]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Canadians need to engage in #CivilDisobedience right now!!! https://t.co/OVKs6nUCwM]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>