<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for May 3rd 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Is your State still vaccinating?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TRAVEL ADVISORY FOR PASSENGERS ARRIVING NIGERIA FROM BRAZIL, INDIA AND TURKEY https://t.co/N9ym9SFNQ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The vaccine begins to generate protective immunity 10 to 14 days after the first dose. The current recommendation is that peo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Vaccination card proves that you have taken important step to protect yourself and your loved ones from diseases.   Your vacc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drfaisalshuaib: I had an exciting meeting with MR. CUI Jianchun, the Chinese Ambassador to Nigeria, where we discussed strengthening pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for April 25th 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Is your State still vaccinating?  #YesToCOVID19Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: We can reduce our risk of #COVID19 infection by adhering to all non pharmaceutical measures on #COVID19 prevention: Wear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Without health, we can not do anything. I wish to encourage you to take the COVID-19 vaccine because it is the right thing t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for April 23rd 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Is your State still vaccinating?  #YesToCOVID19Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNICEF_Nigeria: Vaccines bring us closer!   The #COVID19 pandemic is a devastating reminder of the chaos caused by diseases we cannot p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Myth: COVID-19 Vaccine was developed to kill Africans.  FACT: COVID-19 Vaccine was not developed to kill Africans. The Vaccin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Myth: COVID-19 vaccine contains controversial substances.  FACTS: COVID-19 vaccine was not developed using controversial subs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Can I have the vaccine if I have symptoms of COVID-19?  If you currently have COVID-19 symptoms, you should wait until you ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for April 22nd  2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State performing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: When we ignore #COVID19 symptoms we expose everyone around us to #COVID19.  If you develop any of these symptoms; cough, s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @officialnyscng: https://t.co/yQMq7wjdoA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @officialnyscng: https://t.co/Ez9LmuGSZk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Are you a health/frontline worker? Have you received your first shot of the #COVID19 vaccine?   To get vaccinated, register]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: I just took the COVID-19 vaccine and I encourage Nigerians to take the vaccine. It is safe, free  effective. Its important]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The National President, Nigeria Union of Journalists (NUJ), Chief Chris Isiguzo Ikechukwu and his team, today, received their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: You are advised to continue to wear face mask, practice physical distancing  sanitize hands your hands frequently. The #COVI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The available Vaccine in Nigeria is safe for use. Before a vaccine is certified for use, it must receive approval from WHO. H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: Most people who are infected with #COVID19 may not show symptoms but can spread the disease to other people.  Let's contin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Heres Nigerias #COVID19 Vaccination Plan. We are currently in Phase 1. Other Phases will be announced in due course.  #YesT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Vaccination remains one of the safest, most effective and important medical interventions for preventing illnesses, death and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialOSGFNG: The #PTF on #COVID19 receives donation of 100,000 doses of COVISHIELD vaccine from India, donated by the Acting Indian]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drfaisalshuaib: As the world commemorates #WorldHealthDay2021, we acknowledge the amazing job of our health and frontline workers in th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chikwe_I: Today was the last day of our @PTFCOVID19 Meeting. Following Mr Presidents approval, the PTF transitions into a Presidential]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NCDCgov:   Today, @PTFCOVID19 National Chairman, Boss Mustapha, announced its transition to a Presidential Steering Committee that wil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for April 6th, 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State performing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FMICNigeria: The vaccine is safe for everyone, it contains no microchip, nor can it alter our D.N.A.-Oba Adeyeye Enitan Ogunwusi, Oon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: Let's continue to worship safely during the #COVID19 pandemic: Maintain a distance of 2m from other people Wear #facemas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FMICNigeria: I want to confirm that the vaccine has no side effect...Until more than 79% of Nigerians are vaccinated, thats when we c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: Good respiratory hygiene practices protects everyone around us.  Cough into your bent elbow or into a tissue. Dispose us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chikwe_I: Our sister agency @NphcdaNG continues to lead the rollout of #COVID19 vaccines in Nigeria  If you have gotten the 1st dose of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: Everyone has to wear #facemask to reduce the spread of #COVID19.  Wear you facemask properly at all times. Adhere to other]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: PRESS STATEMENT:  Nigeria is continuing in the process of administering roughly 4 million doses of the Oxford/AstraZeneca vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: Persons who have  have recovered from #COVID19 can take the vaccine.  Visit https://t.co/eWYVYUduLG  click on COVID-19 Va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FMICNigeria: The essence of taking this vaccine is to help us really fight this #COVID19 virus . A combination of the non-pharmaceutic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FMICNigeria: This vaccine is safe, properly researched, it is in use in many countries. We urge all Nigerians to submit themselves to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NigeriaGov: The Federal Ministry of Health has proposed the sum of 296 billion Naira for the purchase of Vaccines to cover 2021 and 202]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for 1st April 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State performing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @inecnigeria: Hon.Chairman INEC, Prof. Mahmood Yakubu receives first jab of COVID-19 Vaccine. https://t.co/tEvZhl7UJC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @inecnigeria: National Commissioner and IVEC Chairman, Festus Okoye Esq receives first jab of COVID-19 Vaccine. https://t.co/Wj7cN1arvu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNICEF_Nigeria: "As a frontline worker, getting my first shot of the #COVID19 vaccine is empowering. It means I will no longer pose a r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccine Testimonial: Archbishop Augustine Akubeze, Archbishop of the Catholic Archdiocese of Benin  I didnt exper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LSMOH: #COVID19Lagos Vaccination Update as at March 28th, 2021.  1,247 persons were vaccinated on March 28th, 2021 comprising of 547 M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LSMOH: #COVID19Lagos Vaccination Update as at March 27th, 2021. 671 persons were vaccinated on March 27th, 2021 comprising of 339 Male]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for March 30th 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State performing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: I have been there, but survived. You dont need to go there, stay safe. Take the COVID-19 vaccine.  @ALIBABAGCFR   #YesToC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The ED/CEO NPHCDA, Dr. Faisal Shuaib met with the Executive Governor of Kogi state, Yahaya Bello to discuss and resolve issue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for March 29th 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State fairing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccine Testimonial: Alhaji Abdulfatah Enabulele, Chief Imam of Benin has a message for you.   Listen here   #YesTo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: #COVID19 spreads amongst persons who are in close contact.  Maintaining a distance of 2m from other people will  help to l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Edo state Deputy Governor, Rt. Hon. Comrade Philip Shaibu shares his #COVID19 vaccine testimonial  COVID-19 is real. There]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The Executive Governor of Yobe State, Alhaji Mai Mala Buni, yesterday, received his first dose of the #COVID19 vaccine at the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: #Facemask serves as a barrier  limits the spread of respiratory droplets.  Wear #facemask to public places. Wash your re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for March 28th 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State doing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 vaccine prevents moderate to severe forms of COVID-19. When one is infected with COVID-19, the vaccine produces anti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The Catholic Bishop, Issele-Uku diocese, His Lordship, Michael Odogwu yesterday, received his first shot of the AstraZeneca V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: #COVID19 Vaccination in progress in Oorelope Police station in Oorelope LGA, Oyo State. #YesToCOVID19Vaccine https://t.co/BmE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FMICNigeria: The Emir of Zazzau, HRH Amb. Ahmad Nuhu Bamalli being administered the #COVID19 vaccination in his Palace  #YesToCovid19Va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNICEF_Nigeria: "I'm glad I have taken my #COVID19 jab. The vaccine is safe and will give me protection as I go about my duties," says]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: #COVID19 spreads when we touch contaminated objects or surfaces. Hand hygiene is an effective way to curb the spread of #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The Speaker, House of Representatives @femigbaja talks about the AstraZeneca Vaccine doses and intervals.  Listen here   #Ye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for March 25th 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State doing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for March 24th 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State doing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: #DidYouKnow Persons living with underlying health conditions such as Diabetes, Hypertension  Obesity can get vaccinated a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Breaking News: The Executive Governor of Oyo State, Engr. Seyi Makinde has just received his shot of the #COVID19 Vaccine. #Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: To register for #COVID19Vaccination follow the steps below: Open a web browser on your device Enter https://t.co/y4qxy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: HRH. EZE and LOLO Anthony O. Moses the IJI II of Agbozu Autonomous Community of Uzuakoli, Bende LGA of Abia State displaying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Easy steps to register for the #COVID19 Vaccination.  Have you registered? Feel free to share with your family, friends and c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: His Excellency Governor Abubakar Bagudu and the First Lady, Kebbi state, @DrZSB , yesterday, received their first shot of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LSMOH: #COVID19Lagos Vaccination Update as at March 22nd, 2021.  13,395 persons were vaccinated on March 22nd, 2021 comprising of 6,58]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chikwe_I: Grateful for @ACTAccelerator's leadership in scale up  equitable access to vaccines, diagnostics  therapeutics for #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: If you develop any of these symptoms; Cough Fever Sore throat Loss of sense od smell Runny nose Abdominal pain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccination Update for March 23rd 2021, in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State performing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The COVID-19 Vaccination has commenced across the Country.   Will you like to get vaccinated?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialOSGFNG: 215,277 eligible Nigerians have been vaccinated with 1st dose of #COVID-19 vaccine @NphcdaNG https://t.co/w8OHhvCru6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Pregnant women are advised to consult with their doctors to determine if the benefits of the vaccination outweigh the potenti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: For e-Registration support, questions and concerns, kindly contact our Call Centre on 0700-220-1122.  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: COVID-19 Vaccine: Health workers proudly pose, flashing their vaccination cards, after receiving their first shot of the #COV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LSMOH: #COVID19Lagos Vaccination Update as at March 19, 2021.  13,563 persons were vaccinated on Friday March 19, 2021 comprising of 6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: His Royal Highness, the Emir of Katsina, Dr. Abdulmumini Kabir Usman yesterday, received his shot of the #COVID19 vaccine at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: The @PSH @MrAMAbdullahi at the #PTFCOVID19 media briefing today stated that evidence has shown improvement in the manageme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG:  COVID-19 Vaccination Update in 36 States + the FCT.   Hows your State performing?  #YesToCOVID19Vaccine https://t.co/0QvU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Will the #COVID19 shot hurt or make me sick? Mild side effects may occur as with other vaccinations. These are signs that the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: In order to curb the spread of #COVID19Nigeria we must continue to adhere to all non pharmaceutical measures on #COVID19 p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drfaisalshuaib: COVID-19 Vaccination Update: 122,410 eligible Nigerians have so far been vaccinated with the #COVID19 vaccine, a week a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: FACT: No Nigerian so far has developed any known severe side effects following vaccination with AstraZeneca vaccine   #YesTo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: We are grateful to MTN Group (@MTNNG ) for their kind donation of 300,000 doses of the Oxford/Astrazeneca vaccine.   Nigeria]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: #COVID19Vaccine is #FREE  Visit https://t.co/eWYVYUduLG and click on COVID-19 Vaccination e-registration to register for v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Such joy! An excited health worker displaying his vaccination card, after receiving his shot of the COVID-19 vaccine!   Have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: No. COVID-19 vaccines do not contain any materials such as microchips, implants or tracking devices. The vaccines contain nor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fmohnigeria: #COVID19 spreads amongst persons who are in close contact.  Maintaining a distance of 2m from other people will  help to l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfAkinAbayomi: #COVID19Lagos Vaccination Update  As announced by @LSMOH and @LagosPHCB, Lagos residents and the general public are he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FMICNigeria: EU MEDICAL REGULATOR ANNOUNCES ASTRAZENECA IS SAFE, NO INDICATED LINK TO BLOOD CLOTS  European Countries Restart Use of As]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: The Executive Director thanked the European Medical Agency for conducting their work effectively and transparently.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: He further added that Regulators and vaccine safety experts have a duty to investigate if an adverse effect is detected in o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NphcdaNG: Dr. Faisal reaffirmed that the health and safety of the Nigerian citizens is the priority, adding, Administering safe and ef]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>