<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[We offer our sincerest condolences to all of the Physicians in India who have died fighting COVID-19. We hope the situation improves soon. The medical community in all countries must not forget how politicians have treated HCWs and physicians as disposable. #indiacovid  #nooxygen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reinstate Dr Chelsea Ray at MMH https://t.co/J4UPfsWwdz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deliberately silencing medical students, and punitive actions should not be tolerated in 2021. #notmymedicalschool #letthemdoctor https://t.co/ubPC4Ej7LD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Humana Health Plan Overcharged Medicare by Nearly $200 Million, Federal Audit Finds https://t.co/9awBNxKtIz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We fully support the mandatory vaccination policy put forth by @MethodistHosp   Thank you for taking such a strong position  84% already been vaccinated  BELIEVE in SCIENCE  RT  drown out vocal minority #MedTwitter #MedStudentTwitter #NurseTwitter https://t.co/WIeGuoSAOE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We fully support the mandatory vaccination policy put forth by @MethodistHosp   Thank you for taking such a strong position  84% already been vaccinated  BELIEVE in SCIENCE  RT  drown out vocal minority #MedTwitter #MedStudentTwitter #NurseTwitter https://t.co/4uosuXXHQF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KKhs1d4Dey]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZachJonesMD: After correcting a RN (via text) to not refer to myself or colleagues as providers but rather Anesthesiologists, said RN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For its winter meeting, the organization flew about 30 board members and ABEM staff -- some accompanied by family members -- to Maui and lodged them for about a week at the luxury Fairmont Kea Lani resort. https://t.co/Mtijo6anag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrKeola: Ive spent much of the day processing the death of a friend who was an ER doctor. He died a few hours after we had dinner. He]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertMcNamar12: Disturbing video. Senior EM leader working for private equity owned TeamHealth telling young docs they are powerless.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RockyColo: @Covid19Docs Patients  this is a must read. Know as much as you can about the facility where your surgery is to be performe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watertown Regional Medical Center in Wisconsin has replaced all of its anesthesiologists with certified registered nurse anesthetists (CRNAs), sparking outrage on social media and reigniting debate about the role of advanced practice nurses. https://t.co/oWLeKCnz3o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cardiologists were awarded $10.6 million when it was found Detroit Medical Center (DMC)  its parent, Tenet, retaliated against Amir Kaki, MD, and Mahir Elder, MD, when the doctors repeatedly reported concerns about patient safety and potential fraud. https://t.co/r1YdYv05yZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevinShahMD: Forever grateful to all the doctors on the frontlines this past year for the #COVID19 pandemic   #NationalDoctorsDay #Heal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC issuing encouraging statements on mask-wearing and vaccinated individuals. We will only reach no mask necessary country-wide if we can reduce the 24% of adults who will not get a vaccine to less than 15%. Please talk to your friends and family! https://t.co/2mtKGjaark]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrQuinn15: #MedTwitter  Good for sharing... Patients should know about differences in training. https://t.co/dlvxoohiEe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @for_concerned: So basically you are saying that nurse Practitioners are better than physicians at all facets of hospitalizations?  Desp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Walgreens @WalgreensNews @VillageMedical_ https://t.co/BnnfiLs3B3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bills that attempt to dismantle the Physician-led team are just one of the many insults that our elected officials have thrown at Physicians. All patients, COVID or otherwise deserve a Physician in charge of their care. https://t.co/5NxuSEBmVD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Other parts of the world are struggling with variants of COVID. While there are encouraging signs that vaccines are protective against serious illness, there is still a lot we don't know. For physicians, nurses, and scientists, the fight continues. https://t.co/kjMSA4Q1yh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boogerpickerDO Good question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The takeover of CMGs and replacement of Physicians with NPPs (Non-Physician Practitioners) has been accelerated due to the COVID pandemic. We hope hospitals will value patients' safety over profits to prevent deaths such as this.  https://t.co/8WGGaZ15Y1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rlamartini Was there herd immunity in July when we had these case numbers? The numbers can be explained by the holiday surge that we warned about.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rlamartini We aren't ignoring it, rather the data shows that vaccination is much better at preventing illness and death than previous infection. Take a look at Manaus, Brazil as an example of why we should NOT use prior infection as an indication of herd immunity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@The_Jerf Variants were spreading in Israel at the time of the study. The effectiveness against the new strains at preventing minor illness is less than the effectiveness at preventing hospitalizations and deaths. The exact numbers are still being debated/discussed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Physicians are just as eager to stop wearing masks in public as everyone else. Once we reach herd immunity via vaccines we will pressure state and national officials to lift lockdowns and mask mandates. Until that time, lifting these mandates is premature and irresponsible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Data out of Israel showing that the Pfizer vaccine effectiveness at preventing deaths and minor infections is holding at the same rates as previously published rates (95-100%). We encourage all to take a look at the raw data and get vaccinated!  https://t.co/b8er4f5s2X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Envision just fired two doctors at our site in the middle of the pandemic. The reason we were given is that our volumes have been down over the last 6 months. Of course they have! It's a pandemic. What a way to thank your frontline heroes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jong_kat: Heard about some fascinating research from @AngelaReiersen on Fluvoxamine and the role of SSRI's on COVID in their https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're happy to announce that after almost 10 months of difficult negotiations, we have reached an agreement on our first union contract for OHSU house officers! https://t.co/RHTaUUrxBo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With Covid cases and deaths rising like never before, national uncertainty and recent traumatic events, ongoing moral injury and sheer exhaustion from navigating it all, please know Physician Support Line is here for you. https://t.co/1i9qby6Sg6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CABugDoc1: Similar stuff happening @UCSF where people like @Bob_Wachter got vaccinated in the first group because he was attending on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They employ so many people in the city/state I personally know people who dont see patients that are getting vaccinated. The school of medicine (Pitt) is being strong handed by UPMC (our hospital system) to pull medical students off of services.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPMC is refusing to vaccinate trainees (all healthcare students) and asking them to be pulled off of clinical services because they dont have enough vaccine yet there are dozens of accounts of them vaccinating their full time stay home admin staff.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenauster: A @UPMC rep just confirmed to a town hall of Pitt med students that they are vaccinating non-patient facing employees bef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sujangogu: I am very grateful to have my 2nd COVID-19 vaccine shot as over 350,000 people never had this opportunity. However, even aft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UPMCnews @PittDeptofMed @PittMedAlum @PittTweet @UPMC @ChildrensPgh @UPMCPhysicianEd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Students have been asking for a vaccination plan for over a month now  still nothing. Other medical schools in our state are vaccinating students or at the very least have a plan in place. Pitt has not advocated for students.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[University of Pittsburgh has no vaccination plan in place for medical students  UPMC will not be vaccinating students as of their last public statement on Dec 22. Some students have also been pulled off rotations w/ less than a days notice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jdwein39: It is astounding to me that public health departments and hospital administrators dont understand that medical students have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmpressAPGAR: @Covid19Docs I wrote this when I heard from peers nationwide that they weren't being vaccinated. It's unconscionable. htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IAPublicHealth @uiowa @DesMoinesUniv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iowa Department of Public Health, University of Iowa, and Des Moines University are absolutely refusing to vaccinate medical students. None of the above entities have announced when we will be vaccinated, despite us being in hospitals and clinics daily.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Law Aims to Provide Clarity for Patients Seeking Practitioners   The law requires health care professionals to clearly and accurately state their license and degree when advertising their practice and providing in-person care to patients. https://t.co/LyiuLyui9V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @enginerdmd: Its dangerous to go alone! Take this.  #CovidVaccine #COVID19vaccine  #COVID19  #ThisIsOurShot #MedTwitter https://t.co/oN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Private equity continues to acquire medical practices while affordable health care sits at the center of political discourse. The dichotomy between these ideologies is glaring. https://t.co/HLbnia4PSy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Mutated Virus Is a Ticking Time Bomb https://t.co/kn9tdglT9t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AustinChiangMD: Relieved, but emotions guarded.  Somehow my wishes in yesterdays tweet were heard. Many colleagues nationwide are stil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @medic1895: @RSPugliese Do you know if we have vaccines sitting around waiting to be given and lack staff to do so or is the poor availa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GayatriJoshiMD: Got dose 1 of #CovidVaccine 10 days ago.    Had no reactions or adverse events. Just mild arm soreness for ~48 hrs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrHussainL: We live in a polarized and politicized world. But there is at least 1 person the vast majority of Americans trust: their PE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wisconsin hospital says employee intentionally discarded coronavirus vaccine vials https://t.co/nvb7Uq2QOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As it buys up medical practices, private equity is popularizing a favored Wall Street cost-cutting tacticand stripping patients of rights. https://t.co/0PNG5LzySr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraHegabMD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Front-line health care workers: If COVID-19 kills me, take care of my dog https://t.co/o8HI8O02ZO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week the tension between the haves and have-nots of health care workers finally reached a flashpoint. Our primal fears manifested in a systemic breakdown reminiscent of The Lord of the Flies. https://t.co/N3SeaNNqKm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My HCA hospital, located in the middle of a covid hot spot in TN, told its traveling nurses it would be paying them less to renew their contacts. We will be short 26 nurses this weekend  for the foreseeable future. An already bad situation is being made worse by corporate greed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is on top of a recent nursing strike around 1 month ago, where 99% of nurses did not come to work for 2 days and thus medical residents were utilized to essentially run the entirety of the hospital.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Montefiore New Rochelle, the hospital that was the EPICENTER of this pandemic in March has not even mentioned timing of receiving the vaccine to its medical residents, attending, nursing staff.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congress acts to restore competition to health insurance by removing 75-year-old antitrust exemption.   This law allowed the insurance industry to be exempt from federal antitrust scrutiny  become monopolies.     https://t.co/GRRsFngjkE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jondcooper2: Help is on the way!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnnyC_IrishMD: During a global pandemic, Insurance companies have enjoyed record profits.  Simultaneously, I and my frontline emergen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrSchepel The screenshot is an email from our union. They have been completely powerless in doing anything about this. It's all smoke and mirrors from the administration trying to appease and reassure that we're getting vaccinated soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KateWalshCEO @The_BMC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not sure how nurse educators/C suite/managers are more important to vaccinate than those seeing consults in the ED, but apparently a lot of thought went into screwing the residents over. https://t.co/A7S16u0soy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While everyone around us is buzzing with excitement about their vaccination appointment, we become more and more resigned and resentful, especially since we pull the longest hours, have the fewest days off, and are expected to see COVID patients without being able to refuse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's shameful and a slap in the face after all the front-line work we're expected to do.  People are starting to notice but no one is doing anything about it. Residents are too afraid and/or defeated to protest.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BMC did vaccinate a few ICU and ED residents early on, so at least they did that part right and are a bit better than Stanford. But the rest of residents were not prioritized for vaccines despite being forced to see COVID patients.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[However, there are some departments where no residents have been contacted to schedule a vaccination, or it has been offered to 1-2 residents in the department (out of a resident cohort of &gt;30).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Residents were supposedly in Wave 1 of the vaccine roll-out, which included approximately 3500 people in the first cohort, with 2500 emails being sent out to "front line staff" as of yesterday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- Some attendings pulled strings to get themselves to the front of the vaccination line, while their residents had not yet been offered the vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- For example, residents will spend up to an hour doing a procedure in the ED on a COVID rule out/positive patient while some attendings who have been vaccinated don't even know where the ED is located]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- Each of those departments have residents who are exposed to COVID on a daily basis (ED, wards, etc) while their attendings avoid COVID rule-out/positive patients]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- Chairmen of all departments have been vaccinated  - In several departments, all of the attendings were vaccinated prior to any residents being offered the vaccine  - Additionally, all the midlevels (NP/PA) have been vaccinated prior to the residents in those departments]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- The first person vaccinated was the associate chief nursing officer, a non-clinical administrative role  - Many other non-clinical administrators were vaccinated in the first couple of days of vaccine distribution, including staff educators, managers, etc.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boston University Medical Center (BUMC) is on par with Stanford with regards to vaccine distribution and omitting residents.  They may've posted a TikTok dance video that went viral about the arrival of the vaccine, but they really screwed up its distribution:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drjessigold: I am honored to share with you the stories of Martin  Isabelle (thanks to @readingswan  @itsmefi).  It is time we talk a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Valleus556: In spring of '19, insurers and their wonks attempted to quietly pass legislation that would line their pockets at the expen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewMakeTweet: Health workers: let's create spaces to talk directly to people we know, to answers their questions, and to address the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Only Seven of Stanfords First 5,000 Vaccines Were Designated for Medical Residents https://t.co/v2x9xL4ygy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drdanchoi: Dire warning from EM docs  Blocking honest arbitration in place of government or, even worse, insurance-controlled pricing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICU availability in Southern California at 0%, and its going to get worse, officials warn https://t.co/8bpTgih7xz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AMLandryMD: Lets set the record straight. The health care workers taking pics and posting/tweeting about receiving their vaccine aren]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ykramerezha: @Covid19Docs This began with testing. Med schools @ Yale, Harvard, Illinois, Michigan, Duke etc. have been diverting tests]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A member of marketing at Mount Sinai Hospital posted on instagram showing him getting the vaccine "at the same time as the entire ED."    Meanwhile, most ICU staff haven't even gotten a date for when they can expect to get a vaccine. Vaccine distribution has been too opaque.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AGangiMD: ~2 people died of #COVID every minute yesterday ... this is REAL! Please #STAYATHOME,  #MaskUp, and #WashYourHands  &gt;2,750 de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oregon doctor's license revoked over refusal to wear mask during pandemic https://t.co/KTHWSLTfyA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fgheadshrinker: Please sign and share this petition to help get RN Cliff Willmeng his job back. We must organize to stop employers reta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @choo_ek: In the past month many of my healthcare colleagues have taken non-clinical jobs to step out of this care environment. Wonderin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @usnehal: Physician leadership. We need more of this  When I was an administrator would say if we were not delivering outcomes of qualit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Surprise billing" in health care  don't reward the villain   If insurers win and Benchmarking becomes the national solution, they will have full control and become even more powerful.  https://t.co/y8I4TYphLo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DoctorJesseMD: Bleak outlook ahead: US is 'rounding the corner into a calamity,' expert says, with #Covid19 deaths projected to double]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beaumont Cardiologist Wants Executives Fired   Robert Safian, MD, wrote system's board about toxic culture, pursuit of profit over people https://t.co/6wf0XqM2lh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlokPatelMD: Special thank you to #medtwitter and a raised glass to @Covid19Docs. Here, in the perplexing world of social media, it's k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meganranney: "Covid Combat Fatigue: Doctors and Nurses Are Running on Empty" https://t.co/sLFZQEbvWK by @KatherineJWu with @Cleavon_MD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Urge Congress to Ensure that Emergency Physicians Have Due Process Rights https://t.co/pjponQhEGk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @globalgyno: I keep going back to spring when physicians and nurses were told they may have to(and some did!) wear garbage bags to prote]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lately, our biggest concern and challenge is having adequate PPE [personal protective equipment] at work and feeling like were in as safe a work environment as possible. Our concerns are being ignored and dismissed. https://t.co/tL40hVfwap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanford Health's president and chief executive, Kelby Krabbenhoft, says he had virus, won't wear mask https://t.co/OnHXVdMR8Y]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>