<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FCTwenteBenson: Just rang the Donegal Tout hotline to report Tipperary getting robbed in the 2009 All Ireland final]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GRHutchinson: Please RT.   Londoners, PROTEST vote tomorrow. Vote for anyone except Khan.   Bring power back to the people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Misleading you say..... https://t.co/gEsUJdyx3X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Joeby52: https://t.co/SVfA5CxRag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisWickNews There is no amount of money they could offer me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were all on the same side anyway. We all want our lives back. We all want our children to have their childhoods reinstated. Our teenagers their rebellious years available. We all want to see our families and friends. To travel and experience life. Just not in the same way! https://t.co/qGXSxf94AC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But they care about you so much! https://t.co/cgxuHGlGy8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TraceyOMahony81 thoughts? https://t.co/m3vCFPwLh1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ballydally3Mm @adamabyss Time to start distributing flyers to those in the q?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarroniDean Nothing to see.... https://t.co/sQ90l9WTVu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jordan120 Do it. Ill invest.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And anyone who trusts politicians with their lives are idiots. https://t.co/Ei6LvghcIg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This tweet must be flagged for misinformation. https://t.co/xhoQ48ji3S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking isnt it?! https://t.co/Cp3xIRmMfr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TOMMYK48566324: @SwanSmirk @SaraHaboubi1 @lennymac41 @Sabdublindr Don't believe anyone knows but this podcast is very insightful.  http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NEUnion @GavinWilliamson https://t.co/ek1aV1JBV3 your facts are incorrect. You are spreading misinformation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/PTOvuhjtdn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichealMartinTD @LeoVaradkar @CowenBarry @RTENewsNow @rtenews @drivetimerte this is what the Irish gov plus its lap dogs in RT have done too. https://t.co/8Bwz6SCQqi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elizabe32413720: https://t.co/pApiFtn1qT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tazalot1981 Time to flood the Rat Line with false claims. Have them all chasing their tails.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DoTheRightThing #ProtectYourChildren #NoMasksInClass https://t.co/rB99Cb6NfE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jordan120 Stay safe. Protect the health service. Save lives. Sit in your arse and do nothing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@voice_stolen Those who are blindly following the rules and quoting MSM back to me as if its fact.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nc1908Neil Its just shocking how MANY there are!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tarynabell @AndyBird21 computer viruses are a real thing. https://t.co/WgHFt3EZFM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont think these are real ppl. Im refusing the believe we have such complete and utter idiots walking among us https://t.co/AfwGTweVYM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@latimes @sozh No. Grasping at straws when they fail to understand how some ppl are able to think for themselves.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @3_resurection: So be aware this post will get you 30 days in facist book jail!! Someone else did it so I thought Id give it a go and i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy The dog wouldnt attack the guy they were beating. Shows he was not being aggressive towards the police first. Totally barbaric.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How many States are now fully open? https://t.co/LiREotvKnq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Vhtempopro @JohnLalor18 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnLalor18 The hail stones are so perfectly formed. Is that typical? I feel I am rather paranoid these days! https://t.co/5FWP0Fcyeu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OldNormality Form an orderly queue!! https://t.co/SfXTfKWNaZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/FoaMjHo3vE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikolovScience He is evil. And he hates kids.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Walkabout24 Its all a fairytale]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thewle Protecting their assets? Trying to garner sympathy?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaoMc2 Pedodemic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@geezerpaulr https://t.co/3rrP6bv4Ay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@megandraheim @NateSilver538 Those who had SARS in 2003 have shown to be immune from this own. T cells provide life long immunity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Psyop2020 @CarnellAnita To protect their assets?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rubes3047: Why is the Pat Sweeney story not on mainstream media? Disgraceful what's happening to him and his children. #PatSweeney]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/SGJ6g6ptwz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@voice_stolen Sorry you hear that. https://t.co/VCORNqVYYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy This jab is meant to induce an anti body response and create the spike protein. Surely the very least everyone should be getting is a sore arm and feeling a bit under the weather. Many ppl arent having any reactions at all though. Have they been tested for antibodies after?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv Her reasons I married a mass murdered!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theartistcoach: @disclosetv Maybe now they can focus on killing each other instead of the global population?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @petedjackson: If it was about health, there would be:   No Alcohol being sold   Cigarettes banned   Fast Food Restaurants Closed ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IrishSecondary: How about school in supermarkets? There's no Covid-19 in big supermarkets.  Maths = at the till Business/Accounting= in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@woodsharp #CovidAnxietySyndrome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@capnbobstoaster From what I understand agenda 21 was the start of a 100 yr plan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. Yes I do. https://t.co/fX9seRsu1L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TeenHeard @HealthFreedomIE @NormaFoleyTD1 @INTOnews https://t.co/NoLZnuKxt6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Way way too late. https://t.co/ShZ9ulMchn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YorkusMarcus Shwab?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_nonessential @amiebaby3691 @Sandralanigan #FreedomAirways!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke https://t.co/LeBZfwQbMw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @youth_unheard: Legal restrictions on freedoms are never necessary. If it's airborne ebola, you don't need to make it illegal to leave t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @knowles_joseph: Cant reply, but maybe I can retweet until this is the only tweet on everyones timeline.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@connollyjojo Oh god. The level of evil in this world is beyond anything we could have ever imagined.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @squawkying: @JackPosobiec Thank you for sharing this horrific treatment by the Irish Gardai towards Catholics exercising their constitu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carlin_ron @STEPHENHARI @FatEmperor @M4ttmc87 @mjack15 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carlin_ron @STEPHENHARI @FatEmperor @M4ttmc87 @mjack15  apologies. So many on here who actually believe they do!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@har36161137 Frankly anywhere would be better than Ireland right now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sandralanigan https://t.co/byzik72JUO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carlin_ron @STEPHENHARI @FatEmperor @M4ttmc87 @mjack15 Oh please!!!! Wake up! Are you anti freedom? Are you anti family? Are you anti children? Are you anti truth?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rixkerson @ItsABadFlu https://t.co/ek1aV1JBV3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant share this enough! https://t.co/F0wvmQDkXi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cant believe I want to live in Florida. Will they accept asylum seekers from ireland? https://t.co/sSmwRrhXQ8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShooBrown @STEPHENHARI @FatEmperor @M4ttmc87 @mjack15 Theyll start using the tag line it could be you! But highly unlikely!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#EndLockdownsNow https://t.co/vBUT1vhB5N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KoletteOfficial Agree. They all need to be held accountable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IanDunt Explain what a variant is. How are these variants of this virus different to every other respiratory virus weve had? Explain how those who had SARS in 2003 which is 80% similar to this one are immune due to T cell immunity but these variations are somehow different?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The truth? On RT? https://t.co/6GDllIJqm5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanRallyOh https://t.co/eKYPCtBRtj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Matthews_angst: There is only one way to beat this #Takeoffyourmask NOW ! https://t.co/Tn57xmwz7S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: Holland  People having a party in a supermarket The only place where large gatherings are allowed... https://t.co/mRdYlWKFA8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/t3w8mLw9hG https://t.co/RW4acnVRud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @queenslittonno1: @Sacha_Lord This is pretty much the forecast for the next week at our dales pub, weve had to close on Bank Holiday Mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanRallyOh https://t.co/8hqSvqxIU3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[oh my god. We need to collect these rules and start giving awards https://t.co/JP7I7RGtXn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti3: 6000% Increase in Reported Vaccine Deaths 1st Quarter 2021 Compared to 1st Quarter 2020 -  https://t.co/xFKCX4ZLvk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lYm6JZHwcI https://t.co/6SbxiY3GwX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: Emergency? We don't need no stinkin' emergency!  https://t.co/C40ZjuYNGN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreedomIsrael_: There are five countries in #Europe that have vaccinated less than 3% of their populations.  Simple #question to the va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmandaJStone4 Those who are complying are continuing this ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulSpe13674058 Perhaps....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @thetimes https://t.co/ek1aV1JBV3 #TakeOffTheDamnMask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9RHdqoUcQR https://t.co/h1aPU1GlQH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolineCoramUK It seems nothing is as it seems..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theyve all lost the ability to think. https://t.co/NJVXXp1dmz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PatSweeney https://t.co/CVRz7xPop8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Blood362: @Georgia47089544 @Simon93449053 @Elizabe32413720 @theboyjai I was a nurse for 20 years. Every year we had flu epidemics. We h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gerryodonnell0: What the hell is going on in Ireland?? A man films garda breaking up a mass in Athlone and they raid his house at 3.30]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LizaRutherford7 Seems thats the way anyone gets to the top...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@allisonpearson @BBCNews Watching the BBC or RT isnt good for our health]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LizaRutherford7 Wanted to ask that too....anyone know? How can we find out?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnMurphy51 Maybe I have it? I mean Im a bit tired. What do you think?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jay_Beecher @LwCorrie Do you wear one for 8 hrs a day? https://t.co/ek1aV1JBV3]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>