<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLibertyDan: Im not an anti-vaxxer, Ive just never seen a government want something so bad and it be a good thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidBlindWife: No improvement   19 days steroids   55 days blind  59 days since #AstraZeneca #vax  100% blind in left eye 30%-60% blin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OldNormality Completely agree with your tweet. The individual below is a geriatrician in Dublin's Mater Hospital. I don't want to say much more as might doxx myself but I sincerely hope I never meet him again and keep your elderly WELL away. https://t.co/q8PGlDwkKK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @modern__grl__: Yesterday at heathrow without muzzle and nobody asked a thing. Don't be scared and don't comply.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarmaladeMax: So the virus confirmed to have been in Italy in September 2019.   With lockdowns not even invented, how did the virus sta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: NOT ON BBC "NEWS" Turkish government forces clash with Muslims inside mosques. https://t.co/KCDdBV63cm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turkish Government forces attacking Muslims in Turkey  https://t.co/6SjeyUSWKl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime Is the Mandela Effect related to this? Celebrities "dying", then not? Jack Palance, David Prowse, Denis Norden? I guess so. Last question: which "Doctor" and his series from Doctor Who is the best to watch to explain all this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uk_granny: My lodger works in the vaccine programme, she witnessed death of a healthy 32 year old yesterday at the Crawley vaccine cent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is this why health insurers like #VHI and @Bupa won't cover you if you've had the vax? The depths of evil of our Governments and the media know no bounds. https://t.co/C38uhZPPDY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime Thanks. It's interesting because so many things I thought would happen to me and for me just shut down with no explanation. I also had a sudden run of many people close to me "dying". Where are they now?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TiceRichard @metpoliceuk All coming from #Freemasonry folks. Here's the Irish police performing a Freemasonic dance ritual on Irish television. Freemasons are Satanists and trying to wipe out Christianity. https://t.co/6CmIPBAr7w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime I've been questioning my very existence (or not) my whole life so fire away!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime Thank you. What have masks and lockdowns got to do with all this, if anything?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @7tine76: Bill Gates called his experimental gene therapy "the final solution" on National Television.  Why do people think he did not m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime That's the second time ITV has screened Skyfall in only a few weeks. Very odd.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3.30a.m.  33  #Freemasonry #Gardai   Is this real or a #falseflag? https://t.co/bfUGtG4Pek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buy everything on DVD that you want NOW. https://t.co/1ZzYItIPBC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@peachypuk Also "Casablanca" an absolute must see!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@peachypuk Good for your teenager - watching films from an era of real creativity and quality! She's unconsciously teaching herself screenwriting! Watch "Field of Dreams" with Kevin Costner from 1989. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thewhitmore Errr Laura...I presume your daughter has a birth certificate...anyone can buy it and get the baby's name for 10 from the General Register Office. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: Pharma and Gates see India as the world largest untapped market for vaccines and other Covid paraphernalia. This is why the med]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThreadsIrish: 1. Why Does Economist David McWilliams Claim He Isnt In The World Economic Forum Whilst They Think He Is?  David McWil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThreadsIrish: 1. Did You Know The Great Reset In Ireland Has Been In Place Since July 2020 ?  They have been trying to keep a relative]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThreadsIrish Why do they need vaccines in 2023 if everyone gets it now? This is a diabolical experiment in evolutionary humanism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThreadsIrish: Strap yourself in. This ride is going to get very bumpy over the next few years Im afraid.     already ordered for 2023]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: WORD UP SiSTER! https://t.co/YwNfcq6ZfG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @blackswan_t2: You have got to be brain dead now to have not worked out that this is a huge satanic ritual. https://t.co/QQGND5wYC7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime Cringe Cringe. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ih8evrybdy: I believe the only way you could know this and a if you were involved in the manufacturing of bio weapons. Call me suspicio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidBlindWife: My wifes 1st dose of the #AstraZeneca #vax caused her to go BLIND due to an inflamed optic nerve  Her neurologist has c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @matthewdmarsden: My time machine goes back to the 80s, 70s etc, too. Where do YOU wanna go?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealNoseyParker: Yes Boris' dad wrote books on population control and also a fiction book on a virus. But they SWITCH GENDERS of their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlchemistsW: @ShuttleMrGeo DISCERNED  CONFUSED  Flu  Herd Immunity Gone  Unpresidented Roll Out  Untested Vaccines  EVERYBODY  Gene T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All were paid to push Covid porn, and why I've had the car radio turned off since July 2020. https://t.co/9y734sW9SO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @opinionatedmum1: Clubbers of the 90s  - Mashed off their tits on Es, dancing on bars, hugging strangers   Clubbers now  - Willingly a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twice in the space of a week I've seen EXTREMELY naughty children screaming, lying down on the floor and kicking their parents in full public view in the supermarket. Lockdowns are causing this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdrianBoarder: @ShuttleMrGeo Del Bigtree just posted this. The article doesnt appear to have a link to the document. https://t.co/bKDD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidBlindWife: Still #AstraZeneca Blind No improvement today  Trying to adjust to life with blindness Shes very anxious out of the hou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: This video has just been published, as part of an official campaign by the Israeli MOH - in the "vaccinated Israeli society th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: YES DANNY! that's the spirit......POWER TO THE PEOPLE https://t.co/kT7kUFccdQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamplingDanny: Shoom events will not be taking part in medical apartheid. Weve built the electronic music scene on core values of unit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieEmmaUK: Take off your masks before facial nudity becomes a fetish category on PornHub.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndyBird21: Anyone who seriously thinks theres a virus at this point youre seriously lost or a deceiver.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarahsuss: Its official: Fully vaccinated is popping up in peoples dating profiles now like were all a bunch of shelter dogs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonahofNinevah I like you, but:  1. You talk non stop about yourself 2. Have a daft cartoon hipster beard as your profile shot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What else would you expect from #Freemasonic @Disney ? https://t.co/xsq54d99ov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonahofNinevah https://t.co/OfRGlfVzCO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mr69313316: @Albion_Rover @ShuttleMrGeo It's strange the way none of the celebrity folks have had complications from the vaccine shots?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Thorgwen: So far i have been locked out of Twitter for posting valid responses from insurance companies re: restriction to cover with m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: https://t.co/ozVyAwlmaF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @christianmorris: @Allycon3 Get angry at @rte - if those woke cokehead scumbags had even asked one challenging question it could have be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBGRichie: Not often you can fit three pricks in a photograph https://t.co/ZrB5vXuZjN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryMakow: https://t.co/j0YL21SW5z  Bizarre Phenomenon: Unvaccinated Getting Sick, Pets Dying Just from Being Around The COVID Vaxxed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Noconsent12 @mism_2020 Glad to hear your Dad is stabilising.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BOFirinne: Priests are 'essential workers'.  The contribution of the Church to the well being of communities and as such to people's he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Freemasonic @BBCNews   #DefundtheBBC https://t.co/08yRbRT70y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeeHurstComic: The generation that lapped up Anonymous and V for Vendetta are happily accepting vaccine passports. Comical.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoystonPotter: Fact! Gates so much as spelled it out! I am not sure who you are, Jeff, but your short and poignant admonishments and co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @5pectr3: @ThreadsIrish It looks like the answer is in that last email. With the vaccines being emergency, if you take the vaccine, then]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidBlindWife: No improvement in my wifes blindness today   12 days on steroids   48 days going blind  52 days since #AstraZeneca #va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @L00k0verThere: @ShuttleMrGeo @sar247365 Please read this and share it. It's the only piece of useful information I have been given (by]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DickPower369: This was recently discovered and found in Cappadocia Italy  Draw your own Conclusions... hes 3 Thousand Years Old. http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaskatronPrime @Arthursdriver @di2122 Really, Mr "Cray Cray" - or should I say, Cringe Cringe?  https://t.co/kKXUoD1r4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This fuels rumours that Q is true.  Where actually is @AnthonyHopkins? https://t.co/QU80iPvi25]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I felt so ill over the weekend as if I'd been hit by a train.  Went to homeopath today who asked me was I around anyone vaxxed with Pfizer - and my uncle who's fully vaxxed visited last Friday.  Homeopath said crazy amount of shedding going on and winter will be carnage.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jackiedoran10: The unluckiest Woman in India.    First she died in the street during a gas leak in May 2020.    Now she's dead again in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thetruebluechef: Those stroke adverts recently weren't just a coincidence. You know that.......? .......Right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The New York Post @newyorkpost caught using photos from an Indian gas leak to boost the phony #CovidIndia story. Your daily reminder the mainstream media is #ScumMedia.   #FakeNews #FakeNewsMedia #IndiaNeedsOxygen #India #Scamdemic #CovidHoax https://t.co/jIe6hcVxdv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CatrionaColllns: Doctors wont tell us this, let your families and friends know. https://t.co/iBtdNpdKv0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jayeankh: @joeyjojojunior_ @ShuttleMrGeo @valeriekeane53 Yes and it really is proving unsafe to be around the vaxxed- reports of miscar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Albion_Rover: laughing emoji mocking vaccine concerns - then dead within 48 hours:  Another proof that informed consent is not happenin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dumpingtea1773: @Daveison5 @DrTessaT They talking about the shedding type of issues.  URGENT! 5 Doctors Agree that COVID-19 Injection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh yes https://t.co/7ydUR9fEY1 https://t.co/diXXPxyFF1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @john_mcguirk: - Banned a woman from leaving quarantine to attend her dad's funeral - Banned the JJ vaccine for most adults - Banned br]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Noconsent12: My daddy has fought cancer for 12 years survived a plandemic without getting infected but is critically ill in hospital 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Noconsent12 Dolly, a homeopath will help. Follow me and DM if you need assistance in finding one in NI.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Noconsent12 Dolly, get some Carbo Veg 30c in liquid form from a homeopathy store. Bang five times on your hand and give him two drops on the tongue every ten minutes. It restores oxygen levels. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffsekerak: Steer clear of the injected. If anybody's going to be spreading some scary shit. IT'S GOING TO BE THEM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThreadsIrish: I asked a very specific question from the VHI about vaccine cover  They totally ignored the question    What are they tr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OldNormality: You cant buy more than 12 paracetamol at the supermarket (for your safety ),  yet theyre paying dim celebrities to sel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmmaUK Tom's tweet reads like a slur from Terry Wogan in 1986.  https://t.co/FEeMcmTr3n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieEmmaUK: Utter garbage.  @GBNEWS has lost viewers before its started with the tripe uttered by this person and @tomhfh over the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy @GMaolruanaidh Thanks so much.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaxZorin17: Harrowing Covid scenes from India....  However, it's due to a leak from a chemical plant. Don't be fooled by your screens.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GMaolruanaidh Same here a few weeks ago. "Peacefully" my arse. My mind has been racing since this happened. I want answers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leaked email from large Dublin  accountancy firm sent around this morning.   Employees being set up for mandatory vaccinations.   #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/gznVubSE6P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JulieBalfour9 @MHilltobe And a member of the Freemason Death Cult. Does @reallorraine seriously think Satan is impressed?  https://t.co/0o3xsd1P4A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@superhip83 @fionamflanagan1 @WWakeUpTime https://t.co/0Ow14qNe9J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaskatronPrime: @bubuman12 we live in a computer.  when its memory is full, you move to a new one.  we don't all live in the same one a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeomraShakti: @SaraHaboubi1 Everyone is talking about this in all parts of Ireland. @EamonRyan what is going on with our skies  https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KarenMcO3: @SaraHaboubi1 They know we are onto them...he's off home! https://t.co/oS9iZbGSbI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karlwizowski We noticed this also this morning. Heavy streaks Dublin area. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karlwizowski: Hello Spray. https://t.co/L5p7IkZdn2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RedpillEire We saw this also this morning, Dublin area. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RedpillEire: Heavy Chemtrailing today https://t.co/iLytc9DBla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What were they thinking? Freemason @Keir_Starmer kneeling to Satan. https://t.co/V7XKwULO4f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guns https://t.co/qZSpPNb85O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: The crimes of the lockdown lunatics are endless - they are traitors, a danger to our society and to science itself: #Lockdo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This  https://t.co/ALv206zgQR]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>