<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@enews Youd have to be blind to not see this coming. She treats him like ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNN Hey @PeteButtigieg this is the infrastructure we need! Not bloody train service. Welcome to 2021! Can you get on this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey @PeteButtigieg this is the infrastructure we need! Not bloody train service. Welcome to 2021! Can you get on this? https://t.co/lODEOU7tDZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LoriShemek: A recent study out of BYU has linked lifestyle choice to Alzheimer's disease.  Growing evidence that the brains in humans w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Oh look  profits higher than any fines the DOJ throws at them for lying, and fraudulent behavior. #Pfizer https://t.co/dk9o68Dr9M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh look  profits higher than any fines the DOJ throws at them for lying, and fraudulent behavior. #Pfizer https://t.co/pmA4bxhPYk https://t.co/dk9o68Dr9M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: Big Pharma has turned America into a country of pill popping, anxiety ridden, overweight, unhealthy, weak people. And]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's almost as if 24/7 covid propaganda, for over a year, just ain't doing it. People dont think its worth the risk. Save the $3Billion. https://t.co/8uuxPoh402]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VanessaGray158: So Bill Gates wants to impose biometric id on all 7 billion people on the planet - for mass surveillance purposes - but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CeciATL 86yr old MIL  90yr old FIL went to HI right after covid lockdown. The 14hrs of travel on the heels of quarantine had my FIL telling her he wished to live alone  was sick of her  sadly we lose the best step FIL ever, in fact im closer to him than my own dad! Divorced in 2 mos.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drmikehart: A new study has confirmed what people have been saying for years, frequent and light cannabis users, on average, are more p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CSS976: 25k on landscaping and my pets think I did it for them.  https://t.co/wOE0gxfktC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnConstas: L-Theanine: Your Natural Relaxation Solution  THREAD https://t.co/f0EbOxZL46]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gregkellyusa https://t.co/CH8lw5Itiz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gregkellyusa https://t.co/LIoc2PKLLV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stevecamperlin @gregkellyusa Unlike Bill Gates you mean?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhosePolitics @bellaccione @gregkellyusa Millions didnt read a vax insert w/ingredients. Willingly, proudly even, became lab rats in an experimental mRNA, first time ever in humans, vaccine. A cell phone, but cant/wont research, cause propaganda 24/7  fatties with comorbidities - no, this doesnt seem like such a loss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does anyone else think she knows these vaccines are part of his long talked about, DEPOPULATION plan  that mass casualties/injuries are on the way, so she wants out before the SHTF? Or did the pics w/Epstein do it? Or his BioTerrorism? Or trying to make us all eat fake food? https://t.co/ynFfc1W3gD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog You would think the person who is running the world as a genius who knows everything from software to vaccines to food to health woulda been able to hold his marriage close  fix all the issues w/his eyes closed  hands tied behind his back! Why TF do U listen to his propaganda?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader We're all mostly dependent on Big Tech, like @Google if we're honest,  so I find it interesting that you're living with @FrankLuntz   paying $5,000/mo of taxpayer money to the opposition. I hope they vote you out of the party very soon. I can imagine those late night chats...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Listen he made 98Billion over the course of the pandemic, and before it he had 98Billion. Those kids are well set at 1% of almost $200 billion.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@richardursomd My kid had this after the H1N1 swine flu shot. Childrens hosp said it was Guillain barre syndrome. In ICU 3 mos then almost the same at Nat Rehab Hosp. 8 other kids on the ward same thing. Within a yr of 5x week outpatient therapy we met 32 other families w/it. No vaxx 4 us!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My kid had this after the H1N1 swine flu shot. Childrens hosp said it was Guillain barre syndrome. In ICU 3 mos then almost the same at Nat Rehab Hosp. 8 other kids on the ward same thing. Within a yr of 5x week outpatient therapy we met 32 other families w/it. No vaxx 4 us! https://t.co/lpu1me0zbx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnforca My daughter had this after the H1N1 shot. Childrens hospital said it was Guillain barre syndrome. She was in ICU 3 mos then almost the same at Nat Rehab Hosp. 8 other kids on the ward same thing. Within a yr of 5x week outpatient therapy we met 32 other families w/it. No vax 4 us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Black teacher being a racist pos to the Mexican officer, tells him he's a murderer and he'll never be white Holy fuck people, homeschool your kids. Teach them good character, cause she certainly won't. The woke have lost their minds. Her child was listening to this garbage!! https://t.co/0D8wb3kHqN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ugh, another woke bish telling us what we can say  what not to say, in upside down #clownworld Fat AF = Anorexic. Please In 2015 they put her in Sports Illustrated  some womens healthy exercise mags trying to tell us FAT is healthy. She's lucky the Wuhan 'rona hasnt got her. https://t.co/UHIlvfQnok https://t.co/zt8fpKTdkB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Leftylockdowns1 https://t.co/1zcOLT5VkN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Leftylockdowns1: What Are No-Vaxxers Thinking? Interesting piece that quotes me a couple times  https://t.co/aQZWaqxjWc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wish this was actually something he'd do. #TaxationIsTheft https://t.co/6mXfQ5LjjM https://t.co/hMVb6LZQPa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzPatterson: Melinda Gates isnt the only one that wants Bill Gates out of their lives.   Signed, Every American]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant fix his own marriage but thinks he can fix the world  https://t.co/lYcr4cATSM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wantRstateback @ChefGruel For every $100 spent, the restaurant made $70. We pulled in almost $50k over weekend, but it was in a tourist area  30 yrs ago.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChefGruel 17-19 worked as waitress/bar tender in Irish restaurant, so I always tip 20%, but I also clean the table  pile up dishes, pickup anything my kids dropped on the floor  generally try to be a good human. I wish restaurants etc just paid them a living wage  tips r icing on cake.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HKBelvedere Ours was a wooden metre stick in Ireland. Brought up to front of class, had to raise our skirt  bend over the table  take our lickings. Or if teacher walked by a hard rap across our knuckles. The 70s/80s. Mom would give an ear boxing, or hit you with her slipper/shoe/hairbrush!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TWines4congress: @NatSecCNN @ZcohenCNN @KatieBoWillCNN They spied on a Presidential candidate and his team with no consequences from th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Duke_of_Bourbon @Lukewearechange Easy to predict when you take $200 million  divert it to the lab in Wuhan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lukewearechange We had stopped them when Obama was in office. Fauci went around Trump  got them restarted w/out his knowledge. Listen to @joshrogin on @joerogan he lays it all out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RothweilerEvent https://t.co/cpqRSJIumM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LumpyGravy3 @dnforca We can only hope ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MAGARebirth: I don't listen to my own doctor...  Fauci never stood a chance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Are those Eagles perching behind you  whats that creepy thing by the bank on bottom right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnStossel @elonmusk When I was a kid, SNL was counter culture. Today, they cant stand free thinkers. They hate him cause they cant control him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OneGSisneros Kefir grains in raw milk (or whole milk) at 75-80 degrees! Takes about 24-36hrs  usually have one cooking on counter  one in fridge ready to drink, or use in a smoothie etc., so easy! Healthier by far than store bought w/extra ingredients.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[80% of our #immune system is in our guts. Brewing your own #kefir just takes a few minutes prep. I used to be unhealthy, w/IBS eating a SAD diet of processed food  junk. #Keto  #fermentation saved my life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Leerose1985 Seriously, buy them a one way ticket outta America. Deserted island preferably.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@naomirwolf @joshrogin said this on Joe Rogans podcast and @joerogan is the complete opposite of MSM, but other than that, the Professor gets it right. A $200Million payment to the lab from our government went to funding corona  other deadly viruses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@msnorthcott @joshrogin  said it on Joe Rogans podcast. Joe Rogan is the opposite of MSM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goes on to say,  that "Scientists" think boys playing girls is just fine  not a factor in any sport, except possibly running. I think if anyone had the right answer, it would be the tranny who won Olympic medals!! https://t.co/XgCkv3slNf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@knniemi @CandyTa86367420 @ChefGruel CA is a shit state for the reason she stated man, she can afford a house on half an acre on $13 per hr!! Allowing her to raise a family w/special needs child.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 month old racist babies OMFG I am so glad I homeschooled my kids. https://t.co/5hqFXHVWGB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What could possibly go wrong?! Hope they stay in CA. You get the govt you deserve apparently. https://t.co/uUNvyLqyYg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BookOfGates: From poor health to good health. From misery to joy  Everything is normal. Everything is fine https://t.co/xZobbFI3TW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EpochTimes @WhiteHouse Waiting for the inevitable results ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deaflibertarian Meh. Sometimes it's all I can muster. Most times i reply in my head  don't answer anything back, so a thumbs up is better than no response, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fox5dc How can he say that it's safe  effective, when everyone knows this is being tested currently  that's why it's only got emergency use, not full FDA approval. It's not even free, taxpayer money is being used to pay for it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealJoelSmalley Sending sincere condolences to his family x way too young.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dannybarefoot @robbysoave Is every business now going to hire bouncers for their doors, who will require seeing "your papers" or is that a step too far? Vaccine injured families arent gonna comply.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @citizenhush: Imagine all the people. https://t.co/YP1aWTz0K8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here I thought Bill had quit w/propaganda after his last 2 showsThe only reason our govt is against it, is because they can't control it, or get taxes from it. In fact people today could theoretically work under the table  aren't forced to pay taxes because it isn't traceable https://t.co/gsDJpzcInM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billmaher Here I thought Bill had quit w/propaganda after his last 2 showsThe only reason our govt is against it, is because they can't control it, or get taxes from it. In fact people today could theoretically work under the table  aren't forced to pay taxes because it isn't traceable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Richard_Harambe @HollyBriden How come no pics of the cat with kids? Or dildoes? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wiseconnector "Federally" funded. Call it what it is, taxpayer funded.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wiseconnector Equity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KaylayShorter Yes! Along with banning #phthalates they're killing our fertility! Seed oils in food, coal tar in cosmetics, 1,4-DIOXANE to make suds, DEA  TEA, formaldehyde, Homosalate in sunscreens  this list could roll on if anyone @US_FDA really cared.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheKevinBoyd https://t.co/Ypt2ukv1Eg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Omg yes! My own little personal jet pack. Trains are definitely NOT the future. Even at 200mph. Interact w/strangers? Ewww. NO, so last century! @PeteButtigieg  Tax payers would be thrilled if you'd just take care of the potholes tbh  stay outta the way. #JetPacks https://t.co/zDicnh4kx6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @heckyessica: if your man wants an engagement ring, youre marrying a chick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timcast https://t.co/PFDkQk64tB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@weaponizedsoul1 @currencyofcool @Cernovich https://t.co/JsWH1EmRGd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@weaponizedsoul1 @currencyofcool @Cernovich https://t.co/K3yTA0Kcxm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@weaponizedsoul1 @currencyofcool @Cernovich Omfg. Smart phone in your hand  not even willing to do a cursory search on #duckduckgo  You are wrong. They are paid for speeches, scripts, jabs. https://t.co/2dE30pYaPq To the tune of it being in 2018 a $151Billion dollar industry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Cant stand that paid schill #RandyRainbow #Propaganda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KennedyNation @joerogan I mean, on health, it makes more sense to listen to @joerogan rather than #BillGatesBioTerrorist  https://t.co/c7L7n9hi5D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic https://t.co/LIoc2PKLLV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@currencyofcool @Cernovich Drs are the original influencers,  paid by Big Pharma. For every jab they give, they get $$$$$]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A great podcast @joerogan about #WuhanVirus  how Anthony Fauci was able to go around POTUS  turn on the $200 Million funding for Wuhan Lab, previously shut down by Obama over fears that a deadly virus might escape the facility. MSM  their involvement due to hatred for #Trump https://t.co/8C0YyKiBzM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realitybyAshley Just listened to juicy scoop about this, Vanessa signed an NDA  cant discuss it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@riccimike @VP Vaccine "equity"... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kirstiealley Depends on the strain!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Meditate_Pray @RyanTAnd They dont just fall into your lap man!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 The chutzpah!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanTAnd Have adopted two already  would gladly step up  do it again!  Thank you Mr Anderson for putting your money where your mouth is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How is it at all possible that Biden gets 80+ million votes, yet, gets so few views? Where are all the people who voted for him? #VoterFraud  #PresidentialAddress https://t.co/2js9hRCaWP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RonPaul: No medical treatment should ever be forced. No one should ever be pushed around to get a medical treatment.  We must each deci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matthewherper @asymmetricinfo Where are we, and why havent we been banning #phthalates they're killing our fertility!! Also seed oils in food, coal tar in cosmetics, 1,4-DIOXANE to make suds, DEA  TEA, formaldehyde, Homosalate in sunscreens  this list could roll on  on if anyone @US_FDA really cared ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reason: In Oklahoma and Texas, parents who let their kids play outside will no longer fear neglect charges https://t.co/JbtCWqEJ6x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_whitneywebb: Isnt weird that, last year, if you reported on any issues with these trials, you got attacked, censored and deplatformed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KikiwahT Anti vaxxers are also just parents of vaccine injured children. It's crazy that im now going to be put on some list somewhere because of my actual life experiences. H1N1 swine flu vax paralyzed my kid w/Guillain-barre syndrome. Residual Bell's Palsy  autoimmune issues still.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TPCarney: Subsidizing child care makes no sense. If you're gonna spend money on parents, why not give them money and let them decide wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZachHomol: Howd 80 mil people support a dude whos raising taxes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RothweilerEvent @Breaking911 @US_FDA For damn sure! w/Dupont close behind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How about banning #phthalates they're killing our fertility. Also seed oils in food, coal tar in cosmetics, 1,4-DIOXANE to make suds, DEA  TEA, formaldehyde, Homosalate in sunscreens  this list could roll on if anyone @US_FDA really cared. WHAT WOULDYOU ADD TO THE LIST TWITTER? https://t.co/27eG0NX4EV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 How about banning #phthalates they're killing our fertility? Also seed oils in food, coal tar in cosmetics, 1,4-DIOXANE to make suds, DEA  TEA, formaldehyde, Homosalate in sunscreens  this list could roll on if anyone @US_FDA really cared. WHAT WOULDYOU ADD TO THE LIST TWITTER?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want introduced to law, bills like this one,  concise  2 pages long. All bills over 5 pages should be rewritten. Thousands of pages mean you have added in things taxpayers dont want @GOP @SenateDems If you're 18 - a legal adult, allowed to #vote then U can do EVERYTHING at 18. https://t.co/1ymo1mAjgw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TomRectorJr1 @RepThomasMassie https://t.co/aXwvO8jjXA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomSchuIz: Yesterday, I had a heart attack  My cardiovascular system is completely normal  healthy  But last week I took the Pfizer va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh look, yet another #PaidFor cringe ad by #BigPharma  Studies I've read mention brain washing happens in 2 months, it's been a year of 24/7 #Propaganda  I dont want you to succumb to it! https://t.co/kTQANBR8Es]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mercola I mean I wish it was shocking, but sadly today they all seem corrupt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whatmatters432 @jennife91535551 @kirstiealley How much promotion is there, in a grocery store? Companies intentionally keep workers under 30hrs so they dont have to pay em benefits. That sucks. Families need insurance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[especially if a patient has to take repeated doses over months or years. Hmmmm...   Very interesting article from 2016 #moderna #AstraZeneca #COVIDVaccination #ConArtists #mRNA]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>