<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Sign up to our site it's free, Show us your world. #moda #fashion # #modafeminina #style #love # # # #noticias #lookdodia #q8 #instagood #look # # # # #instagram #coronavirus #venezuela #instadaily #igdaily https://t.co/SUsMptBtw3 https://t.co/AwJvHOI9yq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sign up to our site it's free, Show us your world. #moda #fashion # #modafeminina #style #love # # # #noticias #lookdodia #q8 #instagood #look # # # # #instagram #coronavirus #venezuela #instadaily #igdaily https://t.co/SUsMptBtw3 https://t.co/aZI2gKUpJ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sign up to our site it's free, Show us your world. #moda #fashion # #modafeminina #style #love # # # #noticias #lookdodia #q8 #instagood #look # # # # #instagram #coronavirus #venezuela #instadaily #igdaily https://t.co/SUsMptBtw3 https://t.co/sJEQLlvNNE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[   - Yahoo! - Yahoo! https://t.co/vzwrZUKKfE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ -  https://t.co/pTYDiN7K7k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[  - https://t.co/vzkeNwn033 https://t.co/uH1uDJsqtZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RBI Governor Shaktikanta Das says SFB loans to MFIs for on-lending now classified as priority sector... - Moneycontrol https://t.co/mW0PNsPZoV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[stanbul merkezli 7 ilde FET'nn gncel talebe yaplanmasna ynelik operasyon - Cumhuriyet https://t.co/mT9Oi5H7Ys]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Son dakika... Yeni koronavirs vaka says akland! 30 bine yaklat... - Haberler - Habertrk https://t.co/hQWdPPykYT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 Mays 2021 koronavirs tablosu - Posta https://t.co/e9G2sL0HbL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[C gi 23 tui ginh 9 hc bng ton phn tin s - VietNamNet https://t.co/SkqbWaiBzI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WWEWWENewsDanielBryan Daniel Bryan's WWE Contract Expired Last Week - WhatCulture https://t.co/dQkK6HhjKy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US tax court hands win to Michael Jackson heirs - https://t.co/wvWm7MYzPt https://t.co/oYKuPzyv3i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Chloe Bishop saved the Line of Duty finale! Actress Shalom Brune-Franklin wows viewers - Daily Mail https://t.co/w5sMWGE5zo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[35 23 | |  -  https://t.co/6eAwwncPQD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[-   -  https://t.co/ipP9DuCpCx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) In Gaming Market to Scale New Growth Heights During Forecast Timespan 2021-2026 | Niantic,Sony,Ubisoft,Next Games,Valve,esDot  NeighborWebSJ - NeighborWebSJ https://t.co/C6HovLpoI6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Currency rates in Pakistan on, 5th May 2021 - BOL News https://t.co/EjZAVznllW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago Fire's Miranda Rae Mayo And Showrunner Talk Stella's Stressful Episode, Casey's New Lease On Life And More - CinemaBlend https://t.co/6IgIDD9ynb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ira Khan loves distracting boyfriend Nupur Shikhare while he works out, see pics - Republic TV https://t.co/ojOzLivtzb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FOOTBALL #JosRiga Sport FOOTBALL Vis attend aussi une licence pour la D1B ce jeudi - RTBF https://t.co/t6mwIn6F7B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Der Sport-Tag:09:14 Beckenbauer: Erfolge von Hansi Flick "nicht wiederholbar" - n-tv NACHRICHTEN https://t.co/6Z2Ka5e43v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Olympische Spiele: Lindsey Vonn hlt nichts von Protesten auf dem Podium  Heiliger Ort - DER SPIEGEL https://t.co/rEiaHDmI4S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SVWB042021 #WerderTransferNews Kaderplaner Steidten: Transfers fr Bayer, im Herzen Werder Bremen! - https://t.co/8zfeB0YuZQ https://t.co/W57ypt8ykg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deportistas sin piedad con Pablo Iglesias: 'Se va la mayor rata de la historia de Espaa' - AS https://t.co/5lhdDOJQuX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dimagrire e allenare il corpo con questo oggetto economico in una breve sessione al giorno e ritornare in ... - Proiezioni di Borsa https://t.co/SPfXHyNLCM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CooperativeGroupVeganismVegetarianismBusiness Co-op slashes the price of plant-based food in quest for net zero emissions - The Guardian https://t.co/HzSfLxn2B3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[            CO2 - https://t.co/2ZCrE9LfXc https://t.co/7525sq0J6D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tv tg utsatta fr stenkastning i sdra Uppsala - Sveriges Television https://t.co/ZWM1IubBtO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(5)7220210505 - LIVE https://t.co/OcpQ7iZZHK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 5 -  https://t.co/YtZHN4VsKb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GBP/EUR: Will Eurozone Service Sector PMI Data Drag The Euro Lower? - Currency Live https://t.co/2O3kbJJAsx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hydrogen Peroxide Market 2020: Global Business Insights and Development Analysis to 2027  KSU | The Sentinel Newspaper - KSU | The Sentinel Newspaper https://t.co/gQg866XnGn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[S.O.S. Colombia, la splica del Paro Nacional que se tom chat de transmisin de la ONU - El Espectador https://t.co/4vQhjYWwr1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No habr compra de aviones de guerra, anuncia el Ministro de Hacienda Jos Manuel Restrepo - Vanguardia https://t.co/QlSemvXB7q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MinisteriodeDefensa #Cali #PolicaNacional No hubo un ataque directo a los funcionarios de la ONU: ministro Diego Molano - Noticias Caracol https://t.co/4Ng7f2a3bK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ -  https://t.co/SSOOPyek25]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[  - Yahoo! - Yahoo! https://t.co/LmANES2Cbe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tesla: Zoll und Arbeitsschutz ermitteln in Grnheide gegen US-Autobauer - Business Insider Deutschland https://t.co/ySJDIexP1l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stellantis dej de fabricar 190.000 coches en enero-marzo por suministros Por EFE - https://t.co/6kIiQyRLxt Espaa https://t.co/t3WfGaNfRK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Siemens Energy gana 88 millones de euros en su primer semestre fiscal - Yahoo Noticias Espaa https://t.co/2Xvkt2mMP1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WTT- -  https://t.co/qoyXDIUgE4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[75 -  https://t.co/72W76pyKBn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Declaring outbreak in school left to officials' 'discretion' - Winnipeg Free Press https://t.co/TL7pyWB0Dm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UCHealth Is Finding Ways To Treat Patients With Blood Clots Linked To The Johnson  Johnson Vaccine - CBS Denver https://t.co/qWeRFV8AxD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15.5 -  https://t.co/KmsrdUl84K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VW: well sell you Level 4 autonomous driving for 7 an hour - Top Gear https://t.co/gcec8dAH1T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sharjeel says learning a lot from Yousuf at NHPC - The News International https://t.co/bgpnXPpGSh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Budowa drogi S14 ruszy pen par. Stecol z Chin dosta zielone wiato od wojewody - Wyborcza - d https://t.co/e1CDoRfo57]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[  .       - .ua https://t.co/U2XisFc6Qk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl ended up in psychiatric hospital after being locked up alone in cell at state home, care abuse inquiry hears - https://t.co/vU794mSNX4 https://t.co/1VQ04noXAm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid 19 coronavirus: Customs worker fuming after losing her job over vaccine policy - New Zealand Herald https://t.co/0QZgduRq9s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two pandemics clash as US doctors find that Covid-19 spurs diabetes - The Straits Times https://t.co/FQUGWraRr4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada's Alberta sees first death from AstraZeneca jab - Free Malaysia Today https://t.co/aZBXEX810W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US Customs seizes RM2.1mil Top Glove shipment - The Star Online https://t.co/Mv20CSN47x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Terbongkar, Wanita Pengirim Sate Beracun Ternyata Sudah Nikah Siri dengan Polisi yang Jadi Targetnya - Kompas TV https://t.co/DHzOEROQGh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Duterte receives China's Sinopharm vaccine - https://t.co/CjuZUEM61L https://t.co/Zl2sEWnaXY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MTN becomes first mobile network firm to list on Rwanda Stock Exchange - News24 https://t.co/GSHDN7H2BM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Asia shares subdued by tech retreat, US futures steady By Reuters - https://t.co/6kIiQyRLxt https://t.co/QerJOimduk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wine giant Gallo close to $400 million center in S. Carolina - Fox Business https://t.co/hrDnmJHP49]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Politics #Pharmaceuticals #BiotechandPharmaceuticals #HarrietTaylor Almost 20% of unvaccinated Americans still prefer JJ Covid vaccine after U.S. pause, survey shows - CNBC https://t.co/poCLaAiJ8G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MKTREPREPBACTDBTDIVEUBHOTRESSTXUKGBWEUEUROP FTSE 100 rises on boost from miners, banks; Croda shines - Reuters https://t.co/DxliGhQ6nN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyundai recalls more than 390000 vehicles for possible engine fires - CNA https://t.co/eXsvOT0wba]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orders and backlog up by about a fifth at Aker Solutions in first quarter - Energy Voice https://t.co/NjjeEdUA2e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 vaccine will likely be approved for 12-15-year-olds soon in Tennessee - NewsChannel 5 https://t.co/qcDXqpfrkx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McAfee and Ingram Micro Simplify Cloud Security - Business Wire https://t.co/9WLkAnyXna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Achieving CIP Compliance, NERC-Style | The State of Security - https://t.co/pywZ3dhI2e https://t.co/afbxIxnyS9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Migrantes podem vir a ser tantos quanto populao de Odemira e Aljezur juntas. Escassez de gua agrava-se - Expresso https://t.co/bhff89a31O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Son dakika: Merkez Bankas yl sonu enflasyon ve dolar tahminini ykseltti - https://t.co/5J72k7I0EM https://t.co/qHtYwzU47Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Korona asnda bir torpilli grup daha bulundu. retmenler, askerler, polisler dururken - Yenia https://t.co/bTBxgzf6VS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ABD Hazine Bakan'nn aklamalar kresel piyasalara sert sat getirdi: Dolar/TL 8,30 etrafnda dalgalanyor, yarnki PPK bekleniyor Yazar Reuters - https://t.co/6kIiQyRLxt Trkiye https://t.co/UY64RfxSl3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 yln zirvesine kan enflasyonu Merkez Bankas nasl aklad? - BLOOMBERG HT - BloombergHT https://t.co/eydNXbCr8O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#dai_video #has_video Benzema, Deschamps sait pardonner - https://t.co/rSmPl0NucF https://t.co/IKg0Vd8jcU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Un report des qualifications africaines pour le Mondial 2022 ? - SO FOOT https://t.co/yWgvcjxGHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch out for us, Gen Undi18! - The Sun Daily https://t.co/Zb12bhgyqA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Toscana, dalla prossima settimana possono prenotare il vaccino anche gli over60 - La Repubblica https://t.co/pqbHPN9aOb https://t.co/UqpiBkCZBr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sign up to our site it's free, Show us your world. #moda #fashion # #modafeminina #style #love # # # #noticias #lookdodia #q8 #instagood #look # # # # #instagram #coronavirus #venezuela #instadaily #igdaily https://t.co/SUsMptBtw3 https://t.co/deMmvzTYBl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccini a Napoli, alla Mostra d'Oltremare arriva la polizia: i 60enni rifiutano Astrazeneca - https://t.co/35w3EwKWZ5 https://t.co/7u8yylcbwu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sostegni bis, nella bozza contributi alle imprese in base al fatturato e smart working nel privato fino a settembre - La Stampa https://t.co/XYGkAxs43f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rsa Milano, zero morti di Covid per due settimane di fila. Effetto vaccini, ora le visite dei parenti in... - Corriere della Sera https://t.co/ANdt6ekSz0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DiMarted, il professor Bellavite sconvolge lo studio: "Perch gli italiani fanno bene ad aver paura dei vaccini" - https://t.co/VjWjEwlIzw https://t.co/jpzl2EWB64]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cacciari: "Mi fermano mentre torno a casa e invece al Duomo..." - Adnkronos https://t.co/woenLDHUzP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BoaAksoyLenfomaArkaSokaklar Arka Sokaklar oyuncusu Boa Aksoy: Lenfomaya yakalandm - Hrriyet https://t.co/czfAjWPv5i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reyting sonular 4 Mays 2021 Sal! Dnn reyting sralamasnda kim birinci oldu? Sal reytingleri - Habertrk https://t.co/OASd0zJaTl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zafer Algz: Marketle ev arasnda mekik dokuyorum - Milliyet https://t.co/cR8TqChN1u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ak da yok evlilik de! - Sabah https://t.co/jRr0LafLjd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[|  -  https://t.co/qa13Rf8Lmy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1.4        -  https://t.co/jWvawdugrM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Or, euros, ambiance : Le mariage VIP de Nabou Dash - https://t.co/Aea0esl9hL - Actualit au Sngal https://t.co/aEmXr4leAO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How bird's eye view tech aims to unlock Nairobi traffic jams - The Star, Kenya https://t.co/aAflLUL4e2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mercedes bevestigt: Grosjean neemt met priv-test in stijl afscheid van de Formule 1 - GPfans https://t.co/BGsovARJkU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Challenges continue for filling COVID-19 vaccine appointments - KCRA News https://t.co/oFkMq6RA1L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MAN CITY 1-0 PSG | CHAMPIONS LEAGUE SEMI-FINAL (2ND LEG) | WNRH LIVE SHOW - Man City https://t.co/3Z6e6ZfyM2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WARRIORS at PELICANS | FULL GAME HIGHLIGHTS | May 4, 2021 - NBA https://t.co/ehlaYFi5Jw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Janek Kroupa: Informace o Hamkov lenm plnu mme od vcero astnk schzky. I je ten mysl vydsil - https://t.co/L1gOTUgMJw https://t.co/65uEtZPt11]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Naamkaran Actor Zain Imam's Cousin Passes Away Due To COVID-19; Celebs Offer Condolences - Filmibeat https://t.co/O1EKZsOWeX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ghum Hai Kisikey Pyaar Meiin 4 May written update: Sai demands the rights of a wife - Republic TV https://t.co/JrAa7OT0zP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coles Express, Pizza Hut, 7 Eleven service station and KFC added to COVID-19 list in Perth - https://t.co/bEbjQEBzyJ https://t.co/au2ZSM6jUJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Het weer op Bevrijdingsdag: bar en boos | Binnenland | https://t.co/oMIwJQAV9M - https://t.co/oMIwJQAV9M https://t.co/724dL7XTVo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If You're Over 65, Doing This Can Reduce Your Alzheimer's Risk, Study Finds - msnNOW https://t.co/3swndJzrIw]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>