<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Science? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elizabe32413720 No way]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suckers!! https://t.co/e0VPEcdLpT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@willdennis1940 @JacquiWoyda @DailyMailUK You know you still need to do a test to travel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JacquiWoyda @DailyMailUK They don't need them. 20s,healthy. No point]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK Suckers...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@auroral79 @jennyrickson Yeah a very good one too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NHS sending this out. Its official. #VaccinePassports are going to happen. Is that about 22-0 to the conspiracy theorists then? #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #CovidVaccine #Propaganda #MasksOff #masksdontwork https://t.co/C4U5WivXmf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ben_sturrock @JamesMelville What pandemic? I'm expecting a. #FBPE, pro Europe or some pronouns in his profile. Maybe a mask emoji]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Protect the kids. Parents, say no to the #CovidVaccine. This is not right! #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #NoNewNormal #MasksDontWork #MasksOff #usforthem #SaveOurKids https://t.co/gwyj5ws27c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK The only old person to die of old age since march 2020...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pourmeavino Wtf. Who would take time out of their sad lives to even bother sending you a message to say that? Sad people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is plain nuts. And we were called conspiracy theorists. Guess who is behind this? That's right, the new bachelor, #BillGates https://t.co/5XRw0kvRVp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jennyrickson Brian Rose has my vote]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goodridgeAFC87 Yep defo especially last year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - You are being lied to and manipulated by the mainstream media inluding @BBCNews about the Covid Crisis in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This scumbag played a part in rigging an election. She isn't one to talk https://t.co/ACJPXaEHuf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @ChathamHouse Pot calling...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pourmeavino Why is it green?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fight_lies It is indeed and I ashamed I voted for him]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DpetrolheadJ Like the world economic forum logo?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And if anyone wants proof of some of that lnvestment before I get called a conspiracy theorist ... https://t.co/6gH0GamFGB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DpetrolheadJ 66?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AriB2783 @zaph0db @SugarFetHeels @MaizyDaizyZzzz @21WIRE For a normal vaccine, you have to complete animal trials before beginning clinical trials. The clinical trial is now, with millions of humans and ends 2023. You been in hiding? This isn't news. It's common knowledge. Even on the v@x companies docs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're an Australian citizen in India, if you try and come home to Australia, you face 5 years in prison or a $66,000 fine. I thought #Australia was enjoying freedom because of their amazing #COVID19 response.?? #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #CovidVaccine #Propaganda #MasksOff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 2020, the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation funded the Tony Blair Institute for Global Change over 22 million dollars. Hmmm what was that for hey? Now do you see why Blair is everywhere, driving policy for #CovidVaccine and #VaccinePassports? Wakey wakey..! #Covid19UK https://t.co/2udah1fmZA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AriB2783 @zaph0db @SugarFetHeels @MaizyDaizyZzzz @21WIRE Deceiving article. They combined the trials with their phase 2. Less time, less subjects. Can't monitor long term efficacy in 6 months. Need years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Grahmptr: JUST IN : The Former Democrat House Speaker for the state Oregon, was arrested and charged over human sex trafficking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AriB2783 @zaph0db @SugarFetHeels @MaizyDaizyZzzz @21WIRE Really? You saying the likes of Ioannidis aren't world leading? Maybe go and look at their research, studies and acknowledgments then crawl back to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vDajTfS8sw  QUICK. LOCKDOWN NOW!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AriB2783 @zaph0db @SugarFetHeels @MaizyDaizyZzzz @21WIRE Expert enough to call world leading professors conspiracy theorists. Pot calling...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SugarFetHeels @MaizyDaizyZzzz @zaph0db @21WIRE Am I gonna listen to Dr Hillary for the Bill Gates funded Ferguson or am I gonna listen to world renowned virologists or family who are in virology. Hmmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Eckqu2F5C4  Imagine if this was #Trump. He'd be all over the media being abused.  #BidenAddress #BidenHarris #BidensAmerica #bidentakeyourmeds #Trump #Trump2024]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zaph0db @21WIRE Errr, bullsh*t from qualified epidemiologists? Yeadon, Cahill, Ioannidis, Bhakdi, Bhattacharya,  have all said the same.....Including the main problem, liver failure in animal studies, resulting in death. Maybe you should do a bit of research away from the BBC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Md3zVztWoJ  Makes sense right? Imagine getting your car brakes repaired and they fail as soon as you leave the mechanics   #CovidVaccine #coronavirusuk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zaph0db @21WIRE Been in development for years but failed every animal trial, thats why a mRNA has never been approved. How many animals was this tested on? Which ones? How have they monitored long term efficacy? They haven't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ah the ever so reliable WHO. https://t.co/yphAIEpjdc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BangoBilly: Ivermectin: Cheap Covid Treatment Shown to be Highly Effective in New Peer-Reviewed Study https://t.co/h0b3pnNFxi via @LD_S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And people call conspiracy theorists mad? https://t.co/iizRrdu1H3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OliveQueen1472 But but but he saves children with his v@ccines ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS. WAKEY WAKEY!!! https://t.co/iUTMsy8yKB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesGibson1138 Obama won a Nobel prize. So it's possible he's in with a shot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 Stupid bit*h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh shit up you washed up tw@. America is on another level of fear mongering. Blame #biden #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #CovidVaccine #Propaganda #MasksOff https://t.co/07jyvQNZZg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If this is real then I'm going to hell https://t.co/kAqaJiZr8Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize. He was one of a few doctors who pioneered the use of #HydroxyChloroquine. He has also been heavily banned and censored from social media for advocating this.   #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #CovidVaccine  #MasksOff https://t.co/hbhQMYpEt9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thewle She's been keeping secrets https://t.co/Si96rEiYfp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Guess the only consolation is its only 2 weeks away until pubs and restaurants can reopen fully.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna Sick bastards]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 https://t.co/FBD4mOnzNO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wendy_hume @garethicke What a wo...wo...man!! https://t.co/TN8r3uxrPj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke https://t.co/jn8yJme5br]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: BREAKING. Bill and Melinda will no longer be fucking each other, but will continue to work together to fuck the rest of us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 Nah.. Don't believe this one bit.. Surely not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nevillebartos12 @BreesAnna We know this but most of the world think he is a god]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna Not really. The man who is totally pro depopulation has funded v@ccines to help people live longer? That's odd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DpetrolheadJ Maybe they were put together many years ago with the plan to imement what's happening now. Marriage of convenience. Middle ages married couple, family people, wanting to help the world blah blah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 https://t.co/eMR31C4rRR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseARosey I'm still in hysterics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Melinda has been naughty hasn't she. She needed a good.... Fauc #BillGates #covidvacccine #COVID19 https://t.co/GnmoHetoDJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goodridgeAFC87 @MaizyDaizyZzzz It's like a robotic, zombie movie. Makes no sense at all. That's the issue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseARosey Ooooo https://t.co/nHs4iPWLqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blades1234567 @KbfNorthernlass ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaizyDaizyZzzz: This vid' says it all.   The general public are mostly brainless pillocks! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @guardian It's 2 weeks away...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 https://t.co/3pfTJEJJIf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DpetrolheadJ Which man will get custody of the kids]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Biffboff2 Both evil scum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@driverjess Hahaha. Maybe his v@ccine isn't big enough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNBCnow Evil scum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Taken over the world and now want to shag other people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Zcz0H2XcKF. Awww Billy has a small willy. Taken over the world, kil*ed thousands and now he can officially shag other people.  #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #CovidVaccine #BillGates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amroger1 @SusanBe36094276 You back the vaccine passports?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dcbwelsh Ah OK, no masksl for me then ;)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Looking4Amerca @KarenH777 Can only test flu with blood samples. Pcr is unreliable for flu but oh so reliable got covid... Strange huh? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrDPoole @KarenH777 It's just prevents people getting seriously ill. Kind of like the flu vax apparently]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LLS_property Madness. Complete madness.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KWDbamTDdU  Says it all #Covid19UK #coronavirusuk #CovidVaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jamescolwill @CoreyLHughes @PoliticsForAlI Masks are major. Stadiums half capacity isn't normal. Wake up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@youth_unheard @PoliticsForAlI GIL for PM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlynJ97 @PoliticsForAlI Haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @thetimes Should've done that in America right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had to laugh. Get tested people... Even if you've had the miracle v@xx. https://t.co/U2owKAujpq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI I scrapped it last March]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 Maturely Put. high five :) all the best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KbfNorthernlass You're kidding? People had a go at you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 Diff Is the covid will still get through the mask and actual projectile further than without a mask. jesus man. wake up. anyway good luck. you carry on with your masks. I'll carry on without. I've managed to survive 14 months without in a 'pandemic'. all the best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmmaUK https://t.co/lZSkjJ5Sdx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 Like trying to stop a mosquito getting through a chain link fence. Studies found 80% of those who tested positive, wore masks regularly. That's a cdc study. Masks don't work. Don't know how else I can spell it out. https://t.co/AOnO1CsaeC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 Wow.  1) stop blood splatter getting into mouths. 2) stop any foreign particles from their mouths or nose getting into open wounds and infecting them. Doubt you'd want a surgeon coughing into your open wound after they've had a spicy burrito for lunch. Nothing to do with virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 Surgeons don't wear masks to stop viruses. That's the point. You're right, they dispose of theirs after every procedure, on highly sanitised and oxygenised environments which prevents them from getting sick and preserves cleanliness. That's medical fact]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI Makes sense because....? Stadiums are outside. Did they not get the memo?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 But how many people do it like that? Barely any. Fact is, they still don't stop viruses, no matter how clean they are. Ask any credible surgeon. Plenty of studies too. Sorry to break the news.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrexitDuck Yep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StockportTom @AceBanned But but but the BBC told them to wear them...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMindsculpter I know. Should set up a charity really]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @Hman74 Look up bacterial pneumonia. So you advocate masking toddlers too? Pray to God you haven't got kids.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned I hope you wear a condom in bed alone. Just in case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMindsculpter I don't think so. Maybe the mask has helped fry a few brain cells]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AceBanned @StockportTom Never worn one. I've being seeing friends and family. Never tested. And guess how many have died as a result.... NONE! Shock horror right? A healthy person being healthy. Amazing]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>