<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The mission, should you choose to accept it, is no life lost to the Covid-19 pandemic.  Some outstanding doctors rose to the occasion.  With the most minimal medical resources. https://t.co/2Dovz5Ss7P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the resistance. Get the book. https://t.co/bUjFhQgZ4J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A concern for favipiravir safety from a very small observational study due to serum concentration variability and association with liver injury.  https://t.co/pasjvKHwjP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Found the source of the information: https://t.co/24fYOSVvnw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Being told that the industrial price of 1kg of ivermectin in India has gone from USD240 to USD700 in the last few months.  At 0.4mg/kg x 5 days x 60kg, 1kg of ivermectin allows to treat roughly 8,000 patients.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One of the co-author is an Assistant Professor of Medicine at the Mayo Clinic and it is great to see a doctor from such  a prestigious institution sticking his neck out for objective science. https://t.co/AdfTn3D0i6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In many countries, a very safe, simple, accessible (frequently OTC) TMPRSS2 inhibitor:  Ambroxol  (which can also be obtained as a metabolite of Bromhexine, the cough syrup)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder: https://t.co/B3oatH4GxP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More eye-popping results from a TMPRSS2 inhibitor (here an exceptionally potent novel molecule called N-0385), both in vitro and in mice model.  Hit the TMPRSS2 receptor hard to defeat Covid-19. https://t.co/yZRYBEDcYF https://t.co/27bNdb69xR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US judges  confirm that denying ivermectin to patients violates a fundamental legal right. https://t.co/HGTyRWuNe3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dahuuu Something like that maybe?  https://t.co/JCVdcJq424]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["After court order, Elmhurst Hospital says its allowing COVID-19 patient to receive controversial drug ivermectin"  Great, but next time, add fluvoxamine to the request.  https://t.co/FDENdJVDtN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Our meta-analysis suggests that Ivermectin could be an effective adjuvant therapy in reducing mortality, particularly in patients with mild-moderate clinical presentation of COVID-19."  Includes 38 studies, n=15,002, from US/Indian researchers.  https://t.co/MiaBmMXnsu https://t.co/62q5aDxWI4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cov19treatments: Critical resource for your family and friends.  Directory of Doctors Prescribing Effective Outpatient COVID-19 Therapy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The recent nitazoxanide US phase 3 study: https://t.co/RfYPxw67m8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A favourable article on Nitazoxanide, pointing to successful interim data from several undergoing trials in Latam.  Have the positive results of the recent Phase 3 US trial made that repurposed drug acceptable to main media now?  https://t.co/eSi94TWrjT  https://t.co/M0CZHpjHNU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Chetty has achieved no hospitalizations in 4,000 South African Covid patients, with a multi-drug therapy uniquely including Promethazine.  That drug came 3rd out of 7,811 candidates in a recent, large, in silico quest for repurposed drugs from China.  https://t.co/66fBxdmUru https://t.co/pqzM0Mo3na]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iranian retrospective study (n=991) points to 25% mortality benefit from aspirin use in hospitalized Covid-19 patients in multivariate Cox model:  Adj. Hazard Ratio 0.75 CI 95% 0.57-0.99, p=.043  HCQ not far behind:  aHR 0.805, CI 95% 0.625-1.032, p=.087  https://t.co/MZk7jeN7jy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The hysterical obstruction of ivermectin treatment by some US hospitals is totally outrageous.  "you offer nothing" https://t.co/6a8hubrR1W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another reason to load up on Vitamin C  https://t.co/Aax7MGMuiM https://t.co/haBuZ8hheA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zero hospitalization? How's that possible? Only Fluvoxamine has done that so far.  Promethazine? Are you a FIASMA as well?  Yes, indeed.  That solitary, admirable front line doctor has connected all the dots months ago.  When will our inept bureaucrats?  https://t.co/UJXPWGdp4t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[... Dr. Chetty gradually ticks all the right boxes given the clinical knowledge of Covid-19 accumulated elsewhere over a year.  Treating with hydroxychloroquine, ivermectin, prednisone, all fine, but then comes the clincher: the selection of the anti-histamine Promethazine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jaw-dropping interview of a South African doctor who has treated 4,000 Covid patients without hospitalization or loss of life.  I am ashamed to admit that I reluctantly watched that long video, prejudiced about the low credibility of African boasts.  As the discussion unfolds...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AOlavarria "Pronto"...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder of the very positive results of the only large Randomized Controlled Trial with a Zinc arm to date.  https://t.co/kfdAe1YK1B https://t.co/RZXFqsVJKI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really feels like the downtick could be imminent: https://t.co/3iITj7SeUS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Epicurve trends and vaccination campaign impacts: so hard to disentangle... https://t.co/vxewFvn7eW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great MCA analysis from Pr. Raoult clustering patients by severity of disease (from green to red).  Much to ponder about but remarkable is the position of Zinc deficiency along the 1st axis, signalling a grave risk factor. https://t.co/GGgjs01u2I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow the French science...  From May 19:   Outdoor restaurant limit: 6 per table  Indoor seated audience limit: 800 spectators  Makes solid scientific, evidence-based sense, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@griffglen Does that beat the NHS Covid-19 Home Kit?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EuRob9 No]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Ivermectin Meta-Analysis Demonstrating Safety  Efficacy Targeting COVID-19 Published in Peer-Review Journal"  https://t.co/iaYd0iBwO5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another outstanding interview with a US MD having success prescribing ivermectin + fluvoxamine.  @drbeen_medical, you have a lot at stake here and your admirable courage to stay the course in those difficult times does not go unnoticed.  https://t.co/njdF5RFI1n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis of the anti-inflammatory benefits of fluoxetine (Prozac) in Covid-19 thru gene expression impact.  "treatments with fluoxetine approximate inflammatory IL6ST and NFBK1 gene knockdowns more significantly than dexamethasone"  https://t.co/zs3mlKYB2b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Badly under-researched but highly promising: a useful systematic review of melatonin in Covid-19.  https://t.co/NRSDMEqo82 https://t.co/FtyvW6VhOH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vids99 Yes indeed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see the number of active Covid cases already falling rapidly in India.  https://t.co/Cqg2JQMMYq https://t.co/zYrLDc2LL8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eslJjVKyGT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Example of the Covid home kit offered in Goa: https://t.co/OVnAIVJpAy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India relies on home isolation for most of the Covid-19 cases. Some healthcare authorities try to provide a Covid kit like this one: https://t.co/969nqi3D8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Brazilian Ministry of Health is going to publish a federal Covid-19 treatment protocol likely including ivermectin and hydroxychloroquine.  https://t.co/AdedPU2TFQ  https://t.co/GPNhdTgWWA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Extraordinary things going on in the Philippines... https://t.co/cFdHx2LIY4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jpkiekens: This is the full recording of our webinar with three distinguished medical doctors from South Africa, Canada and USA, about]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Divroet Should not post pre-coffee. Thanks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The IVIG meta-analysis:  https://t.co/bAJ6yYzfnQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meta-analysis of 7 studies including 825 hospitalized patients. "The severity of COVID-19 is associated with the efficiency of IVIG. In critical subgroup, IVIG could reduce the mortality [RR=0.63 (0.45-0.88,I2=25%). No significant difference in the severe/non-severe subgroups." https://t.co/KyaKWPiCPN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A nice summary: https://t.co/BAY60ZLuWY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indian mass media slowly catching up with the official inclusion of ivermectin and budesonide in the national Covid treatment protocol.  https://t.co/BN17d90XqP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saudi open-label RCT (n=254) shows no benefit of favipiravir + hydroxychloroquine in hospitalized Covid patients in poor shape, 42% diabetic, 92% with bilateral infiltrates and 94% requiring O2 at baseline.  https://t.co/wB6vKlNo2D https://t.co/0Gj1pogGSQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[... which means intubation, mechanical ventilation or death, but remarkably very few progressed: 3% in the control arm.  The resulting low event rate raises the issue of statistical power, for instance in the mITT aspirin arm:  HR 0.4 CI 95% 0.10-1.55, p=.18]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hard to read Indian open-label RCT (n=900) of moderate hospital patients (median 6 days from onset, age 53) treated with atorvastatin and aspirin, separately or as a combo.  Primary outcome = clinical deterioration to WHO Clinical Ordinal Scale  6...  https://t.co/2mrYIA4a9c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshBloomACSH "It is not an antiviral drug, it is an antiparasitic drug"  Do your homework before publishing unprofessional hit pieces cherrypicking a single badly flawed study. https://t.co/NMRgbEgtsn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Is a Mask That Covers the Mouth and Nose Free from Undesirable Side Effects in Everyday Use and Free of Potential Hazards?"  A difficult question. Several concerns raised.  https://t.co/A3k2ESt4o7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ebusati I am afraid that it is the only head-on comparison in RCT.  You have a PSM study here:  https://t.co/MfYjfMhxCC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ebusati https://t.co/8hRgy4Dk1K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Madagascar is the only country that has decided to rely on artemisia to fend off Covid-19, and the outcome looks alright so far. https://t.co/2GTHb6Wrjk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Small review of antimalaria artemisin's potential against Covid-19.  Many trials on their way.  https://t.co/eiktlhsqwo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What can India do?  A local article reminds its readers of an affordable option with the title:  "Corona kit for 150 rupees" ($2)  The Ziverdo Kit (ivermectin+doxycyclin+zinc)  https://t.co/ScBXzau4fV https://t.co/4OuyEiglGO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An article from Colombia presenting the ivermectin controversy in a favourable light:  https://t.co/XEvaVxa5yj  https://t.co/89KqWmcX3H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To force people to go to court to obtain ivermectin is sheer insanity. https://t.co/cMOTBsVMTP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timSpoon4 @drakchaurasia @lairdwd2 @fouzisultan @zegirish Not me: Merck https://t.co/16BOi9pqyk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Together Trial DSMB must:   Drop metformin  Increase dosage for the rest of the trial  Extend length of Ivermectin treatment  Create a combo arm Fluvoxamine+Ivermectin  @TogetherTrial https://t.co/yWQx6UmqUw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The ultimate observational study on BMI and Covid-19 from the UK (n=6,910,695).  https://t.co/FGwxgEPBfZ https://t.co/bKXOgUakgc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happening today https://t.co/a909qMjDiC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Converting the Log Hazard Ratios into more readable numbers, with the superiority of faster acting Calcifediol highly visible: https://t.co/5B7xRM6bn7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And in the end, you win.  Despite all the sickening efforts to suppress it, the ivermectin research by the FLCCC doctors is now in print. https://t.co/JjTWA5tntm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Statin chronic usage associated with better Covid outcomes in an Italian observational study (n=501), likely due to their anti-inflammatory properties.  https://t.co/FC3iFck4oy https://t.co/R8UHDjMoJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The simpler ROX index ([SpO2/FiO2]/respiratory rate) outperforms NEWS2 as a predictor of severity in Covid-19.  https://t.co/6Xi05vsRM2 https://t.co/eVhq3rf3Lm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pyramax has already shown efficacy in vitro:  https://t.co/1RVEid3xvA https://t.co/9qBI0Kbkqt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Korean have completed their Phase2  domestic clinical trial (n=113) of antimalarial pyramax. Results soon.  They have launched a larger trial (n=402) in the Philippines, and another one is running in South Africa.  https://t.co/41rYD8aq2H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most impressive proxalutamide results to date:  https://t.co/xraFTrl86m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The phase 3 anti-androgen proxalutamide trial has started in the USA.  https://t.co/6O2D5HmXAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["A significant reduction in mortality in patients hospitalized with COVID-19 is associated with the prescription of vitamin D, especially calcifediol, within 15-30 days prior to hospitalization."  Large database analysis from Spain.  https://t.co/PO6UVzEUCe https://t.co/IU8Zin0exu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierreKory: Yup. Speaks to my other war on a colossal, global doctoring "fail" in COVID-19: the use of an anemic dose of 6mg dexamethas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/16BOi9pqyk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great, but with the mistaken recommendation to take ivermectin on an empty stomach: it should be taken with a meal to maximize the benefit. https://t.co/V8rzwz0N1r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VBUPIND The side effects reported at higher doses are dizziness and blurry vision and they are both transient.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VBUPIND Brazilian, African doctors have been there before and they say: escalate the dose until you get a response.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Czech hospital has now treated 150 mostly serious Covid patients with ivermectin.  It likes what it sees and it has already filed for a randomized, placebo controlled trial.  https://t.co/2lEGLoTpLR  https://t.co/XwToHRLuBo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calcitriol (a form of vitamin D) supplementation is associated with a reduction of risk of mortality by 43% in a large (n=8,076) observational study of chronic kidney disease patients (HR 0.57 CI 95% 0.41-0.80, p=.001).   https://t.co/8M2WNWdP9U https://t.co/XFi3baz8CL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dfreedman7 @Mompracem_ @drakchaurasia @PierreKory @Covid19Critical @veryvirology @brucep13 @YoDoctorYo @__ice9 @drbeen_medical @GeorgeFareed2 @joevaron @richardursomd More than one for those who properly follow the data. https://t.co/gw9F7c15mf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another surprising Iranian Double Blind Randomized Controlled Trial with local herbs and good outcomes.   sugarcane - saccharum officinarum  black myrobalan - terminalia chebula   mastic  - pistacia lentiscus resina  https://t.co/L101WCiihk https://t.co/qDuZi5j47b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRJHealey @Keith040856 @IanKitson4 @SwaledaleMutton @CovidBlindWife @Claudebandana Here you go https://t.co/EA4ZGPH7Vj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JanieHsieh The national protocol has just included ivermectin/budesonide as well. https://t.co/rJFPqm6RO0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid-19 treatment protocol of the State of Kerala, India (35m people), which includes Ivermectin and Budesonide. https://t.co/xiMR8Vs75Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arvindcanchi @ICMRDELHI @aiims_nd @MoHFW_INDIA Here you go. Largely enough for presumption of efficacy, with an exceptionally good safety profile. https://t.co/k7arPr4Rny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From the largest party in Bavaria, Germany, advocating:  "a temporary approval of ivermectin and accompanying  studies, because on top of vaccination, we absolutely need a 2nd barrier with therapeutic agents against the virus."  https://t.co/Sa3NNF7Uop  https://t.co/U32VZZRDZl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,000 mg Vitamin C and 400 IU vitamin E daily do not affect hospital discharge velocity in small (n=72) Iranian Randomized Controlled Trial.  https://t.co/mbAusuNzGW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pr. Raoult (h-index 188) has updated his hospital's Covid-19 scoreboard up to April 26:   15,379 treated with Azithromycin+ Hydroxychloroquine  71 deaths at an average age of 81  Case Fatality Rate 0.46% (France 1.9%) https://t.co/fItIYZmuHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Early, high-dose, bolus treatment of severe Covid-19 patients with methylprednisolone makes a material difference in small (n=83) observational study from Italy:   @Covid19Critical   https://t.co/v52jvfUdDs https://t.co/h1na7542CN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scharer_alex @tehcaster Sure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hopefully India will look like that soon.  Nice gradient on the way down. https://t.co/fOfJ3Xv9hp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A member of the Philippines's parliament wants to freely distribute ivermectin to the poor in his district and is ready to take the regulator to court if it opposes him.  https://t.co/0opGmyx0ES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And a reminder about this beautiful paper on vitamin D in Covid-19, all the way back to June 2020:  https://t.co/AqpPavXDFv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are a hard-nosed Randomized-Controlled-Trial-only kind of guy (given that causal inference from association is particularly tricky with vitamin D for several reasons), here are the 5 vitamin D RCTs to date: https://t.co/DPt4G6Zxx5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Umpteenth observational study (n=220) showing an association between serum vitamin D levels and Covid test positivity.  https://t.co/98GQu2neLT https://t.co/cn79U6or4Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xTLuUeIn7n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pUfxxIYNil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Previously:  https://t.co/HH3iLV06eb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some good results from Famotidine (Pepcid) in tiny (n=20), single-blind, placebo controlled trial of Covid inpatients (6 day discharge vs 9, p=.01).  Not enough to put an end to the data famine on that promising Covid-19 drug.  https://t.co/39NtfNHRP4]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>