<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSThisMorning: Taliban fighters reportedly captured a district in northern Afghanistan this morning  part of an offensive against Afg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSThisMorning: The attorney for Derek Chauvin has filed a motion for a new trial.  This comes amid a separate controversy over a photo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joseph Zalman Kleinman, Holocaust survivor who testified against Nazi commander Adolf Eichmann, dies at 91  https://t.co/T07B9meici]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, has written a children's book inspired by Harry and Archie  https://t.co/jw5VoLUKBP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 arrested after spiritual leader's mummified body found decorated with Christmas lights in Colorado home https://t.co/eBVrpnJdw2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 impacting India's G7 delegation in London https://t.co/jJpzIy1Map https://t.co/6ZKd1c2TGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. begins reuniting families separated under Trump's "zero tolerance" policy https://t.co/JtfgLKrfcu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Stargazers in Washington were mesmerized by a string of lights in the night sky Tuesday night. The unusual objects were determined to be Starlink satellites launched by SpaceX earlier that day. https://t.co/YQSVTxJ3g4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Family of Ashli Babbitt, woman shot by officer during Capitol riot, says it was murder and plans to sue for wrongful death https://t.co/v14XGfiTMS https://t.co/a9Cl7g9mf1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: The U.S. Coast Guard came to the aid of a capsized 40-foot boat off the coast of Point Loma in San Diego, California this week, rescuing 29 people in what officials said was a human smuggling attempt. https://t.co/mBumlXpOqV https://t.co/cHFj3LYM0f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Referee who came out as transgender makes sports history in Israel https://t.co/gMDfBdoUW5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THE WORLDS NEW STAGE: The Italian government announced an upgrade to the iconic Colosseum: A new retractable wooden floor that will allow visitors a view from the center  an original feature of the amphitheater. The project will cost over $22 million and be completed by 2023 https://t.co/0eASyAQasa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOTS OF LOVE: None of Liao Baoxings triplet daughters wanted to miss out on hugs when he returned home to Shijiazhuang, China after an extended business trip recently. All three four-year-olds were soon jumping into his arms! https://t.co/Owa9tB5mb5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. begins reuniting families separated under Trump's "zero tolerance" policy https://t.co/8KSn9rqCsG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best movies on Netflix right now https://t.co/iwZAeVZjFT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman receives gift of motherhood from stranger after cancer diagnosis https://t.co/ibv0hyhPJM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man dies after being shot by FBI agent outside CIA headquarters https://t.co/gKJEUbDsJB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Federal spending could drive a rise in interest rates, Janet Yellen says https://t.co/1vlGSk2lTE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At-home COVID-19 rapid tests could play critical role during pandemic https://t.co/lge3ALxKjd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[City of Milwaukee approves $750,000 settlement for NBA player Sterling Brown in police misconduct lawsuit https://t.co/A5M8Bik1iq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daughter of 73-year-old violently arrested by Colorado police says officers "need to go to jail" https://t.co/iE0loWt9Ao]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MAY THE SHOT BE WITH YOU: Darth Vader walks around a COVID-19 vaccine site in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, fist-bumping and taking selfies with people waiting in line for their shot. https://t.co/dcUpnnNqyW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Returning Bruce's Beach in California to the Black family who originally owned it https://t.co/FxxYISRcwW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Births fall to 42-year low in U.S., new CDC data shows https://t.co/ymqS4AeOCr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: A tornado hit Jackson, Mississippi on Tuesday as the region braced for severe weather. Storms left thousands without power and damage was reported across several counties. https://t.co/4STIPLj5P6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden sets goal of fully vaccinating 160 million adults by July 4 https://t.co/hoIu5n1ER9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IRS is holding millions of tax returns, delaying refunds https://t.co/vlxhE2Iuiz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ROLLER COASTER OF LOVE: Kings Island showed its love for Bob Ross by using dolls in the famous painter's likeness to test one of its Cincinnati, Ohio roller coasters. https://t.co/0oYmuSBGKm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Restaurants face nationwide chicken shortage https://t.co/bATUqA7nio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: Despite an average of 2.3 million COVID-19 vaccines going into arms each day, 80% of people who are trying to decide wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Belgian farmer was annoyed by the stone in his tractor's path. He moved it and the French border https://t.co/3pNuKmQ0RQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This hippo at the Cincinnati Zoo spent hours catching raindrops in her mouth. Not everyone is bummed out by a rainy day, the zoo said. https://t.co/zoIFpTt49l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyundai recalls more than 390,000 vehicles due to possible engine fires https://t.co/YmqmHG2sHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: A mother and son from Guatemala are being reunited for the first time since they were separated at the border under the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stevenportnoy: It was the year a sitting president died, two nuclear bombs were dropped, the world witnessed unimaginable horror and th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman receives gift of motherhood from stranger after cancer diagnosis https://t.co/vdgpqbq6iA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYC Comptroller Scott Stringer, a top candidate for the Democratic mayoral primary, is looking to rebuild support after a sexual misconduct allegation. Meanwhile, three major female candidates are pushing to gain traction after low polling. @erinmdurkin has the latest on the race https://t.co/3qOmwNdDn9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Derek Chauvin seeks new trial in George Floyd case https://t.co/kO1IxSoOEr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The tight battle for control of Virginia's House of Delegates https://t.co/jPTm7hGung]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: TALIBAN OFFENSIVE: From the moment U.S. troops started withdrawing forces from Afghanistan, the Taliban went on the off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best movies on Netflix right now https://t.co/MABGN7o0Nf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Target offers $5 coupons to those who get vaccinated in its stores https://t.co/QSEXbVBEAP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. begins reuniting families separated under Trump's "zero tolerance" policy https://t.co/9VJFRvQzSt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: Tension continues to mount within the GOP over Rep. Liz Cheneys criticism of former Pres. Trump.  @NikolenDCon new au]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: TORNADO OUTBREAK: Nearly 40 million Americans across the South and Plains are facing the threat of tornadoes, damaging]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: At least two dozen people are dead and more than 70 others were injured when a portion of Mexico Citys elevated metro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: The FDA will expand emergency authorization as soon as this week for Pfizers COVID-19 vaccine to be administered to an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSEveningNews: Pres. Biden set a new goal: to get 70% of adults in the U.S. vaccinated by July 4.  The push is part of what he's calli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Severe weather threatens nearly 40 million across the South https://t.co/uOptc2gHzF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At-home COVID-19 rapid tests could play critical role during pandemic https://t.co/U1EgZ1hMQD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID is killing 120 people an hour in India, and it could stay "really grim" for months https://t.co/VbygjPBXzx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The FDA has now authorized five over-the-counter, at-home COVID-19 tests, which have results ready in 30 minutes or less. @DrLaPookexamines the new tests and walks through how they work https://t.co/OYWRS0QBiF https://t.co/bqqpSw5aXy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Biden administration will be enlisting the help of local primary care physicians in the next phase of the U.S. immunization effort. White House Vaccinations Coordinator @choucair speaks with CBSN about why local doctors are "even more critical" now for vaccine plans https://t.co/CoKMYNOlXx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justice Department objects to National Rifle Association's bankruptcy plan https://t.co/AhG5P8GPWz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Referee who came out as transgender makes sports history in Israel https://t.co/zZDlGvyFPm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["McCarthy appears to be running out of patience": @NikolenDC explains the growing rift between House Republican Leader Kevin McCarthy and top GOP Rep. Liz Cheney, as they remain "at odds" about the role former President Trump should play in the party https://t.co/Nj065CIsxp https://t.co/w6BPELDUIA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: CBSN's "Red  Blue" has news and analysis on the day's top political stories https://t.co/Nj065CIsxp https://t.co/ERMPaMQ8Aq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Companies call out efforts to restrict voting in Texas https://t.co/gwjAHCFWZh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House to hold additional hearings on January 6 attack on the Capitol https://t.co/r4ocbJrjsf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police searching for 19-year-old Buffalo State College student who disappeared more than a week ago https://t.co/RvdrwNxGBN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisiana lawmakers reject bill to limit transgender youth in sports https://t.co/zBYosXAm66]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Federal spending could drive a rise in interest rates, Janet Yellen says https://t.co/ME9be0xhqH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democratic Congressman Charlie Crist launches third gubernatorial bid https://t.co/ohNuNNhMEi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@weijia asks what else Biden administration can do to promote vaccinations if it won't require them for certain things, such as travel  Biden says there can be more vaccine production and bringing in community "spokespersons" to support vaccine efforts https://t.co/NsM2qvpWI2 https://t.co/ESQxH9kG8l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boosting public confidence in those who have not yet received the vaccine is Biden's final focus in the next phase of fully vaccinating the U.S. population. He says, "this is not a Democrat or Republican issue https://t.co/3IFLzsl02L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman charged in attack on flight attendant during late-night flight from Miami to JFK as reports of unruly passengers increase https://t.co/wh5oq5iekz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Major U.S. sports unions sign letter opposing voting rights changes in Georgia and other states https://t.co/fKCKi5zhZq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When asked how easy it will be for the WH to implement these new vaccine goals, Biden says "most people will be convinced by the fact that their failure to get the vaccine may cause other people to get sick and maybe die" https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/ySSAROT9Qe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crane removes train car from collapse site in Mexico City, where at least 23 people died and dozens were injured. https://t.co/Xf7HDZgq5r https://t.co/4m4pS9dHaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On vaccine sharing, Biden says that by July 4 the U.S. will have sent 10% of its supply to other countries https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/24sjxxRXN8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden sets new goal to get at least one vaccine shot to 70% of the U.S. adult population by July 4th: "no one should wait" https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/KzxRcsGYut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We're going to it make easier than ever to get vaccinated," says Biden https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/wFnuuVAFSf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pres. Biden announces new COVID-19 vaccination goals and a three-phase focus:  1. Kids between the ages of 12-15 2. Making it easier to get a shot by allowing walk-ins 3. Moving from mass vaccine sites to smaller sites  https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/qV25XbcMuh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What we know about the "unprecedented" U.S. Capitol riot arrests https://t.co/HDyY1yC0qD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Biden sets goal of fully vaccinating 160 million adults by July 4 https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/MLUiRXvtu2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden administration to shift the way COVID vaccine is supplied to states https://t.co/m39cEe7rfe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. companies are stealing pay from low-wage workers, report says https://t.co/xKhZx7TWZu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Restaurants face nationwide chicken shortage https://t.co/RKqS1aJSQo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man dies after being shot by FBI agent outside CIA headquarters https://t.co/YnzQTF00RR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On recent state laws banning transgender youth from playing sports, Psaki says the president will continue to "convey that transgender rights are human rights," but when asked if the administration will take any legal actions, Psaki defers to the Department of Justice https://t.co/WAMmNauleX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This is not the totality of what the president hopes to do," says Psaki when asked why Biden's families plan offers only 2 years of community college tuition instead of his campaign proposal of free college/university tuition for students from families making less than $125,000 https://t.co/5PAxzfCXpR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rocket debris from China's space station launch is hurtling back to Earth  and scientists aren't sure where it will land https://t.co/U39Ahc2s3j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheDebriefCBS: NEW: 2020 was a tumultuous year. 1945 was almost certainly worse. This week, with the help of authors and historians, @M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ahead of Pres. Biden's remarks on vaccine hesitancy later today, CBS News' Weijia Jiang asks the WH press secretary what data the WH is seeing on why people are holding out on getting the vaccine. Psaki says, "the biggest challenge is access" https://t.co/HPYAapFHWL https://t.co/t2gxYkYh4B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Jonas opens up about "amazing" time at home with baby daughter, why there are 250 replicas of his right hand https://t.co/VuaMbkQFnV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook will make a decision this week on whether to reinstate fmr. Pres. Trump's account. When asked if Trump rejoining and expressing his views on the platform will change how the Biden administration runs things, Psaki gives a simple "no" https://t.co/H9n7JKbYS7 https://t.co/1gqbQ3Zypc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is the Biden administration doing everything it can to help India deal with its escalating COVID-19 situation? WH Press sec Psaki says "we are in close touch" and summarizes the supplies, equipment and assistance sent to India from the U.S. https://t.co/H9n7JKbYS7 https://t.co/ec1rjAMedw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Psaki reiterates that reports over the weekend about the release of four Americans held hostage in Iran are "not true" but says that is an issue being "raised at the highest level" https://t.co/H9n7JKbYS7 https://t.co/W6zNmIcsuv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Returning Bruce's Beach in California to the Black family who originally owned it https://t.co/0jgGz6Fi0v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: WH Press Secretary holds briefing with press https://t.co/H9n7JKbYS7 https://t.co/uGtcdG3GAr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Towns and cities around Myanmar saw protests on Sunday that left at least five people dead. These protests come three months on from a military takeover of the country. https://t.co/M5OYI1oLtH https://t.co/iuv8rXeRyR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID is killing 120 people an hour in India, and it could stay "really grim" for months https://t.co/DMNZqmTwg5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSThisMorning: Chicago is one of the most segregated cities in America, but "My Block, My Hood, My City" is bridging those divides by]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senior Swiss diplomat in Iran falls to her death from high-rise home in Tehran https://t.co/RO7WOcwVxV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Belgian farmer was annoyed by the stone in his tractor's path. He moved it and the French border https://t.co/ALUFxDZD6Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drone video shows an unfinished section of the barrier along the U.S.-Mexico border. President Biden ordered an immediate halt to wall construction on his first day in office. https://t.co/M7eFkpw48C https://t.co/IBury22HxI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India's cricket league postpones season indefinitely as COVID crisis worsens https://t.co/9ENtlajOs9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A probationary DC Metro Police officer was fired and three others are being investigated after a reckless driving incident that left two police vehicles badly damaged. https://t.co/Zq0zy8KVAt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: AG Garland testifies on 2022 budget request https://t.co/77Xk2rjeI8 https://t.co/xfUAXGIdqS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women sue LAPD after officers handcuffed and held them at gunpoint during a traffic stop https://t.co/fHKQyfENVs]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>