<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[In a pandemic, confusing government messages about #COVID19 vaccines arent helpful: @globeandmail editorial https://t.co/IXpWUkaMXo #cdnpoli #vaccination #RiskCommunication]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RitaTrichur: Please read this column by my colleague @picardonhealth  It is bang on about so much.  Opinion: Fixing long-term care in O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DTFinegood @CBCVancouver and not using the word "complicated"! :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrFahadRazak: With angst re NACI, very helpful interview with @picardonhealth. I'm one of the scientists guilty of 'dancing on the head]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@cdavidnaylor delivers a Master Class on #COVID19 vaccines and, firmly but politely, tells us everything that is wrong with NACI's muddled messaging.  #vaccination #RiskCommunication https://t.co/Yyjuu0H250]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ltamblynwatts: BREAKING: hugs are back for #LongTermCare residents! Revised Directive #3 released today also allows communal dining and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We may never achieve long-term global #HerdImmunity for #COVID19. But if we're all vaccinated, we'll be safe from the worst, by @GidMK  https://t.co/YQDFImZuP3 via @ConversationEDU #vaccination #GlobalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['We have to protect our hospitals' -- @jkenney. Alberta introduces sweeping measures to stop #COVID19, including shifting all students to online learning and closing all workplaces with outbreaks.   https://t.co/vjROnSanZq via @cbcnews #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: From the annals of vaccine inequity:  12 year olds in high-income countries might get vaccinated in a few weeks/months  72 ye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The kids are not all right: Educators worry about absences as #COVID19 challenges continue for parents, students, by @calphonso  https://t.co/Ie9H9gLP7X via @globeandmail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Germanys Anti-vaccination History Is Riddled With #AntiSemitism. Jewish people were blamed for spreading disease, and considered expendable victims, by @jacobinoire https://t.co/SsQTRcBM1I via @TheAtlantic #COVID19 #antivax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its Not #VaccineHesitancy. Its #COVID19 Denialism. Reluctance to get vaccinated is concentrated among young conservatives, who are skeptical of the pandemics harms, by @GrahamDavidA https://t.co/RxnZu8CcUD via @TheAtlHealth #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Millions Are Saying No to the Vaccines. What Are They Thinking? Feelings about the vaccine are intertwined with feelings about the pandemic, and a worldview, by @DKThomp https://t.co/i0JtMyvGlw via @TheAtlHealth #COVID19 #vaccination #antivax #VaccineHesitancy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For the second day running, Ontarios embattled long-term-care minister @DrFullertonMPP refuses to say the s-word -- sorry -- about the carnage in #LTC, by @robferguson1   https://t.co/mRyPUbHaNT via @torontostar @NeglectedNo  #onpoli #eldercare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexGelle: Qubec now has its own version of the @VaxHuntersCan!  Vacclrateur (@vaccelerateur) tracks available last minute vaccine s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wise words from science communicator extraordinaire @jayingram #COVID19 #scicomm #RiskCommunication https://t.co/HY63tC8DJW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disbanding NACI is not the answer. They do important and valuable work. They just need help with how to deliver messages to the public, as opposed to other scientists. https://t.co/fusphzgcCC  #COVID19 #vaccination #RiskCommunication https://t.co/7Wx7ImOduT https://t.co/DV44t2okSn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PM Justin Trudeau urges Canadians to get #COVID19 vaccinations as soon as possible, despite expert panels confusing advice that some could wait, by @TondaMacC @aballinga  https://t.co/5fmm421x1h via @torontostar #cdnpoli #vaccination #RiskCommunication]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The West Has Been Hoarding More Than Vaccines, by @WaldenBello  https://t.co/QZjIsPdFr7 via @NYTopinion #COVID19 #vaccination #TRIPSwaiver #GlobalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seven questions you shouldnt ask an #Indigenous person, by @TheDHTaylor  https://t.co/iiys6Fj4qH via  @GlobeDebate https://t.co/K43V4epycL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GERONursing: @IRPP @picardonhealth @DrSamirSinha @prof_TamaraDaly Please consider including perspectives from not-Ontario in your futur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The impacts of catching COVID are far greater and far deadlier' -- PM, top doc try to calm fears, say all vaccines are safe and effective after NACI guidance causes confusion, by @JPTasker  https://t.co/68tqknRJvz via @cbcnews #COVID19 #vaccination #RiskCommunication]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada's big for-profit long-term care home operators -- Extendicare, Sienna, Chartwell -- pay their top execs millions in 2020 bonuses despite #COVID19 deaths, by @davidmilstead  https://t.co/IzfLYS5xHk via @globebusiness @NeglectedNo #LTC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CaulfieldTim: The headline that many Canadians saw this AM.   Yep. My first reaction was AAAARGH (and then sh*t!).  This messaging hurt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why people dont drink: Its none of your business, by @picardonhealth (2017) https://t.co/17UWyrNOLx via @GlobeDebate https://t.co/ZnPTu0DwtA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: Since the vaccine rollout began, only 1.3% of new #COVID19 cases in Canada have been in people who have received at lea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pharmacists association disappointed, worried NACI advice will stoke #COVID19 #VaccineHesitancy, by @mrabson https://t.co/svpkvJD2vJ via @globeandmail #vaccination #scicomm #RiskCommunication]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NathanStall: "Prior to #COVID19, there was no plan to improve the lives of elders in care. Thousands of deaths later, there is still no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is NACI's messaging about vaccines so confusing? Q+A w/ @picardonhealth, by @michelle_eliot  https://t.co/aHQ74EU1kX via @cbcvancouver @LesliBoldt #COVID19 #vaccination #scicomm #RiskCommunication   https://t.co/OxsYzDxNxh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cmckenney: Over 800 Registered! Join me along with @picardonhealth @MoiraWelsh @moadam_ #SusanZorz #MaryConnell How do we ensure the we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario #LTC Minister @DrFullertonMPP back in isolation after brief exposure to accountability https://t.co/Hrzm79Hebu via @TheBeaverton @johnadams51677 #COVID19 #onpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@martinlaroche13 Merci!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CU__Trust: .@picardonhealth talks about when we might be able to vaccinate kids, and why he's optimistic about schools opening in Septe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheGlobeEvents: Happening now:  The Globe's @picardonhealth is hosting our webinar on curbing the rise of chronic illness in Canada. #P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pfizer forecasts $26-billion (U.S.) from annual sales of #Covid19 vaccine. Vaccine will generate 73% more than forecast based on contracts signed until mid-April, by @JuliaKollewe  https://t.co/br3Rg6wWkC via @guardian #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta to announce new public-health measures amid highest #COVID19 rates in North America. Explosive third wave threatens to overwhelm hospital system, Premier @jkenney warns, @byJamesKeller  https://t.co/wzz6b7dxYm via @globeandmail #cdnhealth #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Post-vaccine recuperation.  https://t.co/EfbVMQsbTS via @NewYorker #COVID19 #vaccination https://t.co/8vlS6cWQvE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What makes #COVID19 vaccine skeptics change their minds? The White House and public health experts studied Americans who went from no to yes on shots, and learned some important lessons, by @ddiamond  https://t.co/cTqvW6RuuR via @washingtonpost #vaccination #VaccineHesitancy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Coronavirus Hell of @jkenney's Own Making. The #COVID19 devil runs free, yet again, in Alberta and the premier has no excuse, by Andrew Nikiforuk https://t.co/MWSHFHqGJe  via @TheTyee @DennisKendel #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This thread on NACI's recommendations on AstraZeneca vaccine is worth re-reading now that NACI has issued similar advice about the Johnson  Johnson vaccine. #COVID19 #vaccination #RiskCommunication https://t.co/nBaRDuiJvM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SabiVM: Have received so many concerned messages from people who I recommended get vaccinated with AZ just last week.   Ill be honest,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grief and stress through three waves of the #COVID19 pandemic are taking their toll on front-line health-care workers, especially nurses and doctors in intensive care, and some are getting out, by @MarianneKlowak https://t.co/qJyjCrjpD2 via @cbcnews @GRDrobot #cdnhealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Commission probing long-term care says for-profit companies can build LTC homes but should no longer be in charge of care, by @kahowlett https://t.co/UxlUdblzwd via @globeandmail @NeglectedNo #onpoli #eldercare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry seems to be the hardest word: Long-term-care minister @DrFullertonMPP wont apologize for Ontarios slow and reactive #COVID19 response, despite scathing report, by @robferguson1   https://t.co/EiqiDEYwOq via  @torontostar #onpoli #LTC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a Ford government without shame, long-term-care minister @DrFullertonMPP offers more disgrace under pressure, by @bruce_arthur  https://t.co/Se8mzp5h1U via @torontostar @HowardOvens #COVID19 #onpoli #LTC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uoftmedicine: Practice physical distancing, you must.  #MayThe4thBeWithYou https://t.co/HOi3aruxCM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: [a sexplique] - La troisime vague de #COVID19, un dfi de taille pour lOntario, avec le chroniqueur  @picardonheal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pandemic has undeniably caused extraordinary stress and sadness, but our brains will bounce back from #Covid19, by @raf_ideas https://t.co/DM4UmUHQQX via @NYTopinion #resilience #MentalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teenagers Are Struggling, and Its Not Just Lockdown, by @EmEsfahaniSmith  https://t.co/sCvw9hBSre via @NYTopinion #COVID19 #MentalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La mort peut attendre. En raison de la #COVID19, Benot Pelletier, lancien ministre des Affaires intergouvernementales a t plong dans un coma dont il a failli ne jamais se rveiller, par @ihachey   https://t.co/G647EUUv9l via @lp_lapresse https://t.co/wNwm9Rn4o3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When can we stop wearing masks?The U.S. has loosened its rules about masks. When will it be Canada's turn? by @prisksh https://t.co/eoibmx8eMm via @cbcnews #COVID19 #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The human machine: A #COVID19 outbreak at an Alberta slaughterhouse claimed 3 lives. A year later, at another plant, it happened again, by @joeldryden @sarahcrgr  https://t.co/DJqkfDaz9W via @cbcnews #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Torontos city-run #LTC homes had a peak mortality rate less than half that of for-profit homes. #COVID19 shows the value of keeping public services in public hands, by @GraphicMatt  https://t.co/K34UlgWtRA via @torontostar @NeglectedNo #onpoli #eldercare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the hell, NACI? #COVID19 vaccines work, with small risks. The vaccine messaging is awful, with huge risks, by @bruce_arthur  https://t.co/pNeXO8n59z via @torontostar #vaccination #scicomm #RiskCommunication]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Which #COVID19 vaccine should you get? Canadas expert panel says, That depends ..., by @TondaMacC  https://t.co/K2Sg6ylsSh via @torontostar #cdnpoli #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadian scientists face a faster, more competitive world after #COVID19. The pandemic 'dramatically altered the scientific landscape by accelerating both the pace and scale of research, @cca_reports report says, by @IvanSemeniuk   https://t.co/RTuz3PPYBI via @globeandmail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Generation Z cannot become Generation #COVID19: For an entire swath of teens and 20-somethings, the pandemic has stolen a crucial part of growing up, by @GZN_oguz https://t.co/tIfLiWBZrc via @GlobeDebate https://t.co/SJHzsPx3WZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The one-shot Johnson  Johnson vaccine should be offered only to people 30 or older who dont want to wait for access to the Pfizer or Moderna vaccines, an expert panel says, by @kellygrant1 @MariekeWalsh  https://t.co/ID6cO1WzUk via @globeandmail #COVID19 #cdnpoli #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: The reports keep coming but so do the vague responses: Its looking increasingly like Ontario has no interest in fixing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @perreaux: Great thread. Weve all had to come to terms with the fact the experts, whether part of government bodies or not, have often]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MDMA as a tool in treating mental illness. Q+A w/ Dr. Evan Wood of @BCCSU https://t.co/OICOvZ9mBG via @TheCurrentCBC @mattgallowaycbc #psychedelics #PTSD #MentalHealth https://t.co/gaNYMo8LUX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Psychedelic Drug Passes a Big Test for #PTSD Treatment. A new study shows that #MDMA, known as Ecstasy or Molly, can bring relief when paired with talk therapy, by @RachelNuwer  https://t.co/7xlKxzQXHW via @NYThealth #psychedelics #MentalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Advisory committee #NACI continues its confusing messaging, saying Canadians 30+ can get Johnson  Johnson vaccine or hold out for another shot if they're worried about blood clots, by @adamsmiller  https://t.co/8Pq70sk6Ev via @cbchealth #COVID19 #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry' seems to be the hardest word: Long-term-care minister @DrFullertonMPP wont apologize for Ontarios slow and reactive #COVID19 response, despite scathing report, by @robferguson1  https://t.co/FrAGYswPdp via @torontostar #onpoli #LTC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Broken marriages becoming pandemic's other toll. Isolation giving many couples the time the needed to figure out things aren't right, by @HallieCBC  https://t.co/wDVQyvUi8j via @cbcnews #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The worlds longest-imprisoned journalist deserves justice. Dawit Isaak has been held in solitary confinement in Eritrea for 19 years, without any charge or trial.   https://t.co/bI2b701FQi via @GlobeDebate @RSF_inter #JournalismIsNotACrime  #WorldPressFreedomDay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dgardner: If I were writing a chapter on risk communication, I would use what NACI has done to illustrate every possible mistake.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScienceUpFirst:  Les gens ont bien plus peur dtre attaqus par un requin que de se noyer, pourtant le risque de ltre est moins gra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario #LTC Minister @DrFullertonMPP responds to scathing report on #COVID19 response by vaguely promising change, blaming previous governments, by @kahowlett https://t.co/LNiXoNyeEl via @globeandmail @NeglectedNo #onpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@BillGates and @melindagates are getting a divorce, a split that is likely to send shockwaves through the worlds of philanthropy, global health and business via @NYTimes  https://t.co/psEw9BHy1j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The reports keep coming but so do the vague responses: Its looking increasingly like Ontario has no interest in fixing long-term care, by @picardonhealth via @GlobeDebate @NeglectedNo #COVID19 #onpoli #LTC #eldercare  https://t.co/DvgEqadGjD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: Finally got my first dose of #COVID19 vaccine!  (Moderna.) Vaccin (et majeur)! https://t.co/s4Cs8VJyTa #vaccination ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBCQueensPark: I asked Minister @DrFullertonMPP if she or her government is going to apologize for what happened in long-term care. In]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Economic resilience is another way  of saying were not following restrictions , by @ParkinsonGlobe  https://t.co/UuPu9pvVlr via @globebusiness #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brent_T_Jolly: Here's the FULL list of 2020 @CAJ award nominees.   Shout-out to our remarkable team, especially committee chair @markus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Congratulations to the finalists for the CWA/CAJ Award for Labour Reporting:   @sarahcrgr @joeldrydenCBC Calgary  @ctvw5 team]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jana_pruden: I love journalism awards season, as a time to see and celebrate some of the amazing journalism being done in this country,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Congratulations to the finalists for the Student Award of Excellence:   @bykarinazapata, @nathanw_yycCalgary Journal, Mount Roya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Congratulations to our Written News finalists:    @shanifanasserCBC Toronto @Aaron_DerfelMontreal Gazette @mollyhayesGlobe a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Congratulations to our Written Feature finalists:   @Jane_GersterGlobal News  @JamesBagnall1Ottawa Citizen  @BruceDeachmanOt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Congratulations to the finalists for the APTN/CAJ Reconciliation Award:  @zoehtennantCBC Radio  @writermjs The Narwhal   @poi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Here are our Data Journalism finalists/Voici nos finalistes, Journalism de donnes: @cbcnews team  @cbcmarketplace team  @phil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caj: Congratulations to our Daily Excellence finalists:   @CBCNS team  @jmbryden, @JimBronskillCanadian Press   @jwsthomsonThe Nar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenBranswell: .@WHO Director-General @DrTedros is seeking a second term. Remains to be seen if he will be challenged. https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine shortages blight Indiasefforts to contain #Covid19 crisis. Indian government accused of complacency, with shortage of jabs likely to continue for months, by @HannahEP https://t.co/E6z79hgbPc via @guardian #vaccination #GlobalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How two young math geeks solved the mystery of Mexico Citys #Covid19 dead.  Everyone suspected the official death count was too low; two citizen sleuths unearthed the startling truth, by @marybsheridan   https://t.co/I3jdGJr5cq via @washingtonpost]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than a year into the pandemic, were still figuring out what risks were willing to take, and forced to play the role of amateur epidemiologist, by @JoelAchenbach  https://t.co/pZWhopNRir via @washingtonpost #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario Long-term care minister @DrFullertonMPP dodges questions in 1st press conference since scathing report on #LTC released. "We were overdue for a pandemic," she said at a 20-minute news conference, by @Samantha_KB   https://t.co/GqHgAb8FzU via @cbcnews #COVID19 #onpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['It's a mess' -- Site crashes, technical errors and long lines marked the opening of vaccine booking for people 18+ in Ontario hot spots, by @RhythmSachdeva  https://t.co/d8N5XF3qYP via @torontostar #COVID19 #onpoli #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More people are dying of overdoses in B.C. than of #COVID19. Government negligence is on full display, by @mlgagnon_XVII  https://t.co/O2iC0rOAwz via @georgiastraight @tlupick #opioids #HarmReduction]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How many more images of #Covid19 disaster does it take to jolt rich countries into action? The crisis in India forced the west to respond. But without an ambitious  plan, other nations may suffer similar fates, by @NesrineMalik https://t.co/vMXGAxj8pI via @guardian #GlobalHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reaching #HerdImmunity Is Unlikely in the U.S., Experts Now Believe. Widely circulating #coronavirus variants and persistent #VaccineHesitancy will keep the goal out of reach, by @apoorva_nyc  https://t.co/ptRM2FB23u via @nytimes #COVID19 #vaccination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigerian investigative reporter Tobore Ovuorie (@DaughterOfMit) receives DW's Freedom of Speech Award for defending the voiceless, work that almost cost her her life. https://t.co/ilFJaAaC0N via @DeutscheWelle @journalismforum #JournalismIsNotACrime #WorldPressFreedomDay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[April was a brutal month in the battle against the #COVID19 pandemic, but May will be the month when Canada breaks the back of the pandemic:  @globeandmail editorial https://t.co/r1azsonheX #cdnhealth #cdnpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont you dare ask for forgiveness:  A new report has laid bare the innumerable ways the most fragile among us have been betrayed and neglected during the pandemic, by @RDiManno   https://t.co/4stIO7Buqp via @torontostar @NeglectedNo #LTC #eldercare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario failed to act on surveys of long-term care homes ahead of deadly second #COVID19 wave, #LTC commission says, by @kahowlett  https://t.co/VvZjRA9gUJ via @globeandmail @NeglectedNo #onpoli #eldercare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les employeurs ont un rle  jouer dans la campagne de #vaccination, en utilisant des carottes, ou des btons, par @PhilMercure    https://t.co/CtGACHzciP via @lp_lapresse #COVID19 #qcpoli https://t.co/B9zWbIrrMs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Fertility treatments should be considered essential, say patients. Pandemic closures have set some patients back months, by @KimberleyMolina https://t.co/Dfx13m9MBI via @cbcnews #COVID19 #cdnhealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta Health Services exploring legal options after hundreds attend rodeo that was billed as an anti-lockdown event, by @sarahcrgr  https://t.co/L07vW1usT8 via @cbcnews #COVID19 #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColetteB: "The new data serve as a reminder that the first dose doesnt provide foolproof protection against severe outcomes of COVID-1]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>