<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[We endorse this statement,  the authenticity of the information. We have been working closely with the Government of India for the past year  thank it for its support. We remain committed to ramping up our vaccine production to save every life we can. https://t.co/tLVPjOMp51]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: As a philanthropic gesture on behalf of @SerumInstIndia, I hereby reduce the price to the states from Rs.400 to Rs.300]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CMOMaharashtra: CM Uddhav Balasaheb Thackeray has been assured of maximum support by Mr. @adarpoonawalla and the Serum Institute of Ind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We at @SerumInstIndia have for the past five decades been at the forefront of supplying vaccines and saving lives globally. We care about and respect every human life and strongly believe in transparency, and thus we hope our statement below can clear any confusions. https://t.co/YQ3x38BuFL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNBCTV18Live: #CNBCTV18Exclusive | @adarpoonawalla, @SerumInstIndia says, Rs 400/dose is the price for centre  states now https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT ANNOUNCEMENT https://t.co/bTsMs8AKth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Results from the U.S. based Phase III trial of @AstraZenecas Covid-19 vaccine show 79% efficacy against symptomatic disease and 100% efficacy against severe disease and hospitalization.   Read detailed report here: https://t.co/UjjUbf3QPY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MSuzman @SandhuTaranjitS @gatesfoundation @gavi @serumin Respected sir, we thank you for those kind words, on behalf of our CEO @adarpoonawalla and our team at Serum Institute of India. @SerumInstIndia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @yd_tweets: Thank You @SerumInstIndia for becoming savior for millions of people including His Holiness The XIVth #DalaiLama.   His Holi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: Dear Honble PM @JustinTrudeau, I thank you for your warm words towards India and its vaccine industry. As we await re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tradegovukIND: .@SerumInstIndias collaboration with @AstraZeneca @UniofOxford #Covid_19 vaccine is addressing our greatest global hea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: It was an honour to have the Secretary of State for International Trade, UK,@trusslizand a delegation visit our headq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trussliz: Met @adarpoonawalla at world's largest vaccine producer @SerumInstIndia on   collaboration and trade.  They have made 100]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drharshvardhan: Pleased to have met CMD, @SerumInstIndia, Sh Cyrus Poonawalla Ji  Exec Director, SII, Smt @NPoonawalla Ji, today.  We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VPSecretariat: Shri Cyrus S. Poonawalla, Chairman and Managing Director,  @SerumInstIndia, and Smt @NPoonawalla, Executive Director, ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are truly honoured and grateful to be  a crucial part of the world's largest vaccination drive @drharshvardhan @MoHFW_INDIA under the visionary leadership of Shri @narendramodi Ji. https://t.co/VWf2pZVHWs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Announcement of another #COVID19 vaccine, #COVOVAX from our CEO, @adarpoonawalla https://t.co/DAfyiQDNZc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: Thank you Shri Uddhav Ji @CMOMaharashtra and @AUThackeray for visiting @SerumInstIndia and extending your help and supp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you, for your condolences Hon. PM Shri @narendramodi Ji, for the lives lost today at the unfortunate incident. https://t.co/fRMy3aaDUj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We would like to extend our gratitude to everyone for their concerns and prayers in these distressing times."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...situated at the Special Economic Zone at Manjri.   We are deeply saddened and offer our condolences to the families of the departed. In this regard, we will be offering a compensation of INR 25 lakhs to each of the families, in addition to the mandated amount as per the norms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Statement From Cyrus S. Poonawalla, Chairman  Managing Director, Serum Institute of India.  "Today is an extremely sorrowful day for all of us at Serum Institute of India. Regrettably, there were losses of lives in the fire that broke out in our under installation facility... https://t.co/QJLofvwGRV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT UPDATE https://t.co/m4geL0fpkd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Statement from our CEO, @adarpoonawalla. https://t.co/LGdpN4X1Mq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: Thank you everyone for your concern and prayers. So far the most important thing is that there have been no lives lost]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO @adarpoonawalla leading from the front, by taking a jab of #COVISHIELD to endorse its efficacy and safety. #largestVaccinationdrive https://t.co/w8bptvu26T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ndtv: #NDTVExclusive | The first 10 crore doses of the #Covishield vaccine have been purchased by the government for a special price of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Teamwork #Covishield #IndiaFightsCorona #SII https://t.co/ST2oovkqcf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important Announcement: Joint statement @BharatBiotech and @SerumInstIndia https://t.co/la5av27Mqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ETNOWlive: #MegaETNOWExclusive | I will take the vaccine as soon as @SerumInstIndia's #Covishield is officially licensed by DCGI and wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNBCTV18News: 'Restricted to export vaccine or sell in pvt mkt under current licence for now,' says @adarpoonawalla CEO @SerumInstIndia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themojo_in: Adar Poonawalla @adarpoonawalla on Serum Institute's Oxford AstraZeneca Vaccine with @bdutt https://t.co/3df77aia5Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you, Hon. @PMOIndia Sri @narendramodi ji, for your support. https://t.co/moE5cuh8XR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy New Year! https://t.co/j4N10RE3Xc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrHVoffice: Watch Now!  Union Minister Dr Harsh Vardhan inaugurates the 7th National Summit on Good, Replicable Practices  Innovations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT UPDATE https://t.co/M8LNzmJ6Xl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: It will be my honour and privilege tonight, to address over a hundred world leaders and nations at the @UN special sess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Addressing concerns related to the adverse event reported by volunteer in Chennai, Serum Institute of India shared;  Read Here - https://t.co/QUVv7LBe3D https://t.co/07BDFdEefC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adar Poonawalla Speaks About COVISHIELD - Live https://t.co/nN52Be0xIi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: I am delighted to hear that, Covishield, a low-cost, logistically manageable  soon to be widely available, #COVID19 va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Data of the Phase 2 trials of the @UniofOxford vaccine in the UK reveals that it appears to produce a strong immune response among older adults and has similar immunogenicity across all groups. Read more here: https://t.co/ykwf3zPoxP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: Definition of a good vaccine = 1. Safe  2. Offers long-term protection against targetted disease 3. Can be transported]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SII has announced the completion of enrolment of Phase III clinical trials for COVISHIELD vaccine in India, under the partnership of Serum Institute of India andIndian Council of Medical Research(ICMR).  Read To Know More -https://t.co/0NrpTjjOXx https://t.co/apI5T9DroD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: Now there are clear reports of the terrible long-term effects of COVID19, so dont feel you can get it once and that wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: It gives me great pride representing India at the @ParisPeaceForum, on its invaluable contribution on how to end this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: A lot of people were wondering and asking the question, will these early vaccines be effective for the elderly and most]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important Announcement:   @IAVI, @merckgroup (@EMDSerono) and @SerumInstIndia Join Forces to Develop Monoclonal Antibodies for #COVID19 and Ensure Prompt and Equitable Global Access  Read More Here: https://t.co/NyL1NsEtwY https://t.co/e48CIU5Em5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GaviSeth: Delighted that the collaboration between @SerumInstIndia, @Gavi and @gatesfoundation will now accelerate the manufacture and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Further to our August announcement of delivering 100 million doses with our global partners, we are aiming to produce up to an additional 100 million safe and effective COVID-19 vaccine doses (total now 200 million doses).   Read more: https://t.co/fyS58H27vU  #SII #Latestnews https://t.co/pRDZgyy4HA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update https://t.co/xuA2GF1wCI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: As Id mentioned earlier, we should not jump to conclusions until the trials are fully concluded. The recent chain of e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are reviewing the situation and pausing India trials till @AstraZeneca restarts them. We are following DCGI's instructions and will not be able to comment further on the same. You can connect with DCGI for more updates on this front.  #SII #Latestnews #Covid_19 https://t.co/CUeFY5oLus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We (Serum Institute of India), were going by DCGI's direction and were not instructed to pause thetrials. If DCGI has any safety concerns, we will adhere to their instructions and abide by the standard protocols. https://t.co/u0yaGAU0Eo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We (Serum Institute of India) can't comment on reports of AstraZeneca pausing the trials in the UK, other than that they have been paused for review and shall restart soon. The Indian trials are continuing and we have faced no issues at all.  #SII #COVID19 #Latestnews https://t.co/HWPUrQydWc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: The origins of the Oxford vaccine with Professor Adrian Hill; standing next to the legendary Edward Jenner statue, here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: I would kindly request the media to refrain, from reporting on interim data coming in about patients on the SII - Covis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: A well deserved award, and much needed recognition for the entrepreneurs of @MylabSolutions, who rose to the occasion i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We would like to clarify that the current media claim on COVISHIELD's availability in 73 days is misleading.   Phase-3 trials are still underway. We will officially confirm its availability.  Read clarification statement here - https://t.co/FvgClzcnHr  #SII #COVID19 #LatestNews https://t.co/mQWrqgbzO4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saving lives Immunising people Improving over all well-being  Our continuous commitment towards the nation and the world has led to envisioning a positive and robust future.  Wishing everyone a very Happy Independence Day.  #SII #IndependenceDay #IndependenceDayIndia2020 https://t.co/e4WMamHhno]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Novavax: We are proud to announce a collaboration with @SerumInstIndia to develop and commercialize our #COVID19 #vaccine candidate for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gatesfoundation: This collaboration with @SerumInstIndia and @Gavi will help ensure every country, not just the wealthy few, will hav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NPoonawalla: .@SerumInstIndia and everyone involved is committed to see this project through. More on the roadmap here...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TwitterMoments: The worlds largest vaccine producer, the Serum Institute in India, plans to mass-produce an unproven COVID-19 vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GaviSeth: As @adarpoonawalla rightly says, to ensure maximum immunization coverage and contain the pandemic, it is important to make s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GaviSeth: Thank you @adarpoonawalla for setting a great example of how vaccine manufacturers can help ensure the worlds poorest countr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gavi: We are pleased to announce that we are collaborating with the @SerumInstIndia and the @GatesFoundation to accelerate manufacturin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adarpoonawalla: I would like to thank @BillGates, @gatesfoundation, @GaviSeth for this key partnership of risk sharing and manufacturin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Being the worlds largest vaccine manufacturer by number of doses produced and sold globally, we have always aimed at protecting lives. SII assures quick decisions and undertakes enormous risks, such as our fight against COVID-19.  https://t.co/whwR1oy7t5  #SII #COVID19 #vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have always aimed at saving lives with our Hepatitis vaccines covering everyone across the globe.  On World Hepatitis Day, #TogetherWeFight to voice out to protect the world from this virus for a better tomorrow.  #SII #WorldHepatitisDay #EliminateHepatitis https://t.co/7VSJNt3OVP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, is leaving no stone unturned to launch Covishield vaccine as early as possible.   #SII #Covid_19 #CoronaVirusUpdate #vaccine https://t.co/6fyeSain9c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We hope to manufacture two to three million doses by end of August, pending certain licensing and approvals from the government.  https://t.co/mMSoYf99DE  #SII #Covid_19 #vaccine #coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, in conversation with @Zakka_Jacob on @CNNnews18 discusses how the vaccine is likely to be released in December or first quarter of 2021, pending necessary approvals from the government.  #SII #Covid_19 #COVID19Update #vaccines https://t.co/NpnGQyX86A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, in conversation with @ETNOWlive, says, We saw a good T-cell response which means people will have long-term protection coming about.  https://t.co/GDT5pnO3UX  #SII #Covid_19 #vaccines #coronavirus #COVIDUpdates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We hope to begin phase three of the human trials of COVID-19 vaccine in India in August, which will see around 4,000  5,000 volunteers.  https://t.co/yrkL7mLrPw  #SII #COVID19Update #vaccine #coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kiranshaw: Adar Poonawalla on Oxford Hope: 300 Million Doses of 'Covishield' Corona... https://t.co/UWekzYlHN1 via @YouTube one of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In conversation with @CNBCTV18News, our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, says, It is safe with mild reactions like fever which is expected of any vaccine. It does not cause any severe side effects, so safety is definitely proven.  https://t.co/yXowksRKYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, in conversation with @BDUTT, says, We are very well poised and will be playing a major role, because of our capacity and ability to produce.  #SII #Covid_19 #coronavirus #vaccines https://t.co/RetKeZuA6J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covishield will be launched if the trials are successful in UK and India. Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, says at least 300 million doses of the potential vaccine will be ready by December 2020.   https://t.co/KmOFIJnc52  #SII #COVID #vaccines #CoronavirusVaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Along with the efforts of @UniofOxford and @AstraZeneca , SII hopes to start phase three trials in India soon.  #SII #COVID19Update #VaccineTrials https://t.co/mUjPcyWSdw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla in conversation with @BDUTT  throws light on the takeaways of the COVID-19 vaccine.   #SII #COVID19 #COVID19Update #CovidVaccine #coronavirus https://t.co/dA1tVDAQMM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As everyone is fighting with COVID-19, Oxford vaccine and SII give some positivity to the people, as it (the vaccine) shows promising results and provides immunity in 14 days of the first dose.  https://t.co/LQLXxT6y6U  #SII #Covid_19 #vaccine #coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[. @Naveen_Odisha CM of Odisha congratulates our CEO, @adarpoonawalla for the promising results shown by the COVID-19 vaccine.  #SII #COVID19 #Vaccine https://t.co/FMr6DQntY4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Speaking in an exclusive interview with @IndiaToday, our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, throws light and give insights into COVID-19 vaccine.   https://t.co/bwKPOMuGXb  #SII #Covid_19 #vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our CEO, @adarpoonawalla, interacts with the CM of Odisha, @Naveen_Odisha, for giving an update on the COVID-19 vaccine and looks forward to helping the state to meet all its vaccination needs.   #SII #COVID19 #COVID19Update #vaccine https://t.co/Bg0nCoAvNb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the Oxford vaccine offers a ray of hope among the people to fight this pandemic, SII is all set to seek regulatory approvals for clinical trials in India and begin manufacturing billion doses of the vaccine soon.  https://t.co/G0Busd3U96  #SII #COVID19 #vaccine #coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Naveen_Odisha, CM of Odisha congratulates our CEO, @adarpoonawalla for the promising results shown by COVID-19 vaccine.   #SII #COVID19 #vaccine #coronavirus https://t.co/FMr6DQntY4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We thank all the doctors for offering us their selfless  empathetic services and ensuring the well-being of humankind. #SII #NationalDoctorsDay2020 #doctorsday2020 https://t.co/OmzWrW3Fwx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 vaccine update: We are aiming to get 20-40 million vaccine shots available to the Indian market by September-October at an affordable price of 1,000/ dose.   https://t.co/GHAPQUd2UU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are extremely thrilled to share that Serum Institute of India has not one but two vaccine candidates in its arsenal against the novel coronavirus (Covid-19). Both candidates are likely to enter human trials in India by September-October.  https://t.co/bcL50eTOIY #SII #Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A vaccine to combat COVID-19 in the pipeline to be ready by 2021. https://t.co/BqdAaiJnIh #SII #Vaccine #coronavirus #covid19 #coronavirusvaccine https://t.co/L5rLB4oL1S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amidst the crisis, the research and development team at Serum decides on testing the tuberculosis vaccine for boosting immunity against coronavirus. https://t.co/AQJLiixY76 #SII #Vaccine #Coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We'll start manufacturing at great cost and risk so that we get a head start on a vaccine that MAY work. https://t.co/Kh2S2GQcHk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serum Institute of India in the development phase for Live Attenuated Vaccines(LAV) to combat the pandemic. https://t.co/oL8V3UTHWk #SII #Vaccine #Coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a first of its kind collaboration, Serum Institute of India and New York-based Codagenix Inc co-develop a live-attenuated vaccine(LAV) that is nearly as strong as that triggered by an infection with the wild-type pathogen. Read on to know more.  https://t.co/w7FhCkHmXe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the Coronavirus outbreak intensifies across the country, the #government has designated #test centers in various states. Heres listing down the testing facilities currently authorized to test in the country. Contact them at the earliest in case of developing symptoms.  #SII https://t.co/RWAvHhPun1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Researchers and scientists from around the world are racing against time to develop a vaccine against the virus. Until then we urge you to strictly follow personal hygiene measures and practice social distancing to keep yourself safe and healthy. #SII #vaccine https://t.co/YNQgY5IS0o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As per WHO officials, healthy people dont need to wear masks. Only when a person develops a cough and fever, he/she becomes a suspected patient and needs to switch to medical masks to prevent the spread of the virus. Here are some dos and donts of wearing a mask. #SII https://t.co/xIRwU60x1P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Distance now to cover more miles later!We, as responsible citizens, must follow the government policies to curb the #COVID19 pandemic. Monitor your health and consult the doctor at the slightest symptom of an infection.  Stay home, stay safe. #SII #Vaccine https://t.co/ZKnO4yvBR1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the Pandemic-centric information being disseminated every hour, it is crucial to keep ourselves updated with the right set of effective measures and avoid believing unverified and false information.Stay healthy, stay safe, practice proper preventive measures. #SII #vaccine https://t.co/NsPfywEUIS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID19 has forced an atmosphere of fear and concern among the citizens of the world. Following a specific plan of action for the day to day functioning of your household and community is of utmost importance in this period of uncertainty and panic. Keep a check on everyone. #SII https://t.co/3bp8BuL2CW]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>