<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jengleruk: I have added a link to the full text of the letter inc an English translation here:  https://t.co/uwOWNXoVHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jengleruk: "We are 28 doctors and researchers who have written a debate article in which we, based on medical knowledge, explain that S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: You are here. https://t.co/lfNLmFH4qZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nypost: COVID lockdowns cost countless jobs, don't appear to have saved lives: study https://t.co/7ps49KvDmU https://t.co/7UEkA6bVvL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Over 650,000 people lost their jobs in hospitality in 2020 despite only 226 outbreaks of covid in pubs and restaurants.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: So SAGE now admit that the risk of Covid in a pub or restaurant is 'relatively low' with just 226 outbreaks in them sinc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: My critical thinking protects you. Your critical thinking protects me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Trade body UK Hospitality warned recently about  2bn in rent is owed by hospitality businesses with 40% of premises st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thesotonsaint: @conspiracyguy10 BREAKING: people queue efficiently to enter shopping store.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: There is a strange phenomenon in major cities, where most people overwhelmingly support politicians whose policies create th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SabinaWalker18: Israeli People Committees Report Find #Catastrophic Side Effects Of Pfizer Vaccine To Every System In Human Body (May]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @seaman_dj: @richardursomd @blayone But but but Dr. Fauci said differently! If we all go to restaurants we are safe. We just sit down an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida takes VACCINE-PASSPORT BAN a step further as governor signs bill into law, halts all local Covid-19 restrictions in state https://t.co/5UaS8ehC35]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorgerPieter: RT: Florida(USA): common sense vindicates.   In the USA, now 22 states liberated themselves from the useless COVID restri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WybrenvanHaga: Dr. Carla Peeters  Beschermingsmiddelen en testsamenleving brengen natuurlijk immuunsysteem in gevaar.  Mondkapjes zijn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mamaindigo: @richardursomd Here's the entire video. Listen to these doctors. https://t.co/X7U9SaMBHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Must see video, doctors speak out about covid misinformation and masks. https://t.co/Xye19cqnK5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctors speak out on Covid https://t.co/0dOkETgr4N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @richardursomd: It was a lie from the very beginning. We had treatment from Day one!!! https://t.co/aHt7BMjg7h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oakentersagain: It was a lie from the very beginning. We had treatment from Day one!!! https://t.co/1nkQ51HeHj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigKellyMP: Another US State joins in banning vaccine passports  Arkansas Governor signs law BANNING vaccine passports   We need to b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorgerPieter: Very good, Mrs Bik! Let's beat fraud.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @msteenhagen: @MinVWS In n woord Orwelliaans. Ik heb even rondgezocht, en het lijkt erop dat in voorgaande jaren er helemaal niet zo'n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine Passports: THIS Is Where It Leads https://t.co/sTf4ADfHi9 via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcrclaims: The government wants to persuade you that June 21st will return normal that a Great Reset as proposed by WEF is what a pipe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drnathimdladla: @NickHudsonCT I like the mention of the ridiculous practice of walking into a restaurant with your mask on, and taking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: Masks are generally absurd, and outdoor masks are theatre of the absurd, not least because covid barely transmits outdoor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TB_TB_TB_TB_TB: I won't stop until the masks are off. Retweet if you're with me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TB_TB_TB_TB_TB: 'Viruses spread among themselves and independent of contact between people'. The superb John Lee. I ask all my follower]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: @goddeketal @ToniaBuxton @GovRonDeSantis Why "you will serve as a control group" The "Florida elephant" has been in the room f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: Governor Ron DeSantis (@GovRonDeSantis) announces that he will suspend all local COVID-19 emergency orders in Florida.  Tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brilliant thread by Tobias Brunner. Must read!! COVID is finished. A vitally important thread. https://t.co/3B2la9Ryt0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny how they're all now insisting how safe activities in the open air are. This is of course just their way of moving attention away from the now obvious seasonality. https://t.co/e83F1BAuOc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great Thread From Tobias Brunner: Clarification as some of you have asked about my position on things Covid, so want to make it clear here what I think of certain topics: https://t.co/YuoeAhAXgd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thread by @TB_TB_TB_TB_TB on Thread Reader App  Thread Reader App https://t.co/YuoeAhAXgd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GirardotMarc: How do Americans do in England with their American english? Fine, right?  It's not 287 variant words that impede proper u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pdubdev: Oklahoma ends emergency orders.   Back to normal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - A huge group of Doctors from around the world have released a statement saying "There is no scientific founda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @konstantinospo7: Denmark says no to JJ. Exactly like Oxford/Astra. https://t.co/Pd96OMaSYm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @allisonpearson: On @BBCNews massive pessimism about opening up. Then the embarrassing fact -1 Covid death!   The disconnect between the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SabinaWalker18: Quoting  Geneticist @CaudeHenrion /translated  SCOOP  After being the 1st country to COMPLETELY  STOP  using the v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigKellyMP: The vested interests are terrified, they know Ivermectin works, but if they save this womens life, they demonstrate supp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Creighton: Is the world finally getting sick of Covid-mania? https://t.co/ZEgXv4jbbl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierreKory: Still heavily involved in this court   case, submitted another affidavit today. Judge used it to severely admonish the hosp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HowardSteen4: Good news from the German Constitutional Court in Karlsruhe. It has upheld the controversial Weimar ruling about masks an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovRonDeSantis: I was proud to sign landmark legislation  2 executive orders to protect individual liberties. SB 2006: Bans Vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hartgroup_org: Despite the fact that there is currently no pandemic in this country, the promised return to normality on 21 June seems]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: "[T]he researchers determined that SARS-CoV-2-specific CD8+ T-cell responses remained largely intact and could recognize]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffreyPeel: Well said Dan. He's right. Let's ditch the masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danwootton: So far as Im concerned June 21st is Liberation Day, whether the Government wants to accept it or not. Social distancing an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Humble_Analysis: There are five nations in Europe which have vaccinated less than 3% of their population.  "Surprisingly" cases are dec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: Gov. Ron DeSantis is signing an EO today suspending *all* COVID emergency orders. He's also signing bill to limit loca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: This should be damning for SAGE.  https://t.co/IR7WDyl5bK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Government Evidence on Masks is Weak and a Mess  Lockdown Sceptics https://t.co/psss3X3LAz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KristinaMFiore: T cell-mediated immunity, other coronaviruses,  the future of #COVID19: @MartyMakary talks with @profvrr https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[T Cells Are the Unsung Heroes of COVID-19 Resistance | MedPage Today https://t.co/ph0XA8S6Bf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: Come on @nypost! This is the kind of panic porn I expect from @washingtonpost.  "The hospitals are full."  FROM THE SAME]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: 1/ Another study shows how well monoclonal antibodies work - and that #Covid is far from an emergency justifying vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Highly cited COVID doctor comes to stunning conclusion: Govt scrubbing unprecedented numbers of injection-related deaths  https://t.co/thghAmcQsF https://t.co/EBPZTEdgfd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UgariticMan: Professor of Medicine Dr. Peter McCullough:  -85% of lives lost to COVID could have been saved had proper therapies been u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: I was at the pub yesterday. 10 of us, but thats not the story. Out of the 10 we had 6 unjabbed including a nurse. I wou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierreKory: 4-months since peer-review.  Increased chest pain each time I was asked "when is your paper going to be published?"  TODAY.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Critical: ***Our scientific paper is published!  Many examples of #ivermectin distribution campaigns leading to rapid populatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorgerPieter: @IkNet @Appie52748507 @MBalbahadoer @MichaelvdGalien Een van mijn vroegere collega's van het universiteitsziekenhuis Zuri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @T4Recovery: COVID lockdowns cost countless jobs, don't appear to have saved lives: study https://t.co/bmvu6aBvuG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: Lies ultimately collapse under the weight of their internal contradictions. YouTubes rules would now have you banned for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: Apparently the Florida legislature has taken the advice of FDOH that masks aren't necessary https://t.co/Q1fOMOZbaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BenMarten: Texas! Alles offen! Keine Maskenpflicht. Keine Impfpsse! Eine freie Demokratie! https://t.co/1W0H3T2zAK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: Mailand gestern Abend trotz Ausgangssperre ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: Elephant in the room  2020:  Sweden  Florida   2021:  Elephants grow exponentially! Sweden  and 25 states ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: "Biden says Neanderthal thinking behind lifting of mask rules "Texas Rangers to reopen stadium at full capacity despite COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: Saxony, Germany  Lockdown for six month now. Restaurants, shops, hotels, schools, closed most of the time. Mask mandates, als]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: "The pictures from India".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: India, New Delhi  This video tells a completely different story than what the MSM is feeding everyone https://t.co/tFb4ejNc61]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: Florida new video  How it started / How it's going: Events including Covid Cases 2 weeks later.  January - New Years Eve  - Nig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: I just can't relate to the spreading insanity............... What on earth is going on.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LorolinAbl: @GillianMcKeith @DeborahKFreedom Yes,in my office we need to wear a mask all day(if we go in).At some point,someone will de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: I can't get my head around the fact that a tiny, group of people, a minuscule number.. make the most terrible choices,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinFogel: Netherlands: "short lockdown, equitable school funding, and world-leading rates of broadband access... we find that studen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor:  https://t.co/GnoHz6EWyd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcrclaims: Useful round up from @jeffreyatucker state side if youre feeling low.  Sadly we still have a long way to go to get close to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BRILLIANT: Dr. John Lee, Prof of Pathology UK - Unlocked Documentary! - YouTube https://t.co/hJx4GxBPA8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: 3rd wavists, need to explain why a 3rd wave of cases is a problem for the NHS, when 99% of all those vulnerable to hosp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: Ew! Gross!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkChangizi: @drkiki It's because vaccination, although it biologically works, is not the needed *psychological* panacea to overcome t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @deeksj: The 1st 2 weeks of school testing did find MORE FALSE POSITIVES than TRUE POSITIVES - data are finally public.  Proportion fals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mockacuckoo: @deeksj Testing=flawed(PCR/LF)but its how cases/deaths are  detected. Masks do next to nothing 2 metres=made up number Asy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rene_devries: @mike_mesce @deeksj https://t.co/i0vuWo5ad8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: Let the blowback begin.  https://t.co/0m8vZClZQ1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: Repeatedly, the ZeroCovid, vax-em-all brigade seems so bloody obviously craven and divorced from reason and science, and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: So researchers looked at 100 people whod recovered from SARSCoV2 and found strong T-cell responses 6 months later - a si]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InProportion2: Interesting view from Dr Yeadon:  some clever people have taken it upon themselves to do Gods work and to do a violent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aginnt: Life continued as normal. But as with now, no one knew for certain how deadly [the pandemic] would turn out to be. Regardless,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Critical: ***BIG BREAKING NEWS*** Indias Ministry of Health issues new guidance for home isolation. It is now recommending a 3-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kevin_McKernan: Well deserved Dr. Zelenko  @jack will you apologize?  This will go down as the end of the modern enlightenment era and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Anti-Lockdown Movement Is Large and Growing https://t.co/n2XTKeJCV0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelPSenger: "There will be a realization, slow at first and then all at once, that what happened over these 14 months was a catastr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: 22 UK Covid deaths in the past 24 hours (deaths for any reason within 28 days of a positive test). 450 UK cancer dea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: Personal protective equipment expert @mamasaurusMeg testifying against masks on children. Powerful.  https://t.co/Gkpj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All Scientists Forced To Retire After Realizing The Science Is Now Settled | The Babylon Bee https://t.co/FXv3QVXp5Q]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>