<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GuidoFawkes1976: Hey @DNC could you answer this question for me please? Thanks in advance! https://t.co/IhiDxqP34q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller https://t.co/D71DJeWDlJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @johncardillo: This is it. This is the tweet. https://t.co/DCjHaKG9rO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 It will improve her looks, tbh.  Maybe she should just stay home then, where she will be safest. https://t.co/0u7qh3uAgJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mrddmia: Very important read in (not conservative) @TheAtlantic.  Executive Summary:  Politics and mental illness  not science  are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Aimeeisthebomb @stillgray https://t.co/HYj2vjzfw1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stillgray: Tucker Carlson slams the embarrassing CIA recruitment video. https://t.co/14nfZZjsGp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC https://t.co/DqyXc3xe86]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jackmurphylive: If the national media were honest they would report on this statement by a top national security official.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GangGreen11 @SebGorka Thats offensive to mental patients ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheJokerMouce:  Eyes on AZ but watch MI!. https://t.co/wu5rhC9piP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stillgray: What is wrong with people? https://t.co/OvvBngyBaT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LouRaguse: BREAKING: Derek Chauvin's attorney Eric Nelson just filed a motion asking for a new trial on multiple grounds including jury]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dcollinsWBAL @wbaltv11 How about HELL NO to injecting my child with an experimental vaccine?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alexsalvinews: Former Pres. Trump launches a new platform that allows him to directly connect with his followers:  https://t.co/MeHRYdm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChefGruel: Farmer Bill - Bill and Melinda Gates farmland was a largely hidden investment until their split became public. Im hoping h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @realDailyWire: 1991: I wonder if well have flying cars 30 years from now 2021: https://t.co/ZSrLCei6Zy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: BREAKING: Lead story on Daily Mail https://t.co/N4CRAiCwjV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyCaller: Tucker Carlson reveals that House GOP Leader Kevin McCarthy rented a room in DC from pollster Frank Luntz:  "Not only are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennaEllisEsq: WHAAAAAAAAAT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tedcruz: Dems accidentally call for abolishing the income tax for those making under $400k.  I accept!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC @DonaldJTrumpJr The gun looks a little corroded tbh. Wonder why? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill STFU! Literally NO ONE CARES what you have to say, Harry! Not the Brits and not Americans!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtgreenee: Love this lady!  She says exactly what most Americans really think.    Its largely the Democrats, media, and white celeb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RNCResearch: Jake Tapper confronts WH adviser Anita Dunn on Biden undermining vaccine confidence by not following CDC guidance by weari]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1SSpawXDga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newsmax: Aaron Babbitt, husband of the late Ashli Babbitt, opens up about how his world changed after Jan 6th plus his lawsuit against]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColumbiaBugle: #Thread Tucker Carlson's Monologue Blasting The GOP For Their Disconnect With Voters And For Listening To Republican Str]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexsalvinews Wait, isnt that racist?! Thats how this works, right?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealOmarNavarro @UpInTheHills You forgot Kinzinger and Cheney! And Burr is already out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: MOsT poPuLAr PResiDEnT EeVr  !!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO  Love you, Candace! Happy birthday! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davereaboi: This is really good. @kyleezempel is a terrific writer.   https://t.co/BT1fByrpSp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Franklin_Graham: Our condolences and prayers for the family of Apollo 11 astronaut Michael Collins, who passed away today at the age of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1SSpawXDga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CatalinaLauf: My name is Catalina Lauf.  I am THE pro-Trump candidate running to take down RINO Adam Kinzinger.  Our campaigns goal is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ericmetaxas Theres my religious exemption!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ericmetaxas: Is it a "mortal sin" to get these vaccines? https://t.co/84VXKjlZNr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drdavidsamadi Well duh. And neither do these plexi glass or plastic cages theyre putting kids in at school like the ones in that photo. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv https://t.co/MI8JNFkUiO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeAngelisCorey: COVID-19 didnt break the public school system.   In a lot of ways, it was already broken." https://t.co/T718QdCscx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: Kamala Harris is using our tax dollars to buy her own book and give it as a welcome gift to kids who come here illegally]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Wizard_Predicts: Massive crowd takes to the streets of London in anti lockdown protest https://t.co/M5G0U13QOE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stuff_charlie: Ashli Babbitt was murdered in front of our eyes in the Capitol Building of our nation three and a half months ago! The k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASimplePatriot: Mic drop  Are yall gonna kill me like MaKhia Bryant?  OFFICER: Are you gonna stab somebody like her?   https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1SSpawXDga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pdubdev: Texas school stayed 100% open.    No masks. No social distancing.    Saw almost zero Covid.    youve been played.   https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: County: We dont have authority over the school board.  School board: We follow the countys mandate to avoid confu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Unclear What Political Party Man Belongs To Since He's Wearing Both A MAGA Hat And A Mask https://t.co/5zLbQU2j5V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaeljknowles: Would you vote for Caitlyn Jenner?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickJFuentes: Thank them for killing Ashli Babbitt?  Thank them for enforcing mask mandates and lockdowns?  Thank them for arresting Jo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BleacherReport: Pat Tillman left the Arizona Cardinals to enlist in the U.S. Army after 9/11. He turned down a $3.6M contract offer at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JudiciaryGOP:  WATCH: North Carolina Lt. Gov. @MarkRobinsonNC lays out the truth on election integrity and voting rights.   Democrats]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kimKBaltimore: If your 13 year old is out stabbing people, carjacking uber drivers or running around with guns, please know...  ...you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CalebJHull: The only time I havent worn a mask in an Uber was in Texas when the driver wasnt wearing one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JusticeTristan: Republicans Demand CDC Explain Why 2-Year-Olds Should Wear Masks @FDRLST https://t.co/pzyJbCWoRq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AbhUosu0MU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ErrolWebber: This is Courtney Ann Taylor, a mother in Georgia. Shes one of the many parents whove HAD IT with mask mandates, especial]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mkolken We have Kamala! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realchrisrufo Wonderful! Are you hiring fellow warriors?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1SSpawXDga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColumbiaBugle: Officer Sicknick died the morning of Jan 7. Capitol Police started the homicide investigation on Jan 8. Sicknick had an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlwaysNoBiden @cleoworks1 Baltimore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: According to the CDC:  There have been 56,789 "adverse events" due to COVID vaccines since December.  There have been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Experts Are Super Smart And 100% Reliable, Experts Confirm https://t.co/YwdRBZ0tgQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RandPaul: Funding for students should follow the student and help create more school choice for parents and their children. https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SKMorefield: Tucker Carlson  @MattWalshBlog on forever masking:  "It's obvious now that masking is not about COVID. It hasn't been abo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeAngelisCorey: The Roman Catholic Diocese of Charleston filed a lawsuit against South Carolina for barring relief funding from private]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rothbard1776: I call for the immediate release of photos of your dad from his 26 trips to Pedophile Island. @ChelseaClinton https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: BREAKING: Democrat mayor who advocated for defunding police arrested for child sex crimes https://t.co/swWvQMGCZC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Real_John92: Nooooooo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CurtisHouck: Without any evidence, MSNBC's Joy Reid and Glenn Kirschner insinuate that Ron DeSantis will be implicated in the sex traff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimKBaltimore it was an honor to meet you and listen to you speak about the future of our party! Keep up the great work! Weve got your back!  https://t.co/IIfJxIEHzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MariaBonanno9 I thought she was a patriot and the future of the GOP...until she caved to the NCAA and Amazon and refused to sign the bill prohibiting men in womens sports. I no longer trust her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EpochTimes @pfizer  Line up for never ending jabs, sheep!  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarmineSabia: And thats not a damn answer. Because you know the answer. Adam Toledo was missing from his house for days, had a street]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RIP Ashli Babbitt, American Patriot.  https://t.co/2wlSxn2F6Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @yaf: BREAKING: After releasing a bombshell investigative video exposing CNN as Left-wing propagandists, @JamesOKeefeIII has been SUSPEN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: Pfizer CEO says people 'likely' to need a booster dose of a COVID-19 vaccine within 12 months of getting fully vaccinated. A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewSaysTV: Hey remember when you were told you needed life-saving vaccination so that select giant companies could sell a bunch of i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: Breaking: James OKeefe of Project Veritas has been suspended by Twitter. This is pure censorship for political reasons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepVernonJones: The time has come. Georgia is ready! https://t.co/ClIcnF6JtI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilMcCrackin44: Teachers who don't want to go back to work, should be treated the same way Reagan treated air traffic controllers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Full credit to @MN_Porcupine for this one https://t.co/XWBVoSsdU4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottTParkinson: When do Americans get their freedom back? ~@Jim_Jordan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: https://t.co/IJ7Le3bxbF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @julie_kelly2: When you see crocodile tears from Senate Republicans SHOCKED at Biden's radical agenda, remember how many voted to empowe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SomeoneElse__38 @Matthew_4_Trump TBH...its too late. They already own the courts. So depressing how the GOP never fights. Except Trump.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @julie_kelly2: As you watch things escalate in Brooklyn Center tonight, keep in mind January 6 defendants have been in jail for months a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laralogan: Indefinite Incarceration for Protesters With Wrong Politics https://t.co/SqJCKqTg41]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1SSpawXDga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stclairashley: It shouldnt be... but this photo is hilarious https://t.co/tfYX84o3SZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LiVe2DaNceATL: Every Single Word https://t.co/zPc4ZFQNTh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aubrey_huff: 2019-2020 flu season 38,000,000 cases.   2020-2021 flu season 1,822 cases.   Flu cases down an incredible 98% in one year!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cleoworks1: https://t.co/z6JTeN2ejq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: One of the dirty little secrets of the GOP establishment is that they don't like to be in the majority. It's much easi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: New photos coming out of Brooklyn Center MN today https://t.co/VmIopH22Lo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottWalker: The most endangered species on a college campus these days is a conservative professor. Survey after survey proves that as]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>