<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@yoavlurie Kia ora, we've just published an update. Anyone in New Zealand who has been at any of the locations of interest at the specified times should contact Healthline on 0800 358 5453, self-isolate and be tested as soon as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An update is expected tomorrow based on results of additional testing and a further public health assessment by New South Wales Health.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry will remain in close contact with its Australian counterparts as the situation evolves. Anyone planning to travel to NSW should take into account that advice from health authorities could change at any time, and be prepared for their travel plans to be disrupted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Individuals in Australia who were at a location of interest at the specified times should follow NSW health advice regarding isolation  testing. The Ministry will be requesting airlines provide this message to anyone flying to New Zealand from NSW in the next 24 hours.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone in New Zealand who has been at any of the locations of interest at the specified times should contact Healthline on 0800 358 5453, self-isolate and be tested as soon as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On that basis the Ministry does not at this stage recommend any change in Quarantine Free Travel between New Zealand and Australia. Information about locations of interest visited by the case is available on the New South Wales health website: https://t.co/XPEZnGG81N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update on New South Wales community case.  The Ministry of Healths current assessment is that the public health risk to New Zealand from the New South Wales community case announced today is low. https://t.co/phCzcc7HQt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dufferistan Kia ora, the stay in Managed Isolation is a minimum of 14 days. A person may need to stay longer. We do not know the reason for this in this particular case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elliotblyth Kia ora Elliot, where are you seeing Alert Level 2 graphics? New Zealand is currently at Alert Level 1.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@essjax Kia ora, you can find a workaround for transferring your NZ COVID Tracer app data to a new phone here: https://t.co/YyC0p7PJLW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This number will fluctuate as smaller clinics close and facilities that can accommodate larger groups of people open.  Mora vaccine data here: https://t.co/I3gLCNbjyQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date vaccinations have been administered at 189 sites by nearly 1,600 vaccinators. More than 3,800 people have been trained to administer the vaccinations.   Over the last seven days there have been around 120 vaccination clinics operating.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were also adding to our stocks of the Pfizer vaccination. We have received around 746,460 doses into the country  enough to vaccinate more than 373,000 people with the two doses required for maximum protection.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the past seven days to Tuesday 4 May 2021, we administered 68,483 vaccination doses to people. This is higher than the 50,034 vaccinations administered in the previous seven days. Overall, DHBs are tracking slightly ahead of plan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 VACCINE UPDATE  A total of 217,603 people have received their first doses of the vaccine, an increase of 45,039 from last Wednesdays figure of 172,564.  A total of 87,297 people have received a second dose and are now fully vaccinated. https://t.co/WR4nwecGXx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NZ COVID TRACER APP  NZ COVID Tracer now has 2,809,553 registered users. Poster scans have reached 262,182,989 and users have created 9,812,177 manual diary entries. There have been 507,758 scans in the last 24 hours to midday yesterday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FACEBOOK LIVE  The Director-General of Health will be doing a Facebook Live session on the Ministry of Healths page tomorrow to answer questions from the public on the COVID-19 vaccine rollout. This will start at 4.30pm on 6 May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For all testing locations nationwide visit theHealthpointwebsite here: https://t.co/WVcesM3HHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TESTING INFORMATION  The total number of tests processed by laboratories to date is 2,037,349. On Tuesday, 5,424 tests were processed. The seven-day rolling average up to yesterday is 4,164 tests processed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WESTERN AUSTRALIA UPDATE  People who were in Perth between April 27 and May 1 are advised to continue checking the Western Australian Government website for updates: https://t.co/3rkSXRUcxo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remaining passengers who werent at the locations of interest at the specified times should continue monitoring their health and if symptoms develop, call Healthline and get a test.   The risk from this event continues to be assessed as low.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BRISBANE AIRPORT GREEN ZONE BREACH UPDATE  Thirty-two people in New Zealand have been advised to isolate at home and continue to isolate until they receive a negative result from a day 5 test. To date, three have returned a negative result.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- One new case arrived on 30 April, tested positive on Day 3, and is in quarantine in Auckland. - One new case arrived on 3 May, tested positive on Day 0, and is in quarantine in Auckland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since 1 January 2021, there have been 53 historical cases, out of a total of 457 cases.   NEW BORDER CASES  Of the new border cases that are not historical, - One new case arrived on 20 April, tested positive on Day 0, and is in quarantine in Auckland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Five previously reported cases have now recovered. The total number of active cases in New Zealand today is 25.   Our total number of confirmed cases is 2,273. Globally, there have been 153,187,889 confirmed cases of COVID-19, including 3,209,109 deaths, reported to WHO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 update  There are no new cases of COVID-19 to report in the community in New Zealand today. There are three new cases and three historical cases to report in recent returnees in managed isolation facilities, since the Ministrys last update yesterday. https://t.co/Jw66sKr7eP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@m_stewart Kia ora Matthew, each district health board (DHB) around New Zealand is managing the rollout of the vaccine in their area. Exactly how and when people are contacted may differ between regions. We recommend speaking to your employer or contacting your DHB.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ErsteRocco Kia ora, Medsafe (NZ's medicines safety authority) only grants consent for a vaccine to be used in NZ once they are satisfied it's safe  effective. All COVID-19 vaccines will go through the same safety tests  must meet the same robust standards.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Baigy56 Kia ora, we encourage you to use our online tool to find out which group you are in and when you may expect to receive your vaccine. You can find the tool here: https://t.co/kEJOP7TzJA We are vaccinating groups 1  2 right now, group 3 beginning late May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jacquietran We like it here too ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toadstool991 Kia ora, the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS) has developed guidelines to use when certifying causes of death for people who died of, or with COVID-19. These guidelines are based on WHO recommendations. Find out more: https://t.co/RT45PxCnBz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@U_Xavierv Kia ora, at this time, we do not have any information on quarantine-free travel arrangements with any other countries. We will provide an update if there are any changes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NZadeptB Kia ora, this was filmed at a local South Indian restaurant, and this person is from India.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There have been 610,337 scans in the last 24 hours to midday yesterday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For all testing locations nationwide visit the Healthpoint website: https://t.co/WVcesM3HHW  NZ COVID TRACER APP  NZ COVID Tracer now has 2,808,374 registered users. Poster scans have reached 261,503,931 and users have created 9,786,939 manual diary entries.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TESTING INFORMATION  The total number of tests processed by laboratories to date is 2,031,925. On Monday, 2,726 tests were processed. The seven-day rolling average up to yesterday is 3,872 tests processed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remaining passengers who werent at the locations of interest at the specified times previously advised should continue monitoring their health and if symptoms develop, call Healthline and get a test.  The risk from this event continues to be assessed as low.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BRISBANE AIRPORT GREEN ZONE BREACH UPDATE  29 people in New Zealand considered casual plus contacts in relation to the Brisbane Airport green zone breach are today due for their day five test. These results will be available in the coming days.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 800 passengers who travelled either directly or indirectly between Western Australia and New Zealand between 27 April and 1 May have now been contacted by the Ministry of Healths contact tracing team and given the above advice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone who has been at a location of interest cannot travel to New Zealand from Australia within 14 days of exposure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you were at a location of interest at a specified time and you are still in Perth and are planning to travel to New Zealand, you are asked to follow the Western Australia health advice regarding isolation and testing on the above website.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So far, no travellers who arrived in New Zealand have contacted Healthline to say they were at any of the locations of interest currently connected to these cases at the specified times.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have recently arrived in New Zealand from Australia and were in a location of interest at the specified time, please self-isolate immediately and call Healthline on 0800 358 5453 for information on when you should be tested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New locations of interest have been listed, and people who were in Perth between April 27 and May 1 are advised to continue checking the Western Australian Government website for updates: https://t.co/l2ZgAcRbk7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WESTERN AUSTRALIA UPDATE  The Ministry of Health is continuing to monitor developments in Western Australia, and New Zealand health officials continue to assess the risk to public health in New Zealand as low. Of note, no further community cases have been reported in Perth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since 1 January 2021, there have been 50 historical cases, out of a total of 451 cases.  NEW BORDER CASE DETAILS  One new case arrived on 26 April, tested positive around day 6 and is in quarantine in Auckland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two previously reported cases have now recovered. The total number of active cases in New Zealand today is 24.  Our total number of confirmed cases is 2,267. Globally, there have been 152,534,452 confirmed cases of COVID-19, including 3,198,528 deaths, reported to WHO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 update  There are no new cases of COVID-19 to report in the community today. There is one new case to report in recent returnees in managed isolation facilities, since our last update yesterday. https://t.co/4whbiH8Tty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Warboi1 Kia ora, you can find visa information for students outside of New Zealand here: https://t.co/VUEUC7PgaS There are some who are permitted if they meet the criteria.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiwi_outlaw Kia ora, ka kite means "see you" rather than "goodbye," as COVID-19 is part of our new normal. We're trying to say 'see you COVID-19, we're getting immunity'. Everyone who can get the COVID-19 vaccine will strengthen our collective immunity, including against new strains.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahNewcombe Kia ora, thanks for your kind words ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mungusrising Kia ora, thanks for your kind words ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pabluu We're lucky to work with some very talented people! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PakehaAotearoan Kia ora, the Cook Islands is COVID-19 free and is the risk of transmission is considered low. Our vaccine rollout will continue, and we're scaling up our programme across the country to administer 1 million doses by June.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Find out more on our website - https://t.co/IQD13yNEED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- you have not had a positive COVID-19 test in the 14 days before you depart. If you have, you must have written advice from a health practitioner that you are no longer infectious. -you are not waiting for the results of a COVID-19 test taken in the past 14 days.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To travel to the Cook Islands on a quarantine-free flight, you must meet the following criteria: - you meet immigration requirements - you need to spend the 14 full days before your date of departure in either New Zealand or the Cook Islands.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quarantine-free travel between New Zealand and the Cook Islands does not include Australia. If you're in Australia, you must spend 14 full days in New Zealand before you can continue your journey through to the Cook Islands. The same rule applies in the opposite direction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone in New Zealand can travel quarantine-free to the Cook Islands, as long as they meet the eligibility criteria and immigration requirements. New Zealand citizens do not need a visa to travel to the Cook Islands.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From 17 May, you can travel between New Zealand and the Cook Islands without having to go into managed isolation or self-isolation when you arrive. https://t.co/PsTHSsc9xI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robincrimp Kia ora Robin, you can find more detailed NZ COVID Tracer app data on the Ministry of Health website here: https://t.co/0Hfu15ce8N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NZ COVID TRACER: NZ COVID Tracer now has 2,807,036 registered users.   Poster scans have reached 260,853,069 and users have created 9,761,852 manual diary entries.     There have been 599,400 scans in the last 24 hours to midday yesterday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A reminder for people who may need a COVID-19 test  please visit Auckland Regional Public Health Service (ARPHS) for all testing locations in Auckland.  For all testing locations nationwide visit the Healthpoint website.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TESTING INFORMATION:  The total number of tests processed by laboratories to date is 2,029,196.  On Sunday 2,246 tests were processed. The seven-day rolling average up to yesterday is 3,779 tests processed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- One case arrived on 30 April and tested positive on day 0. They have been transferred to a quarantine facility in Christchurch. - One case arrived on 1 May and tested positive on day 0. They have been transferred to a quarantine facility in Auckland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW BORDER CASE DETAILS - One case arrived on 24 April and tested positive around day 8. They have been transferred to a quarantine facility in Auckland. - One case arrived on 30 April and tested positive on day 1. They have been transferred to a quarantine facility in Auckland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AUCKLAND AIRPORT BORDER-RELATED CASE UPDATE: All contacts of this case have now returned negative tests at day 12 and this case is now considered closed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The remaining passengers who werent at the locations of interest at the specified times are advised to monitor their health and if symptoms develop, call Healthline and get a test.  The risk from this event continues to be assessed as low.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This means there are now 29 people considered casual plus contacts who have been asked to self-isolate and get tested five days after their exposure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A further two people have contacted Healthline over the weekend to say they were in the locations of interest at Brisbane Airport at the relevant time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BRISBANE AIRPORT GREEN ZONE BREACH UPDATE  All 397 passengers aboard three flights which left Brisbane International Airport after the green zone breach on Thursday 29 April have now been contacted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 800 passengers who travelled either directly or indirectly between Western Australia and New Zealand between 27 April and 1 May have now been contacted by the Ministry of Healths contact tracing team and given the above advice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have recently arrived in New Zealand from Australia and were in a location of interest at the specified time, please self-isolate immediately and call Healthline on 0800 358 5453 for information on when you should be tested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone who has been at a location of interest cannot travel to New Zealand from Australia within 14 days of exposure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[However, if you were at a location of interest at a specified time and you are still in Perth and are planning to travel to New Zealand, you are asked to follow the Western Australia health advice regarding isolation and testing on the above website.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ministry advises people who were in Perth between April 27 and May 1 to continue checking the Western Australian Government website for updates: https://t.co/IoAWVsdKtH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Western Australian health officials are continuing their scoping interviews of the two housemates and it is possible further locations of interest could be added.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So far, no one who has arrived in New Zealand has contacted Healthline to say they were at any of the 17 locations of interest currently connected to these cases at the specified times.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Zealand health officials have determined the risk to public health in New Zealand from these cases is low.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WESTERN AUSTRALIA UPDATE  The Ministry of Health is continuing to monitor developments in Western Australia after a Perth managed isolation facility worker and two of their housemates tested positive for COVID-19 at the weekend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since 1 January 2021, there have been 50 historical cases, out of a total of 450 cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three previously reported cases have now recovered. The total number of active cases in New Zealand today is 25.    Our total number of confirmed cases is 2,266.   Globally, there have been 151,803,822 confirmed cases of COVID-19, including 3,186,538 deaths, reported to WHO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 Update  There are no new cases of COVID-19 to report in the community today.    There are four new cases to report in recent returnees in managed isolation facilities, since our last update yesterday. https://t.co/vtBxVBSRyz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toadstool991 Kia ora, information about your COVID-19 immunisations will be recorded in our COVID Immunisation Register (CIR). Before you leave, youll be given a record card with your immunisation date and the batch number. Read more about privacy here: https://t.co/Jybgqv7Qm3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ipanki7 Kia ora, we provide official information and updates from the New Zealand Government about COVID-19 on this page. Please talk to your healthcare professional such as your doctor, as they will be able to help.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@utunga Kia ora Miles, the COVID-19 vaccine has not been approved for use under the age of 16, but it's still important to show our tamariki in our public information campaign. We have included a wide range of people of all ages in this campaign.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DG_Clara Kia ora, it is here: https://t.co/4saOIQD81B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gabriel1980NZ Kia ora, it is here: https://t.co/9YreyDLFN9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JKato3333 Kia ora, were offering vaccines first to those most at risk of getting/spreading COVID-19, and those most at risk of getting very sick from the virus. There will be enough vaccine for everyone from all of our diverse groups aged 16 plus in NZ to be vaccinated by the end of 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiwi_curly Kia ora Jasmin, thanks for letting us know. We'll look into this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemyoshioka Kia ora, thank for your beautiful illustrations ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiwidonkey Kia ora, we've uploaded the video to Twitter. Feel free to share ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Orthanc Kia ora, thanks for your kind words ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ForestMaid Kia ora, we encourage you to talk to a healthcare professional about your specific medical questions. Vaccine efficacy hasn't been assessed in immunocompromised people, including those receiving immunosuppressant therapy, though it may be lower in immunosuppressed individuals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ka kite, COVID  were getting immunity https://t.co/xqHLARSJCg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please continue to wash your hands regularly, wear masks on public transport, and if youre unwell please stay home and call Healthline to work out whether you need to get a test.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is important we continue to stay vigilant, by keeping a record of where we have been by scanning QR codes and turning on Bluetooth using the NZ COVID Tracer app, or keep manual diaries.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There may be additional passengers identified as contact tracers work with other government agencies to confirm travel histories and contact details.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Around 750 passengers who travelled either directly or indirectly between Western Australia and New Zealand between 27 April and 1 May are being contacted today by the Ministry of Healths contact tracing team and being given the above advice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have recently arrived in New Zealand from Australia and were in a location of interest at the specified time, please self-isolate immediately and call Healthline on 0800 358 5453 for information on when you should be tested.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>