<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LBC: Face masks for schoolchildren should remain mandatory until at least June 21, unions have demanded in joint letter to Education Se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LBC @NickFerrariLBC last point to all the mask Gestapo   If the mask are there to stop a bio hazard ...  Why dont schools, businesses and public places have bio containment systems for all the thrown away masks? Seems pretty dumb to mandate masks but not mandate disposal of bio waste? Fauci is ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LBC @NickFerrariLBC I believe that in the scientific world it is up to the imposer of the governance rule to prove the theory.  The labor union need to conduct their own study and prove the masks are not harming our kids. https://t.co/Am7jBoN2hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LBC @NickFerrariLBC From the Gov site of NIH masks can cause hypoxia not to mention children are least at risk of Covid and more at risk of brain damage due to extended use of the mask during g exertion (you know because kids dont stand still all day) https://t.co/1pcUoGG8jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Blue states lost jobs at double the rate of red ones during pandemic https://t.co/jDlQ1RM1n5 via @MailOnline]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @MailOnline @JackPosobiec our county in OR is struggling to find employees because they all want to stay home and collect unemployment.  24 hour stores are closing at night because they have no employees to work.  Why work when you can make $18/hr equiv to stay home and do nothing. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mamasaurusMeg: Youch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis @CDCgov I think Id like to apply for Political asylum in Florida from the state of Oregon and governor Kate Browns dictatorship ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you Ron DeSantis, we The People (the population not the government like dumbass Joe Biden think we the people is) love common sense governing not overreach tyrannical dictatorships like the Biden administration! https://t.co/Hc9ASYcEq9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DickMackintosh @Barbarajdurkin @DawnTJ90 @Canadianworker2 @Fiddlers__Green @Tcaddy5 @HalBrow68884227 @Narvuntien @gourlay_maurice @MedBennett @Sander_1954 @mentalmal1 @BridgetHolmstro @BenMaughan4 @Climatehope2 @MikeDel21893959 @RobMeekel @TheDisproof @rln_nelson @0Sundance @ArthurBraby @IngersolRobert @GuyGadboisGuyG1 @Circular_Logic_ @TinTincognito @TroyCramp69 @no2wind @Ruth91869132 @DLMtd2 @StormSignalSA @WayneAllanH @JinxNohi @IanDJbrown2 @fishyfish67 @RoyPentland @Cole44749821 @IBergwiesel @jasonpaisley @Rob46401650 @Knah22 @d_e_mol @UCBearcat90 @RijpeW @hadleyjohn @AffitThro @GeraldKutney @SapientHetero @hfjohnsen @nooil4pacifists @dodgydingo1 Yeah but the combustion engine, electric cars and hydrogen cars are cool.  And swinging through trees is hard to travel when you clear forests to make giant windmills that will never produce enough power to run all the electric cars they want to build. Duh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: SPOTTED IN DC https://t.co/WFbwtGgf4K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: DAILY MAIL: Derek Chauvin juror LIED about protest: Cop's hope of appeal boosted after picture emerges of juror at BLM ra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tedcruz: Texas is leading the way against woke corporations  their assault on freedom.  Major legislation moving to prohibit investing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mamasaurusMeg: @paulreardon013 @LaffersNapkin Know what else works? Environs controls.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LaffersNapkin @mamasaurusMeg By providing an alternative medication that works.  Which had been provided and ignored by WHO, NIH, CDC and Congress. 14,000 patients, 7 countries, 238 doc  scientist 300 studies, 400 peer reviewed papers, 1 Nobel Prize and they didnt listen.  https://t.co/EqtbvhNba3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And John Kerry interestingly enough   https://t.co/1Om0UEuvzD https://t.co/GH2qn8J8Xj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: If minimum wage is going to be  $15 an hour that is $2400.00 a month... So why is Social Security for the elderly far be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv https://t.co/1Om0UEuvzD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx Is that what you would like me to tell this boys parents?  People who doubt the usefulness of masks for kids playing are clowns?    Funny thats your best responce to truth.  Your a sheeple and your letting party lines cloud your better judgement.   https://t.co/yuNCgD7XFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv I am not a betting man, but if I was....  I bet theres an evidence connection between her, John Kerry and Irans minister of foreign affairs and Irans leadership council   Maybe Im wrong but speculation is she was pushed... not jumped!  https://t.co/1Om0UEuvzD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@totinos @WINTRELL77 Triple cheese]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv I wonder how many sheeple will believe that she jumped?   https://t.co/EEbFOUUgBI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Good Morning from Florida, where we are thankful for great weather, no state income taxes, freedom, and above all - thank]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @russvought: Big win. 49 states to go:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@russvought I would like to thank the real president for making us energy independent the 2027-2020 were truly the best years of my life financially.  We in OR went from $2.30/gal to $4.25/gal in 4 months.  #joebidensucks #DJT45]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @russvought: Thanks for having me on @AmMomentOrg! Great conversation with @ssharmaUS and @NickSSolheim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: So glad Tucker exposed Frank Lunch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 And showed mainstream media how to be a real journalist.  Hey CNN if you cant name your source back it up with research!  Maybe you can hire Tucker to train your staff how to do that?   Maybe not, that would expose truth and we all know you dont do that  CNN =  News Network]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AmMomentOrg: We've got to use the levers that we have, including government, to get culture back as best we possibly can.  @RussVough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NautPoso: @catturd2 https://t.co/4gMQ5fmFTm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOL https://t.co/jE19n8tyrL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Breaking ... Frank Luntz and Kevin McCarthy to take on a third roommate ... https://t.co/026OGwCboh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Frank Luntz is the Big Lie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: 2016: A New Hope  2020: The Empire Strikes Back 2024: The Return of The MAGA???  #MayThe4thBeWithYou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mamasaurusMeg @KristenMeghan @BrentJeffcoat @Jennife28510664 @greenhousemd @henrymcmaster @drsimonegold @MarkChangizi @MartinKulldorff @jhaskinscabrera @naomirwolf @Emily_Burns_V @districtai @BarbaraCastor2 @Illegalshift66 @denisrancourt I thought so ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreedbyGrace17 @mamasaurusMeg https://t.co/QLXyRP4NHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KristenMeghan @BrentJeffcoat @Jennife28510664 @greenhousemd @henrymcmaster @drsimonegold @MarkChangizi @MartinKulldorff @mamasaurusMeg @jhaskinscabrera @naomirwolf @Emily_Burns_V @districtai @BarbaraCastor2 @Illegalshift66 @denisrancourt https://t.co/QLXyRP4NHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2020istrash2020 @chiproytx https://t.co/QLXyRP4NHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bidenwonthnkgod @chiproytx @All435Reps https://t.co/QLXyRP4NHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/QLXyRP4NHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimboc5 https://t.co/QLXyRP4NHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fldntrjkMV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewellJacks @chiproytx Whats the matter did you run out of Smart Alec responce to the facts laid out before you?  Maybe you have a funny comment I can tell that little boys parents?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseAlberta1 @Jamz129 @SheilaGunnReid @JCCFCanada The PCR test was calibrated to give false positives.  In 2020 they were running 40 cycles   The numbers are a big lie !  Not to mention there are treatments that work! https://t.co/gPa4gG6Y8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimboc5 @Jamz129 And they say were the cult of a conspiracy   The easiest way I can prove this is all BS...  Masks are to protect us from a biological pandemic....  Where are all the biological disposal centers?   Facts dont lie  https://t.co/0FmORLjz7T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kimboc5: Why subject children  babies to a high risk experimental when theres a 99.9% survival rate for them? This is pure evil! Wak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KristenMeghan: A Nurse Practitioner is claiming to know more about masks than a Senior Industrial Hygienist. It's ironic, since I train]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepVernonJones: Laws were broken during the 2020 election and now, rhinos like Liz Cheney expect Americans not to question the legitima]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrewHolden360 @JennaEllisEsq @CNN Keep showing the hypocrisy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kerpen: Nice to see Old Joe FINALLY showing confidence in the vaccine, meeting with vulnerables inside at close quarters unmasked!  Suc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennaEllisEsq: Related, @catturd2? Or just an uncatty resemblance? https://t.co/qBjf5yHk7D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LawrenceSellin:   #CCPVirus #UnrestrictedBiowarfare #OriginOfCOVID19  #UnrestrictedBioweapon #COVID19 #coronavirus #Corona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Parents Disguising Kids As Illegal Immigrants So They Can Receive In-Person Teaching https://t.co/qSVKcauPa7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LawrenceSellin: History's obituary https://t.co/9yZxLq0DKZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nypost: Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis suspends all local COVID emergency orders https://t.co/4kqwMeiekG https://t.co/8USoTXn335]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewellJacks @chiproytx Heres another article that shows your standard medical mask does not stop the microbial size of corona 19   https://t.co/bZjm78qaxA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewellJacks @chiproytx Autopsy report shows cause of death Hypoxia cause from oxygen depletion.  So joke all you want, Im trying to save childrens lives from ignorant people....  Dont be ignorant based on party lines.  Masks dont work for all situations  https://t.co/yuNCgD7XFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewellJacks @chiproytx And yet another NIH study   Clearly one hand of the US Government is not talking to the other.  Why?  Maybe its because, oh, I dont know..... someone is maybe trying to possibly, maybe controll YOU!   WTFU!  https://t.co/1pcUoGG8jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewellJacks @chiproytx Clearly one of us is oxygen deficient heres some info to back up my statement.  Division of NIH clinical trials study  https://t.co/Am7jBoN2hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewellJacks @chiproytx https://t.co/MJ6EkJY53n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/J515gTMR5J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @chiproytx I sent you two government studies that confirmed hypoxia is possible while exerting yourself and you only keyed in on the lawyer.  Your a joke. https://t.co/wQl4JJ1ua6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bidenwonthnkgod @chiproytx @All435Reps Those are government studies.  But I hope your brother doesnt personally kill any kids with his disinformation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2020istrash2020 @chiproytx https://t.co/Am7jBoN2hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2020istrash2020 @chiproytx https://t.co/1pcUoGG8jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2020istrash2020 @chiproytx https://t.co/yuNCgD7XFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bidenwonthnkgod @chiproytx @All435Reps People like your brother are responsible for killing kids like this one for classifying valuable information as a cult https://t.co/yuNCgD7XFz  Autopsy confirmed hypoxia  #MasksOff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bidenwonthnkgod @chiproytx @All435Reps https://t.co/Am7jBoN2hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bidenwonthnkgod @chiproytx @All435Reps https://t.co/1pcUoGG8jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bidenwonthnkgod @chiproytx @All435Reps LOL.  Your brother is a terrible doctor.    Explain to me how masks work based on the infrared photos below. https://t.co/HlyRagzYMR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @chiproytx LOL  So thats all you got out of my 16 replies?    Heres some advise.  Learn to read]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClayTravis: Did you miss murders increasing the most in nearly two generations in 2020? Or the fact that murders are up from those numb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx So @intcsux you have no response?  I am waiting for you to gibe me your superior argument to the facts laid before you.    Ill wait https://t.co/rnKiAXzTKl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dhiggsboson @intcsux @chiproytx See responses   Thank you for the compliment Im rather fond of my intellect.    I cant wait for you to debunk all that information https://t.co/xYw7MimJSE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2020istrash2020 @chiproytx And so again a child in a cancer center is usually lying down or sitting in a bed not running up and down the halls.  . Also masks serve a small purpose for spittle but has been proven to do nothing against Covid-19 .06 micron aerosol microbes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2020istrash2020 @chiproytx Its about exertion if you read the studys you will note that standing still only saw a 1% O2 depletion but exertion was as high as 20% which can cause confusion, dizziness, vomiting and hypoxia.  Thats one mask and our Dr Fauci  wants 2 masks.  That study has not been done]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chiproytx @chiproytx Chip this person just got schooled on reality.  If anyone wants to know the truth click on this conversation.  I replied to their moronic view with facts in 16 attachments and links including a child who died of hypoxia from masks mandate while playing soccer. https://t.co/xYw7MimJSE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx Well? No responce to any of the info you requested?  Heres a participation trophy for being last to come to reality https://t.co/d2jKiw7sUk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx Your smug look should just about be wiped away with all the data Ive shared. Because of brain dead media propaganda this boy is now dead.  Wearing masks after 200 million people have been vaccinated is stupid and chip Roy is right, its about control now  https://t.co/yuNCgD7XFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/LvLBsCBG8p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx Snopes!   https://t.co/PPOh9MCWoK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/Lsv65VB9vY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/WxFmdjKLQz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KristenMeghan @BrentJeffcoat @Jennife28510664 @greenhousemd @henrymcmaster @drsimonegold @MarkChangizi @MartinKulldorff @mamasaurusMeg @jhaskinscabrera @naomirwolf @Emily_Burns_V @districtai @BarbaraCastor2 @Illegalshift66 @denisrancourt And then I run into people like this!    I have attached the conversation and lit him up with a ton of good info if you all want to scroll through it sites papers and links to legal breakdowns. (including our lovely Megan!)  Quite a bit of info in there to truth slap sheeple https://t.co/xYw7MimJSE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx And your retarded to pick on wording and spacing on a Twitter feed that only allows so many characters.  People shove words together all the time to make it fit.  People who make typo Analysis on Twitter are idiots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dhiggsboson @intcsux @chiproytx Click on this portion of the conversation Ive linked several and backed up my statement with research and irrefutable data. https://t.co/xYw7MimJSE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/VQ48ZNFRij]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/bZjm78qaxA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/Rl92kMEl48]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx You wont listen to this because it has Lin wood n the cover but forward to 1 hour and listen to Leigh Dundas.  She breaks down all the facts on the peer reviewed data.  Im sure you wont because people hate being proven wrong.  But it all there   https://t.co/StCTTRRh6z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx Pub med study on surgeons wearing a mask standing still, but again we are not worried about children standing still, have you ever driven by a playground at a school and seen kids all standing still?  moronic https://t.co/1pcUoGG8jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx In the photo below you can see that the mask is causing pressure and the exhalation is actually traveling farther not by much but covid Molecules travel on your exhalation and can drift a loft for hours 6 feet is stupid masks dont work. Molecule size .06 m medical masks stop .3 https://t.co/1Ae3Pyev89]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx What the studies are not comparing is a surgical mask covered with a cloth mask.  So if running while wearing 1 mask can cause hypoxia what do you think 2 masks will do? Dont worry you ask for references Im going to truth dump on you all day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx You would t know truth if it hit you in the face.  Keep wearing your masks I just might save the planet for the ready of us.  Here is a study on going which shows wearing a mask with exertion does deplete O2 by 20% do you think kids stand still all day?  https://t.co/Am7jBoN2hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx Nothing to back them up?   https://t.co/H8WQuZM1f9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/H8WQuZM1f9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dhiggsboson @intcsux @chiproytx https://t.co/H8WQuZM1f9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @dhiggsboson @chiproytx https://t.co/H8WQuZM1f9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@intcsux @chiproytx https://t.co/H8WQuZM1f9  The info comes from this Attorney good looking living in your dream land this is a real problem]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>