<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@ginger_consult2 We have been marketing campaigns for almost everything you currently own - the foods we consume, the cars we drive, the places we live in. Finding new ways to connect with people isnt a bad thing.  What matters is whats behind the marketing.  A &gt; 90% effective vaccine!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back when I was Surgeon General I proposed we do a video like this to promote vaccinations- but it was shot down because we were afraid  people might think bad dancing was a vaccine side effect...  Steady Pom Pi Pi- get the facts, and hopefully youll decide to get the vax! https://t.co/J2z4LmSZ5p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Almost all physicians when offered the #COVID19 vaccine, chose to get it.  Your doctor went to school- a long time- so as to take the best possible care of you. You trust them, and they trust the vax.  So get the facts, and hopefully, like your own doctor, youll get the vax! https://t.co/v1odIKO4RF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My wife is being treated for cancer and at risk for #COVID19 despite being vaccinated. My kids are suffering emotionally from Covid restrictions, but are the biggest risk of viral spread to my wife. Thats why this news makes me so happy! Soon 2/3 of my kids will be vaccinated! https://t.co/l3hTPH15DB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wisdom from @muftimenk:  We often condemn good people because we disagree over a few issues. We refuse to see any good in them. Disagreements do not automatically make a person bad. Learn to distinguish between the one who respectfully disagrees  the one who is evil! #Ramadan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont get the people who follow me on Twitter and then reply to my posts stop talking, or we dont want to hear from you. Do they not understand how the platform works?  What if I followed you around all day waiting for you to talk, just so I could tell you to be quiet?  https://t.co/KRb2ZawMMS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MtinaMorgan Please stop following me if you dont like what Im saying!  Unity and tolerance has to go more than one way if we truly want to build back better!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whenpigsflyyy Whats your point?  That you werent paying attention back then, or that science evolves, or that people shouldnt try to keep doing better or that you just like to troll? Even if you were right, is there no room for forgiveness in your heart?  Be well and get your vax!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@titudeplus Only who God made me.  And thats why I try to be kind to others (though sometimes I fall short- maybe you too?).  Be well. And get vaccinated!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive heard numerous employers say they cant hire, and several potential employees say it doesnt make sense to work, because people are getting more money staying home. Is this because government support has become too much/ too indiscriminate, or because wages are too low? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The man thanked me and said Im too damned old to ever be woke, but every night I pray to God to help me wake up. He said he realizes hell never know what its like to be a black man, but knows that as a white man, hes privileged not to have to worry about things like this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I told the older man while he saw the overt harm in not admitting the black man, I saw the insidious harm in him actually being admitted, but having to tell his boys they couldnt be as loud / playful as the other white teens, or get caught looking at a pretty girl at the pool...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The older gentleman who was telling this story could clearly see the harm and racism in this reasoning.  Whats interesting is Im willing to bet the white women would swear to you-and to herself- that there was no racial bias whatsoever in her thinking...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This white woman not too long ago wouldnt have been admitted to the country club herself.  The man she was against admitting was a pastor at a local church.  Her reasoning?  The man had teenage boys who might invite their friends and be disruptive at the pool...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fascinating convo recently with a very conservative, affluent, much gentleman who was telling me about his not long ago efforts to get a black man admitted to his country club.  To his surprise, the one board member who voted against, was a white woman...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are experiencing not an opioid epidemic, but a syndemic- and we cant afford go backwards. So many worked so hard to make this syringe service program happen,  to create a template for the rest of rural/ middle America to connect people to care. I hope cooler heads prevail. https://t.co/2IybuGm1Q6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DYK adults between 20 and 49 accounted for almost 70% of #COVID19 spread last year?  Simply put, the primary reservoir for this virus in the U.S. is young, unvaccinated Americans.  So if you want to speed our return to a sense of normalcy, consider getting your vax!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You dont have to die from #Covid19 for it to wreck havoc on your life.  More than one in ten recovering health care workers experienced significant symptoms, such as loss of taste or smell, fatigue and breathing problems, eight months later.  So please consider getting your vax!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wil_cooke: Urgent help needed to keep our syringe services program open. Healthcare workers, harm reduction specialists, and first resp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dan_ness https://t.co/rPDpmNUuRL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And similar to COVID there are some on the sidelines who think if only youd run a certain play or featured a particular player (or banished other players to the sidelines), wed surely have won.  But both youth soccer and beating a pandemic are team efforts.  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coaching my daughters soccer team and there are lots of similarities to coaching  through #Covid19. Different backgrounds. Good listeners   poorer ones. Great players  ones who struggle. Different skill sets  levels of engagement/ interest. But we cant win without everyone. https://t.co/RFsHu72SjQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MahaSoxFan So how many deaths wouldve occurred if we had Europes death rate? Not zero. Not even close.  Every death was tragic and we need to make sure this doesnt happen again. Blaming everything and every death on Trump is putting our heads in the sand to many other important issues.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MahaSoxFan My desire to end the pandemic surpasses any desire to fight with you on Twitter, or any political concerns- clearly you and I differ on that. Be well. Ill keep trying this engage everyone. You can beat Trump with 51%, but Dr Fauci says we need 70-85% to beat Covid!  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RHDusi It isnt about what credit anyone deserves at this point.  Its about crafting the right message and facilitating the right engagement to end the pandemic.  So the question is, what do you hate more- Covid or republicans? https://t.co/rlqOTseQBJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RHDusi Youre angry.  Thats okay. But Im not looking for any personal credit. Im saying you cant engage Trump supporters- who you need to get to community immunity and end the pandemic- if you deny him any credit for vaccines.  Hate the virus more than your political foes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MahaSoxFan So youre saying you misspoke, and the prior administration wasnt alone responsible for anywhere near 500,000 deaths, right?  This is more than just a spat over politics.  Blaming everything on Trump and ignoring the many other systemic concerns leaves us unprepared in future.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MahaSoxFan Youre changing the subject/ putting up strawmen to avoid the direct question I asked you.  If we had the same leadership and mortality rate as Europe, would that have equaled zero deaths?  While acknowledging faults, Is it accurate to blame every tragic death on the leadership?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RHDusi Saying it once (while also saying the opposite - Eg we were left with nothing) is less than adequate.  Trump has told his supporters to get vaccinated.  We need both Presidents to do more.   https://t.co/opzymQlzJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MahaSoxFan I readily admit things werent perfect- we must learn and do better. But it has been  continues to be a scientifically  morally disingenuous argument to blame every death solely on politics/ leadership. Public health underfunding and a nasty virus did most of the damage.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MahaSoxFan Honest question- does that mean if someone - anyone else- was in charge- wed have had zero deaths?  Did England,France, or Spain do significantly better?  Or was this just a very difficult public health situation?  And does it mean Biden is responsible for 1000 deaths/ day now?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_Tall_Sister But Im assuming you completely forgot (or are willing to ignore) that Fauci (current leader of our Nations efforts) and CDC and WHO are who was giving that advice based on the science at the time?  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD And this isnt about me. Its about us not being able to move forward unless/ until we can acknowledge and move past the political biases we all have, and extend genuine outreach to those we dont agree with- particularly when we must engage them for the common good!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD One of the most difficult (and damaging) aspects of my communication efforts as SG was that almost nothing I said was judged based on the supporting science or context- it was viewed- even by scientists- through the lens of whether it supported Trump (or Biden), or was critical.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD Agree. And interestingly enough, your point on federal authorities for masks mandates was a point I was making this time last year, and got pilloried for.  Weve got to not just acknowledge the trade offs, but resist framing them politically/ to support or attack on side.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD Agree.  And as I lay out in my op Ed, its both about the right messengers and the right message. And part of that message is helping skeptics feel like people they trust were part of vax development.  We do the same thing w communities of color. https://t.co/IYf49yXoPy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD The point being, no one thing is going to flip a switch on hesitancy. But its about understanding the ecosystem and behavioral motivators.  You need people to feel like theyre part of an effort.  psychological  logistical reasons to say yes,   reasons to say no.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD Sustaining the narrative that the prior administration had nothing to do with vaccine rollout does nothing to incentivize Trump or his followers to embrace the historic achievement of the vaccines development.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtulGroverMD Its interesting that no one who mentions my request to Trump, mentions my just as important call to Biden in the very next sentence... Meanwhile, the Biden administration should give Trump more credit for development of the vaccines...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bartnewland Thats an impossible question to answer. But if its an obstacle for even a small percentage, it will help. Theres little to nothing youre going to do now on the trust side thats flint to create massive change.  Its about patience, persistence, and grinding it out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As vaccine manufacturers complete further studies, which will eventually lead to expanded eligibility among minors, it will help show skeptics that the authorized COVID vaccines are safe, Adams wrote.   https://t.co/pdoc6H26FT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Those who got vaccinated early on were generally high risk,  willing to take a vaccine authorized for emergency use. But many who are lower risk understandably ask if the benefits justify taking a medication that has not received the full and traditional FDA stamp of approval.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My #Saturday thoughts:  community (ie herd) immunity = trust + access. Trust will  when @US_FDA fully approves vaccines,  access will  when vaccines become available to those under 16.   Opinion | Jerome Adams: What the herd needs to hear  https://t.co/THyBFjNlF0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnQuinton3 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bored?  Mindlessly scrolling through Twitter on your phone looking for something interesting- maybe even life altering- to do?    Text your zip code to 438829 (getvax), and share/ reply with what you find out... https://t.co/NF4hLvQNPt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dadsaysjokes: As I put my car in reverse, I thought to myself...  This takes me back.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caitlindsutton ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got an afternoon full of zoom meetings, and dont feel like putting on nice suit pants.  But Im still afraid the one time I go with shorts or sweatpants Ill have to urgently stand up for something and be found out... Opinions?  https://t.co/Mi65I4sHb5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cbscannerbos @US_FDA What do you mean?  I believe in choice and a free market- but that all depends on transparency.  The tobacco industry has been shown in court to have lied about the dangers of cigarettes and about marketing certain products to minorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theres never been a better to quit smoking.  For more info, check out the Surgeon Generals report I issued on smoking cessation last year!    https://t.co/PobMgtzmP8 https://t.co/aMTS3ZReb7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI - a monumental move by @US_FDA happened this week.  More people died last year from smoking than #Covid19   Banning menthol  flavors is a vaccine against cancer and cardiovascular disease!   FDA Moves To Ban Cigarettes And Flavored Cigars https://t.co/zmIu53ENgH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im an optimist, so Im just gonna assume all these people at #NFLDraft celebrations and parties indoors  w/o masks  are vaccinated...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_fnp @TimScottSC Didnt you just accuse me in an earlier tweet of bashing leadership and being too political vs sticking to medicine?  Trump wasnt my guy.  He was the elected President of the United States- which means he was everyones guy.  And I served the country which elected him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_fnp @TimScottSC Well Im sorry you feel that way.  Did you see all my tweets yesterday about  vaccine access?  This is my personal account, so I mix in a lot of my personal experiences with health content.  I wont be offended if youre looking for something else and unfollow me!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DJDianna @rranders32 With a name like Moscow...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mama_feral I absolutely agree with that too. Just saying- I see you comment every now and then and I always appreciate your perspective.  Twitter at its best is people seeing the world through other peoples eyes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@United_Against_ @space_case12 @TimScottSC Thats not what this thread is about.  See my original tweet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrandonnJG @TimScottSC https://t.co/Bli4Xi4lx5 https://t.co/Qp84IcqGDa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlakEmoji @coachglen @TimScottSC https://t.co/jkMhs19gSM https://t.co/WZT47yQq2g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CatEars14 I dont think it helps facilitate engagement and discussion- and thats my point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scalone_maria Good for your daughter!  And we have to acknowledge there is overt racism still in many places and people, and we must fight it.  But the bias so many are concerned about- and have trouble talking about- is the bias that no one intends or is as clear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As much as I hate to bring levity to a serious discussion, Avenue Q said it best- everyones a little bit racist, sometimes, but it doesnt mean were all out committing hate crimes. You can be a good person, and still acknowledge areas / systems you can improve upon. https://t.co/Ub16Ry1xBN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very few people think of themselves as racist, but also very few of us make it through life without experiencing the + or - impact of ingrained and historical bias in our government, healthcare, educational, and personal finance opportunities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We absolutely must find a way to talk about  distinguish between racist people with racist intentions, and racist systems perpetuated by well meaning people. Because the two issues are both real, but VERY different, and one can be a part of the latter without being a racist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidBr70826125 @TimScottSC My experience count no more- but also no less- than others. I think the question we all should be asking ourselves- the actual topic of this thread- is does anyones experience give them to right to be hateful towards others- and especially whilst decrying hate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Michael83142872 @Kahntact @TimScottSC You cant tackle really tough and ingrained structural insults if you push people away with personal insults. And you cant claim the moral high ground on the former while showing the opposite character as it pertains to the latter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Michael83142872 @Kahntact @TimScottSC And for the record, though a simple Google search will show you Ive fought to address infant and maternal mortality disparities throughout my career, Ive been called Uncle Tom and house Nigger by people who didnt think I represented African Americans well enough.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@coachglen @TimScottSC And thats your prerogative. But the irony is Im willing to bet you have at some point in your life felt like people didnt believe you or validate your lived experience. And I bet you felt it was wrong when it happened to you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also happens with many who proudly call themselves Christians.  Many people preach and claim the mantle of tolerance, but are quick to show their own intolerance- usually based on their political beliefs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And people are already taking/ using this wrong  for their own purposes.  Im an independent and this wasnt a swipe at Dems-it was an acknowledgment of the fact that some people use their politics to justify actions and language they claim to disdain. And its my experience.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beckwoodworth @TimScottSC 1) Its usually clear from the types of conversations it comes up in 2) So many people nowadays wear their politics on their sleeves (or at least state it in their Twitter profiles)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrBonillaOnc @TimScottSC As I prefaced- Im not talking about the entire speech.  Im talking about the one part I noted. It is my own personal lived experience.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@classicalfan @TimScottSC It was definitely in a political context- but its hard nowadays to separate the two, as everything about health has become so politicized.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kahntact @TimScottSC This is from a company account?  Im not dismissing your lived experience or anyone elses.  Why are you dismissing mine?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@inclusionchick Read your tweet maam.  Is that accountability? Or is that you making yourself feel better by attacking me on Twitter on a completely unrelated topic.  Again when you read your tweet, is it something Jesus wouldve tweeted?   Feel free to DM me if you really want to talk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I debated posting this as I know people on both sides will take it the wrong way. But this part of what @TimScottSC said last night is my lived experience. Ive been called racial epithets by progressives far more than by conservatives. Be the change you wish to see. https://t.co/hEeXQsJtn9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dudleyland Im not sure what youre talking about, or if youre sure what youre talking about.  But either way youre on the wrong thread.  This ones about potatoes and syrup!   Have a great day and be kind to your neighbors!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PostRepublicanZ Wrong Steve!  This ones about potatoes, syrup, and skiing!   ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@inclusionchick I see youre a big advocate for #Catholicschools!  Im catholic and was always taught to treat others with the kindness youd want extended in return. Maybe you missed that day/ lesson/ sermon? Praying for you. #wwjd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roxtober19 Whats a creemie?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When I was Surgeon General I had a goal of visiting all 50 states- because everyone deserves to see their government leaders. Then #COVID19 happened.  But Ive still made it to every state except Idaho and Vermont.  Tell me why and when (professionally + personally) I should go.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking update: the rightful recipients of the aforementioned cake have been found, and will pick up said cake tomorrow.  My kids are grumpy about the whole thing, but I feel as though I passed some big cosmic karma test!    @wetakethecake https://t.co/AJb6NWx8wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The kids are like, dad it literally says, We take the cake on the box! Its telling us to take the cake!  My response- its probably some Hitchkockian test- you eat the cake and then you lose your ability to taste cake for the rest of your life! Im not falling for that...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey @wetakethecake - any advice?    Now my kids are hounding me about cake!  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gretchemaben So how does it end?  Do I eat the cake?  We need to know!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gretchemaben No way?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A cake was sent to our house, but it was addressed to/ for the former owners. The kids and I are having a spirited debate regarding what constitutes reasonable/ sufficient effort to get the cake to its rightful owners, and then have no choice but to eat it vs waste it...  https://t.co/Pz3CQMx1Fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DblockWWT Always important to me to state that Im pro vax. Especially when so many want to use any opening to advance a different agenda!  Its not virtue signaling- its normalizing science and public health!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got this DM on Twitter.  Sharing it because I believe in the power of positive messages.  You may not always see the change, and it may never be fast enough, but people are watching how we interact with one another. Positive engagement  positive outcomes!   https://t.co/arcoU3Nu6t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drjohnwhyte https://t.co/XjH6zh5CBk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I talk about this in my recent Op Ed.  Respecting the US/ FDA approval process is an important part of maintaining trust in our system. I got vaccinated- and recommend others do.  But I wouldnt force anyone to take an unapproved drug. Most lawyers agree.  https://t.co/THyBFjNlF0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than a little concerning example of cart before horse- especially coming from an AG. Im as pro vax and pro public good as anyone, but weve never in history mandated a non FDA unapproved vaccine.  Lets cross the approval bridge first, and build vs diminish trust. https://t.co/ti5sTgUtEA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MCG2000 @_Grand_Wazoo_ Thanks for helping out your fellow citizen Miriam!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suzannebuzz @ChelseaClinton Youre carrying around a lot of pain and hurt and I understand that. But hate-  no matter how well deserved or who directed towards- Almost always hurts the hater more than the hated.  Especially so if you end up asking/ needing the people you scorn to then assist you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suzannebuzz @ChelseaClinton And again youre still obsessing over Trump/ miss the point. What you do only matters so much. You can win an election with 51% but it takes 85% to beat Covid.  Again its clear youre angry- thats OK. But we cant let anger/ hate for each other surpass our desire to beat Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickPulosMD Agree completely!   Ive always said herd (or community) immunity depends on the size/ place/ risk/ prior infection etc of your herd. Could be your home or your workplace or your college campus. Its not one number or national threshold.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MCG2000 @_Grand_Wazoo_ Check out the article!  I talk about vax clinics at worksites, churches, and schools.  And we need to be more aggressive/ creative about mobile and pop up clinics!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we reach the supply/ demand tipping point and daily #COVID19 vaccinations drop off, weve got to figure out how to to get vaccines in doctors offices. Even with storage requirements, it can be done (Eg thaw and send 5-10 doses at a time- theyre good for 5 days after thaw). https://t.co/jZtLxiPyLZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PostOpinions: @JeromeAdamsMD: "Americans say they trust their own doctor the most. While there are logistical and storage challenges, r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StompemAll @PostOpinions Great question- one tragic answer is the situation in India right now.  Many people thought that they were nearing or at herd immunity via natural infection last year.  Unfortunately now people are dying in the streets because the hospitals are overwhelmed.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>