<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: The COVID-19 vaccine is free, it's been rigorously tested, and it's saving lives. All Idahoans age 16+ can get vaccinated any tim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #COVID19 vaccines can help us get back to doing the things we love.  As of May 3, more than 147 million people in the United St]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: CDH is now offering free customizable presentations tailored to your community group or employer on COVID-19 vaccines.   If y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: To date, a total of 1,074,470 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 607,393 people have received vaccine and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Everyone 16 and older can get a COVID-19 vaccine in Idaho. There is no longer a requirement to live or work in Idaho to get vacci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: St. Luke's launched a mobile unit that's bringing life-saving COVID-19 vaccine to people in the Caldwell, Ketchum, Hailey, and Bo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Getting vaccinated is now easier than ever. Simply visit https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML and youll have the option to pre-register or sc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: Do you have questions about the Johnson  Johnson vaccine? Below is information in English and Spanish on the safety and effe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #COVID19 vaccines are an important tool to stop this pandemic. Millions of people in the U.S. have been safely vaccinated and a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: After you are fully vaccinated, you can travel with fewer restrictions. CDC says fully vaccinated people can travel international]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KTVB: St. Luke's offering walk-in appointments at all its vaccine locations https://t.co/0kNADuy2rb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: The recording of today's COVID-19 media briefing is now available: https://t.co/n996DRWJrZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: COVID-19 QA: COVID-19 and long-term-care facilities https://t.co/8bA2q9Ch9t via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Idahos neighbors can now access the vaccine in our state. #idahocovid19 https://t.co/G12ifrCVY3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: New CDC guidance on mask wearing: https://t.co/dobOSf0Qu1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: People fully vaccinated against #COVID19 can participate in some indoor events safely, without much risk. Outdoor visits and ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: DHW COVID-19 media briefing set for 2:30 p.m. MDT Tuesday: https://t.co/0mCrfatVj5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Do your part. #WearAMask   #SlowTheSpread of #COVID19. Make sure your mask fits snugly against the sides of your face w/ no g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: After you are fully vaccinated, CDC says you can gather indoors with unvaccinated people of any age from one other household with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cityofpocatello: One of the most common myths surrounding the COVID-19 vaccines is that they cause infertility in women. Watch to find]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: An Update from DHW Director Dave Jeppesen: Are you fully vaccinated? https://t.co/aqx0pQUGi6 via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: (1/2) After you are fully vaccinated, you can ditch the mask when you gather with other fully-vaccinated people! CDC says fully v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Everyone 16 and older who lives or works in Idaho can get the COVID-19 vaccine. And its free  there are no out-of-pocket costs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Its impossible to know how COVID-19 will affect you. All of the COVID-19 vaccines effectively prevent serious illness and hospit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: The recording of today's media briefing on COVID-19 in Idaho is available: https://t.co/vASKcK5Woh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cityofpocatello: The mRNA is basically instructions for your immune system to know what to do if it encounters coronavirus and then to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Milestone reached: More than 400,000 people who live or work in Idaho are now fully vaccinated. Way to go Idaho! An additional 15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NampaPIO: Por que vacunarse contra el COVID-19? (Thank you to Healthwise for producing this short video highlighting Nampa resident An]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: IDAHO COVID-19 HOT SPOTS: The 3 counties with the highest COVID-19 infection rates in Idaho include Elmore, Bonneville, and Jeffe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: An Update from DHW Director Dave Jeppesen: Johnson  Johnson Vaccine https://t.co/rSHDFqbVUK via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SWDHIDAHO: Starting Saturday, April 17, Southwest District Health will host a weekly COVID-19 vaccine walk-in clinic at our Caldwell Lo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #WearAMask to prevent getting and spreading #COVID19. If you use a disposable mask, the knot and tuck method can help your mask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Join us at 10 a.m. Wednesday on Facebook Live: Deputy state epidemiologist Dr. Kathryn Turner will answer questions about the tem]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: DHW recommends Idaho providers follow FDA and CDC guidance to temporarily pause administering the Johnson  Johnson vaccine: http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: Ada, Boise and Valley County are in category 2 (YELLOW). Elmore County remains in category 3 (RED). Current data for all coun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: COVID-19 media briefing set for 4:30 p.m. Tuesday: https://t.co/9muyFpr8zD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: IDAHO COVID-19 HOT SPOTS: The 3 counties with the highest COVID-19 infection rates in Idaho include Madison, Caribou, and Jeffers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Frontline workers, your work has been critical in keeping our economy moving during the pandemic. If youve felt stress and anxie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #WearAMask with multiple layers that covers your nose AND mouth and secure it under your chin. Make sure it fits snugly against]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: This chart breaks down what is known about each of the COVID-19 vaccines authorized for emergency use in the U.S. More informatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Protect yourself and your loved ones by getting the COVID-19 vaccine. The vaccine has been tested. It's safe and effective: https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorLittle: I signed an executive order today banning any State of Idaho governmental entity from requiring so-called vaccine pass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: REMINDER: Today at 2 pm @GovernorLittle will make an announcement regarding the COVID-19 vaccine in Idaho.   Watch the announ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StLukesHealth: Join us in the battle to eradicate COVID-19. Get vaccinated. Vaccination openings are available this week at St. Lukes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @siphidaho: Johnson and Johnson 1 Dose Vaccine appointments are now available. Schedule on-line at https://t.co/KfUlWsMM7a or call South]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Join us at 10 a.m. Wednesday on Facebook Live: Deputy state epidemiologist Dr. Kathryn Turner will answer questions about coronav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IdahoReports: Wednesday at 2pm MT, @GovernorLittle will make a COVID-19 vaccine announcement. It will be broadcast live on the @IdahoPT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: DHW's COVID-19 Vaccine FAQ has been updated with information about minors seeking a COVID-19 vaccine, breakthrough cases, vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: COVID-19 QA: Breakthrough cases and variants https://t.co/wRhmC3ZPDG via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: COVID-19 vaccines are safe and effective. Dr. Hafid Mantilla is urging his patients to get vaccinated in this Spanish-language PS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Idaho is reporting 103 breakthrough cases as of today. Of them, three were hospitalized. All of the hospitalized patients had med]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: COVID-19 media briefing set for Tuesday: https://t.co/K3LE1sbqQ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Hundreds of thousands of Idahoans have gotten a COVID-19 vaccine because its safe and it works. The vaccine is the best shot we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: From DHW Director Dave Jeppesen: Im Encouraging all Idahoans to Choose to get the COVID-19 Vaccine https://t.co/XBbXq6OkHJ via @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: On Sunday, April 18, CDH and Albertsons will host a COVID-19 vaccine clinic at Idaho City Middle/High School.  The Pfizer vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: People fully vaccinated against #COVID19 can travel within the United States and do not need COVID-19 testing or post-travel se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: A mask is NOT a substitute for staying at least 6 feet away from others. To protect yourself and others from #COVID19, #WearAMa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Fully vaccinated people may travel, CDC says, a change in guidance as evidence grows that the shots help prevent spread]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Update on breakthrough cases: As of today, 100 COVID-19 infections have been reported among fully vaccinated people in Idaho. The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @audreydutton: Appointments for the last @CrushTheCurveID COVID-19 vaccine event filled up within hours. This one has about twice as man]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Protect yourself, your loved ones and neighbors by getting a COVID-19 vaccine! Keep our communities safe. Do your part and get th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Idaho's COVID-19 vaccine allocation is increasing. Next week the state will receive a total of 82,190 first doses of  vaccine. Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: CDH invites anyone who is 16-years  older  wants to receive protection through the COVID-19 vaccine, to seek an appointment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Studies and surveys have found 50%-80% of people continue to have symptoms up to 3 months after contracting COVID-19 even though]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AARPIdaho: Our town hall with @GovernorLittle begins in a few minutes. Join here: https://t.co/BSi4cUMAKu #idleg #idpol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: If you are sick with #COVID19, or think you might have COVID-19, #WearAMask that fits snugly over your mouth and nose whenever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Even as some restrictions ease, lets keep protecting ourselves and others. #WearAMask. Stay 6 ft apart. Avoid crowds  poorly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: A new @CDCMMWR finds mRNA #COVID19 vaccines highly effective in preventing COVID-19 among health care  other essential workers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Starting today, people who live or work in Idaho who are 16 years of age or older, and have at least one medical condition become]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorLittle: Starting April 5, all Idahoans aged 16 and older, regardless of their age, medical condition, or occupation, will be ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IdahoPTV: ICYMI: Stream Gov. Brad Little's update today on #idahoCovid19.  Idahoans 16+ with at least one medical condition can get vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RedCross: Getting your #COVIDVaccine can help protect yourself and others from #COVID19. This is especially important for high-risk peo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Frontline workers, youve been keeping us all safe, informed, and fed. Its our turn to take care of you. Contact us for free ser]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: (1/2) Myth: A COVID-19 vaccine thats 60%-80% effective isn't worth taking.  Fact: No vaccine is perfect, but a vaccine with 60-8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: @GovernorLittle will hold a press conference tomorrow at noon regarding the COVID-19 vaccine in Idaho. Watch the announcement]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: (1/2) The pre-registration system allows people who live or work in Idaho to add their names to one waiting list regardless of wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Reminder: This week, DHW's media briefing has been rescheduled for Wednesday: https://t.co/nvNiFa0dEZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: In the coming weeks and months, #COVID19 vaccine supply will increase.  As of March 22, more than 82.7 million people in the Un]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: One Year Later: Support group series highlights resilience strategies learned from a year of COVID-19: https://t.co/jCXg8ebwNF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Starting today, People who live or work in Idaho between the ages of 55 and 64 are eligible for COVID-19 vaccine regardless of me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @primaryhealth: Everyone 55+, regardless of health condition, may now schedule their COVID vaccine appointment at Primary Health!   Even]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: People who live or work in Idaho who are frontline essential workers OR between the ages of 55 and 64 with at least one medical c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: We all have a role to play in ending the pandemic. In the past year, there have been over 29 million cases  530,000 deaths fro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: A Reminder from Director Dave Jeppesen: Choosing to get the COVID-19 Vaccine Will Protect Your Friends, Family, and Community htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Idaho COVID-19 Vaccine Advisory Committee to meet Friday: https://t.co/VCNbRhepiE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: Join us at 10 a.m. TODAY on Facebook Live: DHW Deputy Director Lori Wolff will discuss Idaho's COVID-19 Vaccine Pre-Registration]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nicoleMfoy: In Spanish: #idahocovid19  https://t.co/mz8XqjCCzU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nicoleMfoy: !! please remember and share this updating list of upcoming clinics for underrepresented groups like Latinos and others lik]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cityofpocatello: Lorri Shaver, Shaver Pharmacy Pharmacist and Owner, tackles myths surrounding COVID-19 vaccines and some of the most c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: Were in week 14 of COVID-19 vaccines arriving  being offered in Idaho. Many enrolled providers have appointments available]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: If you are getting a 2-dose #COVID19 vaccine, plan to get your second shot as close as possible to the recommendations3 weeks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: If you are 65 and older and you havent gotten a COVID-19 vaccine, please use the state's new pre-scheduling system below to put]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: As of March 14, 627,352 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been distributed in Idaho. Of those, 526,141 doses have been administered]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: DHW created a chart breaking down what is known about each of the COVID-19 vaccines authorized for emergency use in the U.S. More]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: COVID-19 vaccine media briefing set for Tuesday: https://t.co/QT6GT8ZNV1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: If you get a #COVID19 vaccine, wait at least 14 days before getting any other vaccine, including those for flu or shingles. If]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: If you are 65 and older and you havent gotten a COVID-19 vaccine, please use the state's new pre-scheduling system below to put]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: The percentage of PCR COVID-19 tests performed statewide between 2/28 and 3/6 that were positive is 4.6. 23,760 PCR tests were pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: In case you missed it: DHW Director Dave Jeppesen offered remarks about the one-year anniversary of COVID-19 in Idaho (coming up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDHW: To date, 585,382 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been distributed in Idaho. Of those, 470,647 doses have been administered to peop]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>