<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[14...cmon man https://t.co/QLWWQyYzyZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Hahahahah. Great Halloween ad. Truly scary. https://t.co/vDOnFFXKVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get in a basement fast..get a helmet too craig..you are surely gonna need it Better buckle up in your easy chair this may be a rough ride for you https://t.co/zgDejcOpLk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When he calls us chumps ...thats not uniting anyone #Trump2020Landslide https://t.co/hqolzR4OWd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wah wah waaaaaahhhhhhhhh https://t.co/S5LQKZiSCg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: Rt if you're proud to be a Trump chump #MAGA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hes the She Devil https://t.co/gi8Z0OoQEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep..did that last wk..matter of fact https://t.co/FJOFWOfATl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Evil Hilary clinton..can't believe she's even still around https://t.co/XuyJitEleC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sassy_decorator: @HillaryClinton https://t.co/Wm78QHnCB3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maryo52937133: @HillaryClinton Thank God you failed so horribly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Shawna_mari3: @HillaryClinton #TheFindereDocs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaveNYviii: FBI Vault Releases "The Finders" Pedophile Sex Cult Investigation Documents  Why was the investigation deemed a CIA "intern]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JustFollowingP3: @xeni @writersblocla Speaking of the CIA, I thought youd have been all over the declassification of the FBI vault on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FO https://t.co/90sMhSbu7r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScriberrNews: Declassified @FBI documents, released earlier this month, revealed US intelligence cover-up of a child abuse and ritual s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CynthiaYeager5: Trump making it a priority to stop the trafficking of children...all those people who flew to Epstein Island should be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jess_Deplorable: https://t.co/msaHMuh66w people need to read these documents...it clearly talks about the intelligence agency being inv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashekyu: Reposting this even though it'll go totally under the radar, and won't make mainstream news, despite alluding to the CIA traff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PiratesLookAt40: @__TruthSeeker_ Here's a link to Ted Gunderson's investigation into #TheFindersDocs   https://t.co/8OeYzmt77O  It is t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brit yo !!..take your head out the sand https://t.co/MoOagenqeb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MARS0411: @brithume You are defending the indefensible. Stop! In light of doc drop on #TheFindersDocs you should not be supporting any]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ERockRice: 300 pages of docs about US taxpayer-funded satanic child sex-slave cult. #TheFindersDocs #TheFinders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ElizabethleaVos: More ridiculous #censorship: latest interview with Graham Elwood on his show re: #TheFinders cult was demonetized.   S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaveNYviii: Finders documents included instructions on how to obtain children through trading, kidnapping and purchase. (p 9) The Finde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaveNYviii: A Washington based computer company that employed Finders members provided computer training for CIA personnel (p 250-251)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNewsMom: @HillaryClinton @oaaselect Lol. https://t.co/GhjqpA9iak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrDeDente02: @HillaryClinton @bIacksheepaway  https://t.co/UbMiW0Lkk3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Oh hey hil....Birthday greetings  from Bill and monica! https://t.co/h9k0votCVu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GOPChairwoman: By reversing the tax cuts @realDonaldTrump signed into law, Joe Biden would raise taxes on 82% of Americans.  The Americ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NRA @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/230prKD2bJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: Who the hell would remain silent if they were accused of smoking crack, harboring child porn, and posing seductively w/ t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DuckDuckGo: We must do better than subjecting our students to surveillance  violations of their privacy... better than allowing algor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/EvBM6gs7A7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Buzz Aldrin picks Arizona Republican McSally over fellow astronaut Kelly | Fox News https://t.co/O9p28xrSwf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michele349: @1776Stonewall @Vincat12020 Vote Kim Ogg out of office. I will keep tweeting this until it is done. That woman has to go. #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He wont be though.... https://t.co/Rw5QbMJRvk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ronalddahl0069: @1776Stonewall Doesnt biden want make them all legal immigrants ifnhe is elected, another reason to vote trump]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ndlily75: @1776Stonewall @nedryun We are willing to shut down an entire country "because not one person should die" from a random virus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArtValley818_ https://t.co/rbMucbU8UV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnrs48 @CNN @elizamackintosh https://t.co/fPPpFuTjJW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MekonnenYaredS2: @CNN @elizamackintosh https://t.co/EdFimaQmy0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cry me a fucking river cnn https://t.co/JAPbkQUQYO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well if its a blue state isn't it the dems suppressing the vote then ?? RESIGN GOOFY CHICK!! https://t.co/MIZ3kkqypE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @yegg: While Googles anti-competitive practices hurt companies like us, the negative impact on society and democracy wrought by their s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Trump has had tons of results one need not look to far to discover them. Its called the Internet. They need to discern whats truth too. Its not that hard. https://t.co/LtwWozuaad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/39HL9iSTrA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomFitton: If Sen. Harris is within 100 feet of the polling place entrance, than she would be in violation of Ohio law that prohibits s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WhiteHouse: In Maine, Medicare health plan premiums are down 27% under President @realDonaldTrump! https://t.co/FQWjc9ColJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Facts!!! Learn them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They blamed Bush for the housing debacle https://t.co/iB6mloBHhA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomFitton: DEVELOPING: Pennsylvanias voting rolls are such a mess that even PA cant tell court details of how dirty or clean they ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exactly Michelle! https://t.co/9lFkNcAw2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same! #TRUMP4EVA https://t.co/irnMkPqdqM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They seem to have this thing for lying! #Trump2020Landslide https://t.co/zFIkwwWM9t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get off my lawn!! https://t.co/KPBrG81m8I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure...4 states with the biggest population would choose the President  Fuck you Ben...were not doing that cuz its not flippin fair!!! You hacks will stop at nothing to tip the scales to win!! #Trump2020Landslide https://t.co/OHRZBsp5IV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/AkcHuNbiYQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Yanky_Pollak: Trump just played the Biden hairy legs video at his New Hampshire rally... https://t.co/UCkwhjBWy3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: This is enraging. Elmer Manzano was here illegally, jailed for violent crimes 6+ times and never got deported. Houstons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrumpWarRoom: Joe Biden continues to LIE about his familys business deals with foreign countries.  There are a lot of questions here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Niiice!! https://t.co/vXqdEU5HvS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Or Joe Buyden!! https://t.co/yczVhcBvXI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Get off my Lawn"  https://t.co/ctisg86kZ7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And hurry the hell up then! https://t.co/BOMAQCzBnK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ruh roh!! https://t.co/kwuDFmXUcI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Niiiiiice!!! https://t.co/8X5GOJcVnU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I had more folks in my locked down churchs worship service this am!! https://t.co/m67KWYFOSe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whoa!! This is an epic crowd!! #Trump2020Landslide https://t.co/oS17xTK4vV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RichardGrenell: cc: @NYGovCuomo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh hell yah I am!! https://t.co/vCYCmrIaJI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BlackLivesMaga https://t.co/JtfpgXzGH3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: The only thing worse than COVID-19 would be BIDEN-20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is quite disgusting Candace!! Happy Baby!! https://t.co/VBrYiWAZ2b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: Three basic facts Joe Biden has not denied:  1. Hunter Bidens emails are authentic.  2. Joe Biden is in fact the big guy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marklevinshow: As*holes at Lincoln Project spread Iranian disinformation https://t.co/N39LWpPKuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden could be blackmailed as president  (if he were to win)by china They didnt register as foreign agents FARA, allegedly they violated the logan act as well https://t.co/iuliGbSA3H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did the behavior come from being abused homself?? Hmmmm https://t.co/AGoaJdKIG5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DFBHarvard: [RETWWET] If you believe you  your children can look up to Amy Coney Barlett as an excellent role-model.  https://t.co/Kwf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the equivalent of the Obama apology Tour...2009...cmon man..joe you lost the election for sure with this ad..#TRUMP2020ToSaveAmerica https://t.co/Dekb8AwmL5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @SoadKousheshi https://t.co/C1v9dJv9P6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrumpWarRoom: Joe Biden won't have the advantage of a media ally with a mute button when he has to meet with a world leader.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: The Biden family aggressively leveraged the Biden family name to make millions of dollars from foreign entities even thoug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let's hope it does!! https://t.co/ya6GHDjIE6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've got better!! #TRUMP2020ToSaveAmerica  #Trump2020Landslide https://t.co/xv3ON86j3H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[W I N N I N G  MR PRESIDENT !! #TRUMP2020ToSaveAmerica  #Trump2020Landslide https://t.co/zh0jDVknZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DFBHarvard: [RETWEET] If you're in favor for the appointment of a Special Counsel to investigate all things Hunter/Joe Biden  Pay-to-P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DFBHarvard: Don't Go Democrat!  Instead, walk away  go RED!  #VoteTrump  #WalkAwayMovement  #WalkAwayFromDemocrats  #WalkAwayFromDemoc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Richard Fowler is a disgruntled Democrat Loser masquerading as a journalist! Richard Fowler: Senate rushes Barrett Supreme Court confirmation  GOP wants her to help Trump win election  https://t.co/ydtpD5IfsJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow...do you get paid to spread  "dis information??.....HE WAS AQUITTED ....you left out that FINITE DETAIL...youre gonna need a helmet Life's gonna  come at you fast , come nov 3rd #Trump2020LandslideVictory https://t.co/5gRjKUY7du]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ your certainly entitled to be ignorant, but dude...you abuse the privelege!! https://t.co/R25rxek9ZH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AriFleischer: 60 Minutes sat on a story in 2012 showing Pres. Obama refusing to call the attack in Benghazi a terrorist attack, contrar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @prageru: The left has left liberals behind.   @RubinReport https://t.co/8fm1C9lM2G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFirstonTV: New Trump ad on Biden, Hunter  Ukraine   https://t.co/xwoMpmDu1v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wah,wah,waaaaaaahhhhhhh https://t.co/qLTm9uHoie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: Morning Patriots https://t.co/fY2SEC498Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @glennbeck: Over the past year, I've been investigating Hunter Biden's odd business dealings in Ukraine  China while his father was VP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlazeTV: .@StuDoesAmerica:   How much MORE must @realDonaldTrump condemn white supremacy!?   In 2017, did the president REALLY say that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theblaze: WATCH: Rudy Giuliani says he has PROOF Joe Biden was business partners with Chinese Communists #ICYMI https://t.co/XimRg62yfX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its all they got......Shitspeak!! https://t.co/RWRUQPAKFt]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>