<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA['From the desk of Donald J. Trump': Former U.S. president launches 'beacon of freedom' blog ahead of Facebook decision https://t.co/Tz7GNZsLlG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stellantis says chip shortage worsening, could linger into 2022 https://t.co/OQ5L0hnTgO https://t.co/JA61F7Gg3x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senior Swiss diplomat in Iran found dead after fall from high-rise https://t.co/wb4uQVxots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATED Top court orders Indian government to present oxygen plan https://t.co/L8WgkYf7Pl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden aims to vaccinate 70 per cent of American adults by July 4 https://t.co/GmzNjBOD5b https://t.co/WQ0SvKaIIK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we mix and match vaccines? One big question for two COVID-19 doses https://t.co/9yauYCnhpT https://t.co/9I62r02oD6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schools should allow peanuts but stock up on EpiPens, study says https://t.co/I9RE2hWM73]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CHOM morning man Terry DiMonte is stepping away at the end of May after 43 years and lots of memories. https://t.co/BqJ01dK6nG https://t.co/vjYk8KFK7K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India's foreign minister out of G7 meeting over COVID-19 risk https://t.co/NIXjbfyA0r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 things to know for Wednesday, May 5, 2021 https://t.co/Osx3wOhoSw https://t.co/WyW2gL30D0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 things to know on https://t.co/ROXBkUbYGi for Wednesday, May 5, 2021: Alberta death, PM dispels vaccine concerns, future of COVID-19 cases https://t.co/x9WWlZhQGo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indian government faces lockdown calls, contempt charges https://t.co/ZAE3eBDDD2 https://t.co/PidvnoDl3m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pentagon tracking out-of-control Chinese rocket that could re-enter Earth's atmosphere https://t.co/B9S20rbwVb https://t.co/PyCJ19yesn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maralee speaks with Dr. Kendiss Olafson, who is involved in a study looking at how COVID-19's impact on grieving has affected Manitobans. https://t.co/2uBKMmq3NP https://t.co/9FaVZdqMap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook board's Trump decision could have wider impacts https://t.co/Jr3WYw4BlA https://t.co/oVAVMTZirV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[French reporter kidnapped by jihadist rebels in north Mali https://t.co/IRihfimyAi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World's oldest person pulls out of Olympic torch relay https://t.co/05Z9g0wvoD https://t.co/cavFPIK1JW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thousands left out of plan to give workers permanent residency: Migrant Rights Network #CdnPoli @MigrantRightsCA  https://t.co/V2gVWUfZ9t https://t.co/7JdlGRXo8X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trudeau Liberals got earful on police racism from concerned public, emails reveal https://t.co/BuqtYyLiIu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Further evidence will be coming on the possibility of COVID-19 vaccine mixing and matching as the science evolves. Avis Favaro explains. https://t.co/sIH0gGyEzd https://t.co/wIOmlJ57vF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prosecutors seek 'special master' to review Giuliani items https://t.co/0VvFh2B3WQ https://t.co/xX5QyG6AWO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Air force chief stands by Cyclone helicopters despite emergency landing, fatal crash https://t.co/zBIvoPGN7e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Syrian refugee now works at same hotel that was his first home in Canada https://t.co/PgHEAhZQ0g https://t.co/kXi1HTmF0m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill to ensure safe election during pandemic stalls as odds of election increase https://t.co/p08tTBiJcx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nature at its craziest: Trillions of cicadas about to emerge https://t.co/QtffXxYpc8 https://t.co/g9PskuXFKx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least 2 killed after plane crashes into Mississippi home https://t.co/9oToxQjZXL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An escalating third wave of COVID-19 is forcing Alberta to introduce new restrictions. Bill Fortier has the details. https://t.co/Xa8KRhBFxh https://t.co/ym8bH8Yj1j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chauvin's lawyer seeks new trial, hearing to impeach verdict https://t.co/YDqndoqMJh https://t.co/APHfy5A5hB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Return of the cicadas: Trillions of the noisy insects are expected to emerge in 2021 https://t.co/Edj98Hl4TS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suzanne Rogers apologizes amid controversy over photo with former U.S. president Donald Trump https://t.co/lKmIw2ZAjF https://t.co/xW91Z8Xul6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is the government trying to regulate the videos you post? What you need to know about Bill C-10 https://t.co/U6G6PiFgPa https://t.co/a4hf3Fbcpe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least 24 people are dead after a transit overpass with a train filled with passengers collapsed in Mexico. Tom Walters reports. https://t.co/JBrDbpmF10 https://t.co/TPa5QNbwzp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Asia markets mixed after Wall St decline https://t.co/AIyZ2jbRiY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we mix and match vaccines? One big question for two COVID-19 doses https://t.co/Tm7EA9Slyu https://t.co/Igbq3flEd2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden aims to vaccinate 70 per cent of American adults by July 4 https://t.co/2lecjYlzXV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada taken to court over COVID-19 policy that pushes asylum-seekers to U.S. https://t.co/3qRSvm1N3U https://t.co/NKDLI2rk6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[60 years since first American in space: Tourists lining up https://t.co/WOGXgq4AXx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Belgian farmer moves border with France by mistake https://t.co/gUN7oVb45V https://t.co/IBDdJcwNOb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suzanne Rogers apologized for a picture she posted with former U.S. president Donald Trump. John Vennavally-Rao reports. https://t.co/jnjlYhh4wn https://t.co/IAyiK7x00O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indian government faces lockdown calls, contempt charges https://t.co/T0FqKsKvmS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pentagon tracking out-of-control Chinese rocket that could re-enter Earth's atmosphere https://t.co/xXyYpRhbH5 https://t.co/GOM4CfPQUG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook board's Trump decision could have wider impacts https://t.co/rCKCAyRqcy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do you do if you think you have VITT? What we know of the rare clotting disorder https://t.co/ylX54ruKSh https://t.co/swhuUvyxwN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is the difference between mRNA and viral vector-based vaccines? https://t.co/0ZnFUFdF4E https://t.co/OUGft3rVgy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@MerellaCTV has the story of a former Syrian refugee's journey coming full circle back to the hotel that first gave him shelter: https://t.co/dOAXJk22pW https://t.co/tzNy3KyH8V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Martin Firestone, President of Travel Secure, talks about what needs to be done before Canadians start to travel aboard again. https://t.co/HIO8FzQmFn https://t.co/eNbJsnPLcB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Few Canadians contracting COVID-19 after first vaccine dose: PHAC https://t.co/IXDDMXi9a3 https://t.co/q0FXHJwjHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotia is expected to extend its #COVID19 lockdown after recording triple-digit cases for the fourth straight day. @battisctv has more: https://t.co/KaSO8QZde5 https://t.co/sajdI8VCcN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Alberta reports first death from AstraZeneca vaccine, second in Canada https://t.co/N1vdOmrXNw https://t.co/KxNjXdw4iv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World's oldest person pulls out of Olympic torch relay https://t.co/ud3tfJrQdZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prosecutors seek 'special master' to review Giuliani items https://t.co/LDcsanRdRx https://t.co/Fu65cFhIHE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ottawa assured Canadians all authorized #COVID19 vaccines are safe after conflicting messaging from NACI. @AnnieClaireBO reports: https://t.co/y8s9xo4QdM https://t.co/pHvin2Ep9P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daschcam footage shows how the driver of an armoured truck reacted during an attempted hijacking on a highway in South Africa. https://t.co/mwARdWiZqY https://t.co/au9j9Azas2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Canadian rugby 7s coach in favour of releasing independent review of players complaint https://t.co/qjHlUVVzcF https://t.co/3NHxsyEQPQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hamilton Tiger-Cats take tight end Jake Burt first overall in CFL draft https://t.co/wmmb4YkfGq https://t.co/MWvCN8yCVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suzanne Rogers apologizes amid controversy over photo with former U.S. president Donald Trump https://t.co/2skYWMAAOD https://t.co/xUl1Bf3kMj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike McCardell has the last word on a couple who lost their first partners to cancer and the new hobby they've taken on during the pandemic. https://t.co/d1fF6ssL0K https://t.co/64VIrxZWx4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNationalNews:  More than 13.1 million people in Canada have received their first COVID-19 vaccine (+226,382 today)  1,143,239 have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Syrian refugee now works at same hotel that was his first home in Canada https://t.co/LzumLsv1tx https://t.co/3bOfE94A7R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we mix and match vaccines? One big question for two COVID-19 doses https://t.co/4BFviXpbVl https://t.co/iZqYibtXug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China becomes top market for Cuba's legendary cigars https://t.co/vmySghPKrG https://t.co/8n7uQiVBhG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Larry Haas and Jeremy Kinsman talk why China and Russia are using their power to gain political influence. https://t.co/RA4HoEzMFt https://t.co/dVbM25a03p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNationalNews: TONIGHT: The race to restore vaccine confidence after confusing expert advice.  Plus, a catastrophic collapse which ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['New normal' temperature in the U.S. is a degree hotter than two decades ago https://t.co/djnukHouJY https://t.co/LHmFJMDz7a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNationalNews: Khaled al-Mouktaran and his family came to Canada as refugees in 2016, fleeing their war-torn home in Syria.  @Merella]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conan O'Brien ends his long run in late night next month https://t.co/cj56ZYvG4X https://t.co/4YqwIDv2Ap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're on TikTok! Be among the first to join our new community showcasing some of our best videos and latest news.  Come and say hi: https://t.co/pee3QhwJah https://t.co/R7brJb1Zww]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNationalNews: When the time comes around, can Canadians mix and match vaccines for their second dose?  @CPHO_Canada said the advice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chauvin's lawyer seeks new trial, hearing to impeach verdict https://t.co/VrgYRRFy9G https://t.co/06FYGnaKV8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From CTV Kitchener's Stephanie Villella: Many pharmacies in Waterloo Region are facing a shortage of AstraZeneca supply. https://t.co/7CLJsRpCQ9 https://t.co/MBgFkEoZSe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter hears from record respondents over world leader rules https://t.co/Fyz1x0pDiQ https://t.co/4LQTBoLlgI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There were tense moments in the Ontario legislature on Tuesday, May 4 as Merrilee Fullerton, the minister of long-term care, faced calls to resign.  Join the conversation on our new Tiktok account: https://t.co/VlDkUulv0Y @TikTokCanada https://t.co/5sZFptozys]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pentagon tracking out-of-control Chinese rocket that could re-enter Earth's atmosphere https://t.co/wCa2mssANc https://t.co/FMBJNoBSYj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Newest COVID-19 restrictions in Alberta to close patios and salons, move all schools online  https://t.co/4uGWoqlYdb https://t.co/hJmNkvcpyr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will Smith to get fit for YouTube series https://t.co/sVk20UP3na https://t.co/E4Is1sDNrd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Alta. Premier Jason Kenney and health officials announce new public health measures to limit the spread of COVID-19: https://t.co/DPdVeOJWgu https://t.co/QAlgF2SIdO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The mother of Anastasia De Sousa has written a scathing letter to the federal government about its gun control plans. https://t.co/QoiLNIPHq6 https://t.co/Lr21py0Qfu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thousands left out of plan to give workers permanent residency: Migrant Rights Network #CdnPoli @MigrantRightsCA  https://t.co/V2gVWUfZ9t https://t.co/cHpr91QiSC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada taken to court over COVID-19 policy that pushes asylum-seekers to U.S. https://t.co/b5ckvdLxNL https://t.co/e4r6UCGxEj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Belgian farmer moves border with France by mistake https://t.co/O9rC8CUiAq https://t.co/w8yISZCaCW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NDP Leader Andrea Horwath and LTC Minister Merrilee Fullerton debate the province's handling of long-term care homes during the pandemic. https://t.co/VEuw9vplbF https://t.co/P4e52akaga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNationalNews: The death toll from the collapse of an overpass on the Mexico City metro rose to 24 on Tuesday.  As @TomWaltersCTV rep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta adds 1,743 COVID-19 cases, 9 deaths https://t.co/zIMNDF6jKe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mayor of Wood Buffalo, Alta. says he has never been shown COVID-19 modelling https://t.co/Xo8VrIXyDv https://t.co/jTmEevGkT9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is the government trying to regulate the videos you post? What you need to know about Bill C-10 https://t.co/AINi0YQ99i https://t.co/d2VhoZYech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[697 cases, 1 death included in B.C.'s latest COVID-19 update https://t.co/aChpXrkDjy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tories vote against bill on net-zero emissions as it clears legislative hurdle https://t.co/u9A2scXIeP https://t.co/LLMOpr4r9a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Infectious disease specialist Dr. Abdu Sharkawy explains what it means if COVID-19 becomes endemic, and what that could mean for Canada. Read more: https://t.co/OrTCep7pV2 https://t.co/QAQ5PdW1Ii]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mazyria, an endangered Amur tiger, gave birth on April 30 after 104 days of pregnancy. https://t.co/BYu0MfyTIb https://t.co/a1UkYYUpq9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do you do if you think you have VITT? What we know of the rare clotting disorder https://t.co/KkDCKReljX https://t.co/gY6P9Z4zA4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britney Spears slams the documentaries being made about her life https://t.co/wW30EAlV0U https://t.co/XKev9AuNwH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sask.'s 3-step reopening plan relies on vaccinations, officials say https://t.co/RB6BJwRy0I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Korea dairy company CEO resigns over virus research scandal https://t.co/MO2im5eer4 https://t.co/mh4pgWpN3e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Sask. Premier Scott Moe and health officials provide an update on COVID-19 in the province: https://t.co/Hur0sYmw8l https://t.co/4QSmnjhnwy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least 23 people died and 79 were injured Monday night when a train plunged five meters, crashing on a busy street. https://t.co/UpgexuglqM https://t.co/jv5iLlWUly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kenney to speak at 6 p.m. MDT; stronger COVID-19 restrictions expected for Alberta https://t.co/cZiKgmJ0cW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Everybody's tired' as condensed NHL schedule takes its toll https://t.co/7y3jXV5KSp https://t.co/eCuuXIDmp1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['I will not be spoken to that way': Ontario long-term care minister fires back at critics amid calls for her resignation https://t.co/em7o55wZR3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How environmentalist @ManviBhalla is shaking up how young Canadians tackle climate change. @ShakeUpTheEstab https://t.co/lXrLV8f0Lv https://t.co/T7vxsuUonb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada will align policy on 'vaccine passports' with international allies: Trudeau https://t.co/Glrm0dhGM6 https://t.co/Rh3Dfu6pLn]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>