<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @GloriaChecchi apple phones are the easiest to hack!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charliekirk11: If the FBI tapped into Rudy Giulianis iCloud messages in 2019, we should all be asking how is that legal?  I thought Ap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join Robinhood with my link and we'll both get free stock  https://t.co/AWUUYUxawo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Space_Station @SpaceX @maragabrielle30 no one should trust NASA!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScienceNews lack of oxygen from the dirty masks?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marybl62 @justinbaragona @FoxNews I say keep on talking!!! Put an end to child endangerment  abuse!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrickmanInGA @justinbaragona no, its a call to end abuse of our children!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@samajdarn @justinbaragona you should be changed with child endangerment! We The People have had enough of your mental illness! The world is not your mental hospital!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JORGE_C_NY @justinbaragona @TuckerCarlson @nowthisnews @rcbregman Cowards hide behind fear! Be a man!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justinbaragona Maskers Mental Disorder (MMD)! The world in not your hospital!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justinbaragona finally someone is making sense!!! Go TUCKER @TuckerCarlson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Save a child, burn the masks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michael14784676 @KCRG amen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michael14784676: @KCRG @Coleyufo Screw the China Devilcrat Communists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I say they need to be called! if you will not stand for yourself, at least stand for our children! if adults want to be cowards, that is on them, but you dont get my air nor my childs! https://t.co/VPrQlAeVR5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justinamash they need to be called!!! Our children do NOT have a choice!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sfpelosi @TuckerCarlson its worse!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan So happy someone finally did!!! Go TUCKER!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CortesSteve: Unless its Halloween, kids should never wear masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coleyufo: @TuckerCarlson NO Masks!!! Thank you for speaking out!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arthur_oslund @KCRG sure is!!! Enough is Enough!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arthur_oslund: @KCRG @Coleyufo A crime against humanity. How many people have died because the government prevented them from using hyd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arthur_oslund @KCRG Exactly ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arthur_oslund: @KCRG @Coleyufo Why subject yourself to experimental vaccines to protect you from a disease that has a near 100% surviva]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoxanneDenison @justinbaragona my hero!!! Its about time!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJ_Saulnier @justinbaragona @FoxNews why dont you wear your masks and stop worrying about everyone else! NO ONE OWES YOU THEIR AIR!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@samajdarn @justinbaragona we are cheering him on!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justinbaragona Really?!?! Try being medically exempt  than we will talk! You people are cowards!!! Wear your dirty masks but dont expect anyone owes you their breath of air, especially our children! You people are sick!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justinbaragona I agree!!! Its about time!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson NO Masks!!! Thank you for speaking out!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KCRG: CDC says many Americans can now go outside without a mask https://t.co/w0o33YCyJv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KCRG Vaccines are available to those who want them!!! Drop the madness!!! No one is listening anymore!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@heyyitsjanea @netflix me too!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto is splitting up $1 Million in cash! Sign up with my link, trade crypto and we'll both get a piece  https://t.co/TfBZEKHV5K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join Robinhood with my link and we'll both get free stock  https://t.co/eTkyc8QvWu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stimulusbitcoin not true at all!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A police state is not free! We the taxpayers are paying good money to be held hostage by our government!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@turtle639375753 @TrentonGolden5 @POTUS The taxpayers lost money  will spend years paying this money back!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lancegooden: Any state that uses federal stimulus dollars to give checks to illegal immigrants should refund the American taxpayers imm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catoletters: The public indoctrination centers have worked on science.  They made most students hate math  science so much, they refus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catoletters: The Racist Roots of Gun Control: JIM CROW LAWS were foundation of gun control in Americaand the  KU KLUX KLAN was AMERICA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are being played  they know we know we are being played! I am done with the bad actors in the political theater!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government is NOT your friend! If you believe them than you have learned NOTHING from the history you are trying to rewrite!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CivilDisobedi20: @ArtValley818_ Never has been. Government is NOT a friend of the People.   #CivilDisobedienceIsPeaceful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CivilDisobedience Needed! Demand #CovidAudit and #BecomeUngovernable https://t.co/HLF2P0FZQh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[disgusting @SpiritAirlines https://t.co/iVb9MKqSmI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClayTravis: This is wild. Watch Ron DeSantiss full answer on Publix, Walgreens and CVS vaccine distribution and look at the edited cu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: BREAKING: 60 Minutes caught deceptively editing DeSantis interview, cut out his response on Publix, vaccines  https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BNicholsLiberty @lpky exactly!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lukewearechange: What in the New World order hell is this? https://t.co/bbIr5gONXG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iansmithfitness @LibertyforA11 No one should trust the government!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iansmithfitness: The government is not your friend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impeach #Biden  #Harris They are NOT qualified  dangerous to our Republic! #ImpeachBiden #ImpeachBidenHarris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rowithaslash @NeverTobes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BigGameJ1 @NeverTobes @YahMoTweetHere Medical EXEMPTIONS! Wake up America]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philfromthe90s @NeverTobes Simple minds]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saucy_youth @NeverTobes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeverTobes  Thx for fighting the good fight #CivilDisobedienceMovement]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeverTobes: Heres the scene from a local post office in Minnesota today https://t.co/umfIHkgQ2l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coleyufo: I am curious from everything I am reading and yesterday was date stimulus was supposed to be issued to many of the American p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am curious from everything I am reading and yesterday was date stimulus was supposed to be issued to many of the American people (among many others)... can anyone verify that they received it or that they can they trace it? Biden would be addressing the nation... hmmmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LtGovHochulNY @realDonaldTrump Give me a break! Clean out NY of their dirty career politicians!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust WHAT Plan? https://t.co/mxOWUi8Onk via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For the People Act of 2021 (H.R. 1) - https://t.co/o9ZkCOk186 VOTE NO https://t.co/iPOrhHD4aU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @knowaging: In my obsession to figure out how to be able to use #Spaces, I came across this #twittertutorial. It only let's #livestream]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CrazyBengieFB_ @BryanMatthews23 @ShelldoHanson @FrankiLoveMusic @burrosavic @KAM4Texas @DewayneArmstro9 @SteveGjesdal21 @BAYLORICWORLDTV @Link24_ @KarenSobek @Ranal55 @LarsonElaineM @MicheleCruicks1 @QPROPHETESS_17 @MeLinda12946390 @NeasdenParade @Rolfus_Adolphus @realist2016jlp Thank you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CrazyBengieFB_: #ff: @BryanMatthews23 @ShelldoHanson @FrankiLoveMusic @burrosavic @Coleyufo @KAM4Texas @DewayneArmstro9 @SteveGjesdal21]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeasdenParade: @CrazyBengieFB_ @BryanMatthews23 @ShelldoHanson @FrankiLoveMusic @burrosavic @Coleyufo @KAM4Texas @DewayneArmstro9 @Stev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thx  https://t.co/l2aUMsb3zT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Popsunderhouse1: How true is this? https://t.co/SFWLMFjsDt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fookcu_f: Julian Assange is correct @1tastycakes @fookcu_f @AngelWarrior320 @USAF_88 @TwinBus @ItallionTony @TrishForTrump @ValuesChri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPepper1964: @SenTedCruz ~  Thanks to the Dems, inmates will now be getting a $1400 stimulus check. https://t.co/RMaTy8kiJg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is about the just of it! Who really thought they were going to get sent 2000 as Biden promised!?! My guess is his promise got many into a far worse financial situation! https://t.co/he2Qdx7YFd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If anything should be done... 1400 stand alone bill! That is where I draw my line! I am tired of paying taxes to be held hostage at rates that makes burrowing from loan sharks fiscally responsibile!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jillie_Alexis: Americans shouldnt be cheering for a $1400 stimulus check that cost them $5750 of their own money.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedlieu UnAmerican is the closest most of you come! Children arguing over books! There is no clause in the #1A that covers this nonsense!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tedcruz: Democrats Reject Republican Attempts To Prevent Stimulus Checks From Going To Prisoners, Illegal Aliens  Seriously.    https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AmericasDrum: @1_Gabriel_III @20bean20 @andrea77214732 @ArtemisaT4 @Citationsphy @cognitivediss00 @Coleyufo @God_over_all17 @Honnest9 @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SolidRedPeon: Biden tightens $1,400 stimulus check income limits amid pressure from moderate Dems  https://t.co/5SKUthxTQI remind every]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: https://t.co/uX6uHhMlza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepGosar: Did you know H.R.1 allows individuals to vote without an ID and to merely sign a statement in which they claim they are who t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepGosar: Only 9% of Pelosis $1.9 trillion plan is related to COVID-19.  I offered an amendment providing $10k stimulus to Americans]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @80strolls: #COVID19 Audit.  I want a recount of every case and all the deaths.  Medical records, testing lab and company!  #covidaudit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will your local and state government do when they are piled in a mound of debt and a 9% PPE sell your soul bill in dangling over their head! Tax payers are being held hostage by their own money! Let that sink in after you check your local debt incurred! Demand a #CovidAudit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP He was silenced! It is the local and state governments holding the power and control in a mound of debt and a 9% PPE bull dangling over their heads! Follow the money!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SusanStJames3_: Wow! Over 31 million people watched Trump's CPAC speech.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MatthewJshow Corn Pop!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Deborah40695678 @judytgolf @sjksixer @KimbetheStylist @JuJuSkier @ann49720 @M_Graham12qw @XSteveSchmidtX @justmeblah2020 @Vivify_America @Goblin17Queen @zuzga006 @whathe11 @thewin04 @Larry757N @Fly63_ @wessond44 @DorisW2008 @RandiSilva01 @DiscipleBearded @digi11111 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PostJawn @theyre_heeeere @carlanderson333 @SilvaRecord @JChurchRadio @JasonIn16370144 @UfoJoe11 @awakeningMan @blackvaultcom @darkjournalist I have pictures of the real TTSA if anyone is interested!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PostJawn @carlanderson333 @SilvaRecord @JChurchRadio @JasonIn16370144 @UfoJoe11 @theyre_heeeere @awakeningMan @blackvaultcom @darkjournalist Agreed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zAb62J4SUG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you wont stand for yourself, will you stand for our children?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Republicans willing to break away from party to follow Trump, poll reveals https://t.co/bm4RpxYOHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coleyufo: @TonyMar68854421 Everyone DEMAND #CovidAudit on all data!!! City, State, and federal! This is our way out!!! I have been sayi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coleyufo: @EsterAgain @anitawadhwani @JohnCooper4Nash @TNLookout Everyone DEMAND #CovidAudit on all data!!! City, State, and federal! T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coleyufo: @FCKR888_ @RyanRallyOh  #CovidAudit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coleyufo: #CovidAudit DEMAND IT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Waiting for them to attack the name White House -'Utter outrage': White House says US in talks with Iran over detained Americans https://t.co/xhxtRfJiME]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QFMiaCD8z6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Solar panels causing global warming?! Scientists unearth a consequence of solar panels in the Sahara - Inverse https://t.co/xpHVsCJgDG]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>