<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@DianeReidyLagun Same! Cant come soon enough ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The culprit: https://t.co/8G8TCXxCDN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, it happened. Giving a lecture this evening via zoom to the Hematology Society of Taiwan, and of my cats WOULD NOT STOP MEOWING. In QA I was congratulated for having the most academic cat ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So grateful! The Visiting Nurse Association of Central Jersey now providing #CovidVaccine to #MSKCC patients in New Jersey, including #MSKBergen https://t.co/XNka2Ok0os]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MikeFooteMD: We are having a blast giving Pfizer vaccines at the Absynnian Baptist Church on 138th street in Harlem with @sloan_ketteri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ciacobu Would definitely pick up a ! Your poor post-doc!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VJHemOnc: We had the please of speaking with @DrMatasar (@sloan_kettering) on the findings of CHRONOS-3 from #AACR21  Watch here https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MedpageOnco: Adding this to rituximab reduced the risk of disease progression or death for patients with relapsed indolent non-Hodgkin']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASCOPost: Matthew J. Matasar, MD, on Indolent NHL: New Data on Copanlisib Plus Rituximab https://t.co/cSkqCb2h2A #lymsm #hematology #AA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrPaulyDeSantis @Hieflo23 Again, cross-trial comparisons and all  that, but nearly identical median pfs vs augment when using investigator assessed PFS (25m in AUGMENT). That said, different tox profiles, OOP costs, schedules will likely make one or the other more attractive for a given pt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YLeyfman Thanks for the kind words Yan!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmilyMcMack @AACR Not just because...but especially because!  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrAEvens Well, cross trial comparisons and all that, but CHRONOS1 had copanlisib mono ORR 60 mPFS 12m, so combo probably &gt; copa mono in ritux sensitive relapsed iNHL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LYM_MM_CONNECT Most pneumonitis gr1-2 in severity, &lt;3% had grade 3+ pneumonitis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bpromd Patients in CHRONOS-3 were rituximab sensitive. The purpose of the study was to evaluate, in patients for whom rituximab monotherapy would be appropriate, if R+copanlisib would be more effective and safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gritsman_lab @TheLancetOncol @AACR Thanks Kira! Were all trying to translate the work by smart scientists like you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fieldstonegirl @TheLancetOncol @AACR Thanks Rose! The thanks always truly goes to our patients, and their trust and confidence in us to work together to keep them healthy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SantoshVardhana @sloan_kettering I totally forgot about that - but even then was immediately obvious how much smarter than me you are  proud to have you as a colleague and friend!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrAEvens Thanks Andy! And clearly I need to up my hashtag game!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alaccetti interesting work being presented today #AACR21 https://t.co/0ofhI5qSne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OncLive: Copanlisib/Rituximab Improves PFS in Relapsed Indolent Non-Hodgkin Lymphoma @DrMatasar @sloan_kettering @AACR #AACR21 https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CHRONOS-3: #copanlisib + #rituximab in the treatment of relapsed iNHL. Results published today in @TheLancetOncol concurrent with plenary presention @AACR https://t.co/4fTQ6jvX8g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sloan_kettering: #AACR21 Breaking News: New study finds that #copanlisib plus #rituximab resulted in a 48% reduction in the risk of di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CDebyaniPhD @sloan_kettering There is nothing unprofessional about this, full stop.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sloan_kettering: Congratulations to MSK's Dr. Katharine Hsu, who was just named director of @TriIMDPhD, a joint program between MSK, @W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LYM_MM_CONNECT: You are invited to participate in a 90-minute Experts Knowledge Share event on May 3rd!  Come join our faculty and disc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ipreeshagul sounds familiar ... https://t.co/Uydl05ayBm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excited to have @DrConnieBatlevi now joining the #lymphoma program at #MSKBergen - she brings great expertise and compassion for our #MSKCC patients https://t.co/Z1ZwHlxFPJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jitcancer: 1st of its kind scRNAseq #hodgkin #lymphoma Aoki, Steidl et al @BCCancer Super interesting data that hopefully can lead impr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sloan_kettering: #AACR21 kicks off on Saturday, 4/10. MSK experts @rosslevinemd, @Samuel_Bakhoum, @DrMatasar, and many others will be s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NCICancerSurv: Meet Emily Tonorezos, MD, MPH, director of NCIs Office of Cancer Survivorship. Dr. Tonorezos leads NCIs efforts to add]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VincentRK: Calling on all State Medical Boards to immediately issue regulations that all US based physicians licensed to practice in on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep, its a problem. https://t.co/iUTJwQelYP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanmmcbride @blandro Dammit now I want a milkshake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sloan_kettering: As we mark 1 year since #COVID19 was declared a pandemic we look back at the unprecedented challenges we all faced as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VivekSubbiah:  Just In. Official announcement ASCO 2021 will be Virtual   #ASCO21 will be an online only experience due to  #CO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sloan_kettering: MSK is now offering #COVID19 vaccine to patients age 65 and over who live in New York State and are in active treatmen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking at the @axiomhcs Heme Town Hall with Drs. Eytan Stein and @NoopurRajeMD Monday 1/18. Registration: https://t.co/ONNh1ZfM9e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HemSandoval @ABC @hulu Hi Jose! Shes back at @ABC working with and for a former mentor, and thriving! (As much as can be, in such strange times)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A worthy watch - great work by the group at @ABC airing on @hulu - props to my talented wife Mara Matasar-Padilla for her work supporting the program! https://t.co/5PHeWwdUJM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Schwarzenegger: My message to my fellow Americans and friends around the world following this week's attack on the Capitol. https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NYCHealthCommr: Here's how eligible New Yorkers can sign up right now to get the #COVID19 vaccine:   1. Visit https://t.co/Ms3t0gYyg2.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Enrique_Acevedo: Pay attention to who vandalized and who's cleaning "the people's house."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @edokeefe: JUST IN: This is not news we deliver lightly, @margbrennan says as she reports: Trump Cabinet secretaries are discussing in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samwineburg: Take this in: Never once, in the years 1860-1865, was this flag ever paraded in the halls of the American capitol. https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AustinKellerman: Right now on the West side of the US Capitol.  ( Getty Images) https://t.co/1FxSN5Ugc7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020: I'm gonna be the most horrific year ever. 2021: Hold my beer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So grateful to have received my first #COVID19 vax dose. Lets not forget that this is only possible because of clinical trials participants. This is what clinical research can achieve! #ThisIsOurShot https://t.co/hP56m2UyHA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eager to get vaccinated! And patiently waiting, knowing our staff more responsible for daily care of patients with COVID are the right priority for our first doses. https://t.co/nV8z33NXGQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out @DianeReidyLagun in her new podcast #CancerStraightTalk. If you dont know her, youre missing out - remarkable leader, physician, and a truly kind person. This episode notwithstanding, gonna be a great pod to follow! https://t.co/NJ7FMIRAgs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miriamhsajecki @DrAnasYounes @MSN Happy anniversary! Heres to many more years of good health, @miriamhsajecki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[what he said https://t.co/OiKaf635WD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheDoctorIsVin @nyphospital @levainbakery @rosslevinemd @shengfcai @bowman_rl @lindemilesphd What wonderful news Aaron! (Fingers crossed for those cookies too)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drrdean @ClevelandClinic Stay safe, Rob! Hoping that things cool off in Cleveland (and here...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IreneGhobrial Yet another downside to telemedicine - less produce!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PamelaDrullins1 I forgot that this is one of your many, many talents!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrDanPersky @lepikurian I did! Practiced as best I could before the meeting, but I should have recruited you to tutor me Dan!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excited to be participating in the Russian DLBCL symposium with @lepikurian and Prof Poddbnaya... even though Im stuck in NY https://t.co/GJWcZ4DfTE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheJeffBridges Wishing you speedy healing! Im sure youve got access to good care, but just in case: have your pathology reviewed by an expert hematopathologist, and consider a second opinion (even if youve had to start treatment quickly, there may be tweaks you could benefit from)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dr_R_Kurzrock Jaundice + glass eye?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StefanoLuminari @chadinabhan @hematologo @graham74GC @DrRaulCordoba @tobyeyre82 @TheLancetOncol I still use RCHOP14 sometimes, not with intention of improving outcomes, just to finish quicker for pts tolerating treatment well and eager to be done. And only 6.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vgargMD: @McKnightLab_UO Lets get this done, people.  https://t.co/M46TgKDbgn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rschaffel Sorry to hear it Rony. Hope you guys are all safe and healthy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID test positivity rate in NYC 3.25% - if it stays at this level or continues to climb this week, schools will return to all remote learning just 1 week after they opened.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RogueRad Breakfast Club, Ferris Bueller's Day Off, The Matrix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seeing my kid, whoa a highschool sophomore and decided to spend their summer learning about dark matter (thanks COVID), email senior astrophysics faculty asking for pdfs or clarifications - and how quickly and respectfully they responded - gives me hope for academia.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveFDA This is disappointing - we in the medical community expect better from our colleagues and our leaders. Theres no room for racism in medicine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gilles_salles Looking forward to working with and learning from you Gilles!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gilles_salles: Privileged and excited to officially start today at MSKCC. Fantastic team in the Lymphoma Service, and many opportunitie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan Props to @yungposu who taught me this fine piece of history/trivia my first week of fellowship, back when roamed the ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan Depends on definitions: Seaweed to treat goiter = 2700 bce. Iodine discovered around 1800. Radium into thyroid glad ~1910. Idea of Rai in the 1930s, first used for Graves 1941. First report of Rai treating thyroid ca 1948 (first use of targeted cancer therapy)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan I believe the answer is 131-I for thyroid cancer, 1971?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DannyVietti Sweet Lou Whitaker]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnPLeonardMD How did we arrive at this place, where not only do we need to wonder if science can sway policy and behavior, but we fear, or even know, that it won't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drkomanduri @POTUS I think you got the answer to your question, Krishna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A tough week. Gave more bad news than Im used to. Cooped up, stretched thin, and a back ache has kept me from running. But the city is still beautiful. https://t.co/P9WnpD0OAy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@doctorpemm @VivekSubbiah @LaurenByersMD @tmprowell @DavidSteensma @mtmdphd @BldCancerDoc @DrMiguelPerales @drkomanduri @Transplant_Doc @Aiims1742 @NitinJainMD @sanamloghavi @MrinalPatnaik @VincentRK Stay safe and hang in there!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrAEvens Interesting label, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamaalBowmanNY: RT if you think Congress should make Juneteenth a national holiday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ljkbennett This is a perfect example of why Twitter needs to allow laughing emoji reactions ASAP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WhiteCoatsForBlackLives proud to stand with my friends and colleagues at @sloan_kettering #MSKBergen. Racism and systemic violence are a threat to public health and cannot be tolerated https://t.co/asQiSYcCCa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mkdinnhaupt No thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Proud to stand with fellow New Yorkers tonight. Black Lives Matter, marching part the Stonewall Inn - a reminder of just how much work is needed to repair our society https://t.co/9JDXhGLQGW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrJamKothari @graham74GC And the use of cisplatin instead of oxali may further limit its generalizability...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MEI_Pharma @sloan_kettering Looking forward to the discussion!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MediHumdani Hell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@balinoruo @DrMiguelPerales @DianeReidyLagun Shes absolutely the real deal, David. Congrats on your ongoing remission! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out the new podcast by the incomparable @DianeReidyLagun - Cancer Straight Talk. So happy to have had a chance to join her in the inaugural episode! https://t.co/C3KABH6FKV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@doctor_jayson I would say that it is often considered/used where rituximab would be. There is some pushback from payers where ita use isnt aligned w NCCN/FDA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tmhohl71: 1/n Curious about COVID-19 outcomes in patients with cancer? Check out the @sloan_kettering experience. Administration of che]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're going "other," feel free to elaborate!...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is the right response to this? White House gift shop selling COVID-19 souvenir coins for $100 honoring President Trump. https://t.co/cYHLvoctOq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mohty_EBMT @APHP Interesting to hear this at the same time as hearing that early sarilumab data look negative. Will need to see the actual reports and data to interpret.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chadinabhan @barttels2 @Rfonsi1 @ChristosArgyrop @VincentRK @emilymicheleL @PSampathkumarMD @anish_koka @Aiims1742 @DrChoueiri @VivekSubbiah @tmprowell @RogueRad @IshwariaMD @subatomicdoc @MDaware @daviesbj https://t.co/G1c74g2Z3Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theblondeMD I cant remember being this ashamed of my home state.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VivekSubbiah @chadinabhan @DrChoueiri @TheDoctorIsVin @IshwariaMD @n8pennell @UroDocAsh @LeciaSequist @marklewismd @DrSGraff @GeneCollector Work from home has reacquainted me with my old-fashioned stovetop espresso percolator. My Nespresso hasnt been turned on in days!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrPaulyDeSantis @graham74GC @michaelwangmd Would try to get access to a bispecific if possible. Otherwise RBAC if hasnt seen cytarabine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrChoueiri: Just in: #COVID19 Randomized trial of HCQ vs. SOC (n=150): -&gt;90% with mild/moderate disease severity -SIMILAR negative conv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Webinar at 2pm: global perspectives on lymphoma management during the COVID pandemic. Joint at https://t.co/wwDzIP2ysI (event coordinated by @roche) https://t.co/rvW5u07zCg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @melissadderosa: NEW: NYS COVID-19 website has been updated to include data on fatalities including race  Table includes information bas]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>