<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wxphelps: Sunny today, but rain returns tonight. https://t.co/5QoDUL4lC7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to the court's ruling, the restaurant owner who took over in 2009 forced a man with an intellectual disability to work more than 100 hours per week without pay. https://t.co/OehtUwCvYE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The memorandum, requested under FOIA by a government transparency group but denied by the former Attorney General, has been ordered to be released by a U.S. District Judge. https://t.co/YfKCP1y3nK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tornadoes, flash flooding, and numerous damaged homes: the southern United States continues to be battered by intense storms. https://t.co/Q3nV0mpTOE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The details of each state's bills vary from state to state but follow a similar pattern of making it harder for people to vote by mail or absentee. https://t.co/1KAP8RtkFZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The non-profit plans to use funds from the recent grant from United Way to host a 12-week Effective Black Parenting program which begins in June. https://t.co/mxiNXtdKX2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The clinic at the World's Largest Truckstop will be open to those 18 or older. https://t.co/mBwydKULVO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maria's Pizza, which was closed due to flooding, finally cut the ribbon and reopened their doors. https://t.co/h89bzOgtiV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another 27 people remained hospitalized of the more than 70 injured. https://t.co/C0W7L3mtEv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As long as we are open and honest, we can move forward https://t.co/wz9pG9iZq7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The two cases of the "India variant" were both found in Jefferson County. https://t.co/NCSpJnkxPb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following a traffic stop, a search of the man's vehicle revealed two items which resulted in charges in Henderson County. https://t.co/LZ8RDtNL8t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Moline Police have confirmed that a 13-year-old boy has died following an accident with a police vehicle while riding his bicycle. https://t.co/Ql6ohoXdDr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chauvin's attorney claimed in his request the verdict should be impeached due to what he called "jury misconduct," and accused Judge Peter Cahill of abusing the discretion of the court. https://t.co/293D0GeZ5U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The plan is available now for self-funded employers with a July 1, 2021 renewal date or later. https://t.co/K9RO9nW94J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The goal laid out by the President would be equivalent to fully vaccinating 160 million adults. https://t.co/aYXKc6JV8K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marxen is charged with first-degree murder, child endangerment resulting in death, and child endangerment. https://t.co/9AKopZFhRs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Motorists are advised to avoid the area.  We will continue to update this story with any further developments. https://t.co/Ql6ohoFCeR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JUST IN: A man has been charged in the boat crash that killed two last August in LeClaire.  https://t.co/wpon7Bvwzi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In one recall, owners are being told to park outdoors until repairs are made. https://t.co/lbCZXDgNCb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We saw some pretty healthy amounts of rain yesterday, but very little in the way of severe weather. Look for a few showers south this afternoon, followed by sunshine by Wednesday. Here's the latest: https://t.co/dzxcWWyiea https://t.co/EO0hWWACQx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A big thank you to our first responders! Do you know a firefighter? Let them know it is International Firefighters Day. https://t.co/5rr3RXjNF7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lingering clouds this afternoon, along with cool 50's  60's. https://t.co/yCqa7bS6Eq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TV6 is excited to announce a special program called The Pitch, which will air on TV6 at 7 p.m. Saturday. https://t.co/8vACpy8IEh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It was a World War II Japanese Navy mortar that was still live, but they didnt know that at first.   https://t.co/KMFN7IqQeH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clouds across the region today, but we wont be stuck with them foreverlook for a return to sunshine by midweek. Your latest First Alert Forecast is coming up on TV6 News at Noon. https://t.co/5ftzfyQuSZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The FDA action will be followed by a meeting of a federal vaccine advisory committee to discuss whether to recommend the shot for 12- to 15-year-olds. https://t.co/iVV6TCZuYZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some companies are doing a cost-benefit analysis and realize its cheaper to violate the law, even if you get caught.  https://t.co/G5f4x4aXrc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials say the man was hit while riding his bike just after midnight. https://t.co/noDglb2gal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you teachers!!  Which teacher(s) goes above and beyond for your kiddos? https://t.co/yww2VCbq82]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The girl's mother says she will be taking her kids inside stores with her from now on.   https://t.co/e9h2OPGlVe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The U.S. is experiencing a nationwide chlorine shortage. https://t.co/sUxHiPaj3D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Revenge of the 5th is on Wednesday ;)   Happy Star Wars day! Which film is your favorite? https://t.co/87AhyA5JWb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Block was one of 15 to win the award among thousands of nominees https://t.co/crdhtqpN8l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On March 15th, Chrissy Govek started a fundraising campaign through St. Baldricks for a family friend whose daughter is fighting cancer. https://t.co/SkwIuf8yZT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After many spring and summer events turned virtual in 2020, many are coming back this year. What are some events you're looking forward to? https://t.co/ezqvGd0noJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our National Investigative Team partnered with Kaiser Health News to find parts of the country where people have to drive a long way to get to a certified stroke center.   https://t.co/AgJnN2K4PO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IDPH also reported that 9,410,057 COVID-19 vaccines had been administered statewide. https://t.co/PwVajcp5PI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of Monday afternoon, 2,390,239 COVID-19 vaccines - 2,300,798 to Iowans - had been administered statewide.https://t.co/9iqz13IdDK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A SEVERE THUNDERSTORM WATCH has been issued for parts of west central Illinois until 9 pm. Counties in the watch area include Bureau, Hancock, Henderson, Henry, McDonough, Mercer and Warren. Main threats include strong winds, large hail and isolated tornadoes. https://t.co/wftEIMmD8F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A SEVERE THUNDERSTORM WATCH has been issued for parts of west central Illinois until 9 pm. Counties in the watch area include Bureau, Hancock, Henderson, Henry, McDonough, Mercer and Warren. Main threats include strong winds, large hail and isolated tornadoes. https://t.co/811NlTUJcO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The STORM PREDICTION CENTER has put the TV6 viewing area at a MARGINAL to SLIGHT RISK for severe storms this afternoon and evening. The main threats will be damaging wind, large hail and brief heavy rain. Isolated tornadoes will also be possible. Stay tuned to TV6 for the latest. https://t.co/WuHfjsllPX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SPECIAL WEATHER STATEMENT: A line of strong thunderstorms will affect parts of Des Moines, Henry, Lee, Louisa, Hancock and Henderson counties until 3 PM. Storms were along a line from Rome to near Franklin to Wayland, moving east at 40 mph. 45 mph winds and pea size hail possible https://t.co/wdGZmvUKkk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SPECIAL WEATHER STATEMENT: A line of strong thunderstorms will affect western Henry and western Lee counties in IA until 2:15 PM.  Strong thunderstorms were located along a line extending from Milton to near Rutledge, moving NE at 35 mph. 40 mph winds and pea size hail possible. https://t.co/SIP1aiRBT8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The improving picture in many places contrasts with the worsening disaster in India.  https://t.co/BKtzsYqh1v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EPA estimates the proposed rule would save nearly $284 billion over the next three decades and prevent the equivalent of 187 million metric tons of carbon dioxide emissions. https://t.co/NwcU4azvS3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unser was one of six members of the Unser family to race in the Indianapolis 500. https://t.co/ntyi6ECagx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FIRST ALERT DAY in effect until 8 PM for strong/severe storms. https://t.co/rf36VT0GmW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What are you looking forward to this month!? https://t.co/Z9ai30x2ci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wxphelps: A few strong storms are possible this afternoon depending on how things evolve this morning. https://t.co/6vgPCb5anT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We realize everyday that we strap the vest on and put the badge on, were reminded of our mortality and just basically that theres no promise that youre going to be able to come home https://t.co/yfZ65Hux7Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iowa Gov. Kim Reynolds said she rejected $95 million in federal money for coronavirus testing in schools because she didnt think there was a need for the funding.  https://t.co/o6LQBrzSU4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So far this year, 997 people have been shot, compared with 718 last year. https://t.co/Xdv7p5YWLb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[88 of Iowas 99 counties have told the state they dont need all or part of their weekly vaccine allocations for that week, according to the Iowa Department of Public Health. https://t.co/NPsxUsjmRu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The woman from Durango was believed to have gone walking with her dogs on Friday near Trimble. https://t.co/FLUNG2rFub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police have arrested two people after receiving a report of trespassers near the home of Britains Prince Andrew, the second-oldest son of Queen Elizabeth II. https://t.co/R0eZbQwtsr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[His death was confirmed by both NASCAR and his family, but no details were given. https://t.co/3Y6a5J0h4Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crews are investigating a possible plane crash, saying that a small plane may have crashed while trying to take off. https://t.co/MR5RL7OZ5k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials say the water tower drained overnight due to a technical malfunction.  https://t.co/o3tdCqCkLe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The White House has been under pressure in recent weeks to join an effort to waive patent rules for the vaccines so that poorer countries can begin to produce their own generic versions of the shots to vaccinate their populations. https://t.co/nl9QVzkyWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Investigators believe the gunman was seeking a specific person he was angry at, but that person wasn't at the casino at the time. https://t.co/0LaovyN6vt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["His brother has a bike so hell be just like a normal kid now and hell be able to ride. So itll be nice for him to get out there and get a little bit more independence."  https://t.co/k6mAz5d5B0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In that area of Point Loma its very rocky. Its likely the waves just kept pounding the boat, breaking it apart, Ysea said. https://t.co/KcxkQpBoti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is an arrest warrant for First Degree Murder with a bond set at 2 million dollars for Michael Bennett. https://t.co/G4lRnsWLgH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials say they found a man in a backyard late Saturday, he was later pronounced dead. https://t.co/G4lRnsWLgH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Expect increasing cloudiness this afternoon/evening, with rain chances later tonight. https://t.co/s6SeYGeUdU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials came under growing scrutiny Sunday for ignoring warnings about safety lapses at one of Israels most visited holy sites, as the country mourned 45 ultra-Orthodox Jews killed in a stampede at a festival there. https://t.co/RnbktVgIdT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A summer full of music is coming back to Galva. The Galva Arts Council announced the return of the Levitt AMP Music Series.  https://t.co/DiGgW71Mks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Its part of respect and caring. We dont want anyone to be forgotten. You wouldnt want your loved ones to be forgotten and we sure dont want anyone elses to be either." https://t.co/Cpl7xnC5eo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some sun, some clouds, and breezy winds for your Sunday. High: 70s  80's. https://t.co/rvKFwrJvo9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our weekend warm spell continues with sunshine, scattered clouds and breezy southerly winds for your Sunday. Enjoy it now, because we'll see some rain chances ahead. We're on the air now with your latest First Alert Forecast on Quad Cities Today Weekend. https://t.co/x9f8Qvg5oK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I normally wake up at 3:55 Monday through Friday and run almost two and a half hours every day before school then I go to work and then we have practice and then I come home and then I try and run another nine or ten miles https://t.co/UgPsWlGren]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The upping of tension stems from Kim threatening to enlarge his nuclear arsenal in January, and the White House's expected approach of attempting to stop DPRK's nuclear program. https://t.co/JayGMth4gQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The measure narrowly failed, 798 to 711, in a vote by delegates to the state GOP convention. https://t.co/UD8tce9OEH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Bob Baffert wins another one at the 147th running of the Kentucky Derby! https://t.co/a6ZdMxraUo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The clinic will be open Tuesday-Saturday this coming week from 8 a.m.-4 p.m. https://t.co/4dJj7P5NUp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The U.S. Geological Survey said the magnitude 6.8 earthquake hit early Saturday at a depth of 47 kilometers (30 miles) off the coast of Miyagi prefecture. https://t.co/D99ekYSCxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keith Mills, a Secret Service officer who protected the late President George H.W. Bush and former President George W. Bush, died Sunday during training, said his brother.  https://t.co/kDIMB6oy9r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Powell and the rest of the Feds policymakers plan to keep rates near zero until nearly everyone who wants a job has one, even after inflation has crept above their 2% annual target level. https://t.co/KMsmO24Zwf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India has opened vaccinations to all adults in hopes of taming a monstrous spike in COVID-19 infections. https://t.co/MX4PNAcNXE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Right now, his prognosis is grave. Alexander, a Belgian Malinois, is fighting for his life after protecting his owner during a confrontation with another man. https://t.co/XrYN0liFL1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Character actress Olympia Dukakis, perhaps best known for her Oscar-winning performance in the film Moonstruck, died Saturday at age 89. https://t.co/6zOikhnWDJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The general manager at Bastians Auto Shop tells TV6 he believes the fire started due to a neighbor burning something near the back of their building. https://t.co/GgXTAKxhHX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Virginia woman created a social media meme campaign to try to get a company to fix a cable that had been down in her property for weeks. https://t.co/6QMp16DDWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sunshine continues with a WIND ADVISORY in effect until 7 PM. https://t.co/YkEWwgtCLA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A WIND ADVISORY remains in effect until 7 PM this evening for the northern two thirds of the TV6 viewing area. Gusty winds up to 45 mph could blow around unsecured objects.  Tree limbs could be blown down and a few power outages may result. https://t.co/GlmSyf2Vyq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warm sunshine and breezy winds this afternoon. High: Low/mid 80's. https://t.co/Skcdz0h6Jk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's official: America and NATO have begun their final withdrawal from Afghanistan ending America's forever war" after nearly 20 years. https://t.co/5D4qWeUGq2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Strong SW winds, gusting to 40+ mph, along with low humidity, will lead to an elevated fire threat throughout the area today. Please try to delay any outdoor burning today, as the combination of strong winds and dry air will lead to rapid spread. https://t.co/dzxcWWyiea https://t.co/mUmBa843Hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sunny, blustery and unseasonably warm today, with highs in the 80's. https://t.co/LDlRYDfrLy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here comes the sun! We're on the air now with your latest forecast on Quad Cities Today Weekend. https://t.co/goSmxuyDRG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 911 call was one of more than a dozen placed from the Columbus foster home since 2017 and the case has cast a light on Ohio's foster care system as a whole. https://t.co/2vE334kqwz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going back to last year briefly, Camp Shalom and Camp Ewalu up at Strawberry Point, Iowa were the only two camps in Eastern Iowa that ran overnight Summer camp. https://t.co/Vbl4UoytQH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The podcast features speakers on a variety of topics, including education, careers, and the military. https://t.co/EWeHluorAa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The capsule will be opened for Davenports 200th anniversary in 2036. https://t.co/tzBFIn8ECQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coomer, the security director at the Colorado-based firm, said in his lawsuit that he had gone into hiding because of death threats. https://t.co/nJs0DtV2jJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Los Angeles County sheriffs detectives are also investigating domestic violence allegations against Manson dating from 2009 to 2011. https://t.co/aHawOEJC5z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While immunization rates have slowed recently, the number of those fully vaccinated is seen as a highly encouraging sign. https://t.co/sTO9lK2tXS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Divos is wanted in Rock Island County on charges of Probation Violation, as well as other charges throughout the area. https://t.co/w1JS85xc2n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[East Moline police are seeking help in identifying suspects who reportedly damaged two restrooms in Hereford Park. https://t.co/APBWHKBRJh]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>