<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Staying well below average #COVID19 hospitalizations this year vs last year https://t.co/gLPqZHEr9M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From ADPH https://t.co/Uzl8dZh4s5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADPH posted this today. Some of Bama Trackers demographic numbers are showing incorrect due to this https://t.co/sG0Wu5tNjU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After a slight increase last week, confirmed hospitalizations are back down some and still under last year at the same time. https://t.co/v1JqRwq4mw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SUCybrarian Yes I should change it. Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnviroBlazerD The CDC stopped updating that page and their variant data.... for some reason.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Outside of Alabama, this is daily new cases globally. https://t.co/QEna6gandk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Grip: UPDATE: Mobile County Health Dept confirms that todays spike in local #COVID19 cases comes from a backlog of laboratory re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALPublicHealth: .@AlabamaNG, @AlabamaEMA  ADPH are hosting a #COVID19vaccine clinic in Macon County through 5 pm TODAY (4/22). This is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[+516 confirmed cases today but 233 from Mobile County, so maybe another backlog today?  Waiting for a post from ADPH https://t.co/Kwb178g0cW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another change to the announcement on the ADPH dashboard. https://t.co/CZDssFMhW0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important message posted by ADPH regarding today's numbers https://t.co/7xhEcw4dGi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stanisthemoose Just shared that, thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADPH: The dashboard will update later today. We are in the process of making changes to several graphs. We are changing info to show the date when persons were first infectious (when person is likely to transmit virus to others) rather than the date we received the report]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No word yet on today's update from ADPH.  Will keep you posted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you haven't gotten the vaccine yet, are you planning to get it in the near future?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another comparison chart https://t.co/M5rapQ1WED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorKayIvey: The @fema Bessemer #COVID19 vaccination clinic at Watermark Place will open this Wed. The vaccine is our ticket out of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday ADPH reported +52 new confirmed hospitalizations, the most in quite some time.  Waiting for today's update to see if that is revised any. https://t.co/eqaVGMavPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnviroBlazerD Great question.  We'll see with today's update about 1:15pm.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New chart on K-12 tracking showing the "Total Cases Per Week".  You can see the increase last week, but still way down compared to late fall / winter. https://t.co/e8wMRXVPCf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@snorman1776 Right just COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A look at hospitalizations this year so far vs 2020 at the same point. https://t.co/EzLOEVFMG3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonmccay Ive got some of the demographic data over time. Going to see on this. Heres a chart for example https://t.co/KjGH1Kwubl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aliner No yet.  The CDC stopped updating the source for that chart and is now putting data here (https://t.co/hWLam8zGUJ), however, Alabama doesn't have enough data yet to be included.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chasemclain: @BamaTracker @riverchasebc in Hoover, AL is hosting a vaccine clinic on April 28th. Must be 16 + and be able to return on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisCampaigns: I was able to book a vaccine appointment for TOMORROW.   Thanks so much, @BamaTracker for making this possible! Looking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorKayIvey: Out of an abundance of caution, Dr. Scott Harris just announced Alabama will temporarily pause Johnson  Johnson #COVI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Related to todays numbers https://t.co/VvANqTzp2o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alabama reported 172 cases today (118 Conf + 54 Prob) and 0 deaths.  Tested increased by 1,182.  (On this day last year 321 cases were reported and the probable count didn't exist) https://t.co/BG0rJsqgHt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADPH corrected the data on the Vaccine Distribution dashboard today. https://t.co/Fwc01WB8Au]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest Alabama #covid19 counts https://t.co/nBIxVeIvJg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TBM7kBQ6Ga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Related to the vaccine data from ADPH yesterday. https://t.co/dzU5Ggtuc1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADPH updated the doses administered count from 1,970,308 to 2,908,059 today.  That is an increase of just under a million.  This is very likely a mistake in the data updated to the ADPH vaccination dashboard. https://t.co/KqMRMFpIrN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rgpatton Havent seen that noted. Would be very interesting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here are the variant counts from the CDC for Alabama https://t.co/NnxROoC5YH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wallaam85 Continued: *If someone meets probable criteria 1 or 2 but has a negative molecular amplification test (e.g., PCR, NAAT, RNA), they are not a case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wallaam85 ADPH def: "1) had SARS-CoV-2 detected using an antigen test*, 2) is known to be a close contact to a COVID-19 case or was known to be part of an exposed group*, or 3) COVID-19 was listed on their death certificate as an underlying cause.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alabama reported 318 new cases this morning (226 Conf + 92 Prob) and tested increased by 3,570.  There were 11 deaths reported.  The state mask order ends today at 5pm. https://t.co/FilxLEWaRL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jsukim21 Not sure.  Have seen over-reported counts adjusted like this before.  Seems to just be related to bad data on ADPH side.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonmccay You are right!  I don't know why though.  Here's the highest days of the week in the last 60 days.  Thursdays lead for tests reported. https://t.co/tIAUrVK1al]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorKayIvey: As Ive previously stated, Alabamas mask order will expire at 5 p.m. on April 9. Today, Im announcing our state will]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryThornton95: Governor Ivey has announced she is following through on ending the mask mandate this week, but she is keeping the bone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update from ADPH is delayed again today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's my #Twitterversary! I have been on Twitter for 1 year, since 7 Apr 2020 (via @twi_age).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bama Tracker Twitter is 1 year old today]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bob_Grip Large increase in the B.1.1.7 count since 3/31 https://t.co/Cn87U2Bd7k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since peak on January 5th, daily reported cases have fallen 96% https://t.co/ULgIfFtTXw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GinaMaiola: .@GovernorKayIvey will hold a press conference Wednesday morning at 11:00. Tune in! #COVID19 #alpolitics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADPH has not updated yet today. https://t.co/mZFZIzWMyY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALPublicHealth: #COVID19Vaccine clinic TODAY in Butler County! Thanks to @AlabamaNG and @AlabamaEMA, who will be on hand along with ADP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @huntsvillecity: VACCINE UPDATE: Beginning today, April 5, Alabama Public Health will extend eligibility for COVID-19 vaccinations to in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorKayIvey: ICYMI: @ALPublicHealth is launching a program to vaccinate homebound people in the next few weeks. Folks that are home]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI:  The ADPH Vaccine Distribution Dashboard now has tabs for demographic data.   This data will be aggregated to Bama Tracker this week. https://t.co/uOnqbRzQIp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorKayIvey: Ive committed to the people of AL that were on a path fwd,  I remain hopeful  optimistic in where we are going. To]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALPublicHealth: .@GovernorKayIvey during a visit to the @AlabamaNG mobile vaccination clinic in Wilcox County Friday announced that, be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALPublicHealth: Check out these two upcoming opportunities to get a #COVID19Vaccine in Florence: - April 8 at 1207 Sherrod Ave, Florenc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seadvm Oh Ill update it, just forgot to do so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CullmanRegional: In order to help speed up the vaccine scheduling process, Cullman Regional has launched an online scheduling tool  to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[228 cases total reported this morning. Lowest numbers since late April/early May 2020. https://t.co/GOf3XdOiSr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Vaccine Providers section on Bama Tracker has helped many people find appointments. Check it out if you are having trouble getting the vaccine! https://t.co/dM4ZpGcV7E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlanJonesHSV: My wife has had hardest time getting Covid vax appointment. Today, using @BamaTracker, located opportunity and got appt i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HenryThornton95 Latest numbers from their dashboard https://t.co/96ThYIDv4Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @citycouncilbham: President Parker wants to notify eligible residents that there are still COVID-19 vaccines available TODAY at Legion]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here are the results of the Vaccine Hesitancy study ADPH briefed today.  https://t.co/G4BmewU1Ao https://t.co/m1J2uWyWZf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you look at %Complete Vaccinated People by county, Lee County really jumps out considering the eligible population. https://t.co/uc7QXIPGQM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrianLawson15: Dr. Harris also said Alabama has seen 113 variant strain cases, mostly UK strain, a few from two California strains, one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryThornton95: Dr. Scott Harris of ADPH is holding his weekly coronavirus vaccine briefing.  Important bits in this thread. https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A bunch of CVS locations around the state have availability as of 8am.  https://t.co/ToyYb9avZc https://t.co/FzwIdaEpnV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have you had any luck finding an appointment? https://t.co/GChIIuc0OU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FordPrefect747 Agree, may adjust]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alabama reported 427 cases this morning (307 Conf + 120 Prob) and tested increased by 4,250.  There were 17 deaths reported. https://t.co/Day8Mh6W2f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADPH's weekly flu report https://t.co/UJy7pCQSLg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maryscotthodgin @jhardingAL @ALPublicHealth Here are some more vaccine data maps if interested https://t.co/bsmKBV0PIM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paul_gattis: A marker of COVID progress: The weekly briefings in Huntsville from govt and healthcare officials will end after next Wedn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jnholsombeck Based on patient residence, per ADPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @huntsvillecity: Latest #HuntsvilleAL COVID-19 Update  March 24, 2021  Watch Live  https://t.co/SBG9hL39GX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In addition to the provider list and CVS tracking, the Bama Tracker Vaccine Providers section now includes tracking of Walgreens locations by city across the state. https://t.co/lAWQfCdfHv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALPublicHealth: #COVID19 Vaccination Clinic in Greene County at the Greenetrack at 524 Co Rd 208 in Eutaw has Pfizer vaccine available]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ICURIS38 I don't believe so, because the data for hospitalizations comes from a different source.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALPublicHealth: #COVID19 Vaccination Clinic in Coffee County at Enterprise Civic Center @ 2401 Neil Metcalf Road has Pfizer vaccine ava]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder, today's case count numbers could be high as they will include the data from yesterday.  This is due to technical issues noted by ADPH on their dashboard yesterday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReporterEric: A COVID-19 vaccine appointment that isn't a month away can be a tough find right now. @BamaTracker is working to simplify]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HenryThornton95 Only via the change in the cumulative totals each day. Weekend lag would have to be accounted for also.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest vaccine data from ADPH https://t.co/tpWjXykh0Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnviroBlazerD It is my understanding that a sample of tests are sent to the CDC to be tested. https://t.co/TgJse9prJ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CDC reports 94 cases caused by the variant B.1.1.7 in Alabama https://t.co/wSw5ay74Cs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrcoEsquandolas Yes based on patient residence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wisekris Very good question!  Unfortunately this is the first batch of this data I have gotten.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important notice on today's data from ADPH: https://t.co/CIlU7FUmys]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TLocke_ On the most recent update I added a marker to indicate it is probably due to the backlogs that happened last week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These counties had confirmed cases removed from the totals https://t.co/VaBsGOX7u7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So today's increase in new cases looks odd because apparently a bunch of number corrections took place.  Overall +10 cases were added to counts as many counties had a reduction in both confirmed and probable cases. https://t.co/bRe9V8UM96]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more maps check out https://t.co/bsmKBV0PIM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's a look at how the state of Alabama is doing on rolling out the vaccine.  This map is the percent of eligible population per county that has completed the vaccine series. https://t.co/1qJkUGTc93]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stanisthemoose: @BamaTracker Lowest number of confirmed covid cases since 4-23-2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernorKayIvey: Ive amended our health order to reflect the @CDCgovs latest guidance - making the return to the classroom even easie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you and I'm really glad he was able to get his vaccine! https://t.co/3o7e5cuOcY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarshaSturdeva1 Based on Patient Residence]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>