<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GarySidley: Dominic Raab's recent comment that restrictions such as #masks may be with us beyond June 21st clearly shows: If we don't l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: Everything would be better if everybody just stopped lying.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Ten days ago anti-lockdown marchers in London were gaslighted, guilt-tripped and defamed by a number of Inside the Tent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chillie2: Spoke to many ppl today, most notably 3 women living in different parts of Ontario - connected in no way. One from Hungary, o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: They cannot say it, but I will. @Sacha_Lord  @hughosmond brought a legal challenge to restrictions placed upon our industry,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hughosmond: News: after unexplained 2 week delay, Court ruled our claim "academic" as would not be heard before 17th May. After the rul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Unlocked_UK_: Back on YouTube  https://t.co/ORGOylpYvm   Unlocked Exclusive  in a hard-hitting interview, retired NHS pathologist Dr J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: A wise lesson I had learned from my late mother at a young age was never to care what others think of you. External validatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: Not once but almost always, Greta Thunberg wears disposable masks, whilst lecturing us about our irresponsible actions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: If SAGE arent predicting a 3rd wave, that makes Vaccine Passports redundant. Theyd simply be for control.  Thats that.  #Op]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wouldn't even passive aggressively nudge anyone out of my dance space  https://t.co/dBevEy2P7u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hartgroup_org: HART member Dr Gary Sidleys petition, calling for all face covering mandates to be ended immediately, has hit 50,000 si]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HareHoundsBath: Closed for the last 3 months. Finally reopen with a fantastic outdoor space and guess what? @bathnes  want it taken dow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @silkiecarlo: This is a H U G E scandal   mostly false results  missed earnings and education  false imprisonment under statutory obl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timspector: Our elderly are still being held prisoner despite being at no risk to themsleves or others - every day it continues is a di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: PCR positivity is at 0.8%  The lowest its ever been. - @fact_covid   Deputy CMO Van Tam says we are the bottom of possible le]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @deeksj: The 1st 2 weeks of school testing did find MORE FALSE POSITIVES than TRUE POSITIVES - data are finally public.  Proportion fals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If we really were following the data, not the dates, we'd be fully opened up by now and this would all be over. Instead va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: SWEDEN: "PCR technology used in tests..cannot distinguish between viruses capable of infecting cells and viruses that ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zepzep: 1/: Hello hello! Greetings from Hollywood to our viewers from all around the world. Thank you for watching. Thank you for havin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #VaccinePassport they said wasn't happening? That wasn't in any gov manifesto? That no-one has voted on? And if anyone cites the Yellow Fever vaccine certificate - you can get in the fucking sea. #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/u0bHhqjCrH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Telegraph: Are you willing to demonstrate Covid-19 status to gain entry into businesses?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arwenstar: The PM shuts the entire country down for a year with devastating consequences.   The media: not ONE pertinent question asked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: If pubs cannot have people at the bar come June 21st, this Govt will be complicit in the destruction of one of the UKs oldest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Texas fully unlocked 6/7 weeks ago, business restrictions lifted and mask mandate gone. Covid data remains lower. Similar patt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: SAGE modelled a huge surge in Covid cases after the schools opened again. So far, it hasnt happened. Repeatedly, their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karma44921039: Watch this https://t.co/mOEXbcpWjE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LucyHunterB: This is very hard read, but it should be read. A timeline of how Iranian women were stripped of their rights and freedoms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peachypuk: All these absolute melts crying about spreading at the protests. Have they seriously missed the fact that there have never b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timspector: Totally support ending this madness! 1000 people get cancer each day and we dont stop them buying cigarettes or junk food]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My dog walk today might have been a bit quieter than the 'big walk' in London, but my steps were in solidarity with those on the #londonprotest #FreedomMarch #EnoughIsEnough #NoVaccinePassports #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/8oznyqMK98]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Unlocked_UK_: Dr John Lee Unlocked  Covid is the cure worse than the disease? Coming Saturday 1st May https://t.co/josAI5s1nI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timspector: Sorry - No bad news again today - as we are at 1000 new symptomatic cases per day - mostly in the younger population and 33]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ErrolWebber: This is Courtney Ann Taylor, a mother in Georgia. Shes one of the many parents whove HAD IT with mask mandates, especial]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hartgroup_org: HART member Dr Gary Sidley has launched a petition calling for all face covering mandates to be ended immediately. Read]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: In case you haven't noticed, there is absolutely nothing in the 'road map' about ending the mask mandate.  So unless you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Dear @michaelgove , You do not seem to be listening to an industry that supports up to 6m jobs. An industry that supports supp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: South Dakota Governor bans vaccine passports.  Meanwhile the UK gov starts trials, after repeatedly stating they would]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidjthunder: ARE OUR GOVTS *REALLY* "FOLLOWING THE SCIENCE?"  Politicians who impose massively disruptive Covid restrictions repeated]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattletiss7: What has happened with the ESL collapse just goes to show how powerful the people can be when theyre unified. This is why]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: lets talk football  Players can hug and kiss after a negative test but  A bride cant walk down the aisle with her]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Now lets get to this picture.. I get what the PR team are trying to do, but yet again, a kick in the teeth for Pubs. Rules st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: SARS-CoV-2 stands for severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2. The word SEVERE seems to have been forgotten, while]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sacha_Lord: Just announced: 2nd May. 5000 people. No social distancing. No masks. No passports. Fantastic to see Greater Manchester ban]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: We were told we were protecting the NHS. We have. The NHS is not under threat from COVID now that 36m elderly  vulner]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: The difference between Scottish and English indoor Hospitality rules, is an indication that this isnt about indoor ventilatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BigBrotherWatch: Document revealing that Covid passes 'are likely to become a feature of our lives' released when MPs are on recess...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lyndonx: Reiner Fuellmich is getting that support from the thousands of lawyers worldwide to bring the Covid19 scandal set up in Davos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: A married couple are finally reunited, in the same carehome.  We did this to people in the name of saving them but e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: The Caraboa Cup final has shown what level of discrimination could enter society, if vaccine passports are introduced come Jun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @silkiecarlo: To add to the horror on St Vincent, *only vaccinated* evacuees are being accepted on cruise ships or nearby islands. This]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfessorWerner: On 8 April a German court in Weimar ruled that schools are not allowed to impose masks, distancing  testing as this i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TXUUQ: The vaccine passport should be understood not as an easing of restrictions but as a coercive scheme to encourage vaccination, wr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - The CO VI D - 19 Jabs are so safe that a total of 490,343 adverse reactions have now been reported to the M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This saddens me beyond belief. What have we become? People who have missed the touch of another person in their final moments are subjected to this? We've no fucking humanity. #EnoughIsEnough https://t.co/0Qlcv1Rqf4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - It's all a big fat lie... An in-depth analysis of NHS  ONS data for the year of the "Deadly" Pandemic prov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: My hypothesis is that the masks serve as a #tool to increase self-contamination and immunosuppression. If it were about our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: SAGE will no longer produce an R estimate for the U.K as a whole. Yes the number that has dominated our lives and has been the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Theyre lying to you  Official NHS data shows only 3.5K have died of COVID-19 https://t.co/reG832OLT7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abirballan: Did everyone get this memo?   As of 19 March 2020, COVID-19 is no longer considered to be a high consequence infectious di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @northerness: A reminder of what EMG-NERVTAG had to say about masks and "face coverings" on 15/09/2020.   So, of course, the governmen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OliviaUtley Also, to be prescribed the pill (typically) there's a pretty thorough run through of your medical history to prescribe the right pill AND you have subsequent periodic checks to monitor your BP before they prescribe you any more! Where's that level of care with the jab??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @the_brc: While Covid status certification may play an important role in certain activities, such as international travel, our members]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Infinitesimal' is today's bullshit bingo word of the day. Knocking the long standing winner 'Exponential' off the top spot after a solid 12 month run ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BareReality: Since Neil Ferguson visited his lover, Dominic Cummings went for a drive, to Johnson sitting INSIDE a cafe it's because th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Now put a pint on that table and watch the scientists explode with apocalyptic predictions of a super spreader event... https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hughosmond: Is this for real?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: If you have to work this hard at manipulating people, something is deeply wrong with what youre selling.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abirballan: Over 50% of people in the #UK have antibodies to #SARSCoV2 (14 March 2021). Many more can be expected to have #Tcell immuni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: The US government has ruled out introducing mandatory federal Covid-19 vaccination passports, saying citizens' privacy a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jengleruk: No safety issues  What an idiot to mislead so badly by stating this based on a short term trial of 300 children.   Pandemr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: The gov were slow to lockdown because they didnt think wed comply. Now they know well comply through fear, they wil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sacha_Lord: Todays ruling against the Government affects not just Hospitality; it shows that every decision made, must be backed up wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thetruebluechef: Remember this time last year the worry was about ventilators?  Everyone worried whether there would be one for them. D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: Vaccine passport proponents claim the unvaccinated have no right to travel, but that travel is a privilege and we should "stay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: When someone says we should learn to live with covid in a similar way to flu they are called a Covidiot. But when Chri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Just a bit of medical apartheid and two tests a week and masks for eternity to flatten the curve. https://t.co/y3sNvRCBtU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKHospKate: I thought it was the vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BigBrotherWatch: SCOOP: Docs reveal Covid certificates were in advanced stages last year - when Ministers were claiming there were no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattletiss7: Hey Government please dont send me or my family any covid tests as were not ill, (if we have any symptoms well stay hom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heachy_1979 "...evidence suggests people in China typically indicate higher levels of trust and lower levels of  concern over data use and privacy than those in the EU and US." Is that because they live under the CCP and saying anything else could have repercussions??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecoastguy: All these gazillions of plastic testing kits are no threat to the environment, I presume? Or the masks? Are we cool with p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LPerrins: Vaccine will get us back to normal.  Now its, mass testing will get us back to normal.  And vaccine passport will get us bac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine passports are the gateway drug to digital IDs and the government are already squirrelling away on the latter: https://t.co/64R6NZdomU   Does anyone remember this in a manifesto? Has it been voted on? #DemocracyIsDead #NoVaccinePassports #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hughosmond: Why would everyone want 2 tests per week? What would it achieve? What would we learn? What would we do with the results? An]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassports #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/JSjqdBW3Ut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Don't think most people really get how much the Govt has wasted. Track  trace is about equal to the entire defence bu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsForAlI:  NEW: 60% of adults in the UK have now been vaccinated against Coronavirus - these groups (1-9) account for 99% of Cov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Vaccine passports are one of the most illiberal and authoritarian ideas ever floated by a UK government. It risks creati]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Stop_CommonPass: 1/4 @nadhimzahawi - you *must* resign. The @netcompany_uk contract was awarded two days before your appointment as Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Heachy_1979: This is the potential vaccine passports have. Very few seem to understand the logic. If it can be applied to viruses it ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: As I have said previously, a number of times throughout this descent into dystopia:  Don't download the app.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoriartyProfJ3 No matter what he's asking, that should *always* be the answer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @skepticalzebra: Don't start them in the first place. There's my advice @michaelgove]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Not good enough. There are no acceptable levels of medical apartheid.  There are no tolerable parameters for totalitarian]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sacha_Lord: I can now confirm, that within hours of receiving our evidence, Judge Swift decided our case was URGENT  @MattHancock has t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No. Fucking. Shit. https://t.co/tWndv9d9pf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: This is an incredibly powerful, succinct and important piece: https://t.co/rzsvVES91s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lyndonx: Covid Passports will be the ultimate tool, that will expand, to control more and more of your kids and your lives. Its no jok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonottibis: REFUSE ALL TRACK AND TRACE APPS OR MOBILE PHONE LINKED IDENTITY APPS TO ENTER ANY PREMISES. If anything at all write d]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>