<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEngland: Today is International Day of the Midwife!   Thank you to all our incredible midwives for the care, compassion and support]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamieWaterall: Thanking all #Midwifery colleagues across the globe for everything that you do this #IDM2021  beyond    #Midwives pla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ICYMI: The latest round of our Schools Infection Survey (SIS) suggests a reduction in the percentage of secondary school pupils and staff testing positive for #COVID19 since schools reopened.   Read more about the study: https://t.co/WZFg6VVj9C https://t.co/KsWlfFtbUI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Professor Isabel Oliver, Director of our National Infection Service, explains how the funding will help double our capacity to investigate vaccines for #COVID19 variants.  Read more here: https://t.co/rQ2CmhcTTY https://t.co/uF3MuIDhJZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Cutting-edge testing centre to fast-track #COVID19 variant vaccines.  The government's investing 29.3m in our new testing facilities to assess the effectiveness of existing and new #vaccines against COVID-19 variants.  Read more here: https://t.co/rQ2CmhcTTY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: We are investing 29.3 million in new @PHE_uk labs to speed up the development of vaccines to fight variants of #COVID19 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GavinWilliamson: Hugely encouraging to see positive cases of COVID-19 continuing to remain low among secondary school pupils and staff.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Tuesday 04 May, 1,946 new cases  4 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  34,667,904 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine  15,630,007 have received a 2nd dose. https://t.co/9AarkTj04D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coming out of lockdown might be worrying for some of us. Worrying too much can have a big impact on the way we feel.   Visit #EveryMindMatters for a range of specific tips and expert advice to help you manage feelings of anxiety: https://t.co/oVv0DEmjTQ https://t.co/UFKPJIpFRA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we come out of lockdown, it's still really important to follow #COVID19 guidance to prevent the virus spreading.  More info on our blog: https://t.co/YyiVugFJPL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're observing #Ramadan, getting the #COVID19 #vaccine will not break your fast.  Accept the offer of a vaccine when you're invited.  Find out more about the COVID-19 vaccine here: https://t.co/0uMqooTSkq https://t.co/rDJvKlaoxW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BLOG: #COVID19 #vaccines: JCVI recommendations on the use of the AstraZeneca vaccine https://t.co/oByKbpMCCa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the millions already #vaccinated against #COVID19.  The #NHS will let you know when your #vaccine is ready for you.  More info about the vaccine: https://t.co/nGXfxIM55P https://t.co/eZCrUNWBpn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ONS: The Schools Infection Survey tests staff and pupils for #COVID19 across England to track the spread of the virus in schools.   Rea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lateral flow devices (LFDs) are one of the tools being used to help us detect COVID-19 and reopen society. Read more about them and how they work in our blog: https://t.co/2vyNicv3X6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Testing is playing a vital role in keeping life moving for us all.    Free #COVID19 tests are available for all adults in En]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BLOG: Science lessons  What We Know About #COVID19 in Schools  https://t.co/Uw5gx2xcrQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The latest round of our Schools Infection Survey (SIS) suggests a reduction in the percentage of secondary school pupils and staff testing positive for #COVID19 since schools reopened.   Read more: https://t.co/Ipz2475Xh5 @ONS https://t.co/YPHQyy33fp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: We're making women's health a priority in future health policy.   Join more than 50,000 women including @drphilippakaye, @Da]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Monday 3 May, 1,649 new cases and 1 death within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  A total of 34,588,600 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine. https://t.co/lg8rneKXVw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today's update to the #COVID19 Dashboard is experiencing a short delay.   An update is expected soon. Please check back here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Sunday 2 May, 1,671 new cases and 14 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  A total of 34,505,380 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine. https://t.co/4LaZiFcZqf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @isaperena: We are launching a study to assess the effectiveness of daily testing of contacts of cases of COVID-19 as an alternative to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Testing is playing a vital role in keeping life moving for us all.    Free #COVID19 tests are available for all adults in En]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: A new study will offer daily testing to contacts of someone who has tested positive for #COVID19  It will explore if daily t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines save millions of lives every year and are the only way to eradicate disease. Vaccines have eradicated smallpox and have nearly eradicated polio. While they arent a silver bullet, vaccines are key to ending the pandemic.  #VaccinesBringUsCloser  #WorldImmunisationWeek https://t.co/ez1DfLWlxV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This bank holiday weekend, our Medical Director, Yvonne Doyle, urges everyone to follow the Hands, Face, Space, Fresh Air guidance as we enjoy seeing friends and family.  Find out more about the guidance on our blog: https://t.co/YyiVugFJPL https://t.co/1Hq47h1dnD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Fri 30 April, 2,381 new cases and 15 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  34,216,087 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine. 14,532,875 have received a 2nd dose. https://t.co/KNJX2PMICa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This bank holiday weekend, it's still really important to follow #COVID19 guidance to prevent the virus spreading.  Make sure you only meet with six people or two households outdoors and remember #HandsFaceSpace.  More info on our blog: https://t.co/YyiVugFJPL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Our latest Real World Public Mental Health podcast episode explores how early experiences build trust  secure the best foundations for mental health throughout life.   Listen on most major podcast platforms: https://t.co/xqAy80GWlO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@DHSCgovuk are seeking views to help inform the development of the governments Womens Health Strategy.  Our Medical Director, Prof Yvonne Doyle, explains why it's really important to have your say about your experience of health  care.  More info: https://t.co/mkYlCBmE3g https://t.co/3oOWleaKTx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're observing #Ramadan, getting the #COVID19 #vaccine will not break your fast.  Accept the offer of a vaccine when you're invited.  Find out more about the COVID-19 vaccine here: https://t.co/0uMqooTSkq https://t.co/WNVufbHhiD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the millions already #vaccinated against #COVID19.  The NHS will let you know when your #vaccine is ready for you.  More info about the vaccine: https://t.co/nGXfxIM55P https://t.co/F1Mm5syOyN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New data from @Sport_England shows how adults in England have adapted to stay physically active despite #COVID19 restrictions.   Were working with Sport England on the safe return to sports after lockdown. https://t.co/8TQaiZMWXD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSuk: If you're aged 40 or over, or if you turn 40 before 1 July 2021, you can now book your COVID-19 vaccine.   https://t.co/95odTg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ICYMI: Yesterday we published our weekly #COVID19 surveillance report.  Case rates continue to be highest in those aged 10-19 years old  are lowest in those aged 70-79.  See the report here: https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9 https://t.co/3oaQmHhJtw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've published updated figures for the total number of #COVID19 #variants reported in the UK.  See the data here: https://t.co/JvZC4DketK https://t.co/Pd5cFLyH1K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We would like to congratulate Sir Simon Stevens and thank him for all he has done to protect and improve the publics health.   Sir Simon has been a real public health champion, a great public servant and everyone at PHE wishes him the very best wishes in his next role. https://t.co/yaH01Qi76j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines save millions of lives every year  are the most effective public health intervention after clean water.   While #vaccines arent a silver bullet, they are key to eradicating diseases  ending the pandemic.   This graphic explains how they work:  #WorldImmunisationWeek https://t.co/alHxcTMrMb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Thurs 29 April, 2,445 new cases  22 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  34,094,048 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine. 14,043,961 have received a 2nd dose. https://t.co/aLQrwqeMiz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Responding to our weekly #COVID19 surveillance report, our Medical Director, Yvonne Doyle, says we cannot become complacent as restrictions gradually lift.  Get your #vaccine as soon as it's offered to you and remember Hands, Face, Space, Fresh Air. https://t.co/09Q0w4IDjn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hospital admission rates for #COVID19 also remain highest in Yorkshire and the Humber.  Have a look at our weekly surveillance report here: https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9 https://t.co/bxchHhC1Rv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hospital admissions for #COVID19 remain highest in those aged 85 and over.  See our weekly surveillance report here: https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9 https://t.co/KhZ6Ne2uVu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our weekly #COVID19 surveillance report also shows that case rates continue to be highest in Yorkshire and the Humber.  Have a look at the data here: https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9 https://t.co/FAHt2ENVjp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week's #COVID19 surveillance report shows that case rates continue to be highest in those aged 10-19 years old and are lowest in those aged 70-79.  See the report here: https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9 https://t.co/nce7JsMmmw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've just published our weekly #COVID19 surveillance report.  Read it here: https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we approach the bank holiday weekend, it's still really important to follow #COVID19 guidance to prevent the virus spreading.  Make sure you only meet with six people or two households outdoors and remember #HandsFaceSpace.  More info on our blog: https://t.co/YyiVugFJPL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've worked with @EquallyWellUK and @NHSEngland on some new videos to support people with severe mental illness to get their #COVID19 #vaccine.   Take a look here: https://t.co/ZIdKD6csnK  @dremmatiffin @wendyburn @CoProNorfolk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ICYMI: Our new research shows that one dose of #COVID19 vaccine can cut household transmission by up to half.  Read more about the study here: https://t.co/y2Ps7CUxuP https://t.co/WTuzGytlbe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: WATCH LIVE: COVID-19 press conference (28 April 2021)   Speakers:    @MattHancock, Secretary of State @DHSCgovuk  Pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: Watch today's coronavirus press conference live on our channels at 5pm. https://t.co/3AhHqU95pK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Wed 28 April, 2,166 new cases and 29 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  33,959,908 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine. 13,581,076 have received a 2nd dose. https://t.co/WzeQ0euUrE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we gradually come out of lockdown, make sure you stick to a group of six and only meet outside.  Lets take this next step safely.   Full guidance here: https://t.co/jjTlOoSJyJ https://t.co/3rRXUkkZEn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All adults in England can now easily get free rapid #COVID19 tests.  You can order or collect packs of tests to do at home and report your results online.  Find out more: https://t.co/SxjCKKBSgX https://t.co/FhmpzsOI12]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our Head of Immunisation, Dr Mary Ramsay, says the results of the study are very encouraging, but it's still really important to practice good hand hygiene and follow social distancing guidance.  Make sure you get the vaccine as soon as you are offered it. https://t.co/R7jOptJDSs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People who became infected with #COVID19 three weeks after receiving one dose of the Pfizer-BioNTech or AstraZeneca #vaccine were 38-49% less likely to pass the virus on to their household contacts than those who were unvaccinated.  More info:  https://t.co/y2Ps7CUxuP https://t.co/QS5LHEzKFt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Our new research shows that one dose of #COVID19 vaccine can cut household transmission by up to half.  Read more here: https://t.co/y2Ps7CUxuP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The JCVI has advised that pregnant women should be offered the #COVID19 vaccine.  If you're pregnant, you'll be offered the jab at the same time as the rest of the population, based on your age and clinical risk group.  Find out more here: https://t.co/qNg2VjlJ2O https://t.co/zBXpcZY0Im]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the millions already vaccinated against #COVID19.  The NHS will let you know when your vaccine is ready for you.  More info about the #vaccine: https://t.co/nGXfxIM55P https://t.co/wlS5Caw8sw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: One in four adults have now had both doses of the #Covid19 vaccine.  Find out if you're eligible to book now:  https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's #WorldImmunisationWeek.   Did you know that Messenger RNA (mRNA) vaccines are a new type of vaccine that tell our immune systems how to create antibodies that defend against a particular infection? https://t.co/3W5luoDMji]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On 27 April, 2,685 new cases and 17 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK  33,843,580 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine and 13,201,811 have received a 2nd dose. https://t.co/utfeqDj3bp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today's update to the #COVID19 Dashboard is experiencing a short delay.  Please check back here soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worrying too much can have a big impact on the way we feel. Visit #EveryMindMatters for a range of specific tips and expert advice to help you manage feelings of anxiety: https://t.co/oVv0DEmjTQ https://t.co/TyWFAjFIyf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We interviewed the experts about finding the UKs dominant #COVID19 variant and the race to understand its impact.  Find out the full story in our latest #DiseaseDetectives blog: https://t.co/tDUduMg2f4 https://t.co/tvMrHEOgJm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Applicants are being sought for an important SARS-CoV-2 genomic sequencing project across 7 PHE labs.   The range of roles provide an exciting opportunity to be at the forefront of the global effort to combat #COVID19.    Search sequencing at https://t.co/jkWL4wRaT8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have any questions about rapid #COVID19 testing, we have updated our blog to include the latest information.  Find out how to get your own lateral flow tests   https://t.co/7qi6FvHthh https://t.co/dzkNg4jYug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All adults in England can now easily get free rapid #COVID19 tests.  You can order or collect packs of tests to do at home and report your results online.  Find out more: https://t.co/SxjCKKBSgX  https://t.co/yEKJLH9jmN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During #WorldImmunisationWeek it is important to remember why vaccines are one of the best tools we have to ensure health and prosperity for communities worldwide.    #VaccinesWork to bring us closer. https://t.co/vWkChawtnb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Stay safe this #Ramadan by following #COVID19 guidelines.   Watch Muslim leaders and health experts including @QariAsim @DrA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamieWaterall: During #WorldImmunisationWeek, read our latest @BJNursing open access #AllOurHealth article, which explores this importa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 Dashboard has now been fully updated for Monday 26 April, 2021   See the data in your area at: https://t.co/qw05K5kAUg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The homepage for the #COVID19 dashboard is experiencing a delay.  An update is expected soon. https://t.co/i7zW0tU5PN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today's update to the #COVID19 Dashboard is experiencing a short delay.    Please check back here soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During #WorldImmunisationWeek it is important to remember that vaccines are key to keeping our children safe and stopping outbreaks of diseases like measles and mumps.   It is vital that children continue to receive booster and MMR vaccines during the pandemic. https://t.co/w8YyWW4dz5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: It's #WorldImmunisationWeek and there's never been a more important time to be aware:   Vaccines are safe   Vaccines are e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The JCVI has advised that pregnant women should be offered the #COVID19 vaccine.  If you're pregnant, you'll be offered the jab at the same time as the rest of the population, based on your age and clinical risk group.  Find out more here: https://t.co/5txJ7U9F2d https://t.co/a91XPRDxpE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When #stroke strikes you have to think and #ActFAST.    Check their Face - has it fallen on one side?   Arms  can they keep them raised?   Speech  is it slurred?   Time. Its time to call 999 if you see any one of these signs. https://t.co/V8u9Qm60uY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The JCVI have advised that it's safe for pregnant women to get the #COVID19 jab.  Dr Dianne Addei explains why you should get the jab if you're pregnant, especially if you are from a black, Asian, south Asian or any minority background.   Find out more: https://t.co/qNg2VjlJ2O https://t.co/TalXSJNQOt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the millions already vaccinated against #COVID19 to protect yourself and those around you.  Get more information   https://t.co/nGXfxIM55P  https://t.co/mOY9I2cTFx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are a safe and effective way of protecting against disease and we must ensure that routine vaccinations are not missed while we tackle the pandemic. Want to know how vaccines work? Watch this video: https://t.co/la0uX7L4xw #WorldImmunisationWeek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard is updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Sun 25 April, 1,712 new positive cases and 11 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  33,666,638 people have received the first dose of the #vaccine.  12,587,116 have received a 2nd dose https://t.co/w8y8UaogGv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Every vaccination gives us hope.  Thank you to all of the #NHS staff, armed forces, volunteers and members of the public who]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are one of the most successful health interventions. Vaccines have eradicated smallpox  have nearly eradicated polio. They have also prevented an estimated 20m cases of measles in the UK over the past 50 years. Learn more: https://t.co/vNNUXr88nh #WorldImmunisationWeek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEngland: If you're pregnant, you should be offered the COVID-19 vaccine when you're eligible.  You'll be offered the Pfizer/BioNTech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: It's #WorldImmunisationWeek and there's never been a more important time to be aware:   Vaccines are safe   Vaccines are e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are key to keeping our children safe and stopping outbreaks of diseases like measles and mumps, so it is vital that childhood vaccinations are kept up to date.  Read our blog on childhood vaccines here:  https://t.co/EwLDdxwmqQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard is updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Sat 24 April, 2061 new positive cases and 32 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  33,508,590 people have received the first dose of the #vaccine.  12,071,810 have received a 2nd dose https://t.co/dPDVDazbP4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines save millions of lives every year and are the most effective public health intervention after clean water.   While vaccines arent a silver bullet, they are key to eradicating diseases and ending the pandemic. https://t.co/9bzYcZlDRQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meeting up with friends this weekend?  It's still really important to follow the guidance to prevent the spread of #COVID19.  Stick to a group of six and only meet outside.  Remember to wash your hands regularly, keep your distance, and wear a face covering where appropriate. https://t.co/6Gdb9ornvq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Dashboard has been updated: https://t.co/XhspoyTG79  On Fri 23 April, 2,678 new cases and 40 deaths within 28 days of a positive test were reported across the UK.  33,388,637 people have now received the first dose of a #vaccine. 11,623,671 have received a 2nd dose. https://t.co/RwrAsjOIUk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The JCVI have advised that it's safe for pregnant women to get the #COVID19 jab.  JCVI member and GP, Dr Maggie Wearmouth, explains why you should get the jab if you're pregnant.  Find out more: https://t.co/qNg2VjlJ2O https://t.co/KYlxTQTULO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: A new study from @UniofOxford and @ONS has shown:   #COVID19 infections fell by 65% after a first dose of the Oxford-AstraZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're observing #Ramadan, getting the #COVID19 #vaccine will not break your fast.  Accept the offer of a vaccine when you're invited.  Find out more about the COVID-19 vaccine here: https://t.co/0uMqooTSkq https://t.co/bL5ERumJ6J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@DHSCgovuk are seeking views to help inform the development of the governments Womens Health Strategy.  Our Medical Director, Prof Yvonne Doyle, explains why it's really important to have your say about your experience of health and care.  More info: https://t.co/Pwws5oOarx https://t.co/b2sN0DwynD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got questions about lateral flow testing for #COVID19?  Our #PublicHealthMatters blog summarises all of the latest information: https://t.co/7qi6FvHthh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All adults in England can now easily get free rapid #COVID19 tests.  You can order or collect packs of tests to do at home and report your results online.  Find out more: https://t.co/SxjCKKBSgX https://t.co/yEKJLH9jmN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ICYMI: Yesterday we published our weekly #COVID19 surveillance report.  Case rates have fallen across all age groups.  It's essential we continue to follow the guidance and remember 'hands, face, space, fresh air' to make sure this continues.   https://t.co/8dYt9zEVk9 https://t.co/we7S7mZwkg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: Additional surge testing  enhanced contact tracing where the #COVID19 variant first identified in South Africa has been fou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've published updated figures for the total number of #COVID19 #variants reported in the UK.   See the data here: https://t.co/JvZC4DketK https://t.co/IbBEqi18JR]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>