<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson Wheres the outrage!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I rather fight for the lives of children killed by assholes than fight a cop who  saved my daughter. #BLM #childrenkilled #StopTheAttacks https://t.co/lJEGwG3XzH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson BLM is a movement for the creator to have homes away from poverty. She should have brought the times in predominantly black poor neighborhoods so that her Tax (donors) money can make q change in the neighborhood]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wake up sleeping  #fakeorganizations #Kidslivesmatter #Government https://t.co/Cu7ud4kiva]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson But no one is talking about this and they dont want to hear it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read it again https://t.co/mBSmGQrIwa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @floccin70104697: @chenweihua @ScottAdamsSays The main problem you have is that is history and current CCP abuses aren't and the people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson I dont get poorer. Unless your wealth increases the the property taxes, living expenses, and so on...I would be happy you made your wealth. Even if I am poorer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@megynkelly She has no idea what shes talking about. Lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PadmaLakshmi My son told me he was a dog. So I threw him a bone. Sadly he didnt catch it and the real dog stole it. So I said: You can be whatever you want to be. But reality will always bite you in the ass!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Monique a beautiful woman of color killed by a privileged white boy! He needs to serve his time! #JusticeforMoniqueMunoz #HISPANICS #BlackLivesMatter https://t.co/DwHF4TOvZP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson Is not the proper way to say it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@popems42 @MELANIATRUMP I want this jacket!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MELANIATRUMP Yes! Vocabulary learning is essential!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ErikRosalesNews: WATCH THIS - @RepGregSteube quoting scripture on Senate Floor in opposition to #EqualityAct. @HouseDemocrats object, t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ErikRosalesNews @RepGregSteube @HouseDemocrats @RepJerryNadler @EWTNNewsNightly I thought we were One nation under God?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Founder of #democratic party refuses to let slaves be free https://t.co/4G8lVBXD6W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @w_terrence: AOC is predicted to be a millionaire soon.  Can someone please explain to me how all these politicians are becoming million]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sandynigeluca: @olgaOlmedo20 @RexChapman @w_derham US population 331,771,304 Covid deaths, less than 267,000  not all those are true c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MassGovernor Hey...at least businesses are open now. So we can wait in a covid free restaurant for the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Nancy needs to get out! I'm not a politician or claim to know but Nancy has to get out. She is old and her views do not go with our modern new life]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson  Im still on vacation!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fix your brain @dhrupurohit  https://t.co/l5uuwIWGy8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[History has me hesitant about the coronavirus vaccine. Trust your gut instead always. #novaccine https://t.co/b3cEVO7Qbp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#LearnTheRisk #stopkilling #NoVaccineForMe #nocovidvaccine https://t.co/PkKlZoLaBE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheSecretLawofA I don't want to fall over! I want the abundance of the flow this water carries but in money!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#leticiawright should not be harassed for expressing her truth. People need to do more research and stop believing that the sky is blue. Man creates a virus. Patented virus. Creates #vacine immediately. #lies Rich vs Poor #covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson I asked a nurse at a major Boston hospital and she said there were three people with covid in ICU#COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RexChapman @w_derham The vaccine trial was 3 phases they completed only 2. Will not continue with the third. They treated only healthy strong people. Even after the vaccine you still need to wear a mask, stay socially distant. The elderly are not getting the vaccine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BTSportBoxing Go Mike!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews My condolences to the family]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@josie_huang @MayorofElSereno These should be sold to the people living in them now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Acosta Really? I thought it was all for the riots and looking and defunding the police?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You pi https://t.co/IvjZkA2eIv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Boilerzz @superego_idolo @MrJonathanCarr @PaulJSweeney @Jeremy_Miles Very well said!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As it should be...FREE! #MenstruationMatters Scotland becomes the first country in the world to make sanitary products free  https://t.co/fys6cNg695]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#food https://t.co/gHa5AH9Etu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read it until you realize the truth. This guy working so closely with Gates too...sounds like dinner will not be your only problem. https://t.co/JwdXLJVXwH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who do you believe and why? Who do you trust? #Election2020  #Government https://t.co/end4M6CMXf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrinceEa: STOP BELIEVING IN POLITICS! This is a controversial message but I sincerely feel that politics will NEVER be enough. Yes, we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrinceEa You just mad me cry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrinceEa: Happiness is the new rich. Kindness is the new cool. Health is the new wealth. Inner peace is the new success. RETWEET]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Men or women we are all light #mudic @indiaarie India.Arie - I Am Light (Lyric Video) https://t.co/RyiJyGwJaY via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson Is like me saying Im going to stop my period with a tampon! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays Maybe NYC?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnson described her father as a pioneer who went against the grain and wrote and created what he felt He wanted to create what really felt organic and authentic. He never acquiesced to the industry." #roots  https://t.co/DfC6eXpBVh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Hamster Dance Tribute 2019 https://t.co/qbIKkWTsxT via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OldKanart @ConceptualJames You should make it and put them side by side. And ask what the people see. To me is hate whether is black, white, orange or green people. Is horrible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonydusJohnson This is horrible. First I don't like how the artist used women's naked bodies to expressed murder. Second...what is the artist saying that cutting someone's head off is acceptable?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveForbesCEO So you still believe that America will benefit from a flat tax rate?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't keep paying more! https://t.co/2xpyw01uIw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grab a cup of coffee and get on YouTube with @ScottAdamsSays for a good conversation https://t.co/7JoZzZzSRA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays @realDonaldTrump Podcast YouTube with cafe tomorrow,!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh, Joey, you did it again https://t.co/9BC7IrAOXj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He asked the president for proof! https://t.co/J4i2OXLFUL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JoeBiden Yes, President! You are right!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JoeBiden Hahahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodnight my love https://t.co/YFc7yFQ3I2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yah! What a great team to bring awareness to the sleepy hollow people! https://t.co/hzqLHOsARO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @DiamondandSilk You both are so honest and real and strong!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've never been a white embrace people of color with such kindness. @DiamondandSilk  https://t.co/IILvgShqcp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichellCClark Booker T. Washington Biography.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As a leader you have to confront problem! https://t.co/E8T6nEteY8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Acosta He's being doing this for years. Is old news]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeonydusJohnson: I'm so sick of talking about race. I'd be ecstatic to never talk about race ever again. This religious, cultish obsess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MllcKenzie My daughter is almost done with college and her dream is...stay home with her kids, home school and be a housewife. Nothing wrong with you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElijahSchaffer @realJamesKlug What was he doing there with a bat? Why call him a trump supporter just because he banged the bat? These are the people that are spreading COVID ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Pendeja]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A bad check today means a good one later https://t.co/UvZki9H55i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@corey_smith70 @AmericaTalks I agree. He seems exhausted and worn out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@g3_and I didnt know they made Chai !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr What???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackCanfield Napoleon Hill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonderulo Nice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Leave the kids alone!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Thespus21 @iSkizm @chadwickboseman You are correct. Is nice that the celebration was moved to be honored.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@duranfanaz @Thespus21 @iSkizm @chadwickboseman Thats the quintessential definition of profiling. Very sad. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harassment! White person that has never experienced racism persuading people to join what? #harrasment https://t.co/PHHIwVnKhk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kalin_burt @robertowiop Scammer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@g3_and These scammers are hundreds and is sad people fall to this prey.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FlintMichigan is still suffering. https://t.co/50BQz1cYZe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maramcewin @KellyannePolls You know nothing about people crossing the border. Tell me, How many times have you gone to help someone get off the boat, or picked them up when they get here illegally?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MVPatJesus @FrankLuntz @KellyannePolls Oh my! How do you know the her?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Thank you for all your hard work. It takes a strong , smart woman to know when is time to say goodbye. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryLemanski @ericsslater @JoJoFromJerz @BeschlossDC @marycjordan @FLOTUS I love when the snow lands on tree branches. Thanks for sharing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryLemanski @ericsslater @JoJoFromJerz @BeschlossDC @marycjordan @FLOTUS So pretty! I trim my tree and another I made it look like an umbrella. Is cute]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sunflowers. Planted and now dead. Pretty while it lasted. https://t.co/T2AHRowXQC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is grass that will die. These are hydrangeas that will die. Next year they will bloom, again. https://t.co/FBXpShGWaX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryLemanski @ericsslater @JoJoFromJerz @BeschlossDC @marycjordan @FLOTUS Im a landscaper I plant these and many others all the time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryLemanski @ericsslater @JoJoFromJerz @BeschlossDC @marycjordan @FLOTUS I know they are beautiful. They grow big. I usually keep them trimmed on the smaller side when the space is limited. I love their flowers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ericsslater @JoJoFromJerz @BeschlossDC @marycjordan @FLOTUS Very nice. Maybe if the groundskeeper would have trimmed the tress properly and kept the beds cleaner it would have looked nicer and no need to take take out a teee that looks mangled.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@uneeklyme19611 @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Shout up! They went in his property!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These two bimbos need to pick on someone thats not seven! Like me! https://t.co/SA5wiuD2oo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @vvshadow @realDonaldTrump I would like to see them to this to me or my kids!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkDice Shes so uncomfortable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Frances_Ramos95 Lol me too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Is a swingers club anyways, is proven that Venereal Disease is higher in elderlies, over 55 communities, and assisted living than high schools. Lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_terrence From an Alfred Hitchcock movie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I stand with @GoyaFoods A company that helped PR during Hurricane Maria! #GOYAGIVES #goyaesbueno #ISupportGoyaFoods]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Frances_Ramos95 Oh no! I wish her well if the moving there or visiting don't worry a hell come@bqck]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>