<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Galvez: Ang target namin we can have the herd immunity sa NCR plus 6 provinces around NCR by Nov. But ang target namin sa iba is we will scale up to 213 days with the same productivity of more or less na target natin sa NCR 120k a day but in our national target, 500k jabs a day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[3/3] Galvez: In order to really get the same effect, we need to get strategic areas where in there is affection and at the same time it has the highest economic and social impact.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/3] Galvez: So theres a possibility talaga na magkaroon ng delay. So in case magkaroon ng delay  were not able to substitute yong mga vaccines na makukuha natin sa mga lugar na nagkakaroon ng constriction we will have a realistic target of having arranged of 50-70 million.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/3] Sec Galvez on the strategy of herd immunity: Ang target natin ay kunin yung 70 million na herd immunity pero nakikita na yong with the restrictions of the global market lalo na yong nangyayari sa India, nandun ang 30 million natin na vaccines na kinuha.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez on administering Sputnik V: Ang ginagamit pa rin natin (prioritization) ay yung A1, A2, at saka A3 na priority list.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[3/3] Sec Galvez: and we are very happy Gamaleya will add to this steady supply na gagawin natin this coming months especially this coming May, June, July.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/3] Sec Galvez: Yon na po ang aming sinasabi namin yong lahat ng portfolio na kinuha sa vaccines ay talagang inaano po natin na maging safe at effective ang kanyang requirements]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/3] Sec. Galvez: Nakita natin na napakadami ng pila. We never expect na yong reception sa Gamaleya ay mataas. We are happy na yung vaccine na inaadminister natin na galing sa procurement natin ay talagang well accepted by the FIlipino people. https://t.co/Vg4rz5QENv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roque on the Sinopharm vaccination of President Duterte: The message sent by the President yesterday ay magpabakuna na ang lahat habang may makukuhang bakuna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/2] Roque: So ang ibig sabihin ni Presidente, kapag marami rami na ang nabakunahan, at napadami natin ang ICU beds at napakita natin na napababa na yong pagkalat ng virus, ay pupwede na po tayo uli mag bukas ng ating ekonomiya.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Roque on the lifting of quarantine restrictions: Ang solusyon sa pandemya ay itong bakuna so pinapadami po natin ang hanay ng mga nabakunahan at tinitignan po natin yong tinatawag na attack rate habang nag-iimprove pa tayo ng ating healthcare capacity. https://t.co/IDk9G3OLGt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Noong nagintroduce kami noong buwan ng Jan, may mga hesitation pa po pero noong naglaunch tayo ng Sinovac at Astrezeneca noong March, gumanda po ang kumpiyansa ng mga tao dito noong nakita po nila yong mga health professionals natin na ang una pong nagkaroon ng vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Paraaque Mayor Olivares: Nasa 35k na po ang ating nabakunahan at ang yun pong acceptance sa Paraaque ay lumalaki. https://t.co/We7PSTiTE2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec. Galvez: Malaki po ang maitutulong ng Sputnik V na magkaroon tayo ng 20 million sa 148 million na target natin mabili ngayong taon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/2] Sec Galvez: Ang ating kontrata ay good for 20 million doses. Initially nagkaroon tayo ng 10 million na payment, yung 15 percent. And were expecting in 4 months yung 10 million doses na yun ay mabibigay sa atin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Sec Galvez: Maganda ang naging reception ng Sputnik V, we never expected na ganito kalaking numero ang tatanggap nito. Kami ay natutuwa sa initial 15k na i-rorollout simula ngayon sa 5 city ay madadagdagan pa po yan. https://t.co/OvBWY1y6IB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/2] Mariana Zobel de Ayala: and this is an important milestone for us today  to be able to be partner with you all to using Ayala mall as a location for one of the first vaccinations sites for Sputnik V. We feel privileged to be a partner with you all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Mariana Zobel de Ayala: We are so honored to be able to partner with the (national) govt and the LGU on this very important initiative. As we all know, Ayala attempted to be at the forefront of partnership w/ the govt against COVID-19 https://t.co/ZcZ4uNCvhA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roque: 1 million naman po ang target na mabakunahan ngayong Mayo mula sa 1 million monthly average simula noong ating vaccination program. 4 na milyong doses ang inaasahan nating dumating sa bansa ngayong buwan ng Mayo. https://t.co/fI5be0dlfA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roque also mentioned that China provided 1,000 Sinopharm doses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roque: Nagbigay ang 1,000,1000 doses ng vaccines ang Tsina. Nagbigay din sila ng mga testing kits, masks, PPEs, ventilators and face shield. Meron silang pinadalang medical expert team. https://t.co/1fgqMKr00F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOW: Press Briefing of Sec. Harry Roque with National Task Force Against COVID-19 Chief Implementer and Vaccine Czar Carlito G. Galvez Jr. and Paraaque Mayor Edwin Olivarez. Watch the live video here: https://t.co/3rqvNGwrfA https://t.co/oiNFN5kNUW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pnagovph: LOOK | @DOHgovph Secretary Francisco Duque III administers President Rodrigo R. Duterte's #Covid19 vaccine on Monday (May 3,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PTVph: BREAKING NEWS: President Rodrigo Roa Duterte binakunahan na ng Sinopharm COVID-19 Vaccine https://t.co/gYJrczEjIQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Govt-private sector partnership vital in success of immunization program, vaccine security  Galvez  READ: https://t.co/XUT1z8BsFi  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["THE BEST VACCINE IS THE ONE IN YOUR ARM" | Sec Galvez, NTF COVID-19 Chief Implementer and Vaccine Czar pleads the public to get vaccinated once it becomes available in their area.   Read: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/jLWiOT2H8G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Vaccine Czar attributed the successful negotiations with Gamaleya Research Institute, the manufacturer of Sputnik V, to the countrys strong bilateral relations with other nations as well as PRRDs independent foreign policy.  Read: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH https://t.co/eWw4680Wi6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Vaccine Czar said that the country is expecting the delivery of bigger volumes from Russian Direct Investment Fund (RDIF) with the arrival of 2M doses this May and succeeding shipments of 4 to 6M doses in the coming months.  Read: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH https://t.co/CeXfF9I1zy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the arrival of 15,000 doses of Sputnik V on Saturday, May 1, the Philippines now has three brands in its vaccine supply inventory, as it fast tracks the implementation of the national immunization program.  Read: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/V6tt1El1Cv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to the information released by the FDA, Sputnik V vaccines need to be stored at a temperature of negative 18 degrees centigrade and must be kept as a frozen solution.  Read: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/3OAgi20eIS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to NTF COVID-19 Chief Implementer  vaccine czar Secretary Carlito Galvez Jr, the country has secured a total of 10M doses with the Russian vaccine maker wherein the contract is expandable to about 20M doses.  Read: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/9wbi9wkOQN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First batch of Gamaleyas Sputnik V vaccines arrive; Govt to reassess logistics capabilities in handling highly-sensitive vaccines  READ: https://t.co/IXMtyUgeyl  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Initial 15k doses of Sputnik vaccines arrive in the country  https://t.co/KbT9mBwIwP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Among those who witnessed the arrival of the vaccines at the NAIA Terminal 3 were IATF Chair  Health Secretary Francisco Duque, Russian Ambassador to the PH Marat Pavlo, and Usec. Robert Borje, chief of the Presidential Protocol and Presidential Assistant On Foreign Affairs. https://t.co/VgJweIt0Wq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Galvez said the 15,000 doses will be used for a dry run in preparation for the arrival of the bulk shipments starting this month. https://t.co/8JfPZd9WAH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to National Task Force against COVID 19 Chief Implementer and vaccine czar Secretary Carlito Galvez Jr, the country has secured a total of 10 million doses with the Russian vaccine maker wherein the contract is expandable for up to 20 million doses. https://t.co/AC9Jby2rzJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gamaleyas Sputnik V is the second government-procured vaccine that was delivered to the country following Sinovacs CoronaVac vaccines. https://t.co/i5uzifPKQI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the arrival of the Sputnik V doses, the Philippines now has three brands (Sinovac and AstraZeneca) in its vaccine supply inventory, as it fast tracks the implementation of the national immunization program. https://t.co/LAzXHEsMLi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PASAY CITY --- An initial supply of 15,000 doses of Sputnik V vaccines arrived in the country on Saturday, 3:50 PM, on a board Qatar Airways flight. https://t.co/ky0TTkkUvM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[Thread] Initial 15k doses of Sputnik vaccines arrive in the country   Visit: https://t.co/Xr9UftvyLu  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/mSbzMtG9Nk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ngayong Mayo Uno, tayo ay nakikiisa sa pagsaludo sa ating mga magigiting na manggagawang Pilipino!   #LaborDay2021 #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/CTeScDZ1bM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the gov't continues to carry out aggressive measures to contain the surge in coronavirus cases, one of its top COVID-19 task force officials has called on the Filipino people to continue the efforts of mitigating the impact of the disease.  Read: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY https://t.co/siDM8QuRsE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Galvez said the government is planning to increase the countrys daily vaccination rate of 500,000 to one million once the country starts receiving a steady supply of vaccines.  Read: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/4ofOIkeO8x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government, Galvez said, is doing everything possible to bring down the number of cases, but it is also the responsibility of every Filipino to protect themselves against the virus by strictly observing minimum health standards and protocols.  Read: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY https://t.co/S9UJJtI5p1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Galvez noted that although there have been positive developments throughout the world particularly in terms of the rising vaccination rate of countries, Indias worsening COVID-19 crisis is a sobering reality that nations must confront  address.  Read: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY https://t.co/32Nuj116qP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, the country has received a total of three million Sinovac vaccine doses, including the one million doses donated by the government of China.  Read: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/p1kIo3iceq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For June, Galvez said the country stands to receive a total of 10,349,210 vaccine doses, which include vaccine doses from Moderna, Sinovac, Gamaleya, AstraZeneca (private sector-procured),  Pfizer doses from the COVAX facility.  Read: https://t.co/s52fpwo23l  #COVID19PH https://t.co/TJLfWPc2ay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOOK! Sec Carlito Galvez Jr, NTF COVID-19 Chief Implementer and Vaccine Czar, on the provision of aftercare program for COVID-19 survivors:   #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/1jTDM02Jre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Department of Labor and Employment (DOLE) prepared the master list of the vaccine recipients to ensure equitable representation of the labor sector in the simultaneous symbolic vaccination.  #RESBAKUNA #BIDABakunation #BIDASolusyon+ #ExplainExplainExplain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the National Capital Region (NCR), the vaccination sites include the Palacio de Maynila along Roxas Boulevard in the City of Manila, Lakeshore Hub in Taguig City and Quezon City Covered Walk along Elliptical Road in Diliman, Quezon City.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays event shall serve as the opening salvo of the inclusion of the nations essential workforce in the immunization program wherein 5,000 doses of COVID-19 vaccine shall be administered to minimum wage earners and OFWs belonging to the Priority Group A4.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOW: In observance of Labor Day, the PH Gov't  pays tribute to the labor sector by holding a simultaneous symbolic vaccination for workers under the Priority Group A4 of the Nat'l COVID-19 Vaccine Deployment Plan this May 1, 2021.    Watch here: https://t.co/e2OYcA8vlG https://t.co/f6OeissssQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ PH to achieve herd immunity by year-end  Galvez  https://t.co/0eEe1EXs3K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The virtual event was organized by the Philippine Chamber of Commerce and Industry (PCCI) and the International Chamber of Commerce (ICC). ###]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The gathering also highlighted the strong partnership between national government, local governments, and the private sector in the acquisition and rollout of the vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Discussions during the summit focused on the importation and distribution strategy for COVID-19 vaccines in the country.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 29, more than 1.8 million Filipinos have been vaccinated. With the recent delivery of 500,000 Sinovac vaccine doses, the government expects to hit the 2 million mark in its vaccination program.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...which cover economic and government frontliners as well as the indigent population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Galvez shared that while the simultaneous vaccination of priority groups A1 (healthcare workers), A2 (senior citizens), and A3 (persons with comorbidities) is ongoing, preparations are underway for the vaccination of priority groups A4 and A5...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to the vaccine czar, the country has so far secured  148 million anti-COVID 19 doses from seven manufacturers. The vaccines are scheduled to be delivered within the year wherein the bulk of the supply is expected to arrive by midyear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we continue to recalibrate our vaccination strategy due to supply constraints  the ongoing surge in COVID-19 cases, we are confident that the country will be able to achieve herd containment within this year, with the inoculation of 50 to 70 million Filipinos, Galvez said.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This was the assurance given by National Task Force against COVID 19 Chief Implementer  vaccine czar Secretary Carlito Galvez Jr, to members of the private sector, multilateral partners,  foreign dignitaries during the Vaccine Summit:Equitable Distribution  Safety on April 30.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PASIG CITY --- The Philippine government remains committed to building the countrys herd immunity by year-end.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[Thread] PH to achieve herd immunity by year-end  Galvez  Visit: https://t.co/5FdU8M4Mn9  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/3ZtcxC2pYX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Vaccine Summit: Equitable Distribution and Safety  https://t.co/uBrhlvr5Sy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: We are looking forward to establishing more partnerships with the private sector not just in our COVID-19 response efforts, but in the implementation of other measures that would allow our country to recover faster and build back better.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: By 2023, we envision to have vaccine self-sufficiency with the modernization and integration of our healthcare system.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: Next year, we will implement our pandemic Exit Strategy. To achieve vaccine security, we will partner with domestic and international pharmaceutical companies to develop our nations capacity to manufacture our own vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/2] Sec Galvez: ...and building our pandemic resilience by increasing the number of COVID-19 hospital beds and reinforcing manpower in high-risk areas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Sec Galvez: As part of our efforts in preparing for the long haul, we are currently focused on implementing our containment strategy. Apart from increasing the vaccination rate, we have intensified our Prevent-Detect-Isolate-Treat-Reintegrate (PDITR) efforts...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: And when we have sufficient vaccine doses in our inventory by August, we shall begin vaccinating the general population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: By June, we shall start vaccinating our government and economic frontliners, as well as members of the indigent population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: As of April 29, we have already vaccinated more than 1.8 million Filipinos with 1,880,975 million jabs administered to our healthcare workers, senior citizens and people with comorbidities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: With the arrival of a steady supply of vaccines and the simultaneous vaccination of priority groups A1, A2, and A3, we expect our vaccination rate to grow exponentially.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: The bulk of these COVID-19 vaccines will be arriving by mid-year and would significantly scale up the implementation of our National Immunization Program.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: ...This figure still does not include the vaccine supplies coming from the COVAX facility, which has committed doses equivalent to 20% of our countrys population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: With support coming from the private sector and LGUs, the PH was able to gain access to larger vaccine volumes at a lower price. For this year, our country is expecting the arrival of at least 148 million doses from the seven manufacturers in our vaccine portfolio.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sec Galvez: As of today, we have completed contracts with five vaccine manufacturers which will provide the country with a stable supply of anti-covid jabs for this year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[2/2]Sec Galvez: ...we are very confident that the country will be able to achieve herd containment within this year, with the help of the private sector with the inoculation of 50 to 70M Filipinos.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[1/2] Sec Galvez: The gov't remains committed to its goal of inoculating 70M Filipinos by year-end. As we continue to recalibrate our vaccination strategy due to supply constraints and the ongoing surge in COVID-19 cases... https://t.co/rc5vUFVa93]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE! The VACCINE SUMMIT: Equitable Distribution and Safety   Co-organized by the International Chamber of Commerce (ICC), the International Chamber of Commerce Philippines (ICCP), and the Philippine Chamber of Commerce and Industry (PCCI).  WATCH : https://t.co/EYonDOxBoC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ntfcovid19ph: PRRD, vaccine czar call for greater cooperation among Filipinos in addressing pandemic  READ: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY  #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Govt to deploy 1 million doses of Sinovac, prioritizes areas with surge in cases  READ: https://t.co/hnEKPeQ2wt  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 vaccination rollout for general public to begin by August  Galvez   READ: https://t.co/s52fpwo23l  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[READ! Dine-in allowed to 10% capacity in MECQ; barbershops, beauty parlors, et al allowed to 30% capacity in MECQ ---     @OPSpox   #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/FetoDPUzpr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PRRD, vaccine czar call for greater cooperation among Filipinos in addressing pandemic  READ: https://t.co/r5E8HQFQPY  #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcooglobalmedia: LOOK: @ntfcovid19ph Chief Implementer and Vaccine Czar Secretary Carlito Galvez, Jr. stated that the moment we have a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcooglobalmedia: WATCH: @ntfcovid19ph Chief Implementer and Vaccine Czar Secretary Carlito Galvez Jr. is confident that once we receive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcooglobalmedia: WATCH: @ntfcovid19ph Chief Implementer and Vaccine Czar Secretary Carlito Galvez, Jr. discussed the current status of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pnagovph: WATCH | Another batch of 500,000 doses of government-procured #CoronaVac vaccines arrives at the NAIA Terminal 2 on Thursday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcooglobalmedia: LOOK: According to data from the @DOHgovph and the @ntfcovid19ph, as of April 27, 1,809,801 Filipinos have been vaccin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VACCINE ROLLOUT UPDATE As of 27 April 2021, 6PM, 3,415 vaccination sites are conducting COVID-19 vaccination in various sites in 17 regions. 86% of the available doses have been distributed, equating to 3,025,600 out of 3,525,600.  Read: https://t.co/HLGpPUbHFT  #COVID19PH https://t.co/0hzrkVVU6J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SAFE, EFFECTIVE, FREE VACCINES FOR ALL | The Philippine National Deployment  Vaccination Plan (NDVP) for COVID-19 Vaccines is guided by President Duterte's declaration to provide the Filipino People with safe, effective,  free vaccines.  Read: https://t.co/hbhU7j07rB #COVID19PH https://t.co/RX9ZXR1XX6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NO ONE IS SAFE UNTIL EVERYONE IS SAFE | According to Sec. Carlito G. Galvez, Jr., NTF against COVID-19 Chief Implementer  Vaccine Czar, "It is the desire of the Duterte Administration to vaccinate all Filipinos for free."   Read: https://t.co/hbhU7j07rB #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/4621pFmcQS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HAND-IN-HAND FOR A BETTER CHRISTMAS | Sec Galvez shared during the Sulong Pilipinas Pre-SONA that the Nat'l Gov't, LGUs,  the private sector are working hand-in-hand to achieve herd immunity to ensure a better Christmas this 2021.   Read: https://t.co/hbhU7j07rB  #COVID19PH https://t.co/O2V2QIoFpD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[READ! All travelers coming from India or those with travel history to India within the last fourteen (14) days preceding arrival shall be prohibited from entering the Philippines beginning 001H of April 29, 2021, until May 14, 2021 --- @OPSpox   #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/zsYGrM3h9c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[READ! 5,000 COVID-19 vaccine doses for A4 minimum wage earners and OFWs on Labor Day --- @OPSpox   #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH #COVIDvaccinePH #ExplainExplainExplain https://t.co/o2txxMwk0p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, the PH has already signed supply agreements with 5 manufacturersAstraZeneca, Gamaleya, Moderna, Novavax,  Sinovac.Set to be signed within the week is the gov'ts supply agreement with JohnsonJohnson for 6 to 10M vaccine doses.  READ:https://t.co/hbhU7j07rB #COVID19PH https://t.co/cgIbLsSk3S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The tripartite agreements between the Nat'l Gov't, the LGUs,  the private sectors, according to Sec Galvez, NTF COVID-19 Chief Implementer  Vaccine Czar, enabled the gov't to access more vaccine supplies for all Filipinos.  READ:https://t.co/hbhU7j07rB #COVID19PH #WeHealAsOnePH https://t.co/gvGfbikCAc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to Sec Galvez, NTF COVID-19 Chief Implementer  Vaccine Czar, the gov'ts efforts will be focused on building up the nations capacity to manufacture its own vaccines through partnerships with local  international pharmaceutical firms.  READ: https://t.co/hbhU7j07rB https://t.co/yEs6U3Ee2q]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>