<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Corriere Ecco perch invece bisogna portare la maschera. Le bande elastiche, tirando le orecchie, allargano la calotta cranica, facendo espandere il cervello. Prova ne  che da sempre medici scienziati ingeneri portano tutti la mascherina! Fatelo sapere alla #Centner, magari ci credono!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine Breakthrough Infections with SARS-CoV-2 Variants - VACCINES WORK | #VaccinesWork #COVIDisAirborne #COVID19 #antivax #AntiVaccine | NEJM https://t.co/4uibJpSNV1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sustainable F1 Portuguese Grand Prix. The five plants, which house around 25,000 solar panels, produce 5.7 Mega Watts of energy, enough to power 2,500 apartments per year | Formula One World Championship | #MiamiF1GP #MiaF1GP #MiamiFormula1GP #MiamiF1 2022 https://t.co/WVezeh9oUG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pfizer COVID-19 vaccine for children ages 12-15 could be approved in May https://t.co/7dfaxZ9l1O via @flipboard |]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mako shark caught biting boat off North Carolina coast https://t.co/jFtObHjlN9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19: Regular exercise could increase vaccine efficacy https://t.co/roVbla1POk via @wef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WFLANews: Shark Attack Near Disney's Vero Beach Resort https://t.co/38bOkPVN8q #FloridaNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillyCorben: To be clear, her position is: if you take the COVID vaccine, it is unsafe for you to be near children or unvaccinated wome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KeithOlbermann: This is Leila Centner. She is a psychopathic slime running a school in Miami that is now barring vaccinated teachers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillyCorben: School founder and CEO Leila Centner's Instagram is packed with debunked COVID anti-mask and anti-vax conspiracy theories]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OOPinellas: Covid vaccine is a hoax but that covid related PPP money sure looked good to #centneracademy! Will they be returning these]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CBSMiami Do you guys know she believes the earth is FLAT???? Please ask her and youll see!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CityofMiami @Manolo4Miami You should visit/force this school and their ___________ owners (fill the space) | https://t.co/MAQOEDaalC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroMCollins: I am certain, if everyone could see the Earth floating just outside their windows, every day would be #EarthDay.  There]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now recovering from COVID-19, Olympian Alex Kopacz recalls 'dark experience' of saying goodbye at 31 | CBC News https://t.co/lX7qaV4fhJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White House Gives Its Position On Centner Academy's Announcement They Won't Employ Vaccinated People https://t.co/6th7jKowZn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe (Albert Einstein) | #COVID19 #Covid #coronavirus | https://t.co/MAQOEDaalC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nytimes By the way.... "Individual Covid-19 vaccination records are private health information and should not be shared by a mandate," DeSantis' executive order reads. https://t.co/OBc3VVmeiG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nytimes Ms. Centner DID NOT found the school, she bought it and just changed the name. The school was named METROPOLITAN INTERNATIONAL founded in 2013. Thats what money can do! We understand now she didnt do it for the kids. And I feel sorry for them!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Laughable and scary isnt it? Maybe a new anti-COVID sect with teachers as followers? I heard that the person mentioned in this article also thinks the EARTH is FLAT! TGI is just ignorance! @nytimes @CNN @ABC @wsvn @Corriere @beppesevergnini #COVID19 | https://t.co/UsoRQkFhWf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are dangerous millionaires around!!!! @CBSTweet @NBCNews @ABC @CNN - https://t.co/GUs1a3o7s2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Covid Upended a Century of Patterns in U.S. Deaths - @Corriere @beppesevergnini - https://t.co/UvE4c9e7Fk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brutamerica: Whatever you do, don't swim away...  Here's how to survive a shark attack. https://t.co/YIeANtzqZe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdrienLASSELLE @FFF @equipedefrance #SuperLeagueOut #QatarWC2022Out #Qatar2022Out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beppesevergnini #SuperLeagueOut #qatar2022Out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LiteMiami can you please play this new song? "Wait for Me" by Dilly on Amazon Music. https://t.co/XYKkFpcblW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman dies in suspected shark attack in New Zealand https://t.co/RpszERVZQk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ketaminh Thats definitely a good tips! I survived thanks to the belt of a tourist who was looking at me bleeding on the beach! And I used the belt as a tourniquet! Lucky!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @weatherchannel: Though shark attack numbers were down in 2020 due to the pandemic, Florida still once again had the most instances worl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnnalisaBruchi @Restart_Rai @corriere @RaiPortaaPorta ...e in Italia intanto si chiacchiera e basta!!! Il #paesedeibalocchi - All 50 states now have expanded or will expand Covid vaccine eligibility to everyone 16 and up https://t.co/UVd0PZXM7a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Americans who bought a house in Italy over the internet https://t.co/WLJ383602Y via @CNNTravel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ @Gazzetta_it @acmilan - Jannik Sinner is the fourth teenager to reach the #MiamiOpen men's singles final. The previous three went on to become No. 1 in ATP Rankings   Andre Agassi (1990) #1  Rafael Nadal (2005) #1  Novak Djokovic (2007) #1  Jannik Sinner (2021) #1...?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excellent singer and song just released - https://t.co/18H0UNIhsR or https://t.co/dqxDmBcuTr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9-year-old Minnesota boy bit by shark in Miami Beach (Via WSVN) https://t.co/Ok4ABXG6ON]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/h7SL1INXEK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Oprah @CNN @BBCWorld #MeganMarkle #ladydiana - History repeats itself, first as tragedy, second as farce (Karl Marx) https://t.co/liVaWnCBCL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnnalisaBruchi @Restart_Rai ho visto su RaiItalia la sua trasmissione. Scrivo dagli USA, sono Italiano e Americano, 51 anni, sono stato vaccinato sabato scorso (opzioni Pfizer, JJ, Mod) mentre tutta la mia famiglia in Italia, amici compresi, non ancora. Mi auguro accada presto]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Bite Club': Shark attack survivors find solace in unity https://t.co/5qluFNgRHm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zaiapresidente #YouCanDoIt #coronavirus Presidente ascolta. In Veneto chi lavora pu pagare il vaccino. Non abbiamo mai preso nulla gratis, paghiamo quel che c da pagare e vacciniamo. Ai pensionati, gratis! Dai forza!!!! Non farti prendere dallassistenzialismo sudista!!! #iopagoilvaccino https://t.co/dVHnhM9N19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zaiapresidente @RaiPortaaPorta @BrunoVespa @zaiapresidente suggerimenti dallestero. Sulla domanda dei 21 giorni, Dr. Fauci ha detto oggi: "Non significa che vogliamo farlo sei settimane dopo. Significa che, in circostanze particolari,  meglio ritardare quelle due settimane che non farlo affatto", https://t.co/PMnqrzkiI3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ValaAfshar Resell it for $1000 and you gain $250! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden's Executive Orders Seek to Restore Obama's Climate Legacy. That's Not Enough | #thatsnotenough https://t.co/7UbtMENXsf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teslas Elon Musk Wants To Dig Tunnels To Alleviate Miami Traffic Jams  CBS Miami https://t.co/9vvX2aOTIm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jrpsaki: With the pandemic worsening, and more contagious variants emerging around the world, this is not the time to be lifting restri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stress and depression may weaken your immune response to COVID vaccines, studies show https://t.co/393a9KjHlE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[mRNA Vaccines Could Vanquish Covid Today, Cancer Tomorrow https://t.co/FKlH4cVk9n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alarmingly high levels of toxic metals found in sharks living in Bahamas https://t.co/nDpB1TzSiN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THANK YOU TWITTER #THANKYOUTWITTER #FINALLYGONE #SADENDOFAMADMEN https://t.co/5T3cNKnjYJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @donlemon @ChrisCuomo @CNN @abc @FoxNews @JoeBiden this is a sick man! Please he cannot get away with it or there will be another one soon after him. It happened in Italy and Germany in 1920/30 - #historiamagistravitae - God bless America ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Disgraceful scenes in U.S. Congress. The United States stands for democracy around the world and it is now vital that the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: Canadians are deeply disturbed and saddened by the attack on democracy in the United States, our closest ally and neighb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmmanuelMacron: We believe in democracy. #WeAreOne https://t.co/dj3hs66KKn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JoeBiden #thisisnotamerica  https://t.co/raNpSwlBXT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nbc6 Thanks @realDonaldTrump good job! You can leave now but you will pay for it! May this person Rest In Peace!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nbc6: #BREAKING: Woman who was shot by member of law enforcement inside the U.S. Capitol building has died, officials say: https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden Please, no, we had enough of @realDonaldTrump We need you @JoeBiden and @KamalaHarris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoaquinCastrotx: Senators @TedCruz and @HawleyMO should immediately resign.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedcruz Please resign and hide forever!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedcruz @Perduesenate @KLoeffler Please resign!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Mike_Pence @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris #democracyalwayswins https://t.co/JsPIY9qNka]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #SuspendRealDonaldTrumpAccount #SuspendTrumpsAccount #SuspendTrump]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You throw the rock first and then run! Too late, coward! You're in the area, you're close to the parliament, you should go and fix this, you idiot! You are the worst thing that ever happened to the United States of America! I'm ashamed of being American! One shot, your blood ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #arentyougoneyet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #arentyougoneyet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your water bottle may soon be made of sugar, not plastic https://t.co/ARrMdfYRCV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To Lose Weight With Exercise, Aim for 300 Minutes a Week https://t.co/4FrzYqgYlc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Woman in her 40s' dies in rare shark attack off coast of Caribbean island https://t.co/hP4nGw8pk8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United Begins Flying Pfizers Covid-19 Vaccine - WSJ | #COVID19 #coronavirus  https://t.co/y1wah3f5ch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Sharks Turned Up at Their Beach, They Called in Drones https://t.co/9hC9Bi5gzw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man dies in shark attack off Australia's west coast https://t.co/9B3ou6Ax5u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Past a point of no return': Reducing greenhouse gas emissions to zero still won't stop global warming, study says https://t.co/zj51Z1ETkJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid Superspreader Risk Is Linked to Restaurants, Gyms, Hotels https://t.co/EkZqNETSJK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its teeth went straight through my leg: Teen surfer survives shark attack in Florida https://t.co/yr9PBcWPI3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @realDonaldTrump @JoeBiden | @CNN @NBCNews @FoxNews @ABC https://t.co/ckmf6Pegs4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After Joe Biden's win over Donald Trump, relief sweeps through America's allies https://t.co/e1DhVjPFE4 via @nbcnews | @realDonaldTrump and friends! @FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @EveningEdit How Hitler seized power in Nazi Germany: 1. Create a crisis. 2. Demonize opponents. 3. Declare a state of emergency. 4. Undermine elections. 5. Make the rule of law irrelevant. 6. Rule by executive order. Number 4 is trending]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ...!!! https://t.co/8UGURCslX1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't worry we'll be both gone by Thanksgiving!  | Slow cooking | @realDonaldTrump @Mike_Pence | Congratulations Biden #JoeBidenKamalaHarris2020 #USElectionResults2020  #COVID19  #TrumpMeltdown #Thanksgiving2020 #TrumpOut2020 #TrumpOut2021 https://t.co/kP1jjt3zYl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thanks #formerpresidenttrump but I have better thing to do! Turn off the light before leaving the #WhiteHouse https://t.co/BGdNOqh7zl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNN @ABC @NBCNews @Corriere @RaiNews we only see Miami shops board up for possible hurricanes. Of course #hurricanetrump is coming! Is this democracy?                                      TODAY IS THE DAY. GO VOTE! PASS IT ON! #ElectionDay #Election2020  #VOTE2020 https://t.co/DTVQ1YYe2a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Mike_Pence @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris @GovRonDeSantis @MayorGimenez ... made in China!TODAY IS THE DAY. ELECTION DAY. GO VOTE.  STAY IN LINE! PASS IT ON! #ElectionDay #Election2020  #VOTE2020  #KidVicious https://t.co/IOqG8LDLn0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#coronavirus #COVID19 this is how COVID get transmitted....! @GovRonDeSantis @realDonaldTrump @MayorGimenez please learn just watching the slides! Simple arrangements are #wearingmasks, #ventilation, #distance | https://t.co/KzReiWHFUG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MayorGimenez @GovRonDeSantis @realDonaldTrump call me #nostradamus please! Wow it is happening as I predicted just four (4) days ago on another tweet! Im available to be hired to manage what you guys are not able to accomplish, due to missing balls! #coronavirus #COVID https://t.co/Kr6EsAnIvQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MayorGimenez: Here is today's New Normal Dashboard for Miami-Dade County. We all need to continue working together to keep our positivi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mike_Pence @realDonaldTrump @Mike_Pence the greatest #bullshitter worldwide. On top, tell the Fox slave to make real questions. Are you in first or second grade? Pathetic lies | #ninedayatomagic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MayorGimenez You might have missed this news. If you look at Europe, the worst is still to come. You better start working on extreme plans | @GovRonDeSantis https://t.co/uvThue80eX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[University of Washington researchers project more than 2,300 Americans could die daily by mid-January, and a total of more than 389,000 people could die from the virus in the US by February 1 #coronavirus #COVID19 | Thank you @realDonaldTrump  https://t.co/GSkF4llfdi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid, ci siamo convinti di essere i pi bravi e ci siamo ricaduti https://t.co/c2l8fddjps]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Post-it I wrote during the New Years Eve party 2019, as a wish for 2020! Call me #nostradamus | #COVID19 #coronavirus | #waitingfor2021 https://t.co/4iRwoVhSxO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US should expect 20,000 more coronavirus deaths by end of October, former CDC director says  WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale https://t.co/pPiRdRccMD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shark attack victim Andrew Sharpe still missing as police recover strips of wetsuit and parts of surfboard https://t.co/T5CMnZWXmJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Drone deployed to warn championship surfer of impending SHARK ATTACK https://t.co/mdAbJUlanR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man bitten by shark while swimming off Miami Beach  Dejavu - I know the feeling. Best of luck to the man. Everything will be fine. Just a few months for a full recovery | #sharkattack #Miami #miamibeach  (Via WSVN) @wsvn @ABC @CNN  https://t.co/3jfh0VGZCh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MayorGimenez Great job @FrancisSuarez. Finally someone understanding what prevention is. For others like @GovRonDeSantis @realDonaldTrump check situation in England, Spain or France as we speak. If we keep acting correctly we can keep #COVID19 under control allowing businesses to operate ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis as we can see #COVID19 situation in Miami is slowly getting worst since everything has been reopened in full. You still have time to react or see England, Spain and France to understand Miami  will be like in a few weeks |  @realDonaldTrump @FrancisSuarez https://t.co/hcKl47NJ9l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The way Italy handled its second wave is a lesson for us all | The opposite of Mr. @GovRonDeSantis | #GoRonDesaster  | https://t.co/RoAvUHIXmZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JoeBiden 1st in Europe to be devastated by COVID-19, Italy redoubled its efforts, and they're now paying off https://t.co/jYI42MNeoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AP_Politics: Official says masks will still not be mandatory at the White House, even after president tested positive for the virus. Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis @FrancisSuarez @realDonaldTrump - Europe lockdown: New coronavirus rules country-by-country while our @GovRonDeSantis clear all restrictions. #Laughable a real  #clown | #rondesantisout | #COVID19 #coronavirus | https://t.co/wWMxxnSpNT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Record number will visit Florida on vacation and leave in a body bag | In the picture #thegenius who decided Floridas future | #totaldisaster |  https://t.co/KhE6sD8Wi1]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>