<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThumbiMwangi: Up to 6 month (5,000) Fellowships in Epidemiological Modelling for Infectious Diseases at @CEMA_Africa @uonbi 8 position]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: My @WSJ Op Ed: The business community should seize the initiative, and engage public-private partnerships, to develop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: Getting back to the office https://t.co/1iJg7WZjg0 by @ScottGottliebMD and @cmyeaton https://t.co/vHGFLjeeJ8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drJoshS: Assessing a Rare and Serious Adverse Event Following Administration of the Johnson  Johnson Vaccine https://t.co/6rXXrhonMi v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timmy315: Hi Twitter, Im Tim Manning, the White House COVID-19 Supply Coordinator. Theres been a lot of confusion around the use of t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASlavitt: Important statement regarding support for India in combatting COVID-19. https://t.co/BMblXBkSIE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theNASciences: #COVID19 Symposium: Response to the Pandemic  Featuring: - Nicole Lurie, Strategic Advisor @CEPIvaccines - Jenny A. Durk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matthewherper the uneven age breaks are stressing me out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am worried I disappointed Iris. https://t.co/jGteh2g5dF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megtirrell: Abbott's BinaxNOW self #covid19 test will be available in stores for $23.99 for a 2-pack: https://t.co/cKl8OetC1G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: Today more than 90% of people live within 5 miles of a Covid vaccine site. 40,000 pharmacies are live with vaccines an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jburnmurdoch: NEW: the variant thought to be responsible for fuelling Indias grim second wave (B.1.617) has been found in the UK, and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnDiesattheEn: This incredibly disturbing fake wikipedia page about the historic first guy to have his consciousness uploaded to a co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nataliexdean: The % vaccine breakthroughs in a population depends on: - Vaccine efficacy - Amt of virus circulating - Length of time si]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidmanheim @dylanbgeorge @iserp_columbia Similar to Laurie's question, I think having ongoing capabilities to analyze and understand data regularly will help us to find opportunities for improvement. e.g. analysis of volume of infected travelers w/ SARS-CoV-2 revealed substantial underascertainment early in pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Again, these events are under investigation and we will learn more from the experts. If confirmed, the events will still be rare. But one in a million is unlikely to be the final tally. 5/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Third, time. FDA said it was 1-2 weeks to onset. People who have received doses within that time would not normally be considered in the denominator either. On Mar 26 there were 2.7M JJ doses administered. (Not exactly 2 wks but closest date I could find.) 4/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Second, the denominator. All of the cases in US have been in women ages 18-48. It is reasonable to ask whether the denominator should reflect that. The expert committee will consider this. 3/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@C_R_Watson First, the numerator. Now that awareness has been raised, more cases may be reported. 2/  https://t.co/zJrlXHv54q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One in a million will not be the final estimate for the unconfirmed JJ events and I think we should be cautious in citing it. The incidence will surely be rare, but @C_R_Watson and I wrote about biases in estimating mortality last Feb, and similar issues are in play here 1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Many reports compare the total reported number of deaths with the overall reported number of cases. This is, intuitively, the fraction of people who die from the disease. But early in an outbreak, this type of calculation is often misleading."  (2020) https://t.co/zJrlXHv54q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nataliexdean: Check out my discussion with the wonderful Dr. @Bob_Wachter on @inthebubblepod! Variants, vaccines, and why there are so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BioAndBaseball @C_R_Watson ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Farzad_MD: 1/ in our continued COVID field epidemiology series  "What's the question?"  April 2021 edition: "Are the vaccines effective]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTomFrieden: The US vaccination campaign is facing a fundamental challenge: getting the vaccine where its needed most. Millions of Am]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jburnmurdoch: NEW: big international Covid data thread, focusing on the contest between vaccines  variants  First to the UK, where thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jkbren: For comparison, Michigan also reports outbreak settings in a similar way to Massachusetts---pretty clear / worrying patterns he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jkbren: A few new bits of COVID data from Massachusetts: - Vaccinations by age - Vaccination by race - Cases reported in school distric]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Wachter: Starting to make summer plans? On @inthebubblepod's next "Safe or Not Safe?" episode, @cmyeaton  @Farzad_MD will answer y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kj_seung @nataliexdean @BillHanage Reasonable! Maybe we'll see an MMWR soon ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenBranswell: Reinfections don't appear to be driving the surge in #Covid19 cases in the US, @DrewQJoseph reports. They still appear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: The rise in Covid cases nationally is being driven by a surge in cases among younger people, including (in some states]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ddiamond: Wasnt prepared for this emotional journey. https://t.co/qc34pbcRZ7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @califf001: We need a different research infrastructure for public health research.  @ScottGottliebMD @cmyeaton @DrWoodcockFDA   There i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: Theres no comparable effort underway in the U.S. We need to know if COVID reinfections are occurring here, and perhap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Continually impressed by the quality of evidence generated by Public Health England and partners. Nice overview of Covid-19 reinfection studies underway. https://t.co/aehikIdP8G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: CT Update from excellent team at Yale. B.1526 continues to increase in prevalence in the sequenced sample. There are n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We shall describe cohorting classes as "the full Harry Potter" from here on out, thanks to @JustinLessler. https://t.co/R7zOhmcxqO https://t.co/T2ylxRpNB8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megtirrell: FDA authorizes three #covid19 tests for asymptomatic screening without a prescription, from Quidel, Abbott and BD. These ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @T_Inglesby: White House COVID briefing today.  Significant news and developments starting with: by April 19th 90% of adult Americans wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 1230 ET! https://t.co/oxhoyvjW4u https://t.co/tPHaaQD87z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The bottom line for individuals is that if you are not fully vax or recently recovered you should still be taking all the usual precautions to reduce risk. That is what I am doing. But big picture, we are in a better position than if we were seeing these trends last fall. 7/7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Working against us is the variants, esp B117 which is now common and spreads more easily. This set us on a tougher course than we may have otherwise faced at this point, but the vaccines work well against B117 so distributing them as fast as possible still top priority. 6/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And now that many people at highest risk of severe illness are vaccinated, we can expect hospitalizations and deaths to be lower relative to case burden. Thats another bit of good news, though I would still like to see cases come down too. 5/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But at national level, unlike previous upticks, we now have vax coverage at ~16% and each day we distribute ~3M doses which will further reduce risk, day over day. This is on top of estimated 25-30% pop immunity from prior infection. 4/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yet some states are resurging. MI and NJ are at ~50 cases per 100,000 per day and hosp rising too. Risk in those states is high, and leaders should intervene by closing high risk settings and accelerating vaccination. Fed govt could help by sending extra vax coming online. 3/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many states are doing quite well. I would like to see cases fall below 20 cases per 100,000 per day as a first goal and 10 as a second goal (and then the lower the better). By that measure, we are doing ok: 35 states are at or below 20 and 12 are below 10. 2/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cases are on the rise in many states. How worried am I? I am concerned, but not as much as I would have been 6 months ago with these trends. Short thread. 1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last April, @60Minutes aired a story featuring @dylanbgeorge about the need for an outbreak forecasting center. Today they aired an update - the American Rescue Plan has $500M for the forecasting center + public health data modernization. https://t.co/6dAYEl1vsZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomorrow the UK is taking a small step toward reopening after months of stay at home restrictions. The UK has one of highest vaccination rates in the world (mostly first doses) so will be interesting to see whether transmission remains low. I very much hope it's smooth sailing. https://t.co/F95cCT1FMc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is so much epi data we don't have that would be useful right now. Data on reinfection, including time from first infection and severity; incidence by age at subnational level; cluster investigations from variant cases; more on pediatric infections and school reopening.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: 72% of those over the age of 65 have now had at least one dose of the Covid vaccine, and 47% are fully vaccinated. A g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ill be answering questions on @reddit with @linseymarr and @JumoDr about what you can do after getting vaccinated. Tuesday Mar 30 12:30 ET. https://t.co/96Ar3gwrUy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dmaccannell: Fantastic new dataset: COVID-19 Case Surveillance Public Use Data with Geography  https://t.co/MKVWCh2RBW https://t.co/BcH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOAFRO: The last #Ebola patient in #Guinea was discharged on Tuesday night in N'Zrkor 38 days after the start of the outbreak.  W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BNODesk: Results from AstraZeneca's vaccine trial in the U.S.: - 79% efficacy against symptomatic COVID-19 - 100% efficacy against seve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottGottliebMD: Covid positivity rates in parts of Brooklyn, Queens are approaching 15%, among highest in nation. NYC deserves close w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wilmotjames: We have been waiting for this, a key part of the Biden pandemic response plan, a state-of-the-art outbreak forecasting cen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KrutikaKuppalli: This is very cool. I love all the innovative and culturally appropriate ways @WHO works to raise awareness - we can l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTomFrieden: Covid Epi Weekly. Progress and Peril.  Vaccinations have already saved 40,000+ lives in the US and the pace keeps increas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great that CDC is now publishing more science briefs accompanying new recommendations. Here's the review supporting the change to 3ft in schools. https://t.co/ruA8j8rSvk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnKingCNN: v busy 12pE hour today: new CDC school guidelines + WH Covid briefing. POTUS and VPOTUS land in Atlanta. Testy China talks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @acsifferlin: The CDC shared guidelines for what people can do when vaccinated, but it's tough to account for the intricacies of individ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting "contact budget" framework for choosing policy controls based on epidemiological conditions from ECDC https://t.co/2Bvn0hCtxf https://t.co/yMZroi31F6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JHSPH_CHS: "This month marks one year since schools around the country closed classrooms and moved instruction online," write Senior Sc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WSJopinion: Expect a closer return to normal classrooms, sports and clubs by September, write @ScottGottliebMD and @cmyeaton https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will school look like in the fall? My latest with @ScottGottliebMD https://t.co/xriNsEggLP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @svscarpino: @HelenBranswell @roby_bhatt @BhadeliaMD @iowajustin Looks like a tiny uptick in RSV from BioFire's data, but--as you pointe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @svscarpino: We have a no-fail mission of monitoring and standing up a response to emerging biological threats, -Dr. Beth Cameron. Tog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andreamatranga No, just my desk. Im not sure why it looks like that. Adventures in DIY lighting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not ideal for TV but I love the late afternoon sun.  Finally springtime! https://t.co/0ZxBNaxRTg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DLeonhardt: This level of population immunity slows down transmission, says @cmyeaton. After millions of infections and the start of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashishkjha: Fun to be on @allinwithchris with @chrislhayes alongside the great @cmyeaton  Discussed  CDC guidance on vaccinated people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidalim: This is pretty nuts  HHS/DoD are estimating about 6 million Covid-19 tests are currently being conducted each day, which wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two new papers find large covid clusters in fitness facilities -  including some examples in Hawaii where every single class attendee was infected. In Chicago, case study, 68%. Indoor gyms are going to be a no for me for a while yet. https://t.co/5SGaGY46vl https://t.co/aEBA9kcv6g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For what its worth I continue to be encouraged by trends in cases, hosp and deaths. May be ups and downs ahead but every day we are administering ~2M vaccines. Will protect recipients and slow transmission. Phased reopening best, starting with lower risk activities. Keep masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cleared that right up  https://t.co/qyim5cWAY5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MorrisonCSIS: @HelenBranswell @DrewQJoseph  off an excellent summary of current thinking on what may lie ahead. as we exit the acute cr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nataliexdean: Out today -- my piece in @nature on a topic I feel very strongly about = the need to coordinate and harmonize observation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnsHopkinsSPH: "After millions of infections and the start of a vaccination campaign, the virus is finally, slowly, starting to run o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My latest op-ed on population immunity - where are we with that and where are we headed? https://t.co/ObOxvGI0ds]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @USofCare: THREAD: The House of Representatives has passed the American Rescue Plan Act of 2021. This popular legislation now heads to t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CaddeProject: CADDE preprint. A SARS-CoV-2 lineage of concern is growing rapidly in Manaus and across Brazil. Using a combination of ge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm hopeful that the leveling off of case counts is a catch-up from last week's winter weather and not another resurgence. Test positivity is still trending down and states with higher % B117 (FL) not seeing a surge. I will be watching closely to see how next week unfolds. https://t.co/0I1ERjmBT9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ddiamond: Interesting @amymaxmen piece: a new COVID database w 24M cases could shed light on variant spread in near real-time.  By the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Wachter: CDC is taking this a bit slowly; I think they'll get there soon. The best and clearest info is on @inthebubblepod, our rec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnsHopkinsSPH: .@cmyeaton from the @JHSPH_CHS talks with @DrJoshS about President Bidens new federal directive to create a National]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @svscarpino: For the past year, we've been building an open data platform for tracking epidemics and curating a global repository of #CO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@svscarpino @amymaxmen Let the record show I did not say dude! I did tell Sam he was wrong though ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @johnbrownstein: Excited to share the launch of @globaldothealth  https://t.co/jrWcW9Uzu0  An open-access epidemiological platform to t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisJansing: "The day will come when the memory of the loved one you lost will be a smile before a tear in your eye...and that's when]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Wachter: On this day we mourn 500K deaths, there's room for optimism about the future. On @inthebubblepod, I ask @cmyeaton  @Farza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nationwide we are currently at 24 cases per 100,000 per day, not far from my first goal! It's a remarkable turnaround and I'm hoping it sticks. I'm concerned about the B117 variant, but we are doing the right thing by continuing to drive down transmission. https://t.co/KWHB5viZVC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TonyFratto I have been amazed all day that its only Wednesday. Not impressed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dylanbgeorge: Mutation happens; here's what we need to do about it to keep everyone safe.    Very grateful for the opportunity to work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JHSPH_CHS: Today we release a new report, Staying Ahead of the Variants: Policy Recommendations to Identify and Manage Current and Futu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nataliexdean: THINK LIKE AN EPIDEMIOLOGIST: Lately I have been asked why we are seeing a dramatic turnaround in cases in the US. Is it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scottjbecker: APHL/CDC #Bioinformatics Fellowships applications are due soon!  Know someone who might be interested, please pass this l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @amymaxmen: Big news. 4 #Ebola Deaths in Guinea. This could mean that bats still harbor Ebola virus in Guinea/Liberia/Sierra Leone. And]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenBranswell: 1. #Ebola update based on info from @DrMikeRyan in today's @WHO presser: There could soon be news on whether these new]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>