<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@UofT_dlsph's Institute for Pandemics (IfP) has established an Advisory Table to help inform the Institutes impact on our health systems. Thanks and kudos to all!   https://t.co/3cnffGiEsd https://t.co/rESy2tGW9w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another excellent and timely front-page @TorontoStar story by @UofT_dlsph's @UofT_ijb. https://t.co/8tELvBBvXQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Big congrats to @LucasCGodoy @VinyasHarish @NicolasIragorri @june_sh_lam @FionaMuttalib and @BijanTeja on winning Banting an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: Ontario update 2/8  Were moving around less  great But too many of us are still going to work. #COVID19Ontario  htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: Ontario update 1/8  The curve is cresting, but just This is a good start. We have to keep driving COVID19 down. #COVI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today at 3 pm I will present the latest modelling from  @COVIDSciOntario. Slides will be posted on https://t.co/oOvVHkUTOm at the start of the presentation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 3/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave to end the Third Wave. Most of Ontarios outbreaks are at work. In the US, effe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please consider nominating a public health hero for this recognition! https://t.co/97KKwJIt51]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Want a behind-the-scenes look at how N95 masks are studied? @jscott_toronto of @uoft_dlsph will tour you around his lab  te]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: This is an early, early sign -- we seem to be heading in the right direction. Rt for Variants of Concern (95% of our C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm very pleased to share that @MerckCanada has given $3 million to @UofT_dlsph's Centre for Vaccine Preventable Diseases for cutting-edge research and education in vaccine science advancement at #uoft. https://t.co/ndhYt3pJON https://t.co/2RzhumPxHk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 2/3  Just by targeting vaccines on hotspots, we can prevent 20% of SARS-CoV2 infections in folks 16-59 years old -- an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 1/3 Speeding up COVID-19 vaccination in hotspots and for essential workers will cut SARS-CoV2 infections, hospitalizat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 1/2 Were all in a position to help our neighbours, family, co-workers and friends stay safe from COVID. Our behaviour]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IHPMEGSU: IHPME, let's  JAM!  Join @ELESHCanada tomorrow night @ 6PM EST to connect with other   trainees  emerging]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ontario Health Teams Impact Fellows Program, hosted by @ihpmeuoft, matches early-career researchers with Ontario Health Teams, where they will support implementation and evaluation of local projects. Apply by May 25: https://t.co/QfPq4CqKuB Kudos @ProfessorFeng @McMahon_Meg https://t.co/VDxw7YBcGN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: Science Advisory Table statement: Ontario is now facing the most challenging health crisis of our time. If we want to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LisaEsther6: Saw 5 patients in a row with shortness of breath. Each one worse than the previous. My colleagues working with me had the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @epdevilla: Today's #COVID19 #Vaccine update: 923,039 doses have been administered to date  residents age 40+ can now book appointments]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @utjcb: The Ontario COVID-19 Bioethics Table is deeply concerned about the enhanced enforcement measures outlined in the Ontario governm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today at noon, @COVIDSciOntario's scientific director, @ihpmeuoft Prof. Peter Jni, will be on @CBCOntarioToday taking questions from the public. https://t.co/YdhriHEkAR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today at 1 pm, I'll present the Ontario COVID-19 Science Advisory Table's latest modelling. As always, we'll post the slides at the start of the press conference on our website: https://t.co/oOvVHkUTOm @COVIDSciOntario]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So proud to share that @UofT_dlsph's @UofT_ijb, in partnership w/ @TorontoStar,  has been shortlisted for @cjffjc's Jackman Award for Excellence in Journalism for the excellent series, "Generation Distress." Kudos @thecribby! https://t.co/5O4i8nKkoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kudos to Dr. Michelle Murti, who just won @UofT_dlsph @UofTPHAlumni's Emerging Leader Award! Big thanks to all the panelists  organizers @ In the Loop, another thoughtful event by the Public Health Alumni Association. @dlsphjournalism @jr_ottawa @akwatukhenti @KateMMulligan https://t.co/IWfPkNM006]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieKeresteci: Do you know there are 9M+ #caregivers in Canada? During #COVID19 we are keeping those we care for safe, often at home,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrRuthHeisey: Thanks to all @WCHospital for helping us launch our First dose AZ clinic! Getting vaccines in arms is key to getting to t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DLSPH_STAGE: Sharing this event in case it is of interest to the STAGE community or others in their networks.  "This  workshop is desig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anishnawbe: Anishnawbe Health Toronto/Auduzhe Vaccine Clinic this coming Tuesday, April 13 - 9:00 - 5:00 p.m. at Native Canadian Centre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: By 2025 ~5 million Canadians will have #diabetes. @DrAleksStan  @DrValRac are looking at the socioeconomic factors affectin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OnyeActiveMD: Morning! BPAO docs in da house at @TAIBU_CHC vaccinating in Scarborough, in partnership with @SHNcares ! Dr. Duate Adeg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @epdevilla: Together, we can #StoptheSpread of #COVID19. Know someone who is 60+ years of age or 50+ living in a hot spot area? pls offe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NathanStall: Promoting #COVID19 vaccination in Ontario hotspots will require both priority allocation of #CovidVaccines and community-b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: Excellent all-in-one-page summary of clinical guidelines for COVID therapeutics. Clinicians: please read  share w/ co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanielJDrucker: Today  lost a giant. A selfless leader who built the foundations of modern molecular #genetics @UofT @SickKidsNews @S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT: #UofT congratulates 2021 Canada #GairdnerAwards co-winner @danieljdrucker @UofT_DoM, @uoftmedicine  @SinaiHealth #LTRI, for game]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: More than 25% of Ontarians older than 75 havent even booked a vaccine appointment  but most want it. The gap: Homebo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: The 8th Annual Ross Upshur Lecture on Public Health Ethics will address some of the many ethical tensions that have been so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: For ED  inpatient health professionals: More clinical guidance on Astra Zeneca related clotting: pls read  share wit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Pillars of the Pandemic, supported by @UofT_dlsph  @CTGHealthcare, recognizes the extraordinary contributions to public hea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wonderful initiative! @homecareceo @CTGHealthcare https://t.co/9YIyonuh58]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today at noon on @CBCOntarioToday, @ihpmeuoft Prof. Peter Jni, scientific director of the Ontario COVID-19 Science Advisory Table, will be taking calls from the public. Tune in if you can! @COVIDSciOntario https://t.co/2MTQrOW9br]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you or someone you know works in an elementary or secondary school in Ontario  is interested in learning about #COVID19, check out/share this opportunity to join a study being conducted by researchers at @SinaiHealth and @UofT_dlsph  https://t.co/ekN7kIAnq4 #OntEd https://t.co/LCUlSlG1UN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another op-ed highlighting the world-changing impact of Connaught Labs by @ihpmeuoft's @MarchildonGreg and Les Boehm.  https://t.co/SEZHfd1jLy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: This. Is. Different. 1/7. Yes, weve been at this for a year;  were exhausted; weve heard it all before. Today, o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: Canadas first Doctor of Public Health program has its first director  @WitekTed, a @ihpmeuoft and DLSPH professor with a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To grasp the revolutionary opportunities of new technologies we must create funding structures that bring together depth  breadth of knowledge  reward collaboration. Our 1st @UofT_dlsph interdisciplinary seed projects on emerging uses of AI/DataSci: https://t.co/R3tiEuuNHD https://t.co/CB3YTHefLX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fascinating piece on @CBCTheNational featuring @UofT_dlsph Assoc. Prof. Paul Bozek testing common masks while the reporter wears them  explaining the importance of fit, not just material. Kudos to DLSPH's Occupational  Environmental Health Division #UofT https://t.co/RC6bFbA8XP https://t.co/kXZ5QRicMz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: Re-imagining #Aging and Restoring Trust in #LTC. If you missed this great panel with @NathanStall, @LisaLevin1, @DrSami]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["In contrast to the private pharmaceutical manufacturers, Connaught emphasized basic research, combining the bench strength of research scientists along with a deep desire to address public health issues." @ihpmeuoft's  Les Boehm  @MarchildonGreg:   https://t.co/HGbdMU3mQb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks to all our fantastic panelists  speakers at the Boehm Lecture yesterday on Reimagining Aging  Restoring Trust: @NathanStall @LisaLevin1 @DrSamirSinha @DLDunc416 @DavidCGrabowski, @Dee_Lender Devora Greenspon @OARCnews   moderator @picardonhealth https://t.co/nHHaKZOvF2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UofT_dlsph's @cjrutty is cited here on the need for a publicly owned, end-to-end vaccine producer, much like we once had in Connaught Laboratories, which originated at U of T and played a major role eradicating polio, smallpox  diphtheria. https://t.co/Lxid0LdWnw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: Re-imaging aging and restoring trust in the wake of #COVID19. Join me Mar 22 @ 16:00ET for this great  Boehm Lectures p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great interview with @UofT_dlsph's @akwatukhenti on his work leading Toronto's Black Scientists' Task Force on Vaccine Equity -- and how to address the 'trust deficit' with communities that have faced discrimination.  https://t.co/KoeaS9EIv3 https://t.co/RS6Gq6WOhE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 3/3 We used open-source data to blueprint this for TO; any community in Ontario can develop the same plan. We offer so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 2/3 Naturally Occurring Retirement Communities  buildings that have many elderly residents, but arent LTC homes. W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVIDSciOntario: 1/3 To beat COVID, we urgently need to vaccinate elderly Ontarians living in high-risk zones  but may older people ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kudos to @UofT_dlsph's @armp71 and her students on the publication of their report for the Government of Canada, "Indigenous Peoples  COVID-19: What We Heard." Q+A with Prof. Mashford-Pringle: https://t.co/itl17kb4rO https://t.co/6GiVQQZKnT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofTMDprogram: Congratulations to our Vice Dean Patricia Houston on receiving the 2021 @cameacem Ian Hart Award for Distinguished Contr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drandrewb: this one of the coolest projects ever been a part of. we partnered with @SanctuaryTO in developing cartoons to help with vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: What should be done to keep medical supply chains open so that health systems have essential items like PPE? Join this @NatP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today at 3 pm I'll present the latest Ontario COVID-19 Science Advisory Table projections. As always, slides will be available on our website as we begin. https://t.co/oOvVHkUTOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teachers pls consider sharing: @UofT_dlsph researchers are studying COVID in Ontario teachers  other education workers. Participants will be tested for antibodies over time, vaccine impact, psychological impact of working during COVID  more.  Info: https://t.co/AxgwduA5CY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: DLSPH Profs. Jennifer Brooks, Anna Chiarelli and Meghan Walker are helping to lead game-changing research to better underst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DFisman @cjrutty may know....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My mom was a nurse and VP of a hospital in her 20s. She resigned on a matter of principle for the protection of her team. On #IWD2021 I'm thinking of you, Unnur Anna Kristjansson Brown, and the bravery of all the women who take a stand to make things better. https://t.co/e1LmwXewCC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NathanStall: Our new @COVIDSciOntario brief on the early impact of Ontarios #COVID19 vaccine rollout on #LTC residents and health care]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to participating in @UofT_dlsph's upcoming panel, part of the Boehm Lectures on Public Health and Healthcare, moderated by @picardonhealth  feat. @NathanStall @LisaLevin1 , @DrSamirSinha @DLDunc416   @DavidCGrabowski. https://t.co/fNjU1cbN6g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof. Peter Jni, scientific director of the Ontario COVID-19 Science Table, will be on @CBCOntarioToday at 12:30 today to take questions from the public about vaccine distribution. Tune in if you can! https://t.co/zQq2avS2fQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ed4socialchange: Please join us for a discussion about shaping Canada's global health future featuring @IlonaKickbusch and discussants]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: Researchers at the Dalla Lana School of Public Health are participating in a national study to estimate how many teachers a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The newest Ontario COVID-19 Science Table brief is out. https://t.co/EziUGHKcJw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OLTCAnews: Join OLTCA CEO @DLDunc416 at this months #BoehmLecture event: "Reimagining Aging and Restoring Trust in the Wake of COVID-1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnTory: Today at 2PM, @TAIBU_CHC is launching #BlackMentalHealthWeek with a panel discussion. https://t.co/zsVzQlcDL6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FYI I'm presenting the latest Ontario COVID-19 Science Advisory Table projections today at 3 pm. As always, the slides will be available on our website as we begin. https://t.co/oOvVHkUTOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm thrilled to share that we'll be announcing a very generous donation from @novonordisk today  in support of diabetes research and precision public health. More from @UofT_dlsph's  @LauraCRosella, @CalvinKe  Baiju Shah:   https://t.co/RJa0bMfUPg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm constantly amazed at how much @UofT_dlsph @ihpmeuoft  faculty, staff and students are doing right now amid the pandemic and all of its challenges! https://t.co/0UZadd7Jxg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: Calling recent DLSPH graduates! The Emerging Leader Award recognizes an alumnus of ten years or fewer who has shown excepti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Dont miss this important round table on aging  health moderated by @picardonhealth. This @UofT_dlsph event will focus on t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cathy was an incredible person. She knew the health system from every angle, and worked so hard to make it better. I love that we are going to train a new generation to follow in her footsteps. https://t.co/W9DbzCD1Z8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IHPMEGSU: ANOTHER  EVENT!? Get ready for  ROUND 2  of our Queer Fireside Chats. March 2nd @ 6 PM EST. Open to all @ihpmeuoft and @Uof]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also, @ihpmeuoft  Prof. Peter Jni, the Table's scientific director, will be taking questions from the public tomorrow from noon to 1 pm on @CBCOntarioToday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: Today, we honour the trailblazing women, professors and students, who work tirelessly to advance science. Happy Internation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today at 3 pm I'll present the Ontario COVID-19 Science Advisory Table's latest projections. As always, we'll post the slides on our website as we begin. https://t.co/oOvVHkUTOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Faculty, students  staff of @UofT_dlsph/@ihpmeuoft: Submit your notes, photos, personal  professional perspectives, journal entries, email drafts  other materials to our DLSPH Covid-19 Archive.  https://t.co/jZZr0FcL18]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WallisCJD: @SteiniBrown @VGupta_MD @UofT_dlsph @ihpmeuoft Many residents and fellows @UofTSurgery @UofTUrology have had great support @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #residentawarenessweek I'm thinking about the amazing medical residents who have studied at @UofT_dlsph. Like @VGupta_MD, who earned a PhD at @ihpmeuoft while a surgical resident! Now more than ever I'm so thankful for your dedication and sacrifice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMakokis: Yesterday we vaccinated our Elders. We started in ceremony, the Elders and matriarchs prayed giving thanks and for future ge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just published in @AnnalsofIM: @ihpmeuoft's Prof. Peter Jni analyzed 1918 Swiss records to learn how public health interventions (or lack thereof) in one canton affected subsequent waves of influenza. https://t.co/c9Otzs6drR https://t.co/WYjCHAU6bR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: To mark this years #BlackHistoryMonth, DLSPH leaders and Black scholars are sharing what this moment means to them. Here's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Commemorating Black History Month, research news, promotions and awardscheck out February edition of the IHPME newsletter:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MathTaskForce: Our first in a series of conversations that will bring the numbers to life; Prof V Kumar Murty in discussion with Dr Pet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_dlsph: If youre over the age of 65 and have a high waist circumference, you are more likely to test positive for COVID-19 regardl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very proud that @UofT_dlsph's @akwatukhenti, Upton Allen and Michael Finkelstein are helping to improve vaccine equity as part of the City of Toronto's new Black Scientists Task Force on Vaccine Equity. https://t.co/FH4UlV4ia7 https://t.co/ruFUfQlmna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wbiih_: our next lecture is one you do not want to miss! please join us as @NCFST founder and current Director of the #Indigenous Spiri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kudos to @UofT_dlsph's Tracy Kirkham  Paul Demers for this research. Another important contribution re. COVID from the Dalla Lana School of Public Health's Occupational and Environmental Health division. https://t.co/zMzBUJzGJF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our latest Ontario COVID-19 Science Advisory Table brief on lessons learned from Israel's vaccine rollout: https://t.co/NA460xvEud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Effective Jan. 1, 2021, #UofT research can publish in @PLOSMedicine  @PLOSBiology without having to pay article processing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing opportunity to learn from some very smart, seasoned journalists who produce in-depth public health journalism that lands in major publications. https://t.co/ITHI8Rlg4w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kudos @UofT_dlsph Prof. Jeffrey Brook, who is developing 'Good Score,' an app allowing Canadians to learn about air quality, greenery, walkability, and other factors contributing to the environmental health of their neighbourhoods. https://t.co/tRTg3s36gc https://t.co/yFXn5DQOaF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrJeffKwong: How will we know #COVID19 vaccines are safe? Weve assembled an all-star panel (@DrSarahWilson @DrBettinger @drkarinatop)]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>