<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination doesn't just protect you from Covid. It also protects the people around you. When you're fully vaccinated, you're much less likely to get infected AND much less likely to spread the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nurses can play an important role getting their patients and communities vaccinated. Here are resources to help you have informed, empathetic, and respectful conversations about Covid vaccines: https://t.co/Sb6pkzofDD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the US, lack of convenient access is still a larger barrier than reluctance to get vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The risks of Covid infection are clearwhen you get infected, the virus replicates all over your body and could cause long-term health problems, even for people not sick enough to be hospitalized. The vaccine teaches your body to fight the virus, then disappears.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most adults in the US have been vaccinated and more and more people are choosing to get vaccinated every day. We can reach the unreached with vaccines and crush the Covid curve by listening and enlisting the messages and messengers that are most effective. https://t.co/TXxqht9Fet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The "natural immunity" you gain after recovering from a Covid infection is good, but vaccination is super-human. After getting a vaccine, your antibodies are MUCH higher, reducing the risk you'll catch or spread the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The end of the pandemic isn't near. Global cooperation is essential if we are to win our continuing war against Covid. https://t.co/3KCR1O0fPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In places around the world facing explosive Covid spread, vaccines won't crush the curve in the short-term. Masks, distancing, limiting travel, and improving ventilation are the only ways to drive cases down in coming weeks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It will take time to expand global vaccine productionwe must start now. India, South Korea, Singapore, Brazil and other countries in Latin America, South Africa, Senegal, and Rwanda all have the potential to increase mRNA manufacturing capacity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In DRC, yet another Ebola outbreak has been contained. https://t.co/7MNQRo5zkS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That means:  1. Protect health care and health care workers 2. Mask up 3. Maintain distancing to avoid superspreading 4. Continue essential services, including school 5. Vaccinate, especially health care workers and older people 6. Learn and adapt.  https://t.co/3KCR1O0fPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pandemic is more severe than ever and, fueled by variants, is an ongoing and increasing risk globally. But effective action can save more than a million lives in the coming year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid is here to stay, but we can reduce its impact by reaching the unreached with vaccinesespecially those most at risk of severe illness and death. https://t.co/8mmc97kFCS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RanBalicer: Puzzling  How come so few outbreaks in Israeli schools, if kids &lt;16 yrs unvaccinated?  7 potential hypotheses:  1. Masks i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heart attacks and strokes are so common that they seem a regular part of modern life. But it doesnt have to be that way. Cardiovascular disease is largely preventable through simple, inexpensive, but underused actions. https://t.co/FFQsI7mJbk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The past couple of decades have made clear that it's a mistake to try to predict the next pandemic. We didn't know SARS or MERS would hit us, or Ebola would spread in West Africa, or that a novel coronavirus would cause a pandemic. The world must be ready for any disease threat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When yellow fever threatened major Brazilian cities, government officials used a combination of risk assessment and planning and sophisticated laboratory surveillance to contain the outbreak. Read more: https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L https://t.co/zMu2T2INNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what a future with virus tamed by vaccines can look like. Thats why its crucial we scale up manufacturing. https://t.co/WfE60C4h4G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Although were closer than ever to resuming life as usual in the United States, globally, the end of the pandemic is horrifyingly far away. https://t.co/NA2upvQskE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tobacco continues to kill more than half a million people in the US every year. Unlike infectious disease threats, the vector that spreads tobacco is a business  the tobacco industry, which is public health enemy #1. https://t.co/4XuxRCG4IF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid killed 1.8 million people in 2020. At the current rate, it could kill even more people in 2021. But this isn't inevitable. We've learned a lot about the virus and how to limit its impact--we CAN control Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't be blinded by the light at the end of the pandemic tunnel.  Six steps we must take to save a million lives in the coming year:  https://t.co/lDB5fHp1SI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the new variants, SARS-CoV-2 is much more transmissible, and more deadly. Maybe we should start calling it COVID-21.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you're fully vaccinated, your risk of Covid infection from ANY activity is much lower than if you're unvaccinated. Get vaccinated and you can do more, more safely.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An anthrax outbreak in Kenya was brought under control in just over a month thanks to a community-based surveillance system and a trained @KenyaRedCross volunteer who knew exactly what to do. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L https://t.co/WO5iYgKrRn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't skip the second dose of Pfizer or Moderna if you've already gotten your first dose. Without the second dose, your vaccine-induced protection isn't as strong or long-lasting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[mRNA vaccines are our best hope for an end to the pandemic  our insurance policy against variants, the possible need for boosters, and production delays with other vaccines  but current capacity is nowhere near the need.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The dangerous B117 variant now accounts for more than half of new cases in the US. Most adults have been fully vaccinated, but those who remain unvaccinated face the risk of infection with a deadlier virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thailand and Costa Rica are showing the world the way forward for effective primary care. I was honored to lead a @CFR_org roundtable with health leaders from these two countries. Watch: https://t.co/di4bvPY4IQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: "As the United States and the world continue to struggle in the second year of the Covid-19 pandemic, one truth has emerged -- it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even if you've already had Covid, getting vaccinated reinforces the protection your immune system has built and reduces the risk you'll get reinfected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Epidemics don't have to happen. Our new report highlights successes controlling infectious disease. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Ebola began to spread in Lagos, Nigeria's most densely populated city, quick action contained the outbreak and prevented what could have been a devastating epidemic. https://t.co/1JLrRdEeOr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you've gotten one dose of the Pfizer or Moderna vaccine, make sure you get the second doseit greatly reinforces the protection your immune system started building after the first shot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important article by @DLeonhardt  How Politics Saves Lives https://t.co/sVkEPvAYPv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The reason there's not enough oxygen is that there are too many cases. Masks, distancing, limiting travel, improving ventilation are the only ways to drive cases down in coming weeks in places w exponential spread. These countries and others show it can be done, even w variants. https://t.co/GjLcNxOY4P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination works best when we do it together. When you're vaccinated and the people around you are too, everyone is safer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid has shown us the costs of failure, but a safer and healthier future is possible. 21/end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its possible to beat infectious diseases. These stories of success give me hope. If we work together across borders to fight Covid and invest in preparedness, we can save millions of lives. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L 20/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For each of these six, we need a focused, well-managed, accountable approach. We MUST do better protecting health care and health care workers. Doing so will save lives from Covid and from diseases that become deadlier when care is disrupted. https://t.co/uQiioTpa1z 19/ https://t.co/ZAQP8taDAd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Six steps we must take now to deal with explosive spread globally. 1. Protect health care  healthcare workers 2. Mask up 3. Distance and avoid superspreading 4. Continue essential services, including schooling 5. Vaccinate, especially HCW and older people 6. Learn and adapt 18/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Variants remain the biggest wild card, but weve learned a lot about the virus and how to limit its impact. Protection measures work. 17/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Globally, there were 1.8 million deaths reported from Covid in 2020. At the current rate, there will be even more deaths in 2021. But this isnt inevitable; pandemics arent natural disasters. We can control Covid. Effective action can save at least a million lives this year. 16/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the 1918 pandemic, in many places, the second wave was deadlier than the first. Im concerned were at the most dangerous phase of the pandemic yet. Covid is deadlier, more transmissible, in more places, circulating at higher levels, and theres more human fatigue. 15/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Variants, wow! Check out the stunning march of B117 across the US. Even with more than half of our adult population fully vaccinated, we still face risk of outbreaks, and unvaccinated people are facing more danger than ever. 14/ https://t.co/8VXnkwPgUD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Transferring technology and stepping up production globally is the most important step the Biden administration can take to help end the pandemic. US taxpayers funded the Moderna vaccine. Not sharing this technology puts us at risk if even more dangerous variants emerge. 13/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Transferring mRNA technology is essential. The technology is outlined in this fascinating @NYTimes piece. The pandemic is the worlds most important problem. We should act accordingly. https://t.co/NYx5FwZlBo 12/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India, South Korea, Singapore, Brazil and other countries in Latin America, South Africa, Senegal, Rwanda all have potential to establish vaccine manufacturing capacity and could become providers of vaccines globally. CureVax might be another resource. 11/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We cant bet lives and global recovery on uncertain vaccines and production. Regional mRNA manufacturing hubs are crucial to provide the best vaccines globally ASAP. Doing so will take longer than we wish, which is why we must start right now. https://t.co/SKhoM4Gvr2 10/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, rosy estimates show there'll be enough vaccines in 2021, but companies missed 2020 production projections by 96%  overall production is at only 1/4 of projection for 2021. Variants, boosters, safety signals, production delays all very real risks. https://t.co/3SOItTec6P 9/ https://t.co/FmdmNae429]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[mRNA vaccines are also quicker to scale up, and theyre likely safer and more effective. Handling is getting easier, and cold chain problems can be addressed. Theyre our best hope for an end to the global pandemic. But current capacity is nowhere near the global need. 8/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All types of vaccines that are proven to be effective need to be scaled up as rapidly as possible. Novavax, JJ, AstraZeneca and others are all important, but mRNA vaccines are the most promising. They are our insurance policy against variants, boosters, and production delays. 7/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our current vaccine infrastructure cant be relied on to meet the needs of the world. Countries with excess supply can make a dent, but vaccine production needs a step-function increase. Until much more vaccine is available, masks, distancing, less travel are all essential. 6/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It takes weeks to months to roll out vaccines and weeks for protection to kick in. Vaccines dont help people already infected with Covid and probably dont help much after exposure. To stop spread now, we need to mask, distance, reduce travel, and prevent superspreading. 5/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even in the best of circumstances, vaccines take months to control the virus. And were in far from the best of circumstances. Globally, vaccines would not crush the curve in the short-term even if there were enough of themwhich there arent. 4/ https://t.co/NilN0JJpVW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dazzling scientific progress resulted in Covid vaccines that are more effective than many experts dared to hope. But although Israel, the UK, and, soon, the US will have a new reality with the virus largely tamed by vaccines, global vaccination lags badly. 3/ https://t.co/xnvw0WbGNL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indias surge is a reminder that the virus is learning about and adapting to us faster than we're learning and adapting to it. Covid, fueled by variants, is an ongoing  increasing risk. The pandemic is more severe than evermore transmissible, more deadly, more human fatigue. 2/ https://t.co/yisZkQ0d3Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Globally, the end of the pandemic isn't near.   More than a million lives depend on improving our response quickly.   Dont be blinded by the light at the end of the tunnel. There isn't enough vaccine and the virus is gathering strength  speed. Global cooperation is crucial. 1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perspective: Cases are decreasing in the US, but if you're not vaccinated, because most spread is of variants, you risk infection with strains of the virus that are more likely to make you very sick or kill you than ever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Team-based care is better care. Better quality. Better access. Better efficiency. Better use of skills. Better. https://t.co/Vkvy7EHaZn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Viruses move at lightning speed. The faster we confront them when they emerge, the more effective we'll be in stopping them.   Preparedness and swift action are key, as these stories show. #PreventEpidemics https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In most US counties, the risk of exposure to Covid is high, very high, or extremely high. See how hard it's raining Covid in your community. https://t.co/IA19TenfUh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctors and other health professionals have a major role to play in getting people vaccinated. Please talk with your patients and community about the remarkable safety and effectiveness of Covid vaccines. https://t.co/PNY2ieA6gB https://t.co/fchQyHiBiF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Recovering from the pandemic and improving health means addressing the roots of failure in our health system. https://t.co/bSCCmWpHZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the US, we pay far more for health care than other high-income countriesfor worse health. https://t.co/36KC6CL1qn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AprilHunter Good question! What we call "natural immunity" after infection is good but vaccination is super-human: antibodies MUCH higher after vaccine. Some people prefer to JJ post-Covid since it's 1 dose. If data confirms, people with prior Covid MAY need just 1 dose of an mRNA vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Protection from mRNA vaccines doesn't start to kick in until two weeks after your first dose, and it's not at its peak until two weeks after your second dose. Don't let your guard down too early.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're all familiar with the story of Covid, but every year there are many near missesinfectious disease outbreaks that were stopped. Our report spotlights the epidemics that didn't happen because of great work of frontline staff around the world. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Concerned about negative effects a Covid vaccine could have on your body? It's NOTHING compared with what the virus can do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines have saved hundreds of millions of lives from deadly diseases. #WorldImmunizationWeek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really big news: Banning menthol cigarettes and flavored cigars is a historic move that, when implemented, will prevent tobacco-caused cancer, heart attacks, strokes, and so much more suffering. https://t.co/VRgcUetE4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomBollyky: .@ThinkGlobalHlth has been nominated for @TheWebbyAwards!   I can't imagine a better compliment for us than being recognize]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCGlobal: Even as the world continues to fight #COVID19, we must better prepare for future major health threats. The stories in this n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @betswrites: How about the epidemics that didnt happen? A new report this week by @ResolveTSL describes the public health preparedness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid didn't have to be this bad. If we learn from outbreaks that were successfully contained, we can prevent the next pandemic. https://t.co/nnVl51G7fS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When it comes to infectious diseases such as Covid, we need to think outside of our borders. The key is to find new disease threats as soon as they emerge and stop outbreaks from becoming epidemicsand epidemics from becoming pandemics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eager to see FDA action on menthol cigarettes and cigars today. Potentially a huge win for the health of our children. We can end the epidemic of tobacco-caused cancer, heart attacks, strokes, and so much more suffering. Let's make tobacco history.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dr2NisreenAlwan: Indias problem is not just Indias problem, just like Chinas problem in late 2019 needed to urgently concern the who]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A fascinating glimpse into the production of mRNA vaccinesand an outline of the technology transfer process needed to expand global manufacturing and end the pandemic. https://t.co/JQUIMQChVD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We don't hear very often about the epidemics that DIDN'T happen, but they hold important lessons. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L https://t.co/4j6TUiD0hB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: The evidence for benefit was already overwhelming and it just keeps getting better https://t.co/OjcEZk5KDS @CDCMMWR https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination drastically reduces the risk of severe illness from Covid. Now the challenge is to reach the unreachedespecially people over 65 and ages 50-64. https://t.co/lhTO0cxEPG https://t.co/SY3cTpBvuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fully vaccinated adults 65 and older were 94% less likely to be hospitalized with Covid in a new CDC study. The Pfizer and Moderna vaccines are remarkably safe and astonishingly effective.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sharing vaccines and know-how with other countries including hands-on technology transfer will be essential to end the pandemic. Encouraging message from @POTUS. https://t.co/2ggGp4VaY6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To improve vaccine equity in the US, we need to better understand vaccinations by race, sex, and age. What gets measured can get managed. https://t.co/BOhws8StUQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've advocated for this for more than 15 years. It NEVER made sense that the one opiate medication that's less addictive and less likely to kill you than heroin was the only one with these restrictions and requirements. Kudos for an important step forward! https://t.co/AQRHtq8aeO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GREAT step forward by @POTUS making #Buprenorphine more readily available and (almost) eliminating irrational requirement for training. There are no quick fixes for our opiate epidemic, but this move will save lives. We must greatly improve our care of both pain and addiction.1/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What lessons has the Covid pandemic taught us for future global health crises? Join my discussion at #SedonaForum21 this morning. https://t.co/V4TQico9Vn https://t.co/9udHJ9lr99]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ugandas officials quickly activated the countrys health emergency response system when Ebola erupted along the busy border with DRC. The result? Only four cases emerged in Ugandaan epidemic that didnt happen. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L https://t.co/6LF1SDZB6a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Covid first hit, many people thought, "It's not going to come here." The world can't afford to be caught off guard again. If we invest in preparedness, we can prevent the next pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RogerMarshallMD: Last year, the entire world was forced to face the COVID-19 pandemic head on. And now, we  the American people  have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @florian_krammer: It is very important for people to get their 2nd shot of vaccine (except for JJ, or if you had confirmed COVID-19 bef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We need to be better prepared when the next major health threat emerges. Tomorrow, I'm joining @theglobalfight to talk about how we can strengthen global health security. #FriendsHealthChat https://t.co/urLzlOdnDi https://t.co/Wb3csZXsda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you get infected with Covid, the virus makes billions of copies and spreads all over your body. When you get vaccinated, the vaccine teaches your immune system how to recognize and kill the virus quickly, then disappears.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Preparedness works. The next pandemic threat is inevitable, but the next pandemic isnt. https://t.co/Hsbc4aFW9K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As horrific as Covid is now, a future pandemic could be even worse. It's inevitable that there will be future disease threats, but it's not inevitable that they will become pandemics. We can stop them. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L https://t.co/mKeEnohzVV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Correct @FrankLuntz! https://t.co/qFRBYT4u0h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In our new report, we tell the story of countries that successfully beat infectious disease outbreaks before they spread. https://t.co/2wtmyJaa6L https://t.co/4j6TUiD0hB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On average, we identify one new deadly organism every year. When the next global health threat emerges, we must be prepared for it so we dont repeat the story of Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tune in this afternoon as @AmandaMcClella2, @agogo_immanuel, and I share what the world must do to make sure the story of Covid doesn't repeat itself. #AspenIdeasHealth https://t.co/jVg66IMp3h https://t.co/T7tFeGu5Rv]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>