<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[POOP WALL: Man builds "compost fence" after a dispute with his neighbor. https://t.co/W3yhHio6Lr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Railbird Festival is back! Organizers say the festival is scheduled for Aug. 28 and 29 on the Grounds at Keeneland along with the Kentucky Bourbon and Culinary Experiences. Follow this link for ticket information ---&gt; https://t.co/9Z05RWQt9Z https://t.co/6GszQxdGb9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York college professor Ari Nagel has fathered more than 70 children and has more on the way. https://t.co/mccB7bc8C0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SOUTHERN STORMS: Parts of the south saw tornadoes, flooding and strong winds. https://t.co/SaqZvtJeJd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHAT DO YOU THINK? Drivers were given the chance to ask questions about changes to a winding two-lane stretch of Shelbyville Road. https://t.co/fuq2EVptVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Portland Christian School announces plans for $2M expansion:https://t.co/PbsyyqzTVS https://t.co/LVWAY0tMtF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indiana man sentenced 28 years in prison after child solicitation conviction: https://t.co/R0XTszbvXZ https://t.co/yn0uESXqZn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[City leaders say clerical error to blame for $1 million gap in Jeffersonville's 2021 budget: https://t.co/Jbg9Z3SoR1 https://t.co/uAzB1odEck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisville leaders want LMPD to testify about Derby week decision to barricade west end Kroger: https://t.co/bfsVqDPTKB | @ChadKMills https://t.co/rQ40qEBhRG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@WDRBNewsat 11 begins now! Can't make it to a TV? Watch live here: https://t.co/Ukl49rl7WQ https://t.co/Ii3diiZ155]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@LouisvilleZoo debuts new accessible playground: https://t.co/7sB25KBW1f https://t.co/IDKXGoLRIO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Play ball! @LouisvilleBats step up to the plate for the first time in 610 days: https://t.co/8fwS6zcyJ8 | @JSchipperWDRB #MiLBOpeningDay https://t.co/90MgeB7WFq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nelson County High School student killed in head-on crash: https://t.co/G70cm97eSc https://t.co/rj670kbXOK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Silver Alert canceled for missing 40-year-old Indiana woman: https://t.co/9kV28FW6X9 https://t.co/gxi1EirJms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@WDRBNewsat 10 begins now! Can't make it to a TV? Watch live here: https://t.co/Ukl49rl7WQ https://t.co/qxQyOItgyk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ericcrawford: THE BATS ARE BACK | Louisville Slugger Field played host to an opening night for the first time since 2019. Columbus pick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Mike Woodson kept Trayce Jackson-Davis at IU; Luke Murray's new job; UK chatter: https://t.co/CmHgkMQuXB | @rickbozich https://t.co/d6R98eIq1z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@ULFieldHockeyfinishing an extra long year in its first Final Four: https://t.co/W2y1iFFwk8 | @TomLaneWDRB https://t.co/rwgHpRl8TY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcWeinbergWX: A Severe Thunderstorm Warning for has been issued for Marion, Larue, Nelson Co. until 5/04 9:45PM EDT. Tune to WDRB or]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisville man found shot to death in California neighborhood home identified: https://t.co/e95pql2qG6 https://t.co/lYSeHuY0tJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@uoflis researching the long-term effects of COVID-19 with volunteer participants: https://t.co/lAOo7X37lX https://t.co/3Y34J9smoe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wine that went to space for sale with $1 million price tag https://t.co/PlXdL1DI5j https://t.co/ZogUUl4o8m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@BuffaloTraceadded 10 new warehouses as part of a $1.2 billion plan: https://t.co/h9pvF1DxvI https://t.co/FsW10DW8EC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A judge upheld the denial of a zoning change for the controversial Prospect Cove development: https://t.co/xUsPgHAMe3 | @christopherotts https://t.co/ud93jfgeWi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A tornado warning has been issued for Washington and Marion counties. Tune in for severe weather coverage: https://t.co/MA0SYnr4jB https://t.co/QM4NyMRads]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcWeinbergWX: A Tornado Warning for has been issued for Washington, Marion Co. until 5/04 8:45PM EDT. Seek shelter immediately! Tune]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@insomniacookiesplans to open its second Louisville location in the Highlands: https://t.co/GdIi1CB86W https://t.co/u9R3w8tkTX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indiana is implementing new system and requirements for youth employment: https://t.co/Y2yh1PcXCb https://t.co/OjHfo5ipwf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@RepJohnYarmuthbacked @JoeBiden's infrastructure proposal, calling the GOP plan an "abdication' of responsibility": https://t.co/Bnt0vt7Jm1 https://t.co/GbWI6IpGhF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chauvin's lawyer seeks new trial, impeachment of verdict: https://t.co/hUJJ4a8uwu https://t.co/W4MvYofXaF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kentucky health departments are working to close the gap in lesser-vaccinated counties: https://t.co/gqbMLVLnVg | @DarbyBeane https://t.co/SN55iwp5lJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MAY THE FOURTH BE WITH YOU! @FallonGlick and @chrissutter celebrated #NationalStarWarsDay at the end of our 6 p.m. newscast, and they had a little help from one of our camera operators, Big Mike, @BMisSasquatch! Rate his Wookie impression on a scale of 1-10 Chewbaccas.  https://t.co/USMXIHRLR0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcWeinbergWX: Rain and storms continue tonight. Updating the risk of strong storms in my video on the  WDRB Weather App... https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ethan the Dog was named a "Compassion Ambassador" for inspiring and uplifting others: https://t.co/Fa2Ylv55Bz https://t.co/PoI9XTBdWe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeffersonville Police searching for woman who went missing after hospital release in March: https://t.co/3L4cqS4M28 https://t.co/r1893Em8hV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JCPS teacher fired months after indictment on sex crimes allegedly involving 13-year-old student: https://t.co/bdWVnuCG6v https://t.co/QfTrQkqhKa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A string of break-ins have plagued Louisville's La Chandeleur restaurant: https://t.co/z0JQDlZhHp | @DaltonTVNews https://t.co/VkPOzkFpob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A capacity crowd of nearly 5,000 tonight at @LouisvilleBats game (per Covid-19 guidelines).   @JSchipperWDRB will take you to season opener on @WDRBNews at 10. https://t.co/eEDMfoMV4h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A former Bardstown day care worker was arrested today on a child abuse charge: https://t.co/jKz0TFBDxv https://t.co/B8KqTrK92G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow @KevinWheatleyKY for updates from tonight's @JCPSKY Board of Education meeting. https://t.co/vAXvAk37o5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Western Kentucky University proposing tuition hike https://t.co/QGgQwmQa14   @wku https://t.co/ZiQlz3DFCu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JSchipperWDRB: Fans continuing to come in... $2 beers help that. @LouisvilleBats @WDRBNews #OpeningDay https://t.co/JsyLOZ4BWa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Whistle Stop restaurant in Glendale reopened today under new ownership: https://t.co/A7ObrhmyEj https://t.co/ZJXbR1UAgS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indiana State Fair returning after 2020 pandemic cancelation https://t.co/alGtxZQEDX | @IndyStateFair https://t.co/OivowCRclI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisville health officials are reporting a spike in COVID-19 cases: https://t.co/uCmYN4FN0J https://t.co/NaWcZA8VHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@Norton_Healthis preparing to open a brand new $15 million neuroscience facility: https://t.co/iUIaFt5oP3 | @KatrinaWDRB https://t.co/aQQObzRguW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kentuckians hesitant to get the COVID-19 vaccine are encouraged to speak to their local doctors, @healthykysays: https://t.co/O1VqRNlCTz https://t.co/8iiydzj1xL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JSchipperWDRB: HAPPENING NOW: @LouisvilleBats fans arrive at Slugger Field for the season opener.    @sluggernation #LouisvilleBats @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @KentuckyDerbyprovided a boost as the tourism industry tries to regain momentum: https://t.co/bX0qsFe4lz | @LASmithReports https://t.co/BujKxWrP1H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Silver Alert was declared for a missing 40-year-old Indiana woman believed to be in "extreme danger": https://t.co/1JTesfpGYg https://t.co/HdiwXRSTYH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BryceJonesWx: STORMS TONIGHT: Another chance for strong to severe storms is possible for this evening and overnight. What impacts you c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mmarshallWDRB: 65 at 131 in Clarksville. https://t.co/4wcX2te4mH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Louisville family was robbed while they were in the hospital recovering from a head-on crash: https://t.co/C5HBm02b6d | @LRatterman_WDRB https://t.co/qcCvrqhNQJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Overpass collapse on Mexico City metro kills at least 24 https://t.co/J7LOQsJGn7 https://t.co/8xogjmTrcm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MISSING. https://t.co/Onqy4Mj1Mf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Bardstown day care worker arrested on child abuse charge https://t.co/jKz0TFBDxv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two people are dead and two others are in critical condition following a crash early this morning near Breckenridge Lane and Nachand Lane: https://t.co/XwsFtYM57D https://t.co/8hg2iV15ld]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A suspect was arrested today after a vehicle was stolen from a Louisville Speedway with a 5-year-old still inside: https://t.co/IvfVUaKtcp | @TravisRagsdale https://t.co/NVA4rVfMtB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man dies after rear-ending garbage truck on Fern Valley Road, LMPD says: https://t.co/oZX6EPmhWl https://t.co/zgkirAth9P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ethan the Dog named 'Compassion Ambassador' for inspiring, uplifting others https://t.co/Fa2Ylv55Bz https://t.co/axGVtgSOom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VIDEO | Bob Ross toys sent for a test ride on the Orion Kings Island  https://t.co/I0hBOQwsMo  @KingsIslandPR#kingsisland https://t.co/pJIBvBXAAb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaltonTVNews: UPDATE: The employee in the video has been arrested and booked in the Nelson County Jail.  @BardstownPD charged Heather J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[STORMS TONIGHT: Another chance for strong to severe storms is possible for this evening and overnight. What impacts you can expect on our blog..https://t.co/OC8Pdc0qHH https://t.co/ABvy66oKWG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Louisville man was arrested and charged in connection with the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol: https://t.co/KybjhzGP8h https://t.co/EskWr56Ihh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US to reallocate COVID shots to states with greater interest https://t.co/4BTh8pZZye https://t.co/q8UY2q5AdY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisville family robbed while they were in the hospital recovering from head-on crash https://t.co/C5HBm02b6d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WELCOME TO the WDRB News YouTube page where you'll find news videos about Louisville and the surrounding area - everything from unemployment to Kentucky bourbon. Plus some of your favorite moments from WDRB in the morning. Click here to subscribe.   https://t.co/EymkKXq4CL https://t.co/nn07zA9I6d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: LMPD says the girl was found safe in the car at the Meijer on Preston Highway. Still looking for the suspect. This story will be updated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: LMPD says the girl was found safe in the car at the Meijer on Preston Highway. Still looking for the suspect. This story will be updated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LMPD NEWS BRIEFING about missing 5-year-old in a stolen car.  https://t.co/eclAv2B3VX via @FacebookWatch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BOIL WATER ADVISORY in Scottsburg, Indiana.  Crews are repairing a 20 main line.  Once repairs are completed, customers will be on a boil water advisory until further notice.  The area affected will include all customer south of Hwy 56 in Scottsburg. https://t.co/oCa1U82Dck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IMS: When you show up to the track in May with your whole squad...  Tag your Month of May squad below!   #ThisIsMay | #MayThe4thBeWithY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kate_Springer: Working from home with this wild girl today. Bless people who do this every day  https://t.co/81PzCTMhKf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Silver Alert declared for missing 40-year-old Indiana woman believed to be in 'extreme danger.' https://t.co/1JTesfpGYg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MISSING CHILD!  Police searching for vehicle stolen from Louisville Speedway on Fegenbush Lane with 5-year-old inside just after 9 a.m. https://t.co/O88nQ1uz5h https://t.co/CwmzfD3gka]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PLAY BALL: The Louisville Bats open its season tonight with many new stadium renovations.  https://t.co/sEAQpHbRO7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LRatterman_WDRB: Can confirm: its raining. A lot. @JudeRedfield https://t.co/rqLFlYUUM6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mother cherishes memory of Louisville woman killed at Derby party: 'I didn't get to say goodbye' https://t.co/lrgdU79scj | @gcorsey https://t.co/QZ8JHI3MVF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HAPPY TEACHER APPRECIATION DAY! Comment below the name of your favorite teacher. https://t.co/ceRQhOjnoU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UofL Health's new text alert service provides up-to-date wait times for ER locations: https://t.co/H8pobf2gxF https://t.co/9RD0PyyXb4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MAY THE 4TH BE WITH YOU! Happy Star Wars day to all galaxies even the ones far, far away. https://t.co/NAqGqBxCj2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JudeRedfield: *STORM UPDATE* https://t.co/mBxTMHUK6Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two people were killed and two others are in critical condition following an early morning crash. https://t.co/JbXMHZHwh8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[STUCK:  A toddler got stuck in an antique wooden barrel during a visit with his grandparents. https://t.co/zqeuynbKuk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most schools are back in session, but COVID-19 restrictions are causing some limitations. So some Jefferson County Public School teachers and students are finding creative ways to get in tune: https://t.co/8pUsqclDRC https://t.co/AVCE2CjcYF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PROSECUTORS: Three men drove around the Hollywood area in late February, on the prowl for expensive French bulldogs to steal. https://t.co/fYEPa4DLeh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its just good to be out in the city again, be around people. https://t.co/FCOuFZLxkO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY: An elevated section of the Mexico City metro collapsed and sent a subway car plunging toward a busy boulevard late Monday, killing at least 20 people and injuring about 70, city officials said. https://t.co/gEsLvpgptL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden quadruples Trump refugee cap after delay backlash: https://t.co/63KFQ6WJD1 https://t.co/K2nRiBkV6M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indiana University to host in-person graduation ceremonies starting Friday: https://t.co/qAapWfIHc7 https://t.co/n9jDRmLRc6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mother cherishes memory of Louisville woman killed at Derby party: 'I didn't get to say goodbye' https://t.co/lrgdU79scj | @gcorsey https://t.co/pguABigR8d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lincoln Trail District Health Department hosting vaccine clinics for vulnerable populations: https://t.co/uzjO6hSfL4 | @SaraSideryWDRB https://t.co/zgWBaEhecm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisville will resume booting cars with outstanding parking citations this summer: https://t.co/VSe16MS6on https://t.co/puHNCEuPsN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kentucky community ready to welcome manufacturer and 700 jobs: https://t.co/EpfLU75HHL | @ChadKMills https://t.co/1YjH165a1A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scott County leaders to decide future of needle exchange program: https://t.co/iVTBOYx74S | @JSchipperWDRB https://t.co/Gqg8xinIOO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@WDRBNewsat 11 begins now! Can't make it to a TV? Watch live here: https://t.co/Ukl49rl7WQ https://t.co/fYbqge0cFn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New playground set to open this fall in Elizabethtown: https://t.co/UGVdkuiJrI https://t.co/2LkSBMyAKz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indiana parents can now apply for pre-K, child care assistance: https://t.co/8aHyZPIj6O https://t.co/HWlRNl5vra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spraygrounds reopen for summer season @TheParklandsof Floyds Fork: https://t.co/63XarZqI8r https://t.co/Bc5zPsBut4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisville residents have until June 30 to apply for low-income utilities assistance: https://t.co/LoILd84glN https://t.co/QtWhSiL3qZ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>