<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[We have just published our academia collaboration action plan that sets out how EMA intends to create closer ties with academics and researchers in the next two and a half years.   The action plan  https://t.co/TJr1hgdzha https://t.co/Ec3sQcr71C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[!! EMA human medicines committee (#CHMP) has started a rolling review of #COVID19vaccine (Vero Cell) Inactivated, developed by Sinovac Life Sciences Co., Ltd.  Link to the announcement https://t.co/DK7qcNGLbu https://t.co/fsq6TNVzjF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA human medicine committee (#CHMP) is evaluating the use of the #COVID19vaccine Comirnaty (currently for ages 16+) in young people aged 12 to 15.  The review is currently ongoing: https://t.co/jy0GVhTnX7  #medicine #COVID19 #vaccine https://t.co/V16mPlmm0m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Executive Director Emer Cooke received her #COVID19 vaccine today.   By expediting the development and approval of safe and effective treatments and vaccines, EMA is contributing to global efforts to save lives during the pandemic.   #SafeVaccines https://t.co/J3tg3omBmZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ECDC_EU: How many Europeans have been vaccinated against #COVID19 so far? How does it look in the specific age groups?  Find all the in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA started evaluating Olumiant (baricitinib) in #COVID19 patients from 10 years of age who require supplemental oxygen https://t.co/sIMh9m7Qzv  #medicine #pharmaceutical https://t.co/k5H4tw7TVT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EU_Health: @ECDC_EU @TwitterGov @EMA_News And in closing, let's share the simple message that #VaccinesWork   The pandemic may have foc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ECDC_EU: @EU_Health @TwitterGov @EMA_News We also set up the "#COVID19 Vaccine Tracker", an interactive dashboard that allows to monito]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EU_Health: @TwitterGov @ECDC_EU @EMA_News It can be difficult to assess the accuracy of information on COVID-19. Checking your sources]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ECDC_EU: @EMA_News @TwitterGov @EU_Health Remember this is a new virus. We need more information on how efficient the vaccines are in r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TwitterGov @EU_Health @ECDC_EU It's difficult to say for the moment as more data is needed, but we are monitoring this very carefully.  We have asked researchers and vaccine manufacturers to gather more information and submit it to us for assessment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EU_Health @TwitterGov @ECDC_EU The safety of #COVID19vaccines is stronger with everybody's participation! Please report any suspected side effect to your doctor, national authority in your country or the vaccine manufacturer  https://t.co/vJaSpm1GMq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EU_Health @TwitterGov @ECDC_EU Most side effects are identified before a vaccine is licensed. Some side effects are so rare, they may only show up once millions of people have received the vaccine. The EU's safety monitoring system is set up to rapidly detect and deal with possible safety concerns.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TwitterGov @EU_Health @ECDC_EU All vaccines are rigorously tested for quality, safety and efficacy in large clinical trials with tens of thousands of participants before they can be used in the EU.  After authorisation, we closely monitor, review evidence and take quick action, when needed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TwitterGov: Hi @EU_Health, @EMA_News, and @ECDC_EU   It's #WorldImmunizationWeek what better time to talk about COVID-19 vaccines?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow our conversation with @TwitterGov, @EU_Health and @ECDC_EU on #COVID19vaccines today at 3:30 PM (CEST)!  #VaccinesWork  #EuropeanImmunizationWeek #WorldImmunizationWeek https://t.co/lUOmJjEzCR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EUnetHTA: The last EMA-EUnetHTA Bilateral Meeting under Joint Action 3 was held today, concluding collaboration that began with the fir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For over 200 years, vaccines have saved millions of lives from deadly infectious diseases.  Vaccines also allow people to come together without the fear of getting ill, this improves the quality of life and their wellbeing.   Find out how #VaccinesWork :https://t.co/1lly7d5rrp https://t.co/4NAl8OPDnq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we dive deeply into #EuropeanImmunizationWeek, we must remember that #vaccineswork. Vaccination is our way towards ending the #COVID19 pandemic and saving lives    Visit EMAs website to get reliable information on #COVID19vaccines: https://t.co/bY95nHrSPu https://t.co/BddyxcZCsZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EU_Health: Today, our lives are defined by COVID-19  What does this mean for our mental health  for those providing care?  Join us on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA and @ECDC_EU today kicked off a new initiative aimed at strengthening post-marketing monitoring of the safety, effectiveness and impact of #COVID19 vaccines in the EU/EEA. Read more: https://t.co/bSL8VHRkLL https://t.co/O5nl6mPEGs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to all #healthcare professionals involved in EMA activities in 2020.   See highlights of involvement https://t.co/pdBZOd6mUD  Read more on how healthcare professionals are involved in #regulation of #medicines  https://t.co/PS90xKOPQq https://t.co/k9g4pX9tcH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to all #patients involved in EMA activities during 2020.   See highlights of involvement https://t.co/2hLBgN4Fhs   Did you know that patients participate in #regulation of #medicines Read more here  https://t.co/u265oFLrv1 https://t.co/ZEyVnrviNV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EU_Commission: European Immunization Week is here.  As vaccinations against #COVID19 are taking place, vaccine production has also been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EU_Health: #Covid19 focused our attention on vaccination  But for more than 200 years vaccines have protected billions of people from d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you miss the press briefing on further assessment of data on Vaxzevria, the #COVID19vaccine from AstraZeneca? You can watch it on EMA's YouTube channel: https://t.co/GfovqACcEP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMAs human medicines committee (#CHMP) recommends 8 #medicines for approval at its April 2021. https://t.co/FjJUjU9EM8 https://t.co/shA01BP3kw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peter Arlett, Head of Data Analytics and Methods: Our work goes on. The safety of all the #COVID19vaccines is our top priority and all new data will be evaluated immediately and the public will be kept up to date.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peter Arlett, Head of Data Analytics and Methods: The benefits of AstraZeneca vaccine outweigh the risks. The work introduced today puts the very rare blood clots into the context of #COVID19 hospitalisations prevented, intensive-care admissions prevented and deaths prevented.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nol Wathion, EMAs Deputy Executive Director: "CHMP has recommended to continue giving a second dose of Vaxzevria 4 to 12 weeks after giving the first one in line with the product information."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nol Wathion, EMAs Deputy Executive Director: EMA will continue to assess further information as it becomes available from ECDC, from the Member States, from the company to decide if its current conclusions should be changed in the light of further scientific evidence.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nol Wathion, EMAs Deputy Executive Director: Overall, the data show that the benefits of vaccination increase with age and with increasing levels of infection in the community.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are starting the press briefing on further assessment of data on Vaxzevria, the #COVID19vaccine from AstraZeneca: https://t.co/D7EZUYvtrg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis of data on Vaxzevria (formerly #COVID19vaccine AstraZeneca) puts risks of very rare blood clots in the context of benefits for different age groups and different rates of infection inform national decisions on vaccine roll-out  https://t.co/crHJnVEksn https://t.co/9XUQEt2OKO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[!! A press briefing following the further assessment of #COVID19Vaccine Vaxzevria by our human medicines committee (#CHMP) is planned at 16:00 CET today  https://t.co/oDe9DGjOGK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA has approved manufacturing changes that will increase capacity and supply of Pfizer/BioNTech  Moderna #COVID19vaccines in the EU  https://t.co/qBqoQTWcm9 https://t.co/QFUCOHqs99]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19vaccines: where are we now?  Rolling reviews in progress, no new applications submitted, authorisations completed https://t.co/VUrFWth9Xg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you miss our press briefing on EMA's safety committee (#PRAC) review of #COVID19Vaccine Janssen and cases of blood clots? You can watch it on EMA's YouTube channel: https://t.co/H4xlcn1Cok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: The #COVID19vaccine Janssen has demonstrated in clinical trials and it is highly effective in preventing infections caused by #COVID19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: "It is important that #healthcareprofessionals and the people coming for vaccination are aware of the risks and look out for possible signs or symptoms that usually occur in the first two weeks following vaccination.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: "At this moment it is not possible to identify clear risk factors such as gender or age.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: "The careful review of the cases and available evidence have led #PRAC to the conclusion that these blood clotting disorders are very rare side effects of the #COVID19vaccine Janssen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: "The reported cases occurred mostly in women under 60 years, within the first three weeks following vaccination.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: PRACs scientific assessment provides health authorities responsible for vaccination campaigns in the Member States with the important information they need to take decisions based on their national situation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: When vaccines are rolled-out to large numbers of people, very rare events can occur that were not identified in the clinical trials. Our role is to detect and analyse these risks and their impact on the benefit/risk profile of the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: Our investigations will continue. We will be imposing studies on Janssen to look further into the data. EMA has also commissioned research into the cases of thrombosis in #COVID19 disease through two research consortiums.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are starting the press briefing on EMAs safety committee (#PRAC) review of #COVID19vaccine Janssen and cases of blood clots: https://t.co/H4xlcn1Cok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMAs safety committee (#PRAC) recommends adding very rare cases of unusual blood clots with low blood platelets to the list of side effects for Janssen #vaccine.   Overall benefit-risk remains positive.   https://t.co/hNusE5blWm https://t.co/5kX1ECgogz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ A press briefing on EMAs safety committee (PRAC) review of #COVID19Vaccine Janssen and blood clots is planned at 5:00 PM CET today  Follow live on YouTube: https://t.co/H4xlcn1Cok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's on the agenda of the April meeting of EMA's human medicines committee (#CHMP): https://t.co/S6nTsNDF5B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA and Heads of Medicines Agencies (HMA) are organising a joint #workshop on artificial intelligence (#AI) in #medicines regulation. Join to hear views from stakeholders and experts about ongoing actions and potential gaps.   Follow live broadcast: https://t.co/W0rzENbZQu https://t.co/EtHHIGce6Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19vaccines: where are we now?  Rolling reviews in progress, submitted applications, authorisations completed. https://t.co/gjOttj6ce3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update on AstraZeneca #COVID19vaccine: EMA to provide further context on risk of very rare blood clots with low blood platelets that occurred after vaccination. Read more: https://t.co/GPc4veMHlg https://t.co/1FpEQxbrE9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update on #COVID19vaccine Janssen: assessment of very rare cases of unusual blood clots with low platelets continues. EMA is expediting this evaluation and currently expects to issue a recommendation next week. Read more: https://t.co/uzwQSf2cXt https://t.co/Ki27oIdcIQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During its April meeting, EMAs safety committee, the #PRAC, carried out its broad range of responsibilities, which cover all aspects of the risk management of the use of medicines, including #COVID19vaccines. Read more:  https://t.co/BSurWDTBs4 https://t.co/zFau6OmBuL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19vaccines: where are we now?  Rolling reviews in progress, submitted applications, authorisations completed  https://t.co/7U100MMqtJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you miss our press briefing on EMAs safety committee (#PRAC) conclusion on the review of #COVID19Vaccine AstraZeneca and cases of blood clots? You can watch it on EMAs YouTube channel: https://t.co/BpYBxkk9E6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: It is of great importance that #healthcareprofessionals and the people coming for vaccination are aware of these risks and look out for possible signs or symptoms that usually occur in the first two weeks following vaccination.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: Further research and analysis of this important issue will take place. The #PRAC will continue to assess all evidence that becomes available on this issue while the vaccination campaigns continue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: Although most of the cases occurred in people under 60 years and in women, due to different ways the vaccine in being use in different countries, the #PRAC did not conclude that age and gender were clear risk factors for these very rare side effects.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: No specific risk factors could be identified, based on the current data. The #PRAC is not recommending any specific measures to reduce the risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: "The #PRAC carried out a detailed review of 62 cases of cerebral venous sinus thrombosis and 24 cases of splanchnic vein thrombosis in the EU drug safety database (EudraVigilance) as of 22 March 2021, 18 of which were fatal."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sabine Straus, PRAC Chair: " The #PRAC has conducted a very thorough review of the reports of rare and unusual blood clotting events in combination with low platelets, with the help of an ad hoc expert group that looked at the data in great detail.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: This case shows that our #pharmacovigilance system works: these very rare and unusual events were picked up, identified, analysed and we have made a clear science-based recommendation to allow the safe and effective use of the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: EMA will continue to monitor all the scientific evidence available on both effectiveness and safety of all the authorised COVID-19 vaccines and will issue further recommendations, if necessary, on the grounds of robust evidence.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: It is important that both vaccinated people and #healthcareprofessionals are aware of the signs and symptoms of these unusual blood clotting disorders and can spot them quickly to minimise the risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: EMA is working with the national competent authorities of the EU Member States and the company to make sure that these risks are proactively communicated to #healthcareprofessionals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: "The #PRAC, after an in-depth analysis, has concluded that the reported cases of unusual blood clots following vaccination with AstraZeneca #COVID19vaccine should be listed as possible side effects of the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emer Cooke, EMA's Exec. Director: "EMAs expert committee on the safety of medicines (#PRAC) has confirmed that the benefits of the AstraZeneca vaccine in preventing #COVID19 overall outweigh the risks of side effects.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are starting the press briefing on EMAs safety committee (#PRAC) conclusion on review of #COVID19vaccine AstraZeneca and cases of blood clots:  https://t.co/BpYBxkk9E6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMAs safety committee (#PRAC) has concluded its review of very rare cases of unusual blood clots with AstraZeneca #COVID19 vaccine.  https://t.co/WGsfRP8PTo https://t.co/aeyzK3bfxd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ A press briefing on EMAs safety committee (PRAC) conclusion on the review of #COVID19vaccine AstraZeneca and blood clots is planned at 4:00PM CET today.   Follow live: https://t.co/BpYBxkk9E6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19vaccines: where are we now?  Rolling reviews in progress, submitted applications, authorisations completed  https://t.co/tIXQvFcyuI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA's Executive Director Emer Cooke, will give an update on the investigation of AstraZeneca #COVID19vaccine and thromboembolic events during the @EUCommission press briefing today at 16:30 CET.  Follow the live broadcast: https://t.co/Abm1u11i8F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMAs safety committee (#PRAC) is continuing its evaluation of very rare cases of unusual blood clots in people vaccinated with the AstraZeneca#COVID19 vaccine   https://t.co/7fEBLZkMC5   #COVID19Vaccines #medicine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you miss #EMAPublicMeeting3 on #COVID19vaccines? You can watch it on EMA's YouTube channel: https://t.co/NZop0XLh9c      Share your feedback via https://t.co/iNfuYGnDYz  https://t.co/KaTbyaBfSm #T488 https://t.co/Djs0GLwhfn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMAs human medicines committee (#CHMP) has adopted several important recommendations that will increase manufacturing capacity and supply of #COVID19 vaccines from AstraZeneca, BioNTech/Pfizer and Moderna in the EU. Read more:  https://t.co/P4vZn0szs2 https://t.co/6BUN7XnygQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fight against #COVID19 is a global effort involving #medicines developers, #regulators, #policymakers, #healthcare_professionals and #citizens  we all need to work together to share important validated scientific information to combat the pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read EMAs:  Key Facts on #COVID19vaccines https://t.co/eHogoaQJec   Info on how #COVID19vaccines are being developed, approved  monitored in the EU https://t.co/IDvxzWlRCa   Info on studies needed to approve #COVID19vaccines https://t.co/XkXoiFv7Lt  #EMAPublicMeeting3 https://t.co/ELjOwV1csA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA is publishing monthly safety updates and clinical data for #COVID19 medicines in line with its exceptional transparency measures for treatments and #COVID19vaccines  #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feedback from the public is important to EMA and will help determine what more we can do to enhance public trust in the #COVID19vaccines and their vital role in overcoming this disease #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the current dynamic situation, vaccination strategies need to be able to adapt and take the changing context into consideration #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most effective and efficient approach to reduce hospitalisations and deaths due to #COVID19 is to prioritise vaccination of groups at highest risk of severe disease #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The choice of an optimal vaccination strategy depends on its goals that need to be clearly defined #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As millions of EU citizens are now receiving #COVID19vaccines over a short period of time, EMA is intensively monitoring safety to rapidly detect, assess and act on any possible issues #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The help of #patients, #healthcare_professionals and the general public in reporting #side_effects is fundamental #medicinesafety - https://t.co/skvtx8bM5N    #EMAPublicMeeting3 https://t.co/sZVAIvNYDQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19vaccines have shown clear evidence of efficacy in reducing #COVID19 disease with a good safety profile demonstrated in large clinical trials #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Variants of the virus are emerging, and regulators are working to ensure necessary updates can be made rapidly to ensure #COVID19vaccines remain effective #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All #COVID19vaccines approved in the EU have shown a positive benefit-risk balance in prevention of #COVID19 disease #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Preliminary real-world data suggest that vaccines not only reduce #COVID19 disease and mortality but also viral transmission; more studies are needed to confirm this effect #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All vaccines are important in the fight against #COVID19 https://t.co/Yt8uRLFm4r   #EMAPublicMeeting3 https://t.co/ZL0cLEzEQY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Four #COVID19vaccines have been approved in the EU so far and data from three more vaccines are currently being assessed using EMAs rolling review.   Follow updates on Twitter @EMA_News #EMAPublicMeeting3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A third public meeting is being held to update the public on the assessment, approval and continued safety monitoring of #COVID19vaccines and their expected impact in the community #EMAPublicMeeting3  https://t.co/S5O4eyvtgt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMAs human medicines committee (#CHMP) recommends 5 #medicines for approval at its March 2021 meeting  https://t.co/3Si89CcFMI https://t.co/YKKLSQORUV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember to follow thelive broadcast of the third EMA public meeting on approval, safety monitoring and impact of #COVID19vaccines in the EU .   Today, 13h00 CET   Follow and share our live tweets on #EMAPublicMeeting3  https://t.co/S5O4eyvtgt https://t.co/aykCU9IMPw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19vaccines: where are we now?  Rolling reviews in progress, submitted applications, authorisations completed  https://t.co/7cWozsCfPM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA is convening an ad hoc expert group on 29 March to provide additional input into the ongoing evaluation of #COVID19vaccine AstraZeneca and blood clot cases. Check out the latest updates on the assessment of the reported cases:  https://t.co/bbINgXToYx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA organises 3rd public meeting on Friday, 26 March 2021, to inform citizens on approval, safety monitoring and impact of #COVID19vaccines in the EU.  https://t.co/S5O4eydRRT https://t.co/v2Iu8Ps0pj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EP_Environment: This morning in @EP_Environment   https://t.co/bbK4x2A46C  Starting with consideration of @j_kopcinska draft report o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMA advises against the use of ivermectin medicines for the prevention and treatment of #COVID19 outside controlled clinical trials.  https://t.co/mQByx8J1Li https://t.co/pZ66LaEkP7]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>