<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@carolco63486262 @DavidBegnaud The mother admits she also hits her daughter just not with the hate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InaWinona @DavidBegnaud The mother says she also hits her daughter as a punishment just not with the hatred the principal did. Is that racist too?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Riley doing my hair whilst Im doing the washing up. https://t.co/gYfOQR6T46]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[photo from Commonwealth Day ceremony. Royals were asked to wear red, white or blue representing our flag. Markel chose to wear green. She has no respect for our traditions; the Royal family, or its people. The US are welcome to keep her!No to US porn actors in our Royal family! https://t.co/UmeY4ju9Kq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vestini1969 @superscuba83 Im fed up hearing about the Z list American always searching for a camera to pose.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dandylione @RanchQuad @Jack_Royston Only ignorant idiots believe Meghans BS  lies. Ignorant people who know 0 about Great Britain, Lines of Succession  History. Not surprising since same people cant answer basic questions about USA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@niniane19 @Karenrparry1 @Jack_Royston Shes stupid and a liar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ColetteParson17 @antone_jackie @Jack_Royston The idiots that idolize the phony are in for a rude awakening when all her lies are exposed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@antone_jackie @Jack_Royston Shes bloody dishonest. Cant wait until all her dirty secrets the Royals covered up about her to save Harry embarrassment are out in the public domain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sbrewer106 @Jack_Royston Because she needs that title to make money. No one was interested in her as Meghan Markle. Faux Feminism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karlaocuellar23 @Jack_Royston Apparently she spent quite a lot $$$$$ to hide her porn videos before she chased after hopeless Harry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FYI for Americans, Tatler started as a journal in 1709. It became a magazine of Lifestyle, politics, society  fashion in 1901. The Barristers quoted are well-known  respected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well now I understand why MM and Harry would hide that a surrogate was used. Surrogate = No Title and Not in the line of succession.   https://t.co/CeJO6qyDeh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ADH_Do @theroyaleditor The only racists in the Royal Family are Meghan and Harry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chantelmorris @VDFromAToZ @theroyaleditor Steady income that she never owned a property and just rented. She was never going to be an A lister. So plan B was to marry very well and buy her way to the top.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lamb  biryani for Riley. https://t.co/IuVUCiZzPq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaganTrelawney @GraceandThanks @PageSix Did they all have recent miscarriages?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prequelizabeth @Ben1Jam Im in America and spotted the lies. Only very stupid clueless Americans believe Markle! Like that Californian eejit who started a Go-Fund page for multi-millionaires  to pay off the mortgage on their $30,000,000 house. When millions in US are homeless and using food banks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sussexsquadpod @hudsonsquare34 You people are so stupid. The British press go after the Middletons all the time. Gary gets a good level of mocking and abuse from the media in UK. Only dummies like you lot dont get it. No one takes him seriously.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PageSix Why does Archie have a swollen red cheek? Did someone hit him?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timcast Shes a racist and a loon.  I wonder if her ideas would change if it were her kid being stabbed to death?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KanklesBruh @Timcast Stay stupid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stardust_lune @kittyfain @royal_suitor Nonsense. An audit shows precisely what they cost.   https://t.co/LX9PIDFNwe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kittyfain @stardust_lune @royal_suitor She didnt. Meghan was receiving free couture from designers which isnt allowed. So, Prince Charles paid for her wardrobe to end the freebies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jared_secret @MmMin57 Because theyre HIS family.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lucesita2412gm1 @Fawn1026 All bling like Diana at Princess Grace funeral https://t.co/HYJA4YJdh8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brucetucker @Devereaux_RBW People like Bill Gates are evil and demented. Hes buying up all the farm land  in America to force his GM monster foods on us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@I_Am_That_I_Is @Mu_Ri_Elle @hudsonsquare34 wardrobe of a 40 year old https://t.co/xgqtXkg7Go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrystal7777 @BombshellDAILY BLM is a Marxist group. The people that run it are crooked and use money to buy property for themselves. Typical Marxist trying to get rich with money supposedly for the poor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KajolMomento @BlackNProud365 Considering no one ever heard of Meghan Markle prior to her marrying Harry. She never owned property, didnt wear Haute Couture she was just another Z list American actress.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@I_Am_That_I_Is @Mu_Ri_Elle LA is the tackiest trashiest place on earth. Perhaps you should be concentrating on your massive homeless, mentally ill drug addict problems there. That, and all the rapists you have in Hollyweird.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WorldtimesM @I_Am_That_I_Is Meghans outfit choices if she was invited to Prince Phillips funeral. https://t.co/xmptczO32q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mu_Ri_Elle Here is Princess Diana attending Princess Grace of Monacos funeral. Oh look shes wearing a diamond and pearl choker and matching earrings with a fascinator and veil. Clueless Dumb arses. https://t.co/in5p7Fju9Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mu_Ri_Elle @hudsonsquare34 Good thing Meghan Markle wasnt invited. She always breaks protocol and dresses like an American trollop.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fawn1026 @CBSNews @CBS @yankeewally2 @FloBixby @Jacquel26877237 @GuzzlingMouthMM @dupers_super @Reashelby1 @Smartiepants73 @ToySoldiers10 @Justmythots8 @2baeyes @GwenJBrewer @MeAfter4 @it_real1 @Luca31404488 @feedferalcats @BarkJack @DCTFTW @quickbeam71 https://t.co/2iSswksx6v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JemenesJose Poland and Malta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlackCockney1 @hudsonsquare34 @MeghanMood Millions of Meth addicts in USA.  Look what lovely teeth American Meth addicts have. https://t.co/XtgLEB3nu9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraReiter Meghan Markle couldnt bring down a bouncy castle let alone a thousand year old institution that the British people want.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraReiter Ignorant twit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraReiter No one cares what stupid North Americans think about our Royal FAMILY.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @downsyndrome_47: One of the victims of T4 project who was brutally murdered by Hitler. His Crime: "being an indivisual with Down Syndro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AboutRose_ So stupid https://t.co/HcdnCMy3f5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hudsonsquare34 @MeghanMood https://t.co/DdAMF4GOsZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hudsonsquare34 @UN Some role model Meghan is! Only chases after rich white men, despises her own family and destroys her husbands relationship with his. Dates porn stars. Now, get stuffed. https://t.co/RNUA9DhxrL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeMari81 Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeghanMood Wow what a difference in 4 days. Someone put on the wrong size baby bump. https://t.co/b4QnWg9qu6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeghanMood Yes instead he dresses in a dirty nappy with a cheap white t-shirt whilst trashy Meghan wears couture her father-in-law paid for. Meghan who never owned property until she married a stupid Prince.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byetwit Meghan Markle isnt a Princess. Ignorant troll.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeghanMood Meghan Markle couldnt take down a bouncy castle let alone a thousand year old institution. Poor Harry has always been the thickest clown of the Royal FAMILY. THE Royal family needs to change the rules regarding marriage  weddings, NO divorced American slags need apply.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gabeshuman1 @yankeewally2 @RoyalFamily Shes a former Yacht girl. She dated a porn star. Shes trash.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yankeewally2 @RoyalFamily Shes truly insane. Everyone can see that her plan was to make money off the titles she received marrying Harry and leave the UK ASAP. She needs to shut up and disappear the horrible money grubbing liar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GayleKing https://t.co/8iFMMiNgL3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yankeewally2 Markle is a fake. Everything about her is phony. My guess is her womb is diseased from the many abortions shes had. No way at 40 can she have a kid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @interest_uk: This isn't the first time this has happened and it wont be the last.  https://t.co/AQdtfLPwGy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArcadeJoe @PAImages @PA @PARoyal Dumb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/auUDn0ZknM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back home now from Leavenworth. Yum we are having Carne Porco  Alentejana tonight. Its Portuguese pork with cockles. https://t.co/PBTEu3Ev5q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TipsyDr @mon_lovesyou Another junkie crack head dead. NOGAF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mon_lovesyou STFU slag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mon_lovesyou Move to Venezuela you stupid cow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KayFellowz I dont even give them back what they would like for everyone like me......death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dessert https://t.co/SDhDK397Uo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dinner at Watershed cafe https://t.co/v1TiOEL0Yn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/Hx8R0uddmW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/YKMOHYkeIq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Blackbird Island https://t.co/pahDyxpZvl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Blackbird Island https://t.co/mjlBNYZDCj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lunch at Munchen Haus and lager at Icicle Brewery https://t.co/v7PlabfkjY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blackbird Island with @petterson_riley https://t.co/SajVhP6uOr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SavedAt18 Thanks Steve. Its lovely here but cold up in the Cascadian mountains]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We also had local hard cider .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dinner at Andreas Keller    Jgerschnitzel with sptzle, Cordon Bleu with sptzle, Sahne Schnitzel. https://t.co/sFz7QKukxF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/u58Yrh9mpv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Leavenworth for Spring break! https://t.co/czrV7AYraR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraWharton15 @Chakrangel1 @kegeiger Hes always been the thickest royal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prestonojohnson @kegeiger Says the bloke with only a few followers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jw5380 @Sen_JoeManchin My dad and brothers cant enter the USA because Biden banned UK citizens due to Covid. So, dad should pretend to be Mexican and climb the wall into Texas and then fly to Seattle because illegals are ok.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JHoganGidley @JoeyCortese1 He cant even answer what day it is without cue cards!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewYorker @tnyCloseRead You might want to work on learning your own US history before talking rubbish about the UK.  https://t.co/WpHqric7oF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tnyCloseRead @benlyle1 @NewYorker Youre fortunate the Royal Family dont sue like Americans do at the drop of a hat. Your piece full of lies makes you look like an amateur at best and a liar. What a lot of rubbish.  https://t.co/axXEm9VLVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NewYorker @tnyCloseRead article of yours is so very stupid  proves US journalists dont research anything! Harry is the patron of Mental Health charities in the UK if Markle was genuinely suicidal he would know exactly who to contact for help. So many lies.   https://t.co/axXEm9VLVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LilaGraceRose https://t.co/CX0lwmzhIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LiveAction https://t.co/CX0lwmzhIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JBsTwoCents I do whites on hot, dark colours on warm, bright colours separately by colour family on cold, jumpers and delicates on cold set to delicates so not hard spin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhitsittSusan @PreciousLifeCom Thats because Twitter loves killing babies through abortion. Abortion needs to be abolished all over the world.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PreciousLifeCom https://t.co/CX0lwmzhIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes it is!! Cheers @PRO_LIFE_UTAH  for letting me share life with DS https://t.co/YircA4szr1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HAPPY WORLD DOWN SYNDROME DAY! My Zoom call with ProLifeUtah #WorldDownSyndromeDay #DSDontFearItEmbraceIt   https://t.co/CX0lwmzhIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@grzemar70 Thank you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From UK Private Eye Magazine.    Lmao https://t.co/eHD9eoCIz0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 @PhilManess3 He looks like he has a lot of flatulence so yeah the wind in him did it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RVerbeet Theres taking control and theres being a control freak that silences everyone elses voice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RVerbeet She bullies her husband Prince Harry. In the interview with Oprah when Prince Harry tried to say something Meghan put up her hand to silence him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Atar_6L6C6 Cool. I would love to make my shoops valuable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Atar_6L6C6 Whats an NFT?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle https://t.co/bpkhJaf5rY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xjxposed @realDailyWire @thecandaceshow @RealCandaceO Says the fake account with a few followers and no photo. Piss off. Im certain youre hideous. Candace is beautiful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MortyChase @realDailyWire @thecandaceshow @RealCandaceO I think youre confusing Candace with Meghan Markle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OzWiz1 @alyssadotmarie @realDailyWire @thecandaceshow @RealCandaceO Tell that to Meghan Markle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XhbRQvLfvi]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>