<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HumanRights4UK: Our purpose is to inform EVERY citizen of the UK of their fundamental Human Rights. If these were taught in every schoo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Truth_Seeker199: I am not alone. And neither are you. We must stand up. We must continue this. We are an amazing country. Let's get our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock What do you want? A fucking medal?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10,000 fine for not having the vaccine... Its coming... Its not public knowledge yet, but give it time.   #KnowTheOutcomeAndYouWillSeeTheJourney]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NellyTells: The vaccine doesnt stop you from getting infected, doesnt stop you from being infectious but we need absolutely everyon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SanityMeTime: @marmorkreb1 I run a holistic salon I treat muscle injury and stress. My 15 year daughter two years was assaulted,man tri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @unhealthytruth: Hey I thought you guys would like to see this. https://t.co/m0D9eFo7BW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xGnz08Gt6G  @piersmorgan  @piersmorgan  @piersmorgan   Cheers mate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Char_lot_J: @SandraWeeden I love to go abroad but any airline company/country that wants me to have the vaccination then won't be getti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: This is highly suspect! What do the #CoronavirusVaccine #PCRTEST, #HIV  #SARSCOV2 all have in common?????. Anyone???  https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/I2wftTeRUQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Charlotte3003G This is brilliant haha  #GoGirl #PowerToThePeople ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9F82lgIXtx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScotTSentinel: Interview with @katesherimani The 'conspiracy mother' https://t.co/TL59mDNTmE #ScamdemicIsOver]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dabornfox: @TheBernician But I would ask the judge to reconsider whether Hancock was not being dishonest by concealing that the Imperia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @unhealthytruth: This is under operation warp speed. This will be mandated, the vaccine, upon all people he says. What the hell?  https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @unhealthytruth: https://t.co/kmpxFcFS0i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emmakennytv: December 2nd lets all get back to normal. What can they do if we just open shops, bars, schools all as they were! The Gov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We the people will be given a passport to freedom if we comply with the mass testing, if we wear a mask, if we get the covid vaxx. We wont be able to exercise our basic human rights without this vaccine.  Oh, but thats just a conspiracy theory, right? #wakeup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @delbigtree: ITS OFFICIAL!!  After 4 years, 190 episodes, 360,000 followers, FACEBOOK HAS DELETED OUR SHOW https://t.co/wgyjWanWXL We m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fiddaman: So, Pfizer announced that their vaccine was 90% effective.  Days later, Moderna, announced their vaccine was 94% effective.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HighWireTalk: In Denmark, there has been a week of protests against a new law that "would be able to define groups of people who must b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matt Hancock will be arrested. #JustWait]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkyNews: Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab says the "challenge" with testing for #COVID19 in airports is 'the very high false positive rat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MassDeception1: https://t.co/CMTm73mk3t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its here Mandatory C-19 vaxx coming soon. Soon enough you wont be able to attend a public event, let alone even leave the country to go on your family holiday without the vaccine.  This information was brought to you months ago by people who were named conspiracy theorists ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump knows whats up! https://t.co/V6Ep7deQr9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BritainFree: "They've used the Public Health Act to lock us up, destroy businesses and inflict damage on the economy. We're saying 'you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cmsmwoo1: @SimonWatson2018 @BritainFree https://t.co/qr2OKJRUA7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: And the Liberal Democrats accuse US of being science deniers - how ridiculous to believe that BOUGHT  PAID for studies can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Tomorrow we need a #NationalSwitchOff of the news. Let the wannabe dictator Johnson declare more lockdowns  restrictions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jblovatt: "I am 80, and it is no business of the Government to tell me whether or not to kiss my grandchildren, or whom I may invite in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lorrain00414525: A friend was diagnosed with cancer in February, they stopped her treatment in March and for the foreseeable future bec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NLeespeaking: @RealDeniseWelch It changed when he was instructed to change it!  https://t.co/ldwhC6tkzH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: So when and why did this directive change?? Were treated like complete idiots. How are we meant to accept ANYTHING an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lorrain00414525: I can't believe Morrisons. As if it isn't bad enough seeing masks everywhere you now have to watch them on the adverts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is sadness when you realise yourself  a significant other are both operating on extremely different levels of consciousness. There becomes a growing divide.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @David28787016: Just at a restaurant watching people walk up to the door, put a mask on, scan their tracking app, then walk to their tab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please. Punish me !!!! https://t.co/W8jXuoe0VU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Truthseeker1985: 10 deaths in England, none in Wales and none in Scotland either! Of those deaths they were between 60 and 97 with unde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LondonRealTV: SECOND WAVE  LOCKDOWN  WILL KILL RESTAURANTS  PUBS WHERE ONLY 5% OF TRANSMISSION OCCURS - WHY?  Is it about time this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottAnd67: If you put a mask on going into a shop and take it off when you come out, it's not a virus you are afraid of. It's judgment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HighWireTalk: "Time to install your update," the painting is captioned. RT Huge Anti-Bill Gates Mural Appears in Melbourne as Crowds Ch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: Dont let the bastards get you down. Go outside, enjoy the sunshine, and remember, the govt and media are enjoying fri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlistairHaimes: Lady on the train panicked when I took off my mask after sitting down, but visibly relaxed when she saw I was having a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They keep popping up on my Facebook timeline with daily COVID-19 news? Do they not cover any other stories anymore?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHY IS SKY NEWS CONSTANTLY ON MY TIMELINE ON FACEBOOK. I am not following them nor do I like their page. So no reason for them to be on my timeline. @SkyNews shame on you for your manipulation, scaremongering and attempt at social conditioning. You are following orders from evil.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: Why do the govt not have to answer these questions. 1) Why is it called the Coronavirus Act not Covid-19  2) Why are y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Notyour28981739: I'm seeing a lot of ppl saying they won't get a vaccine for a virus that has a 99%+ recovery rate.  But y'all vaccinat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomSanders557: @befree200 @opinionatedmum1 Heres a good one.. https://t.co/kWmiMZYxgD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @delbigtree: NO WAY AZ WALKS AWAY from a potential 750 BILLION PAYOUT.  After THEIR OWN INVESTIGATION next weeks headline will read Pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeahButlerSmith: Interesting ...   A randomized placebo-controlled trial in children showed that flu shots increased fivefold the risk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Flu mist being pushed on school kids. A live virus that they can easily shed and pass on to family members. They then get f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: It doesnt matter what new restrictions Boris Johnson announces tomorrow. Even if it is a 2nd national lockdown. If enough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @delbigtree: At the very least it should now be apparent to all that there never was SCIENTIFIC CONSENSUS on the COVID19 PANDEMIC. So ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MassDeception1:  https://t.co/NK8M89EFg6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Nearly 3000 perfectly healthy people test positive for a virus so deadly, they had to get tested to tell them if they have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seriously, how long do they think they can keep this shit-show up for? I think even the most un-woke person can even see through the bullshit now, because it really is, out right ridiculous!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @delbigtree: The W.H.O.  just ADMITTED LOCKDOWNS WERE A MISTAKE by electing the one MAN WHO DEFIED all of their PANDEMIC RECOMMENDATIONS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Small businesses are under attack by people that have lost their morals and values over Covid fear and misinformation. Same pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brixton_Ben26 @piersmorgan I was literally about to say the same thing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan YOU HAVE A 1 IN A MILLION CHANCE OF DYING FROM COVID 19. You are deluded Mr Morgan! Take some time to look at the facts. Wake up for goodness sake. Your ignorance tells me youve signed something to make you continuously support this Scamdemic no matter how ludicrous it becomes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealDeniseWelch  THANK YOU! You are AMAZING! #WeHaveYourBack xxx   https://t.co/5i6OkyH0QY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@edrock90 @Kikimamberoy Ahhh I see! Thank you for letting me know about that, I was really curious! I hope this little one gets justice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @P43Bkx: @peterjukes @Obstkuchen69 @RealDeniseWelch Any dark money funding anything to do with Covid is coming mostly from the Bill  Me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealDeniseWelch @peterjukes Unfortunately you cant get through to someone who still hasnt woken up. Do you wear a mask in your car Mr Jukes?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: Lying by the pool and heard a woman shouting Alexa over and over. One ear cocked to hear her choice of music then real]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kikimamberoy Ive only just come across #StandWithSophie - Who has been filming all of this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emilyrauhala: News: The Trump administration will not join a global effort to develop, manufacture and equitably distribute a coronavir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @saveourrightsuk: Save the Date  Sat 26th Sept  WE DO NOT CONSENT  Trafalgar Sq 12pm  6 months since the Coronavirus Act 2020 came int]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @delbigtree: If you were shocked to hear the CDC admit that ONLY 9,210 HAVE DIED FROM COVID19 while the rest were attributed to SERIOUS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BritainFree: This is getting more sinister by the day.  "Fast-tracked vaccine" and "effective and safe" do not go together: something h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StandUpX2: 40,000 PEOPLE!!!!! BIGGEST PROTEST TO DATE THANK YOU EVERYONE WHO SHOWED UP. WE DID IT #londonprotest #wedonotconsent #nolo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HighWireTalk: BREAKING: GLOBAL PROTESTS AGAINST COVID-19 RESTRICTIONS    Thousands around the world are taking to the streets in protes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidicke You are amazing @davidicke - Im so gutted I couldnt make it. I got goosebumps watching the live stream today though... My goodness!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: Again, if there is a justified reason for this could we know please??   https://t.co/r0qTZrIF7c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: What I find baffling is the amount of well known people messaging me privately to give me support scared shitless to s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: In #Berlin launching @ChildrensHD Europe. Tomorrow, I will speak to largest crowd in #German history. We are expecting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OH COME ON  Give it a rest https://t.co/N1UfXEiXKm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AustExperienced: @MFCPARlS @RealDeniseWelch @pictures0fgirls This is what's causing the hysteria. People clearly have no clue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @itsleepeart: @c0rneIiastreet @RealDeniseWelch @pictures0fgirls Coronavirus = umbrella term for a type of virus (there are currently 7 k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emmakennytv: Why do we need to know how many people have coronavirus? Its ridiculous...we are testing more, so confirming more...these]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealDeniseWelch: So I share the amazing good news that Doncaster hospital has had no Covid deaths for 3 weeks and Pauline says give it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/150lMzBNhg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Hysteria https://t.co/GpxkD4PUVi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#plandemic #billgates #killgates https://t.co/2tnquGTvqF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: If youre in the least bit curious about who #FauciTheFraud works for  and why it matters... #drfranciscollins #CDC   http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drscottjensen: Let's talk about the FEAR FORMULA  It's real...it's happening. https://t.co/KKOehGqrbx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: Please God, take this away. What psychological traumas will these children need to overcome? https://t.co/3FW38D0Vpe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: OMG.theyre coming after AU big time. This is war against their own people https://t.co/5GXUqCqZSI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @miri_af: A nurse who opposes lockdown and masks wants to come forward but is terrified of losing all financial security if he does.  Al]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PfizerBioNTech  #Moderna #CovidVaccine both contain an allergen and suspected carcinogen. Even the MHRA advises people with a history of significant allergic reactions not to opt for the Pfizer vaccine. https://t.co/Ijnq5fRjGY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PfizerBioNTech  #Moderna #CovidVaccine both contain an allergen and suspected carcinogen. Also the spike protein mRNA of the vaccine could be absorbed by human cells  integrated which could induce cancer.  https://t.co/HU4yHiMkO2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During the Phase II/III trials, 50% of #PfizerCovidVaccine participants aged 18-55 experienced systemic adverse events within a month of their second dose of vaccine as did 100% of those injected with two doses of #Modernas vaccine. Please people stop taking it! #Covid19 #Resist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadian politician says #GreatReset is not a conspiracy theory, but an actual set of concrete proposals and #WEF is  he biggest gathering of global hypocrites in history". The  policies would create massive poverty. #Resist #GreatReject  https://t.co/ZR5rO3q0BZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LiquorElixir @darrengrimes_ You will be identified all right. Once you are nanochipped and 5G is everywhere. For now, your mobile phone is on all the time, connected to Facebook and Google. They know more about you than you know about yourself. If you have track and trace then your mask is worthless.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrengrimes_ This is why the psychopathic 'elite' call it the New Normal. They never want it to end. The better to control you.  #Resist and #RiseUp  #StopNewNormal #MasksOff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#covid19 #CovidTesting https://t.co/XWkhJnnoQZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another 'side effect' of the #PfizerCovidVaccine  - but don't worry the MHRA says its safe. Duh !  #CovidVaccine  #COVID19  https://t.co/dhNAjzqLF1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrengrimes_ There is no border within the UK. Also England and Wales have the same legal system. How can something legal in England be illegal in Wales ? They just want to break up the UK and this must be stopped. Now.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>