<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[I just hit submit on an application while chanting "Alea iacta est."  What I am trying to say is that I am way too dramatic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@martinhoenigl @tom_tchill @MRCcmm Of course it will. That's what azoles do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbrownmd @ClancyNeil @ABsteward @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 Well, that means you effectively have mandatory consults. That fixes the issue. But if you don't force it, I be some still don't get treated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbrownmd @ClancyNeil @ABsteward @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 How do you know? I bet if you systematically analyzed your hospital you would find cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrNeilStone: You may mock this "Covid quack" in India who claims vaccines are not necessary and that diet can control Covid   But we ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClancyNeil @ABsteward @kbrownmd @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClancyNeil @ABsteward @kbrownmd @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 Absolutely. I think that we underestimate the attributable, or rather the contributable mortality of candida.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ABsteward @ClancyNeil @kbrownmd @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 Check out the section about untreated patients.   https://t.co/26HTLQGaOY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClancyNeil @ABsteward @kbrownmd @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 I'm talking in this case largely folks who are ready to discharge. I would argue that we underestimate how bad it can be. I have a pretty cool study we are writing up now about this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClancyNeil @ABsteward @kbrownmd @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 Would they though? In a subgroup if patients who people chose not to treat (presumably because they looked good), 90 day mortality was around 70% when we looked at it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BradSpellberg @ABsteward @TomWalshMD13 @ClancyNeil I'd enroll into that trial.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JGPharmD @GermHunterMD The right way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mycoconnection @GermHunterMD LOVE it. You guys are old school Russians anyway.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ABsteward @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 @ClancyNeil Sorry misread. From first negative. Not total. Sorry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ABsteward @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 @ClancyNeil Yes. Total.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GermHunterMD I'm from Europe. After 27 years in America, still freaks me out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ABsteward @BradSpellberg @TomWalshMD13 @ClancyNeil I always do 14 days. YES, some would do fine with less. But our ability to discriminate is garbage. So, I give 14, knowing that the burden of an extra 5-7 d of flu is miniscule compared to any associated population level mortality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IDJClub @FranciscoMarty_ One of the greatest physicians of his generation.  we lost a giant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarlosdelRio7: The @WinterCourseID #wcid21 is about to start. Excellent program, superb speakers  fantastic talks by  @KinnaThakara]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDJClub: Next #IDJClub: May 3 (9pm EDT)  In honor of our late colleague and friend Francisco Marty, a giant in the field of infections]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MohitHarshMD @hrenoID @tanyawildes Trust me, it will fill up. Lines on a CV are like barnacles on a whale. They get there over time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hrenoID @tanyawildes If they show up. Many conferences do not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tanyawildes I have been told that at least here, abstracts don't count. I haven't added the last 20 or so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CesarGBerto I don't think any of the data is convincing. The only thing I ever add on is echonocandins, but I admit it's often out of desperation, not scientific evidence.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tmhohl71 I'm not sure what 5 vs 7 days would do for us. And I agree. But if I order 2q6 and they miss many doses, they are getting at least q8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boulware_dr @kbrownmd Agreed. I have always done 2g.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@khalideljaaly Congratulations my friend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @khalideljaaly: Promoted to associate professor (pharmacy practice - infectious disease)  Thanks to everyone who supported  guided me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbrownmd @alxpenguin Worst headache of his life, high WBC, high protein, lowish glucose. I honestly don't think this is a false positive test. Often is, but this is a pretty solid diagnosis at this point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbrownmd Awesome. That's where I was leaning too. I was just saying it is almost certainly real meningitis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@venkat_id Binding is better for HSV than VZV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alxpenguin I know what you are saying. Gave the same lecture to the residents. Then they told me the numbers and I was not so brave.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alxpenguin Hard to tell. Pleocytosis of &gt;100, so leaning yes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntibioticDoc Wbc was &gt;100, so I'm a little hesitant to ignore.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbrownmd That's true. But this person had real meningitis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stable VZV meningitis w/ V1 shingles. After 5 days of IV-&gt; valacyclovir 2g q6h?  Are folks ok with that plan? I'm kind of comfortable, but have a nagging worry in back of my mind.   https://t.co/ZUW4LlGGwI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wfwrighID @AntibioticDoc @DrToddLee @transplantID @sigal_md @AliceBarsoumian @BradSpellberg @IdVilchez @serotavirus @PrathitKulkarni @Cortes_Penfield @Coyle_CM @GermHunterMD @Darcy_ID_doc @JessicaRQueen1 @laura_certain I've never done it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JulioCZuniga1: Our Crypto-Histo screening in Central America paper just got accepted for publication!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexLawandi @wfwrighID You are correct.  The CrAg stays high for very long.  I never repeat CrAg (well not ever, but never systematically)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wfwrighID Only worth doing to manage ICP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AllisonRBond Wait till you learn about fosmanogepix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahTaimur @IdVilchez There are a few different options here, but I would say not histo. Unlikely to be that. Cladophilophora maybe? But any dematiacious or hyaline hyphomycete could look like this. I would get a Fontana Masson stain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABsteward:  #CID @IDSAInfo by @FranciscoMarty_ RIP Isavuconazole treatment of invasive fungal sinusitis: a post hoc analysis of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CrystalZhengMD I would be happy to.  Let me know.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GermHunterMD That's a big yikes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrultiva I rarely if ever worry about the cyclodextran.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dr_Di5infect: What a great opportunity!! @Vpoplin33 @NoCoastID @JimiJegede]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KUIDfellowship @KUMC_GME Thank you all for the wonderful questions, a lovely discussion and in general a great time.   I look forward to following your careers as they develop! https://t.co/KugQ1Kd758]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KUIDfellowship: Guys.... we were OVER THE MOON today getting to chat with @FungalDoc after having him as a guest speaker for grand roun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NateBahrMD @KUMedCenter @KUInfectDisease @KUIDfellowship @KUIMchiefs @KUPulmCC I'm really excited to do the lecture. But even more excited to have the conversation with the fellows afterwards!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDSAInfo:  TOMORROW @ 2pm ET | @CarlosdelRio7, @TaliaSwartz, @JGPharmD, @FungalDoc  other health experts address the latest question]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bethp_DI I'm just saying. Clinical mycology needs more people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealTimeCOVID19: Join 4/28 2 ET for a live #TwitterChat on #COVIDvaccines hosted by @RealTimeCOVID19   Bring yours  to our experts usi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bethp_DI Come to mycology. There is like 7 of us and we embrace everybody because we are so lonely.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soupvector @JonathanRyderMD @AdamRodmanMD @GermHunterMD It was literally the same thought I've had every time I see it. https://t.co/lSSifQyUT0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soupvector @JonathanRyderMD @AdamRodmanMD @GermHunterMD https://t.co/o5SlQtwGUU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonathanRyderMD @AdamRodmanMD @GermHunterMD Almost certainly not. But IRL it's even more gorgeous.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonathanRyderMD @AdamRodmanMD @GermHunterMD India ink is a very pretty stain. Have you ever done it in person?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealTimeCOVID19: Join 4/28 2 ET for a live #TwitterChat on #COVIDvaccines hosted by @RealTimeCOVID19   Bring yours  to our experts usi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrToddLee @boulware_dr Very. Pressure management HAS to happen in parallel. 90% of referrals and requests for my help because of therapy failure are pressure management failure. Or rather failure to consider pressure management.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boulware_dr @DrToddLee Don't forget the azithro. And of course we have to be careful to extrapolate. But without better data, it's hard to ignore you know?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boulware_dr @DrToddLee I hope this time the date sticks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boulware_dr @DrToddLee So hard to know how to measure but as Day taught us with CryptoDex, toning down the response is not the answer either. At least not in HIV. Transplant....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boulware_dr @DrToddLee I would feel comfortable interpreting it from HIV to transplant, and giving it in transplant patients. When we looked at standards of care and their association with mortality and ID consult 5FC was associated with both. Hard to look at retrospectively.... https://t.co/YDDcSIu2Nw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chitaluc1 @GermHunterMD @BradCutrellMD Congrats! Hope you like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chitaluc1: Finally got my copy.@GermHunterMD @FungalDoc @BradCutrellMD  https://t.co/FWQ8mRFCbs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OncIDPharmd @Rybak_JM @IDPharmacometrx @ABsteward @jc_pharmacist @a_lepak @Russlewis_BO @GermHunterMD The variability reduced. But the TI is still low.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OncIDPharmd @Rybak_JM @IDPharmacometrx @ABsteward @jc_pharmacist @a_lepak @Russlewis_BO @GermHunterMD Yes it is. Better than some of the earlier azoles, but still way worse than beta lactams. Which have an insanely high TI.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OncIDPharmd @Rybak_JM @IDPharmacometrx @ABsteward @jc_pharmacist @a_lepak @Russlewis_BO @GermHunterMD Because with beta lactam the therapeutic index is so high. In fungus we had to do it because we thread a much narrower eye of the needle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NateBahrMD @IdVilchez @SarahTaimur @AbidiMaheen @boulware_dr @martinhoenigl To be honest Nate, I am even cautious of a positive. More helpful than a negative bug yikes is this a bad test.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IDPharmacometrx @ABsteward @jc_pharmacist @a_lepak @Russlewis_BO @GermHunterMD @Rybak_JM I think we need folks like you to do the clinical analyses and teach us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@A_Spallonii @alxpenguin @PaulSaxMD Amy, I would be good enough of a friend to swap seats in that situation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MerylSwanLake @DrNeilStone @GermHunterMD I'd love to be part of these. But Mondays are my crazy days. My clinic averages 20-25 people, so I am crushed when I finish that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MerylSwanLake: #aspergillosis #posaconazole #voriconazole cc @DrNeilStone @GermHunterMD @FungalDoc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boulware_dr @DrToddLee @IdVilchez @wfwrighID @kbrownmd @AntibioticDoc @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @StephaniePouch @BradSpellberg Highly anticipated!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @xkcd: Fully Vaccinated https://t.co/bwP9aTbEsa https://t.co/apVwcJe0Jx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soupvector @hrenoID Right? Not sure where she gets it from.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WinterCourseID @hboucher3 @dan_diekema @CarlosdelRio7 @idpharmd @KinnaThakarar @PreetiNMalani And this year I have the pleasure of being one of the faculty for the first time!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Darcy_ID_doc An old soul. Not even a full 8 months old yet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hrenoID I know I sound like every other super crazy excited patient, but ain't she purdy?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ana Spec would like to tell you that she enjoyed her dinner. https://t.co/9hZpICXhLI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IdVilchez @wfwrighID @kbrownmd @AntibioticDoc @DrToddLee @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @boulware_dr @StephaniePouch @BradSpellberg So far so good.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hboucher3: Join us for the @WinterCourseID Great faculty, challenging cases WeAreID @dan_diekema @PreetiNMalani @CarlosdelRio7 @idpharm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WinterCourseID: We hope you will be joining us for our 47th Annual Meeting May 3-7.  Tremendous faculty, sessions and cases!  Registrat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alxpenguin @PaulSaxMD Sometimes enough to end a friendship, depending on where it ends up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alxpenguin @PaulSaxMD When I visit Guatemala I eat mainly street food. And all my colleagues there are mortified for me.   I say ETEC gives it a nice zing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrultiva @DrToddLee @AntibioticDoc @IdVilchez @wfwrighID @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @boulware_dr @StephaniePouch It's all about the cooperation. It takes all of us to get the beat outcome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrultiva @DrToddLee @AntibioticDoc @IdVilchez @wfwrighID @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @boulware_dr @StephaniePouch That's awesome! I am not familiar with the quality of that particular test, but assuming it's good, y'all are doing it right!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrultiva @DrToddLee @AntibioticDoc @IdVilchez @wfwrighID @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @boulware_dr @StephaniePouch Those are the words that were said to me the few times I diagnosed legionella after 5-7 days of fever and shock I'm the ICU.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrToddLee @AntibioticDoc @IdVilchez @wfwrighID @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @boulware_dr @StephaniePouch Yup. They "go big". And forget the epidemiology.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JayCdoesID That's awesome. Please let us know the etymology.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntibioticDoc @IdVilchez @DrToddLee @wfwrighID @kitagawa_yukiko @IUIDfellowship @transplantID @soupvector @Boghuma @boulware_dr @StephaniePouch Legionella does. Lots of ICUs drop atypical coverage in favor of "broad coverage" because "they are sick."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JayCdoesID 1. Huge congrats! 2. With a name like the Golden Brick, there has to be a story.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dfreedman7 @onisillos https://t.co/RiGOPY38Qr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sigal_md @PaulSaxMD I am very much a yes on oysters. I buy them in a big bag and shuck them myself.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@onisillos I hope, HOPE, that it's the effect of political intrusion into the #IDtwitter sphere.   We will go back. We have to. We just have to. *Says he in a desperate quavering voice*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaartenVHemelen @IdVilchez I don't think I've ever seen positive markers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonathanRyderMD @IdVilchez Ab. And we don't have igra unfortunately.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IdVilchez Also, screen for histo. I've picked up a few people who had arthralgias 2/2 histo being treated for RA.  Adding rituximab on top of that........]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntibioticDoc @D_Winetsky_MD @IdVilchez Remedy. But if it doesn't work, can be followed up by a slow roast.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>