<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Over the past week, Idaho has reported 1,219 new cases of COVID-19 and 12 COVID-19-related deaths. There have been a total of 188,233 confirmed COVID-19 cases and 2,052 COVID-19-related deaths since the start of the pandemic. Details at https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. Wednesday on Facebook Live: DHW's Sarah Leeds will answer questions about grant funding for mobile COVID-19 vaccine clinics. See you then! https://t.co/VMYvJp7InM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-QA: Grant funding for mobile clinics is now available https://t.co/v9akJBif5P via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Milestone reached: More than 500,000 people are now fully vaccinated in Idaho! We want to thank every Idahoan who has gotten vaccinated for protecting themselves and their community. Schedule your vaccine appointment today: https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML https://t.co/wyDce6Twjx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccine is free, it's been rigorously tested, and it's saving lives. All Idahoans age 16+ can get vaccinated any time: Walk into a local pharmacy or get an appointment at https://t.co/50U9XKt9AY https://t.co/EEipZRgdHV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 1,074,470 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 607,393 people have received vaccine and 499,860 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone 16 and older can get a COVID-19 vaccine in Idaho. There is no longer a requirement to live or work in Idaho to get vaccinated here.   The vaccine is free! There are no out-of-pocket costs to anyone who gets the vaccine. Find a provider today! https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[St. Luke's launched a mobile unit that's bringing life-saving COVID-19 vaccine to people in the Caldwell, Ketchum, Hailey, and Boise areas. See the mobile unit's schedule: https://t.co/5GYo8n4dEg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting vaccinated is now easier than ever. Simply visit https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML and youll have the option to pre-register or schedule a COVID-19 vaccine appointment, as well as locate a nearby pharmacy offering walk-in appointments. https://t.co/SGrKlhc7oe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May is Hepatitis Awareness Month! Learn the ABCs of viral #Hepatitis to find out if you should get tested and/or vaccinated. Learn more: https://t.co/2gGJh8hpgk https://t.co/N1gYX4a70K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IDAHO COVID-19 HOT SPOTS: The 3 counties with the highest COVID-19 infection rates in Idaho include Boise, Payette, and Kootenai. They have a 7-day moving average incidence rates of 16.4, 15.5, and 14.7 per 100,000 people respectively. More data: https://t.co/N3bjJKQumX https://t.co/4qvD0mbVFX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 1,057,549 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 603,715 people have received vaccine and 486,271 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The weekly summary of long-term care facilities with COVID-19 is now available:  https://t.co/H9NzbrsXLw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A reminder from DHW Director Dave Jeppesen: We are building Idahos future thanks to Gov. Littles initiative that awards $4.2M to DHW for building and maintenance projects https://t.co/FcKf0HtrXz via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[$9 million in grant funding is available to establish and operate mobile vaccination clinics in underserved communities. More information: https://t.co/SkGGKpVrKz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still on the decrease! Idahos percent positivity for PCR COVID-19 tests from 4/18-4/24 statewide is 4.3%. That's down from 4.7% the week before.   Among Idaho's 44 counties, 20 saw a decrease in positive tests compared with the previous week and 3 remained unchanged at 0%. https://t.co/aZcnGfmv4t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New CDC study found Pfizer-BioNTech or Moderna COVID-19 vaccines are 94% effective against COVID-19 hospitalization among fully vaccinated adults and 64% effective among partially vaccinated adults aged 65 and older. More information: https://t.co/IgDc5YZVYe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After you are fully vaccinated, you can travel with fewer restrictions. CDC says fully vaccinated people can travel internationally without a pre- or post-travel test depending on destination, and without quarantining after travel. More information: https://t.co/0EOiwYmeiP https://t.co/3cC64ICjev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone 16 and older can get a COVID-19 vaccine in Idaho. There is no longer a requirement to live or work in Idaho to get vaccinated here.   The vaccine is free! There are no out-of-pocket costs to anyone who gets the vaccine. Find a provider today! https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting today, anyone over the age of 16 can walk into a St. Luke's COVID-19 vaccine location to receive a vaccination, no appointment necessary. More information: https://t.co/9S6ge82189]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DHW announces new funding opportunity for COVID-19 vaccination clinics: https://t.co/nI3MlOl29g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 1,036,536 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 597,444 people have received vaccine and 471,095 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73eUZir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feeling stressed by the pandemic? Learn about DHW's support group series on coping with the challenges of a year of COVID-19 in this Channel 6 interview with DHW's Lillian Toumey: https://t.co/U32RqJfNPx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In case you missed it: DHW's Tamara Prisock answered questions about COVID-19 in Idaho's long-term care facilities. https://t.co/VMYvJppjfk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join our team! Southwest Idaho Treatment Center in Nampa is hiring for several positions in nursing, client services, food services, and maintenance and custodial. Call 208-505-3343 to learn more or visit https://t.co/jC687xDKYV to apply! https://t.co/0hW2r40qpt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 vaccines being used in Idaho have been rigorously tested by over 100,000 Americans. Over 100 million Americans have been vaccinated. The vaccine is safe and effective. It's saving lives. https://t.co/d4P2KjsDI1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. TODAY on Facebook Live: DHW's Tamara Prisock will answer questions we've received about COVID-19 in Idaho's long-term care facilities. https://t.co/VMYvJp7InM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over the past week, Idaho has reported 1,549 new cases of COVID-19 and 18 COVID-19-related deaths. There have been a total of 187,014 confirmed COVID-19 cases and 2,040 COVID-19-related deaths since the start of the pandemic. Details at https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. Wednesday on Facebook Live: DHW's Tamara Prisock will answer questions we've received about COVID-19 in Idaho's long-term care facilities. https://t.co/VMYvJppjfk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The recording of today's COVID-19 media briefing is now available: https://t.co/n996DRWJrZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Effective today, it is no longer a requirement to live or work in Idaho to get vaccinated in the state. Anyone age 16 or older can now get vaccinated in Idaho. https://t.co/01lJA9J4ft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 QA: COVID-19 and long-term-care facilities https://t.co/8bA2q9Ch9t via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New CDC guidance on mask wearing: https://t.co/dobOSf0Qu1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting today use the states COVID-19 vaccine tool to schedule an appointment or find a nearby pharmacy offering walk-in options, in addition to putting yourself on a list for a provider to call you! Visit https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML https://t.co/5RZmZLAWsn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 1,020,224 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 591,954 people have received vaccine and 460,117 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73eUZir https://t.co/pKSPAh8FMj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone 16 and older who lives or works in Idaho can get the COVID-19 vaccine. And its free  there are no out-of-pocket costs to anyone who gets the vaccine. Find a provider today! https://t.co/PZjHFVHobl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Milestone reached: More than 1 million doses of COVID-19 vaccine have now been administered in Idaho!  Every dose administered gets us one step closer to normal. Keep it up Idaho and sign up for your vaccine appointment today: https://t.co/PZjHFVHobl https://t.co/OnM5xBsJaG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DHW COVID-19 media briefing set for 2:30 p.m. MDT Tuesday: https://t.co/0mCrfatVj5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After you are fully vaccinated, CDC says you can gather indoors with unvaccinated people of any age from one other household without masks or staying 6 feet apart, unless anyone has an increased risk of severe illness from COVID-19. https://t.co/0EOiwY4Drh https://t.co/RhGdZw70m6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IDAHO COVID-19 HOT SPOTS: The 3 counties with the highest COVID-19 infection rates in Idaho include Elmore, Shoshone, and Teton. They have a 7-day moving average incidence rates of 28, 18.9, and 17.6 per 100,000 people respectively. https://t.co/Rh8jhn5vLd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 997,994 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 585,090 people have received vaccine and 444,371 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This afternoon, CDCs Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) voted to lift the pause on the Johnson  Johnson COVID-19 vaccine and resume administering it in the U.S. to everyone 18+. Idaho is reviewing the recommendation and more information will be forthcoming. https://t.co/wqcCHhHe9l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After you are fully vaccinated, you can travel with fewer restrictions. CDC says fully vaccinated people can travel domestically without a pre- or post-travel test, and without quarantining after travel. More information: https://t.co/0EOiwYmeiP https://t.co/9xI9qua8yF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDHidaho: @SaintAlsHealth has a new Mobile Vaccine Unit (MVU) making COVID-19 Vaccines widely available in rural Idaho communities. On]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KTVB: Saint Alphonsus offering walk-in COVID-19 vaccine clinic in Meridian https://t.co/4UAyT2c9qC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The weekly summary of long-term care facilities with COVID-19 is now available:  https://t.co/H9NzbrKyD4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An Update from DHW Director Dave Jeppesen: Are you fully vaccinated? https://t.co/aqx0pQUGi6 via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The percentage of PCR COVID-19 tests performed statewide between 4/11 and 4/17 that were positive is 4.7% -- the same as the week before.   Among Idaho's 44 counties, 25 saw a decrease in percent positivity compared to the previous week and 6 remained unchanged at 0%. https://t.co/SCMiCH80jV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(2/2) More information: https://t.co/0EOiwYmeiP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(1/2) After you are fully vaccinated, you can ditch the mask when you gather with other fully-vaccinated people! CDC says fully vaccinated people can visit inside a home or private setting without a mask with other fully vaccinated people of any age. https://t.co/qjeFV1p4cO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone 16 and older who lives or works in Idaho can get the COVID-19 vaccine. And its free  there are no out-of-pocket costs to anyone who gets the vaccine. Find a provider today! https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its Earth Day and beautiful Idaho is in bloom! Get out there and celebrate with a walk or hike and take in the views. #HealthyLifestyle #EarthDay https://t.co/ideiXnqMBu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 973,157 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 577,163 people have received vaccine and 427,411 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(2/2) More information: https://t.co/0EOiwYmeiP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(1/2) After you are fully vaccinated, you can hug your grandchildren! CDC says you can gather indoors with unvaccinated people of any age from one other household without masks or staying 6 feet apart, unless anyone has an increased risk of severe illness from COVID-19. https://t.co/JFA7cQT0Q9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its impossible to know how COVID-19 will affect you. All of the COVID-19 vaccines effectively prevent serious illness and hospitalization. Please sign up to get your shot today. https://t.co/qEpq43Prcu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. TODAY on Facebook Live: DHW's Dr. Christin Hahn will answer questions about COVID-19 vaccines, including whether they can cause infertility, how they got approved so quickly, whether mRNA vaccines alter your DNA, and more. https://t.co/VMYvJp7InM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over the past week, Idaho has reported 1,555 new cases of COVID-19 and 22 COVID-19-related deaths. There have been a total of 185,465 confirmed COVID-19 cases and 2,022 COVID-19-related deaths since the start of the pandemic. Details at https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. Wednesday on Facebook Live: DHW's Dr. Christin Hahn will answer questions about COVID-19 vaccines, including whether they can cause infertility, how they got approved so quickly, whether mRNA vaccines alter your DNA, and more. https://t.co/VMYvJppjfk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The recording of today's media briefing on COVID-19 in Idaho is available: https://t.co/vASKcK5Woh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 QA: Vaccine safety https://t.co/JX84ElqJw0 via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: As of April 13, there have been no reports to VAERS of people having blood clots with low platelets after Pfizer-BioNTech or Mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 infections range from mild to serious, to even death. COVID-19 vaccination prevents the worst from happening. Please sign up to get your shot today. https://t.co/qEpq43xPNU https://t.co/Dx6LM2Wh2n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 2018, 14.7% of Idahoans were smokers, and 4.4% were smokeless tobacco users. Both smoking and smokeless tobacco use were less common among those 65 years of age and older.  For more statistics on substance use in Idaho in 2018 see the new fact sheet: https://t.co/7Y1u3k8Dpk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 953,914 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 570,163 people have received vaccine and 415,128 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Expanded pandemic aid is now available to current and former foster youth. That includes temporary room and board assistance, transportation funding, and higher education aid, among other services. Find out if youre eligible: https://t.co/O0Fjj12WZK https://t.co/62PhcCXp0x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Aaron Campbell recommends his patients get the COVID-19 vaccine because it's our best shot to get things back to normal. Watch: https://t.co/GZtUrRczpn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Milestone reached: More than 400,000 people who live or work in Idaho are now fully vaccinated. Way to go Idaho! An additional 155,035 people have received one dose of a two-dose series in Idaho. Pre-register for your vaccine appointment: https://t.co/PZjHFVpMML https://t.co/TDKhjLhGkv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 media briefing set for Tuesday: https://t.co/w9RpgPpQn4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(2/2) A total of breakthrough cases in Idaho are posted on the COVID-19 Case, Laboratory, and Hospital Data Dashboard on the "statewide demographics" tab. https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(1/2) Idaho has a total of 154 reported breakthrough cases, which is .04% of fully vaccinated people. Of those, four were hospitalized. All of the hospitalized patients had medical conditions that made them high-risk for severe illness. There have been no deaths.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your life matters. Knowing your #HIV status is a key step to taking charge of your health. Learn more about getting a free HIV self-test right at your doorstep: https://t.co/Uzh2OkExpd #StopHIVTogether #NTHTD #CDCTransHealth https://t.co/ctuWdXegkj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IDAHO COVID-19 HOT SPOTS: The 3 counties with the highest COVID-19 infection rates in Idaho include Elmore, Bonneville, and Jefferson. They have a 7-day moving average incidence rates of 28, 21.1, and 17.7 per 100,000 people respectively. https://t.co/n8w6Ac8fM9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 927,665 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 559,968 people have received vaccine and 399,110 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DYK? 1 in 5 people in the U.S. have an STD. Know your #STD care options so you can continue to #TalkTestTreat  during COVID-19 and beyond. https://t.co/Tov1oMwxtP #STDWeek https://t.co/YGdjuzTM17]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The weekly summary of long-term care facilities with COVID-19 is now available:  https://t.co/H9NzbrsXLw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An Update from DHW Director Dave Jeppesen: Johnson  Johnson Vaccine https://t.co/rSHDFqbVUK via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking for an appointment to get COVID-19 vaccine? Use Idahos COVID-19 Vaccination Pre-Registration System to get on a list, and a provider will call you soon! https://t.co/PZjHFVHobl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is good news, but we must not be complacent. Notably, 20 of Idaho's 44 counties saw increases in percent positivity compared with the previous week. This may mean that the state is heading towards another increase overall. More data at https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The percentage of PCR COVID-19 tests performed statewide between 4/4 and 4/10 that were positive is 4.8. That's down from 5.6% the week before.   The statewide decrease in % positivity is largely due to a decrease of 7 percentage points in Idaho's Eastern Health District. https://t.co/XZQQsLHa8T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The recommendation to pause administration of the JJ vaccine is still in place for Idaho. The CDCs Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) met Wednesday but did not put forth any formal recommendations. ACIP plans to meet again next week: https://t.co/K09U9OOJNI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Frontline workers, youve been keeping us all safe, informed, and fed. Its our turn to take care of you. Contact us for free services and counseling for your emotional, physical, and financial health. https://t.co/pnU3jSBJp0 https://t.co/WiCa9TB8fX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres a striking fact for STD Awareness Week: Once nearing elimination, syphilis has made a comeback. Learn more about the resurgence of syphilis and what you can do to combat it: https://t.co/izv2NCRIOf #SyphilisStrikesBack #STDWeek https://t.co/fTaT7atjp9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 Case, Laboratory, and Hospital Data Dashboard has been updated. We apologize for the delay: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Due to technical difficulties there is a delay in updating the COVID-19 Case, Laboratory, and Hospital Data Dashboard today. We apologize for any inconvenience. Please check back later for updates: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 897,995 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 548,760 people have received vaccine and 380,191 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In case you missed it: Deputy state epidemiologist Dr. Kathryn Turner answered questions about the temporary pause in the administration of the Johnson  Johnson vaccine in Idaho and the nation: https://t.co/VMYvJppjfk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ALL pregnant women should be tested for #syphilis once, BUT one test is not enough for EVERY woman. More info: https://t.co/u6rdnBhpXs #SyphilisStrikesBack #STDWeek https://t.co/aYgidksec6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The recording of this week's COVID-19 media briefing is now available: https://t.co/LMWw4YN91n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. TODAY on Facebook Live: Deputy state epidemiologist Dr. Kathryn Turner will answer questions about the temporary pause in the administration of the Johnson  Johnson vaccine in Idaho and the nation. Join us!  https://t.co/VMYvJp7InM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 886,210 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 544,163 people have received vaccine and 372,534 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us at 10 a.m. Wednesday on Facebook Live: Deputy state epidemiologist Dr. Kathryn Turner will answer questions about the temporary pause in the administration of the Johnson  Johnson vaccine in Idaho and the nation: https://t.co/VMYvJppjfk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 QA: Johnson  Johnson vaccine and severe adverse effects https://t.co/hIRVxcrQju via @IDHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congenital #syphilis occurs when a mother with syphilis passes it on to her baby during pregnancy. Learn more: https://t.co/AF28csgeds. #SyphilisStrikesBack #STDWeek https://t.co/DG8xbz72TU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AARPIdaho: Our  #coronavirus town hall discussion with @GovernorLittle begins in just a few minutes. You can join the discussion here:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DHW recommends Idaho providers follow FDA and CDC guidance to temporarily pause administering the Johnson  Johnson vaccine: https://t.co/9z8RxvvFvz https://t.co/V07qUCUL9s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To date, a total of 875,182 doses of COVID-19 vaccine have been administered in Idaho. 538,763 people have received vaccine and 365,444 people are now fully vaccinated in the state. More data: https://t.co/BYu73fcA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Idaho is reporting 130 breakthrough cases. Of them, three were hospitalized. All of the hospitalized patients had medical conditions that made them high-risk for severe illness. There have been no deaths. https://t.co/Lq2MWkVxzx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talk openly to your partner AND healthcare provider about #sexualhealth  #STDs: https://t.co/p9PZofmy1v #TalkTestTreat #STDWeek https://t.co/QfYE3LVAeG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 media briefing set for 4:30 p.m. Tuesday: https://t.co/9muyFpr8zD]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>