<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/WIkXaMPdm8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZChronicNebula https://t.co/SiCBCMsYMs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AP4Liberty: "The mask has become the MAGA hat of liberals." -@JustinJPetersen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost https://t.co/mQZX38W2vP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KabbalahR47 If you still have a doubt about football being rigged after that on side kick ive got a "15 days to slow the curve" for you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias You have to have your head buried in your ass to believe ANYTHING IN THE MAINSTREAM. TOTAL FAKERY WAKE THE FUCK UP AMERICA https://t.co/CHnIgQx77j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SulleyTruman: When the meme says it all... https://t.co/9o0EkhvbkD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Urylle: The Baphomet-like Twin Towers (Knights Templar Order) has now become ONE through the plandemic. Into the rebirth     ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LBF777: Transgender Couple Bill and Melinda Gates divorcing. There must be more to this.   https://t.co/O9e2HSbs6Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KabbalahR47 Free burger with your death certificate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @911b0t: https://t.co/F25dbOvrus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @argonerd: https://t.co/uGiQebAHNE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NFL Draft Round 3 Pick 65 (pandemic=65/38) 4 and 38 both death numbers  Could "3rd wave" actually be legit? Time will tell. https://t.co/BKPLSfzOqV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indian 2nd wave Covid HOAX Confirmed https://t.co/KhHbig12ks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HeadRushV2: We live in a scripted reality, already planned out. And there's nothing you can do about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/8c17hfPaC9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @33YouSee: Men with shanks made the plane crash into Shanksville!    Unbelievable! https://t.co/RLqcpG7YgQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZChronicNebula:  @POWERADE commercial  https://t.co/RDgcwClfv4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SocialDistancing https://t.co/1Ep6iFTek5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/SUPLKG5il3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Liz_Wheeler: Joe Rogan is correct about the COVID vaccine for kids  young healthy people.  https://t.co/AxGwFxAMVB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DarnelSugarfoo: If you need a good laugh today, this is legit one of the funniest videos I've seen in a long time. I've watched it mult]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NextLevelShittt: cant you see whats goin on here ?? https://t.co/F6VzGWID5f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lukewearechange: Someone is lying here https://t.co/hvVn8yQyU8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieEmmaUK: This should frighten the hell out of everybody.  What having a digital ID means and living with a social credit score lo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@reallygraceful @HeadRushV2 https://t.co/0YkYzwqvoj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mhmed_xo ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1st "Super Moon" of the year Monday night "around 11:33"  https://t.co/LnUY4EKDVc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @USlawreview: If you're still arguing about red v blue you're living in a fantasy land and you're just perpetuating the problems you cla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Next Plandemic  https://t.co/d3XsMKT8lr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesCatagn10: What the world is experiencing in 2021 and going forward is a manmade EXTINCTION LEVEL EVENT via an ongoing series of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thebigfella18: dear sheep  ...please let this repeat over and over and over again...till something finally clicks in that little tiny b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Put them on a hook, they are harmless, unlike your TRASH PROPAGANDA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @An0nK3k: https://t.co/rGLIrmo6h2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MucciTina: The only thing that needs to be changed with this sign is replacing va((ine with experimental  gene therapy drug. https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skolgang55 If I get a hole in my jeans, my wife throws them out. When we go out, she wears jeans with holes in them. https://t.co/NJ8Hu1Sf06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdrianoMazzola: Well well well https://t.co/GwcPBZpMQa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HeadRushV2: https://t.co/7cZqOhrrg9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WarpOperation: https://t.co/jvn2Qq903n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: Break loyalty to the family, and replace it with loyalty to the system. This is what is being taught in your public scho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dnvihN5sdo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Definitely not a satanic ritual https://t.co/gByY1TqPG6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/4IW3HfuxFk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4:02 post time in a blatantly racist fake story. 42=n word  Just like when the black woman accidentally used "gorilla glue" in her hair, anothe fake story. https://t.co/XF0wGEDdwJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OrganicLiveFood: Studies suggest #turmeric is as effective as 14 #pharmaceutical #drugs: https://t.co/NE4cl2jKFf Turmeric can also lowe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/g99zr26jaz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going out amongst the public nowadays   https://t.co/Hm7U9upgRw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @occultb0t: https://t.co/dnHvs3rp9H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philthese @skolgang55 They put it right in front of your eyes. This is from campaign trail https://t.co/l66VIwUHOU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@The_Trxth https://t.co/H6ArlwB3f5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bungeeallday: https://t.co/crsyCXHcZR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KabbalahR47 Could it be more obvious?????? Thats a "security camera" from house across street?? That happens to have the scene PERFECTLY CENTERED with crystal clear audio???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the universe looks like from Earth vs what it looks like on TV.  #SpaceX https://t.co/Uqe50qEjV0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet The Agenda is clear https://t.co/09DljO4fws]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every time I see these FRAUDS at NASA,  I think of the movie Spaceballs . Its really no different. https://t.co/1SR3l0t9sG https://t.co/S4BXlqEQ8g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off https://t.co/f29t6q92um]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WarpOperation: always the secret society numbers. 322 Skull   Bones  https://t.co/ftvtPfL4yl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@USlawreview Senator in 20 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skolgang55 "IT'S NOT THE JESUITS" https://t.co/uLkyLwPOk0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Urylle: Martin Luther King Jr. speaks at Jesuit St. Peter's College and receives degree (Sept. 22 1965)  King was used by the Vatican]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SulleyTruman: https://t.co/Iz2iNVbPAb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bring in the robot police https://t.co/4nhCH9NA9w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is to push the "right" further to the right and say "we need more police"  Just had a guilty cop in Floyd case  Same day cop shoots teenage girl about to stab other girl in another staged psyop and cop is under scrutiny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Psyops everyday  Antifa vs Police in Portland  102 minute video (reflection of 201) Cop has ORANGE ID tag displaying (75777) 7+5+7+7+7=33 Orange=33, 102 Police =102 #propaganda #orderoutofchaos  https://t.co/ZzLHxnrujo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffsekerak: I got injected! Great! You just gave up your sovereignty. Spit in the face of God. Wrecked your immune system for life. Se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @occultb0t: https://t.co/27cOvnGJJZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Urylle: William Cooper Interviews a 32nd Degree Freemason of the Scottish Rite - Southern Jurisdiction:  The Knights of Malta ALL have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Urylle Coincidentally KKK cross very similar. Also KKK=33 https://t.co/IzYCFbnnex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bs_doe @Urylle And Ponzi Scheme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Urylle: She was also killed on TEMPLAR ST The Knights Templar is the Masonic  military order that puts all of these scripted events to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bevvie112 Shot 4 times up against car. No blood or damage to car Video here https://t.co/0TwsSROhr7 https://t.co/aBepmX3jjv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dusty6516: @Antk32107571 In case anyone thinks the pics are fake. Heres video. https://t.co/pOAjLDJX5f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Body cam released in latest police shooting. He puts 4 in her. I dont see blood. The car didnt get bloody or shot up https://t.co/0TwsSROhr7 https://t.co/XvC5DYWrdY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Seekthetruth101: Its at the point which, they know we know , they know we can see   But do not care , theyre just flexing on us knowi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DJcalligraphy: Kamala Harris has the neck of a linebacker... https://t.co/1z0cyNREpb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SulleyTruman: https://t.co/HabazzKe4v https://t.co/3kMkn6xjJi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[330 days of the Floyd case.  Verdict given at 3:30  Now the sentencing will be given in 8 weeks, or 56 days ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone these days has a Ring doorbell camera, floodlight cameras, baby cameras, THEY LOVE THE SURVEILLANCE   The Mask, the vaccine, turns out most loosers LOVE THEM TOO, stand in line for days for the poison.  The CHIP is next, and the walking dead will beg for that as well https://t.co/DEXW4lHKwr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @skolgang55:  https://t.co/wA3wLTSjlR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Six herpes cases from the  SIX https://t.co/jwXau6Mxpi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Acadiansheperd: 2nd degree manslaughter 2nd degree murder  3rd degree murder  223/322 ,,,,,   https://t.co/T2RRYOW6mv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KabbalahR47 These actors are lazy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday, 4/19 it was Pippen's kid, on anniversary of Oklahoma City Bombing where 19 children were killed  Today a 15 year old REPORTEDLY killed on the 22 year anniversary of Columbine  "Massacre" that killed 15 https://t.co/IXrPSFG0EC https://t.co/VuqXOPkU2w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wCCE7JTs9O https://t.co/75etuqlZYU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JPK553 "Pyramid Shaped UFO" ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chauvin Guilty, looks like the Aliens are next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Black community finally gets a Win in Floyd case right when the government starts eliminating them with the ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: After 100 years the Rockefeller "project" has finally been completed. Not ONE free and independent voice at ANY universi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Video of Minneapolis church fire being set https://t.co/Adh0ks6RQT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeadRushV2 Its like when u give a kid a video game controller that isnt synced to let them think they are playing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jayunk12: @HeadRushV2 https://t.co/wzzraSPOxk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @107devorah: @Hazels_Vibes @CROWSPLAY1 @FatEmperor @Albion_Rover @davidkurten @HighWireTalk @TheFreds @JuliaHB1 @SueC00K @CharlesWalkerM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol back in the day me and my buddies would do this exact 2 finger double tap as code that you had to drop a deuce https://t.co/NCtaFYc2SL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeadRushV2 1 Day before https://t.co/9gjRbDVD29]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KabbalahR47 @2LarryJohnson7 The Bull https://t.co/qU3jsllVqL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @2LarryJohnson7: ....I like making people look stupid.  Exodus 22:29 (4):(11) 44 Gematria English Kill 44 Satan is the God of this wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sick  https://t.co/Sbu69n1Rja]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyb0t I thought CON-gress took care of big tech for us  MUAHAHAHA #censorship https://t.co/x98NM3msfq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay safe  https://t.co/OPrd7ANbJU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Mars" helicopter https://t.co/IkA6eH1RVC https://t.co/z1XQaY4YoE]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>