<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SallyMayweather: If it cant be questioned its propaganda, not science.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trad_revival: If prestige was an animal: https://t.co/au7P1U2L9j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KaptainKronos: @Zombie_Land21 It's the gift that keeps on giving. We'll look back in 10 years and still be giggling. Here's another....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @24hrvacation: The beautiful village of Lauterbrunnen, Switzerland. https://t.co/yLHsO5dU9s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @7tine76: Now they've got photographers telling you how to see photos.  wake up people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CFontainebleau:  '   | Le 5 mai 1821, il y a 200 ans, #Napoleon s'teint sur l'le de Sainte-Hlne aprs avoir livr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Teens face homicide charges in rape, murder of Ee Lee https://t.co/vomDEqRl5b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Breaking911: Burglary suspect found hiding in bathroom told cops he saw the woman walk into her home and he wanted to rape her: Deputie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Architectolder: Also Hell https://t.co/lKpintoMzG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @heywildrich: we shouldn't have to live this way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryMakow: Nevada womans first medical bill after JJ shot was $513,000 -  https://t.co/0Dh9hSgPgo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lordgreyofponty: This ends when the public rediscovers how to think.  I think we are in for a long wait....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trad_revival: Rome's beautiful Galleria Sciarra  https://t.co/Mne6nyfyou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoshLekach: Men have been weak for a while; the "pandemic" activated them.   Do the insane and irrational outnumber us?  "Not wearing a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @disclosetv: #TheBigLie: Iraq  Weapons of Mass Destruction https://t.co/7B6igk1tuB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SchwabBum: Sad reality in the UK right now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lporiginalg: https://t.co/XXNovDkCng]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PutOutMoreFlags: https://t.co/UUoITjU0cc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PatriotActive66: Another church fire in France https://t.co/tkkyA5Wxi3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RedPilledPoland: 532 African boat migrants on 4 boats arrived to the Italian island #Lampedusa overnight. Another 236 African migrants]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy10: Primark Merry Hill Shopping Centre https://t.co/melt8rpf68]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: Oh look! But wasnt planned or anything.  https://t.co/f8sWEaYQSv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DackStevon: Get the vaccine. If you wont do it for yourself, do it for Eddie Vedder and Jennifer Lopez. https://t.co/u5fi1TDmrq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @buitengebieden_: Impressive leap!  https://t.co/VNL4bzhhl8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Architectolder: Chteau de Chantilly. This would be a wonderful day. https://t.co/D2kYLuPUqu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickGriffinBU: Great to see other people joining my long-standing effort to raise awareness of the #KalergiPlan https://t.co/X2Fg2150no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpaceFromGreece: it is difficult to believe that a single tree was harmed to build this absolute modernist - brutalist HORROR  @Archite]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScottMGreer: Let's check on the yes-fly list]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HousesVictorian: Charming home inside the Chateau de Monte-Cristo, former residence of Alexandre Dumas near Paris. https://t.co/ox5c88j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UcjaSylwia: Nie tylko kobiety si szpec  https://t.co/KcjeQ1bxhk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JasonBermas: I have been harping on this through my entire career! They shot HEMOPHILIACS many of which were CHILDREN with Factor 8 in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlisonFisk: A spectacular pair of gold bracelets with inset amethysts. From Karditsa, Thessaly. 1st century BC. Part of the so-called P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AOBPSF: #BREAKING  ALERT: At least 37 people have been killed and dozens critically injured at a mass stampede during Lag BOmer celebr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Architectolder: Elegy. Bouguereau https://t.co/WAYojv3sph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ParisAMDParis: Rue Charlemagne. Le Marais populaire  1950s   #Paris 4me https://t.co/LoCDYHQZN2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChurchPictures8: Siena Cathedral (Metropolitan Cathedral of Saint Mary of the Assumption) https://t.co/CIzInvqN2c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ParisAMDParis: Ervin Marton.  la terrasse du Petit bar  1950  #Paris https://t.co/i9oCQySkkD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UrbainNatacha: Chef des armes franaises https://t.co/7pxWsST4gG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LadyMercia: Child rapist who kidnapped schoolgirl suffers 'lifechanging injuries' in prison https://t.co/qGRaFsOrtb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lporiginalg: https://t.co/4FgMi5K4Hk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @umustrise: India  In the midst of an Alleged Catastrophic wave of devastating Covid19, the Police have the time to release A Covid19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SchwabBum: Im sure Ive seen this tweet somewhere before. Its a good one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SamWhiteTky: Something's gone wrong when adults are getting stickers for going to the doctor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Incoherent speech plus the 2 muzzled btches in back, awful ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CamilleVernier1: Ceux qui votent communiste          En thorie     /    En pratique https://t.co/kX9sjOD0ls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Trad_West_Art: Joseph Severn - The Abdication of Mary, Queen of Scots (c.1850) https://t.co/XOVwI3CQvT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wayotworld Used to respect them.. No more.. Hate them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wayotworld: Never forget that the police are NOT your friends. The police are hired thugs for the same traitorous governments that are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wC8OoG8tXr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My pics from 13th century Royaumont abbey, France https://t.co/w7wiskAeXW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How they think https://t.co/929MJEV5x4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big wedding fun... https://t.co/dEg7XixdhK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes I know, I'm Polish, but don't over abuse https://t.co/nacZjjrnaV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not a fan of little boats https://t.co/sYnBAn1eFj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fave dog https://t.co/DZBmvqxbGV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cool those malinois https://t.co/Eh6VmWCtdO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baaaaah https://t.co/hvShZIZVHp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Housebound for a few days so will be posting my fave gifs, non political or covid related]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@STEPHENHARI @FatEmperor @M4ttmc87 @mjack15 @SaraHaboubi1 Somewhat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ReadMoreBible I've always thought so, particularly now.: educate my children/family/friends about the scamdemic program]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ramzpaul: Hey, at least they are safe from a virus that statistically has a 0% chance to kill them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: https://t.co/VWjrFyYxh1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@STEPHENHARI @FatEmperor @M4ttmc87 @mjack15 @SaraHaboubi1 I'm guessing we all know it has nothing to do with a virus. Or cases. Right??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef Fake all along. Thanks WEF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwanOfTuonela Ewwww lol.  What lengths will they go to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I believe they need way more than an experimental covid jab https://t.co/sKllji1i0j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: (def.) mask wearing : In the 21st century the medical establishment recommended prolonged breathing through a personal m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SchwabBum @Biene58149667 "If we can save just one life, it's worth it" mouhahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paleocon_USA @housewife8888 90% of people are non questioning idiots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trad_West_Art Absolutely! Deleted it 6 years ago]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AQuantumCat1 Gross. Manly looking broad.  Guess she had to be in underwear to try n fool us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Architectolder: Dresden https://t.co/LclamsxVWo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @decent_doge Someone?! is making loads of from these fraud tests https://t.co/VogFBWzYgX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PutOutMoreFlags I loved that car!  But after 4th child lacked a seat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PutOutMoreFlags: https://t.co/jNyQoqP4q8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @USlawreview: It's now been 15 months of non-stop corona theater. Yet the vast majority of the people have STILL never even heard of Eve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trad_revival: France  has over 45,000 castles, it would take 123 years to visit them all. (1  / day) https://t.co/XnM256hJcm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @a_centrism: A black girl has a blood cancer, and a marrow registry wisely asks for blood donations from black people.   But having been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @realjohnmonarch: Insane statistic I didnt know until today:  Acetaminophen/Paracetamol/Tylenol causes 50% of all liver failure in the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: It doesnt make you an anti-vaxxer to think its insane to hold the country for ransom for over a year just to have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @exposing_white: Jerry Pastore,57, owned Shamrock Deli in Audubon,NJ.When a man looking for job was told he didnt need any help,he deci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: Australia news live: NSW man, 55, reported to have died of blood clots after receiving Covid vaccine https://t.co/rhczd9RVqP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @USlawreview: There is NOTHING that your Govt  media will not do  say to you in order to advance their agenda. NOTHING.   People refus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johncardillo Evil i$ right. Also can't believe that parents listen to him and muzzle their children]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FitFounder Are you kidding?  I do the opposite]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost European Union did this 2 years ago.  Following the plan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simsy1977 One is a lot imo.  None for me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SchwabBum Still no one. Zero. Zilch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @France24_en: Paris prosecutors seek involuntary manslaughter charges over AstraZeneca deaths https://t.co/oVph0crQcn https://t.co/AG4zR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StupidWhiteAds $54,000 a year girls school ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: The conditioning is strong with this one! https://t.co/pNbXfE6ucW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisWickNews: The media is the virus, peoples fear is the real pandemic and peoples ignorance is our greatest tragedy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryMakow: A plandemic costs less than a nuclear holocaust. There is no destruction of infrastructure and cities. It increases availab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ParisAMDParis: Rue de Rivoli   c.1950  #Paris https://t.co/5ITdOibKsR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ramzpaul: Just give them knives or spears and let them go at it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lukewearechange: Just an average day in NYC https://t.co/vYyjiqfKk9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StraydogI7: Riiight! https://t.co/rJptuCib1B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_whitneywebb: If you think the government will let you go back to normal after their targets are met for covid vaccinations, I encourag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ParisAMDParis: Champs-lyses  1970  #Paris  Pinterest #photograghy https://t.co/hfTVghNIHj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @umustrise:  Australian Cricketers Dave Warner and Jane Williamson, join in on the Indian Covid19 Propaganda. Wearing fake PPE on a fl]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>