<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Trudeau suggests Canadians could begin travelling outside the country again by summer. He also said Canada will align with other countries on any documents needed to prove vaccinations against COVID-19. https://t.co/zL72ssbOcn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The mayor of an Alberta town is hoping authorities can rope in a maverick rodeo movement after thousands showed up to the anti-lockdown event. https://t.co/Q7etE1yNfj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An Alberta woman has died after receiving the AstraZeneca vaccine, according to Alberta's chief medical officer of health. https://t.co/bdoDqGusQ5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta has introduced a series of tougher public health restrictions to combat an alarming surge in COVID-19 cases. But what do Albertans think of the new measures? @LauraKrauseNews has the story. https://t.co/5QKehVNX8Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From schools to small businesses, most Albertans are affected by the province's new restrictions. @CityTara reports. https://t.co/AuxGqVCiYx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: More than 1,300 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been put into the arms of Metis Albertans at a clinic in Edmonton over the last four days. https://t.co/5ruCWXnONJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Suncor Energy will delay a planned maintenance shutdown at its Base Plant oilsands mine upgrader in view of surging COVID-19 outbreaks. https://t.co/Fs413pjlQr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: BREAKING:  Alberta confirms a woman in her 50s has died from VITT following an AztraZeneca vaccine.   It's the first death t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: A prominent Texas doctor is urging the United States to do more to help Canadians get vaccinated against COVID-19. https://t.co/GdLhAb63dz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For the first time, Vancouver proclaimed May 5 as Day of the Midwife. But as Kier Junos reports, while the day celebrates midwives, it also calls attention to the increased demand for midwife services during the pandemic. https://t.co/X4i1BETiVm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Continuing his pattern of overpromising and under delivering': Notley responds to new restrictions https://t.co/Hsz8CbEswS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Business Report: Vehicle sales have shifted back into high gear, despite the pandemic. Plus, how will Bill and Melinda Gates split their fortune in divorce proceedings?  https://t.co/entBbCbYrp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney is using May 4 to provide new details about its upcoming Star Wars themed hotel. Plus, Will Smith proudly shows off his dad bod. https://t.co/3DWNVmyuqb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Raptors are taking on former teammate Kawhi Leonard and the Clippers tonight in a must-win game. Lindsay Dunn looks at the probability of the team making the post-season. https://t.co/hfFB7VQQv3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Kenney QA time!  Can kids go to school Friday?   Kenney says Thursday is last day for in-class instruction until May 25th.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Why not open vaccines to all ages?  Kenney says "hopefully this week" they will be making this announcement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would an Atlantic-style bubble help Alberta slow the spread of COVID-19? https://t.co/Ds5M8Ss4rp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Do you want a new base of supporters? (!!!)  Kenney says it comes from a false story about things he said in caucus.   Kenne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seven churches and three individuals in Manitoba are challenging the province's pandemic restrictions, saying they violate their charter freedoms. https://t.co/lxkVMFADdW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Conservatives want the prime minister to fire his top advisor, accusing her of mishandling allegations of sexual misconduct against a former top soldier. Nigel Newlove reports. https://t.co/oWIE0Jg1tf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: "Stop the spike" website is live.   #yeg #yyc #ableg #covid19ab   https://t.co/EeRS4Kqtq1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: "You get your first rodeo free."  NDP leader Rachel Notley raising concerns over Alberta's new COVID enforcement plan.   #ye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Health officials are trying to explain after NACI told Canadians they can wait for an mRNA dose if they dont feel theyre at high risk for COVID-19. https://t.co/TujjWZ9EbE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Notley says Kenney has a an "obligation" to take questions from media after announcement.   Says it's because there are so m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: "You get your first rodeo free."  Notley says that by focusing on repeat offenders with new enforcement measures, it becomes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Heads up.   Your brunch viewing for Wednesday morning as Premier Kenney takes questions on new public health measures.  (The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Notley says Alberta needs a leader they can trust, and one who makes decision based on science and evidence and not politica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Notley says he believes that Kenney is "overwhelmed by the challenge of the situation."  Says the people of the province des]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Rachel Notley is calling for Premier Kenney to kick UCP MLAs who publicly oppose his measures out of caucus.   #yeg #yyc #ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One of the key justifications by premier Jason Kenney in announcing new restrictions Tuesday is surge capacity in the ICU.  Dr. Noel Gibney reminds if you get in a severe vehicle collision "you're going to need an ICU, whether you believe in COVID or not." https://t.co/rUzawXIkih]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: "Our caucus would pass a bill on sick pay in a matter of hours if only the premier would take the padlock of the legislature]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Notley is calling for greater support to be provided to small businesses and changing the threshold to qualify for got assis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Notley says Kenney sat on his hands as school boards, parents and students asked for help before schools were shut down.   S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Notley points to the announcement that the measures will last for two or three weeks.   Notley says this is confusing, creat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: For example, gathering limits are being shifted today down to 5.   Currently, the most recent update on gathering limits is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Looking for the updated "stop the spike" website that the Premier referenced so you can get more details on today's announce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: NEW:   Here's the extensive list of new public health measures being enacted in Alberta.   #yeg #yyc #ableg #covid19ab https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: BUT!  Alberta regions that don't meet the 'hot spot' definition will roll back to a different set of restrictions - not as s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Rachel Notley says the Premier is overpromising and underdelivering by making false promises and false hope, setting up furt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: The province says they are increasing COVID fines and focusing on repeat offenders.  But the language remains vague in terms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lawyers claim Alberta's COVID-19 restrictions violated pastor's charter rights. https://t.co/qEeWON7lSh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: NDP leader Rachel Notley reacts to new provincial restrictions https://t.co/aOaI0dLAxB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Recap - All schools closed for at least 2 weeks - Restos/patios closed to in-person dining for 3 weeks - Hair/Nails also clo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: What do you make of the new public health measures announced by Jason Kenney in Alberta?   #yeG #yyc #ableg #Covid19ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: NEW:   Alberta doubles max COVID fines up to $2000.   #yeg #yyc #ableg #covid19ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: BREAKING:   As of Sunday, personal services (ie hair, tattoo, nail, tanning) will close for three weeks.   In-person dining]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: BREAKING:   Retail services now reduced to 10% of fire capacity.   Outdoor social gatherings limited to 5.   Place of worshi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: BREAKING:   Workplaces with COVID outbreaks will be forced to close for 10 days, with the exception of critical workplaces.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: NEW:   Alberta announces all schools will go online this Friday until at least May 25.  #yeG #yyc #ableg #covid19ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Kenney says the arrival of variants in Alberta is putting pressure on our health care system despite vaccines administered t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Premier Jason Kenney announces new provincial restrictions. https://t.co/cjJ2gJASeY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trudeau says he believes his own Liberal MPs and politicians from all parties need to do better to create safer spaces for victims of sexual assault and harassment. https://t.co/cWFi9HTyo6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta has identified 1,743 new cases of COVID-19, 876 of which are variants of concern. The province has also identified an additional case of the B.1.617 variant, the strain that has wreaked havoc in India. https://t.co/syXwSqvjpl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta schools to go online, retail capacity reduced, restaurants back to take-out only: sources https://t.co/SyuHRAhhGO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fifteen young climate activists are taking their court battle to the next level as they try to compel the Canadian government to develop a climate recovery plan based on science. https://t.co/3GWeXvfmoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An air passenger rights advocate says he flagged problems with refund rules to Ottawa more than a year before authorities said the pandemic brought the issues to light. https://t.co/rGnOZz8ahL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: NEW:   - 1743 new COVID cases in Alberta on 14585 (12%+) - 671 in hospital (+13), 150 in ICU (-4) - 9 new deaths -23,623 act]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau will issue a formal apology this month to the families of Italian-Canadians placed in interment camps during World War II. https://t.co/WLbhfe8HjD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trudeau suggests Canadians could begin travelling outside the country again by summer. He also said Canada will align with other countries on any documents needed to prove vaccinations against COVID-19. https://t.co/zL72ssbOcn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two brothers at a Montreal-based comic book company are suing Marvel Entertainment -- again. They say some Marvel characters have body armour strikingly similar to the clothing they created for their superheroes. https://t.co/gs13lRe3QQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan, the Duchess of Sussex, is releasing her first childrens book entitled "The Bench."  https://t.co/HkSsFixcPR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A lawyer for pastor James Coates, who is accused of violating COVID-19 rules, says Alberta's health agency decided to penalize the church leader as a way to censor him. https://t.co/GEEiwJ737M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Quebec man has been arrested on human trafficking charges following a joint investigation between the Calgary Police Service and the Alberta Law Enforcement Response Team. https://t.co/KeNcHdGxtJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many parents across Canada say the federal governments plan to facilitate $10-a-day childcare across the country would completely change their financial lives. https://t.co/OC0OM0Rp8o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Liberals' firearms legislation is an offensively hollow bill," say family members of those who died in tragic shooting sprees at Montreals Dawson College and Concordia University. https://t.co/U5iAgTLuEK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ConocoPhillips plans to sell its roughly 10 per cent stake in Cenovus Energy Inc. as part of a plan to pay for a repurchase of its own shares. https://t.co/aX4cEJZylW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: Of course, the address is likely aimed to demonstrate the gravity of the situation in Alberta - although it does not allow f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: Premier to announce new restrictions in 6 p.m. address https://t.co/JWSQf9OFMX #yeg #yyc #ableg #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cspotweet: BREAKING:   Premier Jason Kenney will be announcing new public health measures via a televised address Tuesday night at 6 PM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@jkenney to speak just after 6:00 p.m. #yeg #yyc #ableg #abpoli https://t.co/aDDK0RdV0R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada is fast tracking yet another COVID-19 vaccine shipment. One million doses of Modernas shot are expected to arrive on Wednesday as opposed to next week. https://t.co/5pQnnRZ9go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In todays @thebigstoryfpn: Did the pandemic teach us how to tackle the climate crisis? https://t.co/08Q14O2uKh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 1,300 doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have been put into the arms of Metis Albertans at a clinic in Edmonton over the last four days. https://t.co/5ruCWXnONJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suncor Energy will delay a planned maintenance shutdown at its Base Plant oilsands mine upgrader in view of surging COVID-19 outbreaks. https://t.co/Fs413pjlQr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The National Advisory Committee on Immunization is coming under fire after contradicting the advice Canadians have been receiving for weeks to take the first vaccine against COVID-19 that theyre offered. https://t.co/zGkg4Ii19G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A prominent Texas doctor is urging the United States to do more to help Canadians get vaccinated against COVID-19. https://t.co/GdLhAb63dz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I just don't understand." Bowden mayor says he tried to see what could be done to prevent the "no lockdowns rodeo" over the weekend. https://t.co/jhZcF6pMLZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICU, critical care docs pen letter to Kenney begging for action to curb COVID-19 spread https://t.co/YYGXciqWQc #yeg #ableg #abpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CityRachelle: I'll be covering day 2 of the trial for James Coates. The pastor is on trial for violating Alberta's public health orders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and Health Canada provide COVID-19 update https://t.co/kFvl9xuhSR #cdnpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarlyDRobinson: Concern from the frontlines over staffing levels and ability to manage this wave of #COVID19AB without triage protocol.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kenney says new restrictions are coming, condemns those continuing to violate public health orders https://t.co/6FRvxudOEM #yeg #ableg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cmaconthehill: The latest #COVID19 numbers for Canada #cdnpoli https://t.co/MpFTj260Er]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The City of Edmonton approved alcohol consumption in some river valley parks. @LauraKrauseNews has the story. https://t.co/3t7Z6tBHtb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Strathcona County Emergency Services says the dry, spring weather sparks a risk for wildfires. https://t.co/lDbUdn9siF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Edmontonian finding new life for old video games https://t.co/P8kFktzKcP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertas third wave: a look behind the numbers https://t.co/9tW4R6fKgi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pandemic causing professional setbacks, shift in career attitudes: survey https://t.co/8zYYMMZKVy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kenney says new restrictions are coming, condemns those continuing to violate public health orders https://t.co/6FRvxuvq3m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is Asian heritage month. Lindsay Dunn speaks with Sportsnet NBA Editor Steven Loung about the growing racism towards Asian players in sports and how members of the sports community are trying to change that. https://t.co/xAvBwULSil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NACI says the Johnson  Johnson COVID-19 vaccine is recommended for adults over 30  and tries to explain its position, that Canadians do have the option of waiting for an mRNA vaccine, rather than getting AstraZeneca or JJ. @Xiaoli_3000 has more. https://t.co/kiqIuz9Fka]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadians are hoping a cure for MS is one step closer. Audra Brown reports on how the MS walk went virtual this year and how you can get involved. https://t.co/kQxGsN6iFG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the E.U. looks into easing non-essential travel, some experts say its almost time for Canada to follow suit with its own verion of a vaccine passport. Adrian Ghobrial looks at what that could look like and when it could happen. https://t.co/lofyPhXi3L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats happening in India and Brazil could happen elsewhere, warns the WHOs Director-General. @meldug on the global concern over surging coronavirus cases. https://t.co/CuPW5zM8JC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quebec report on youth protection calls for charter of children's rights https://t.co/JnTRPRclAI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When @aaronhoyland sent out a tweet looking for a charity to give a new life to his old video game console, he was inundated with response 26 and other's looking to donate.  @CarlyDRobinson has more on #YEGConsoleDrive. #yeg https://t.co/x5srq8y5ia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta pastor calls COVID-19 restrictions "sinful", admits to breaking public health orders https://t.co/BOtOpfS5Ic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Class dismissed for politicians  13 but nor for schools? Critics question Premier Kenney's motivations for shutting down the legislature. https://t.co/kojw6TXnek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 5,000 international air travellers positive for COVID-19 since February https://t.co/Rhd4OLtVX9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['I just don't understand:' Bowden mayor says he tried to see what could be done to prevent no-lockdown rodeo https://t.co/jhZcF6pMLZ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>