<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@zchagla @KindrachukJason @zeynep @KrutikaKuppalli @sci_questions But Id bet that a variant like B.1.1.7 with both a fitness and infectivity advantage that lead to more virus shedding AND higher receptor binding affinity would outcompete a variant like B.1.351 with only higher binding affinity in a mostly susceptible population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zchagla @KindrachukJason @zeynep @KrutikaKuppalli @sci_questions B.1.1.7 has both enhanced fitness and infectivity. B.1.351 doesnt seem to be as fit but has greater affinity for ACE2 in vitro  some ability to evade Ab neutralization though that might not matter depending on population immunity  other circulating variants in the community.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@onisillos @LancetMicrobe Celebrating in the fashion of my new country https://t.co/XLzdrpCYu8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notdred @ENirenberg I personally can't believe I omitted that, considering I was corresponding author on a letter to NEJM about it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jwgain01 So that's a little tougher and depends a lot on the community. Was there already a big surge of COVID, suggesting there's some natural population immunity that could augment vaccinated people? What current measures are in place to reduce transmission?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notdred https://t.co/CUvcMrN3F9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jwgain01 It depends a lot on the specific community, but in places where vaccination rates are high and transmission is steadily decreasing, a summer timeline makes sense. The challenge is avoiding premature reopening, as NY is doing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notdred The most infuriating part of this is that the person quoted relentlessly attributes all of her bad  incorrect takes to "optimism," as if that excuses saying things that are at best unproven  often demonstrably untrue.   Also see: herd immunity, regarding IPAC as optional, etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrMay5 @hawksninja I agree wholeheartedly with all these comments.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JessicaBourqui2 I think that if an "expert" thinks that a temporal and unsustained decrease in cases is evidence of reaching the herd immunity threshold, they are not an expert. Same thing if they think that because they think the herd immunity threshold is the target to relax precautions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CynthiaFlynn15 Don't get me started.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VikiLovesFACS @JoeRhisga @dr_barrett @stuartjdneil @StephenBDugmore @andrew_croxford @GidMK @SiouxsieW @HIVTox @GYamey Definitely not a stupid question, and something I indirectly work on. An immune response that clears a virus infection is not always "normal" and can lead to longer-term immune dysfunction. As Dr. Male says, this is an ongoing area of research in general.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobbDawson4 Don't dumb down a complex situation driven by multiple variables to a single explanation or excuse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reducing this emergency to a quip about variants or transmission not only fails to educate the public about the complexity of the crisis, but does a tremendous disservice to the people who have lost their lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm no expert in complex systems analysis, but you don't have to be to understand that "double mutants" or what WHO has tweeted are grossly oversimplified and do not adequately explain a national public health disaster (nor should they be used to advance personal agendas).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The reality is more complex. It's many factors: failed leadership, misplaced priorities, lack of access to health care, PPE,  vaccines, lack of epi data to guide evidence-based policy, demographics, epidemiology, misinformation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So what's the point of all this? Well, I've been more and more pissed off by hot takes attributing this tragedy to individual factors that are either beyond our control (variants) or the fault of specific people (WHO didn't say it was airborne) or misinformation (herd immunity).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The present situation demonstrates clearly that this model's estimates were extraordinarily incorrect, and one more example of what I've taken to calling "catastrophic optimism." Optimism is important, but not at the expense of necessary precautions. https://t.co/rExgj1aElY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At the time, @winterapples wrote an in-depth piece for Science, dissecting the model's flaws and including the perspectives of many Indian scientists, who strongly disagreed with that conclusion. https://t.co/42ySr5900d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government pointed to a paper from September 2020 by their commissioned "supermodel" committee that likely grossly overestimated seroprevalence and suggested the herd immunity threshold had been reached. https://t.co/WEONwQDtUb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This was bolstered by "experts" who took it upon themselves to make definitive proclamations about this (sometimes as part of delivering a decidedly anti-vaccine message, ahem, Jay Bhattacharya). https://t.co/Itki5Rh81L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And this has been further complicated by a narrative that India had reached herd immunity in 2020, thus justifying government complacency, premature reopening, and policies that endangered people. https://t.co/AN2ST0RxG3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And getting that data is a real problem when the government is spending more time trying to suppress criticism than prioritizing responses, including basic data collection that will allow for more effective public health interventions. https://t.co/mbfKjjwhRQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are still crucial for long-term suppression of the pandemic and for preventing a 3rd wave. But realistically, vaccines aren't going to be enough to contain the epidemic occurring right now without reliable data about regional hotspots to surge limited vaccine supplies. https://t.co/zkyCdWIGMX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["It's because there aren't enough people vaccinated!"  Sure, that doesn't help, but also that's the result of government complacency and pursuing unrealistic policy goals motivated by politics rather than public health. https://t.co/dfMqEQrICO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Both Drs. Chanda and Jha were scathing about the government's failure to act on warning signs that became the appalling tragedy we are witnessing today. https://t.co/m3fMLHnU4M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But the greater failure is in the government's inaction and bad policy decisions that put people at risk, per Dr. Sumit Chanda. We've seen this time and again here in the US and elsewhere around the world. https://t.co/WXJh0BTgqM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And btw, though this is a primarily outdoor event, close contact among large crowds with many infected people is a recipe for disaster. With enough people crowded for a sufficient duration of time, both aerosol  direct contact transmission will occur. https://t.co/DNWSTRrX3q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And on top of that, the government implemented policies that put people at grave risk, including by encouraging large gatherings. https://t.co/a9I7cOqOHi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So the real problem with aerosol transmission isn't that WHO didn't bother to tell India about it. It's that you can't realistically say "get N95s  air purifiers  CO2 monitors to India NOW" when frontline HCWs are lacking basic PPE and supplies  there's inadequate testing. https://t.co/hhumivZwZQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since that time, Dr. Mishra conducted a study that shows, indeed, a respiratory virus like SARS-CoV-2 does indeed spread through inhalation. Which, again, WHO has acknowledged since last July. https://t.co/ERl7zFtZAt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And this wasn't news to Dr. Mishra, whose institute released guidance in March 2020 encouraging, among other precautions, interventions for aerosol transmission including masks, distancing, staying home, and ventilation. https://t.co/3gBebbRwlf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And other scientists in India, like @RakeshMishraLab, director of @ccmb_csir, discussed aerosol transmission and the need for well-ventilated spaces: https://t.co/7cyCwrBBpd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While the ICMR continued to attribute spread primarily to droplets at the time, they acknowledged the importance of masks and distancing and also said they were closely following the topic. https://t.co/XR4QgBvgIM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["It's because WHO didn't send India the memo that this virus is AIRBORNE!"  Except when @WHO released their scientific brief discussing aerosol transmission in July 2020, the Union Health Ministry stated they were following this closely. https://t.co/Rm9iwh8N3C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And for their contribution to the overall cases, more transmissible variants are a problem in the surge of severe cases that are overwhelming the inadequately funded health care system. The variants may cause more infection, but more people are dying b/c they can't access care. https://t.co/hkrS6He3s8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["It's because of more transmissible variants!"  This might contribute, but as Dr. @ashishkjha points out, 40% of the population lives in multi-generational households. This is conducive to the spread of any variant, especially to older, higher risk people. https://t.co/ejFttDAdtP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seeing a lot of explanations that attribute the horrific surge in India to one thing or another (variants, aerosols, vaccines, etc), all of which betray a facile understanding of how a crisis like this occurs. https://t.co/WMkrIoFrvl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yougoodman16 @eggmcduffie @louUHvul We study all vaccines long after they are on the market. Every vaccine is thus "still in a test phase." And both mRNA and adenovirus-vectored vaccines have been studied for decades. We have a sufficient understanding of the immune system to evaluate their safety and efficacy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@katharinemjames @AdithyaR_YXE @BallouxFrancois Based on your profile pic and comment, you are opposed to masks and "lockdowns," so I'm genuinely curious why you are jumping in to the defense of Zero Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yougoodman16 @eggmcduffie @louUHvul Except his "scientific basis" is based on a bunch of stuff that, from what I can tell, he just made up about the currently authorized vaccines to promote his pet (untested) hypothesis about natural killer cells.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeremyFoote1 @BallouxFrancois That's not what "zero Covid" describes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yougoodman16 @eggmcduffie @louUHvul Geert Vanden Bosche is not a world renowned vaccine doctor. He may not call himself an anti-vaxxer but he's spreading anti-vax propaganda that has no basis in science.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_isagundogdu_ @Claude__Cat @GidMK No. SARS-CoV-2 is a completely different virus with unique evolutionary origins and nothing in common with any influenza subtypes. But flu can "shuffle" elements of its genome (called "reassortment") to make viruses of unique subtypes: H3N2 + H5N1 = H3N1, H5N2, etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ViaOshawa I think the guidance is complicated, but I also think it's reasonable. You should use a risk-benefit analysis to identify people who should be offered this vaccine, and ensure that they are able to provide fully informed consent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dagda9918 @hypoautonomic @GidMK LOL there's that too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hypoautonomic @GidMK Farms in general are one source of zoonotic transmission. People also have contact with birds more often than you might think. Also, in birds, influenza is a gastrointestinal infection. Zoonotic transmission doesn't occur when a bird coughs on you...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ViaOshawa I've only been in Canada for 2 weeks, so I'm still learning about NACI, but it seems roughly analogous to the ACIP in the US. Are you asking about their guidance today to make JJ and AstraZeneca conditionally available?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Claude__Cat @GidMK So those are a couple reasons why H5N1 was called "bird flu." The 2009 H1N1 pandemic was called "swine flu" because it adapted to humans from an ancestor that was found in pigs (pigs get flu from birds  pig adaptation can result in viruses that infect humans)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Claude__Cat @GidMK H5 binds better to alpha-2,3-linked sialic acid (found more in birds) than alpha-2,6-linked sialic acid (found more in the human respiratory tract). So it infects birds more efficiently, which is probably why it doesn't spread in humans. It's adapted to infecting birds.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Claude__Cat @GidMK For example, influenza uses sialic acid as its receptor. Sialic acids are sugars that "decorate" the surface of proteins on cells. Sialic acids can be different from each other based on chemical linkages, and that changes binding affinity to hemagluttinin (H) on the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Claude__Cat @GidMK Because H5 subtypes are more commonly found in birds and H5N1 was zoonotically transmitted directly from birds to humans, but not efficiently from human-to-human. All flu is originally avian flu, but we say "avian flu" meaning viruses more adapted to birds.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @GidMK He's an engineer-turned-keto zealot-turned-COVID-denier. In other words, he's totally unqualified to make absurd claims of the "lockdowns kill more people than COVID" variety. If you don't know him, you probably crossed paths with his like...Twitter is replete w/ these grifters.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GidMK It has nothing to do with sunlight or temperature or whatever else triggering the reactivation of made-up latent flu. It's a combination of ecological factors driving bird migration, zoonotic/epizootic transmission, and human behaviors in response to environmental conditions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GidMK Influenza is seasonal because its natural reservoir are migratory birds that go back and forth between the northern and southern hemispheres, and because winter weather is more conducive to transmission, which is through inhalation and contact. Close quarters=more flu spread.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GidMK In virology jargon, we'd say this is total horseshit. The only thing getting triggered here is an eye-roll emoji.   Influenza viruses are not capable of establishing latency, nor is it reactivated from said non-existent latency by a "seasonal trigger."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlastairMcA30 @GidMK I am a virologist and this is bullshit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JGPharmD Absolutely. Though I'd argue that this doesn't necessarily mean they will be unhappy. From my personal observations of some friends and family who have gotten divorced, that was essential to their happiness.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lonestarangle @AndrewHalayko @KindrachukJason The FDA does not grant EUAs for vaccines that fail to meet high standards for safety  efficacy. So yes, in this case, it does mean the vaccines are safe  effective in adolescents.  And everyone should consider a vaccine, then get one. I'm happy to address concerns you may have.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @amy_tabb @JenniferNuzzo Agreed. Ultimately the solution may lie in two things you've mentioned here: 6.6M vaccines are less than half of the doses the US is currently getting delivered weekly. If there were more tech transfer and IP sharing, we could also scale up production.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amy_tabb @Brian_Orak @JenniferNuzzo Exactly. This has to be a balance. It's not only vaccinate 12-15 year olds in the US or give vaccines to other countries. It's both.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GidMK @WrongAgainIvor @KatyMcconkey @dr_barrett @stuartjdneil @StephenBDugmore @andrew_croxford @SiouxsieW @HIVTox @GYamey I'm just catching up on this thread now and...good grief. It must be nice to read things and put them into whatever context you want.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JGPharmD To be clear, I'm not excited or gleeful they are getting divorced. The end of a marriage is usually sad.  It's just rare for me to use this word in anything but jokingly saying it to my husband when he annoys me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was waiting for this news. But with it should come a larger discussion on a point raised by the brilliant @JenniferNuzzo: how to balance protecting our kids with the desperate global need for vaccines in high-risk adults. https://t.co/L8fi5sRHdG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@minussr1 I messed up the conjugation, as usual. My Russian language skills are really, really bad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialImpurity . He also corrected me immediately. I cant keep up with all the conjugations, so clearly I have not yet mastered this word as I believed.  In my defense, I learned this word so I could jokingly demand . I also know how to say   ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Russian language skills are so atrocious that my spouse visibly winces whenever I attempt it. But I have to thank Bill  Melinda Gates for the opportunity to use one of the few words Ive mastered:  (razvoda). Aka divorce.  Him: Holy shit, did you see...  Me: !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @notdred: Maybe this is Melinda Gates' way of announcing support for the TRIPS waiver]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now THIS is a good vaccine incentive program https://t.co/c5vLBPBRiw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notdred Just audibly snorted with laughter when I read this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KindrachukJason @notdred At least here's a good use for those CO2 detectors some people are selling as a way to estimate exposure risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@meNabster I'll wait to see the data on that one. No vaccine is 100% effective and I can't see how they could have determined any efficacy if the clinical trials are still ongoing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BB52UK Probably not. The number of RCAs is still very low. It's mainly a safety concern for immune compromised people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SatoshiCrow @MoNscience What's your evidence that it was?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoNscience Eager for #MapleSyrupOrigins to join the other pool of origins hashtags that never took off #PopsicleOrigins #PangolinVirus etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, here's a novel SARS-CoV-2 origins theory. https://t.co/JPlCytDV2N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@reluctantlyjoe @covid19ny Also nobody ignored repurposed drugs. The repurposed drugs identified turned out not to work (see: hydroxychloroquine).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dmaccannell @pha4ge "Language in the RFP could have been better..." A universal truth!  I'm glad to be wrong about funding being contingent on waiving creator rights. I totally agree with you on the need for capacity building and engagement!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GermHunterMD LOL no. I sign articles that I write. I was just interested in it because I think a lot about how to make research more equitable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChupameGil @spitta1969 A vaccine is not a football team. It's not about whether I "totally support" it or not. Anvisa has demanded more data to address this question. Ultimately they will decide if it meets their standard for regulatory approval.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChupameGil @spitta1969 No, she doesn't. I also said that 1. there are no reported problems with the first Ad26 dose and 2. there are no reports of adenovirus infections with the second. We agree.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dmaccannell @pha4ge I guess my question here is what specifically is mischaracterized. I've seen the issue of contributors waiving rights to data in exchange for funding raised elsewhere. Don't get me wrong, I think PH4AGE has a crucial mission, but I haven't seen this particular issue addressed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Open sharing of data is critically important during a pandemic, which by definition impacts the entire world.  But that sharing needs to occur equitably. Open data can't be at the expense of the scientists who generate it. https://t.co/4hNUMBOZlR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoonofA I guess you didn't read the whole thread where I discussed the limit of detection in extensive detail. And what data are you citing to support your claim that "a few Ad5 are not a danger"? A few replication-competent Ad5s can quickly become millions because they replicate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bogofs Sort of. The E1 deletion serves another purpose besides making the virus replication-deficient. It also makes "room" in the genome for the spike insert. There are ways around this, but for safety reasons you don't want to make a vaccine that is going to spread unchecked.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GraceTatter: Want to dig in deeper into news alerts about herd immunity? @angie_rasmussen and @aetiology spoke with @KimberlyEAtkins fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But Anvisa is right to demand more answers. That is why regulators like Anvisa exist: to ensure that critical medicines like vaccines are both effective AND safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you live in a country that has already approved Sputnik V, or if you have been vaccinated with it, don't worry. The Ad26 component has no problems associated with it there are no reports as of now of Ad5 infection. Congratulations! You are now immunized against SARS-CoV-2.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sputnik V appears to be a very effective vaccine and it can do a lot of good. My hope is that these issues are addressed satisfactorily and in a transparent way. This can be solved by doing more testing to find out exactly how much RCA is present in a given dose.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thus Anvisa was right to reject Sputnik V on this basis. I'm not even going to get into the propaganda campaign to boost Sputnik's profile at the expense of competitors, but suffice to say this hurts efforts to vaccinate the world.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So it's a crucial safety measure to ensure there is no RCA in a vaccine preparation. The 1 RCA/30 billion particles FDA standard ensures that there is essentially NO RCA in viral vectored vaccines. Gamaleya is arguing that some higher but unquantifiable amount is...sure, okay!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And while Ad5 usually does cause common colds as a respiratory pathogen in most people, this does present a safety issue for some, particularly for people who are immunocompromised. People can die from adenovirus infections. https://t.co/hM0reFRzdH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why does this matter? That doesn't sound like a lot. And doesn't Ad5 just cause minor colds anyway?  Well, it matters because that's the thing about replication-competent viruses: they replicate exponentially. So 10 viruses can become 100, 1000, 10000, 100000...you get the idea.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So Sputnik's makers are splitting technical hairs to get around acknowledging that each dose of Ad5 vaccine has 0-99 RCAs in it. They are arguing that this is still way below the (comparatively very high) threshold that they arbitrarily set for residual RCAs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So I think Anvisa read between the lines. "Less than 100 RCAs/dose" means there WERE plaques detected, but so few that they couldn't accurately quantify RCA titer. If they detected nothing, they would have listed this as "NOT DETECTED" like they did for placebo.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 100 RCA cutoff is thus conveniently set at the lower limit of what you can accurately measure using the plaque assay. But the assay detects less virus than that, though it can't be accurately quantified. Just 1 plaque (~10 RCAs) means there's replication competent virus there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Dr. Racaniello explains, you count plaques at the dilution that gives between 10-100 plaques. This means that undiluted vaccine on a plate (a 10X dilution) needs to produce at least 10 plaques to accurately determine infectious titer. So 10 plaques on a 1:10 dilution=100 PFU. https://t.co/Q3lP1ZWfMX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So why this weird measurement? "Less than 100 RCAs /dose" doesn't sound like an actual quantity. Time for some virologist scrutiny. The limit of detection for the plaque assay is 100 plaque forming units (PFUs), because this is the cutoff for accurately quantifying PFUs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But the vaccine RCAs were reported as "less than 100 RCAs/dose". That's a little different than "NOT DETECTED" and sure sounds like they saw plaques in their plaque assay! https://t.co/iuN7SLLiAi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I also raised my eyebrows at how Gamaleya reported residual RCAs. It was reported differently for the vaccine compared to the placebo in their clinical trial. The placebo obviously doesn't have any Ad5 in it, but they tested it anyway: "NOT DETECTED" https://t.co/UNKNznI7pz]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>