<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for supporting @EveryDoctorUK. It means a lot to us. Were doctors holding the government to account. Ju  https://t.co/EQbR3zRhre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much Iain! https://t.co/118VMItpPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We only have 51 EveryDoctor masks left! I just counted!  Our masks are comfy+soft, and each contains a donation which funds our work supporting NHS staff+patients.   Order yours here quickly! Ju  https://t.co/JkiFynE4P1 https://t.co/v4LTkLlJlN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve just finalised my 3rd legal statement for the courts. @EveryDoctorUK is taking the government to court along with @GoodLawProject. Were holding ministers to account for failing to protect NHS workers and patients.  12 days until court  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for everyone helping to build my following. @EveryDoctorUK is taking the government to court in a fortnight for failing to protect NHS workers and patients (handing out dodgy PPE contracts). Ill update you with everything that happens ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigeye54 Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much to everyone joining EveryDoctor! Its brilliant to have you on-board. Ju ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine if every time you turned on the news and saw something worrying about the NHS, you knew you were doing something to improve things?  Thats what happens for EveryDoctor supporters. Please join us today!  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarieHeleneTho2 Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ooh, @stephenfry has just followed me! Hello Stephen! Please could you support NHS staff by sharing my pinned tweet?Ju ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We all need masks to keep our communities safe- and we have less than 100 EveryDoctor masks left!  Our masks are comfy and soft, and each contains a donation which funds our work supporting NHS staff+patients.   Order yours here before we run out! Ju https://t.co/JkiFynE4P1 https://t.co/dxDqKWkdol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for helping (see my pinned tweet). Almost hit 125000!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This am Im meeting our lawyers to finalise my legal statement to be used in court against the government in a fortnight. My team and I built files of evidence of the horrors frontline doctors experienced during the 1st wave. Were now holding the government to account ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Laurence Fox is creating a brand out of gaslighting NHS staff  I spend my life advocating for them  His twitter following is 285k-will you help build my Twitter voice louder than his? Im fed up of seeing our doctors+nurses talked about like this Ju, Chief Exec @EveryDoctorUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@radiodandy75 Its so kind of you, thank you x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much Deanna! https://t.co/zQaWEf2DQb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SurgeryGopher No! Lots available!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEWLook! our new fancy EveryDoctor pens have arrived! If you support our work, please consider ordering one! (Each one contains a donation which helps us to advocate for NHS staff and patients!).   https://t.co/CYH1Ci28zx https://t.co/Ebivn1nROy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We all need masks to keep our communities safe- and we have less than 100 EveryDoctor masks left!  Our masks are comfy and soft, and each contains a donation which funds our work supporting NHS staff+patients.   Order yours here before we run out! Ju https://t.co/JkiFynE4P1 https://t.co/IcYmFEAvlL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for ordering Fiona! If anyone needs to order EveryDoctor masks, click here! Weve almost run out! https://t.co/CYH1Ci28zx https://t.co/wGnEajiqfb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for ordering an @EveryDoctorUK mask! Were so glad you like it! https://t.co/Tuvit5bc9E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Whovian242 Yes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have less than 100 EveryDoctor masks left! Our masks are carefully made to be comfy and soft, and each contains a donation which funds our work supporting NHS staff+patients.   Order yours here before we run out! Ju https://t.co/JkiFynE4P1 https://t.co/OHBFnq7QeW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EveryDoctorUK: Outsourcing damages the sustainability of the NHS  leaves us vulnerable to cost increases by private firms. We must hal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeterStefanovi2 @EveryDoctorUK Thanks so much Peter ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One year on from this interview, were preparing to go to court against the government. Ministers did not protect NHS staff and patients. https://t.co/CzMWuyMluC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine if every time you turned on the news and saw something worrying about the NHS, you knew you were doing something active to improve things?  Thats what happens for EveryDoctor supporters. Please join today  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whys it significant that doctors are taking the government to court?  Because in our profession, the truth matters. People matter. Safety matters. Dignity matters. Hard work matters. Accountability matters. Decency matters. Lives matter.  Well get answers about dodgy PPE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EveryDoctorUK: 24 MPs are supporting an Early Day Motion to give NHS workers a 15% pay rise with us  @nurses_united. Thank you so much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine if every time you turned on the news and saw something worrying about the NHS, you knew you were doing something active to improve things?  Thats what happens for EveryDoctor supporters. Please join us today  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much to @jon_trickett for tabling an Early Day Motion with @EveryDoctorUK and @nurses_united, calling for a proper NHS pay rise. Thank you to the 24 MPs who have already signed up (well thank each one individually). We cannot accept further real terms pay cuts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @Denis_campbell for this excellent article. NHS privatisation is spiralling  @EveryDoctorUK   https://t.co/7jStEwqtpg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much, your support means a lot to us. Ju  https://t.co/mF7WpQq5Hs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JDBakewell: The more I read about Govt plans to let the American company Centene buy up the NHS the more outraged I am!  No one voted f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have less than 100 EveryDoctor masks left- I just checked our online shop! Our masks are carefully made to be comfy and soft, and each contains a donation which funds our work supporting NHS staff+patients.   Order yours here before we run out! Ju https://t.co/JkiFynE4P1 https://t.co/wBfxkmapIG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for ordering our masks Dave, were so glad you like them! Guys we only have 100 masks left, if youd like to order just click here   https://t.co/CYH1Ci28zx https://t.co/kwJZBB7dc3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ahh thanks Lucy. The sewists have done such an amazing job; theyre UK-based sewists employed by @mfep_uk , were so lucky theyve made these for us x https://t.co/AE1YpvP9ZK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Umm the masks are now disappearing before my very eyes (on the app which keeps buzzing at me). Thank you so much for keeping your communities safe, buying a sustainable product, and supporting EveryDoctors work in the process!xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are so humbled and proud to have been shortlisted for this prestigious award because of our work in securing essential protections for NHS workers during the pandemic. @EveryDoctorUK https://t.co/TfD4Mp1oZ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We only have 130 EveryDoctor masks left- I just checked our online shop! Our masks are carefully made to be comfy and soft, and each contains a donation which funds our work supporting NHS staff+patients.   Order yours here before we run out! Ju https://t.co/CYH1Ci28zx https://t.co/f20keXB5BA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every piece of merchandise we make helps to fund the work @EveryDoctorUK does. If you need masks (and we all do, we are not in the clear yet), or a lovely coffee cup, just click here! Ju   https://t.co/CYH1Ci28zx https://t.co/oxhC5Sa1wy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please read this thread from @trishgreenhalgh. And please follow her recommendations  https://t.co/D26wN7IjIg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This doesnt surprise me at all. The medical profession has shouldered an unbelievable burden and the workload continues to be enormous. NHS staff need to be properly supported; this must be a wake-up call.  @EveryDoctorUK   https://t.co/EHzRynrL7k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hello! Lots of lovely folk are asking if they can join EveryDoctor and become part of what we do. This is so generous of you. If you click here, you can become a regular donor (a bit like donating to charity). Thank you so much to everyone joining, Ju https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huge thank you to every single NHS worker at work today. Things are really tough on bank holidays; busier than ever, and were so grateful youre there, keeping patients safe. X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for joining @EveryDoctorUK Cliff! https://t.co/wsa5S7lfSe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we have confirmed our next steps, well update everyone. We are so grateful to these MPs for engaging with NHS frontline workers on this critical issue. Julia, @EveryDoctorUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following our MP briefing about NHS privatisation on Thursday, MPs from 3 different political parties so far have approached @EveryDoctorUK, interested in setting up an All Party Parliamentary Group on NHS privatisation. As soon...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hello! Lots of lovely folk are asking if they can join EveryDoctor and become part of what we do. This is so generous of you. If you click here, you can become a regular donor (a bit like donating to charity). Thank you so much to everyone joining, Ju  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In case anyone missed this on Thursday, just an update from court https://t.co/Nxej2tZutg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Steve_p_photos @EveryDoctorUK Hello! You can click here to join us, thank you so much for your support! https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for your support @PeterStefanovi2 x https://t.co/aR90aRFLMw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lots of people are joining @EveryDoctorUK, thank you so much! Please let me know who you are so I can follow you back! Ju]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exactly Rosie. Your daughters experience is horrifying, and shell have seen things shell never forget. She was expected to endure more than any person should do. That needs to be heard. It must never, ever occur again.  https://t.co/aHVMvK9SzX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If youd like to join the movement of doctors who are taking this government to court in a fortnight, then please click here. We really appreciate all of your support x  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[that a pandemic plan will be created and adhered to and that none of our friends and colleagues will ever, ever die needlessly in this way again.   NHS staff matter. Please cover their stories. I have given up my medical career to fight for NHS staff. We will not be silenced.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who trawled our dossiers of evidence to create statements as co-claimants. We are the doctors who understand what really happened on the frontline. And were bringing these cases because they matter. Because we hope that if we win, that NHS staff will never face this again...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[domain, and our own efforts at dispersing this information, we are being ignored consistently by the media outlets covering these cases. And this weekend weve been described by one journalist as silent partners in the cases.   We are not silent partners. We are the doctors...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Re-traumatising for members to have to confront these PPE cases; to confront the knowledge that while they soldiered on in bin bags, VIPs were being handed billions in public money, often for unsuitable PPE.   Despite the knowledge that we are co-claimants being in the public...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[doctor members were experiencing unimaginable horrors. Taking these cases on was a leap at a time when we were already fighting for adequate supplies, fighting for really basic protections for NHS staff. It was a big deal to us and our members; and frankly at times it has been...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont often get angry, but I feel really rattled tonight. EveryDoctor has devoted a significant portion of our limited resource to fighting the government in 4 legal cases since last May. When we took them on initially, my husband was working on the frontline in ICU, and our...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are co-claimants in the 4 high profile cases against the government regarding PPE. Thank you Judy for sharing this. Journalists; please be accurate in your reporting  https://t.co/YDb51puS80]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were not silent partners.  Were co-claimants in the cases.   Those are the facts. I dont know where you sourced the information to write your article, but it has an omission if it failed to state that @EveryDoctorUK is the co-claimant to these legal cases. https://t.co/7DgiNw3iAq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dimartindale @EveryDoctorUK Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dimartindale @EveryDoctorUK You could click here. We really appreciate it  https://t.co/45rio6IwwB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please could you let me know if youve joined @EveryDoctorUK, so I can follow you back? I believe really strongly in the power of building our community. Ju    If you need the link to join, its here! https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for joining @EveryDoctorUK Neil! https://t.co/bC0Uih16dT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That magic money tree is absolutely blooming right now isnt it?   But only for rich people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@swalkere17 Cheese and pickle probably?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No money for student nurse bursaries.  No money to fix hospital repairs.  No money to pay NHS staff properly.   But plenty of money for a big boat.   Whats happened to this country?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Toasties are really under-appreciated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[T - 16 days til we go to court against the government re dodgy PPE  Be a part of what we do. Hold this government to account  Join @EveryDoctorUK today!   https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We dont need a Royal Yacht. We need to care for people living in poverty, and fund the NHS properly.   RT if you agree]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much Thomas! https://t.co/013ev6q0W2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were running out of our @EveryDoctorUK masks again! We all need to wear masks still, to keep our communities safe. Click here for yours! (Ours are soft and comfy with a pinchable nose!). Ju  https://t.co/CYH1Ci28zx https://t.co/BQq6Sclb83]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please read this thread from the barrister on the EveryDoctor team, Meg. https://t.co/WpWAGhB5sq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SweMohas @chrismc15327463 @EveryDoctorUK @mediamacaque We have a barrister on our team- @megs1970 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hello  @chrismc15327463! Your article about PPE cases doesnt mention @EveryDoctorUK, who are a co-claimant in the 4 legal cases. Please amend the articles for accuracy. Our press officer is @mediamacaque if you need info. Our NHS doctor members are crucial to these cases. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone please help!@chrismc15327463 has written an article about the PPE cases in The Mirror and hasnt mentioned EveryDoctor, who are co-claimants in the cases. It may be an honest mistake so please be polite, but can we all tweet Chris and ask him to amend the article?Ju ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mediamacaque: Hi @chrismc15327463 @MirrorPolitics @DailyMirror Please would you adjust your piece to credit @EveryDoctorUK in this case]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megs1970: @EveryDoctorUK is a co-claimant in these cases. Its a huge amount of work for our small team. Our friends and colleagues die]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tiffin1963 @EveryDoctorUK Sorry?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW! Lots of our supporters have asked if they can join EveryDoctor and contribute monthly (this is so kind, thank you)  So weve built a special page so you can join!   Please join today and help us to hold this government to account!  Ju https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Luckily we have a fantastic new press officer. Well get to the bottom of whats happening here. NHS staff matter and their voices must be heard in the media. These dodgy PPE cases are about them and their lack of safety at work. Hundreds were unprotected and died. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tiffin1963 @EveryDoctorUK Theyre mentioning Good Law Project consistently, but not the grassroots group of doctors who represent those who had no PPE on the frontline.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please help! The media are not mentioning @EveryDoctorUK in articles about our legal cases against the government  We cant understand whats happening. NHS staff matter  If you see articles like thisplease ask why @EveryDoctorUK hasnt been named  https://t.co/0dIsN3J7dU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Be a part of what we do. Hold this government to account. Join @EveryDoctorUK today!  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for joining EveryDoctor Sue! And thank you to everyone else too, we really appreciate your support! https://t.co/F4mqDhm6ss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many of our wonderful supporters are joining the movement to change UK healthcare.   Please join EveryDoctor today and help us to push back against NHS privatisation and hold the government to account.  Lets do it together! Ju   https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[T -16 days until we go to court against the government for failing to protect NHS workers.  @EveryDoctorUK  @GoodLawProject]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IamOneTiredHCSW Im so sorry, its so so awful x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW! Lots of our supporters are joining EveryDoctor today- thank you!  Have you signed up yet?  Please join today and help us to hold the government to account!  Ju  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megs1970: 100% matters to me. Im going to fight as hard as I can to stop it happening. Theres no public mandate for it, never was. 87]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James thank you so much for joining @EveryDoctorUK   Guys- weve built this new page so you can join us. Wed love to have you on-board. Ju  https://t.co/HemNRPKriV https://t.co/eheNUgZc5T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does NHS privatisation matter to you? It matters to me.   Its accelerating. Were fighting back. @EveryDoctorUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW! Lots of our supporters are joining EveryDoctor today- thank you!  Have you signed up yet?  Please join today and help us to hold this government to account!  Ju https://t.co/HemNRPKriV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lila740141 This morning did today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(Some regions managed to source funding to set up vaccine centres in December, but this was not straight-forward and was often down to massive efforts at a local level.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Understaffed and over-worked, like every other aspect of the NHS. If you are frustrated, please tell your MP. The government needs to invest properly in the NHS in order to care for patients better. Its not GPs fault]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[to pay staff. They set up vaccination centres when there was a lot of uncertainty about the vaccines still, and they did this alongside their usual work (busier than ever before). When GPs cant answer the phone or dont have appointments, thats because theyre underfunded...]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>