<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Julie82902847 @EMclearan Okay, how about the fact that most black children are raised by a single parent and their culture suffers from that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Black supremacy strikes again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twincities83 @avataylor02 @JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 Twitter canceled Trumps account along with others because liberals dont like free speech. They only want their kind of speech. CANCEL CULTURE!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twincities83 @avataylor02 @JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 You obviously haven't done your research.  Typical liberal.  Children's accounts on disney plus took away a few disney movies you schmuck. Y'all have short term memory. Thank the demoncrats for destroying America right now. #AllLivesMatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Donna_Guthrie1 @NYCPDDEA You're anti-cop?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @RonDeSantisFL Wish in one hand and crap in the other. See which one fills up first. You're very ignorant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid You're funny. Florida is lit under republican control. Demoncrats only know how to ruin a good thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ilhan You want something you go work for it. Nothing in life is free you ignorant shmuck.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Julie82902847 @EMclearan Yet over 50% of all crimes are from black people and most blacks dont care about black on black crime because it doesnt fit the narrative.  There's a lot of black Republicans fighting for this stuff. Its the black democrats that dont care.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twincities83 @avataylor02 @JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 Speaking of US history. The left are the ones who created the kkk and blm. Both racist groups and only harm others. Thumbs up to your party. It was the Republicans that freed the slaves mind you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twincities83 @avataylor02 @JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 What has Republicans canceled? I know the left tried to cancel Goya. They wanted Aunt Jemima and Uncle Ben gone. The left are canceling disney movies. What has the right canceled?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoriBush Black supremacy strikes again!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingJames Protect our young white men and women!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Toure Because a lot of blacks like to play the victim still.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Julie82902847 @EMclearan I see it in every race except blacks dont think they do it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twincities83 @avataylor02 @JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 Woke is cancel culture. Woke is saying white supremacy is holding the black man down. Woke is saying blm riots are peaceful protests. Woke is identifying more than 2 genders. It's all dumb ass ignorant shit!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Julie82902847 @EMclearan Hence the left]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twincities83 @avataylor02 @JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 What the left is pushing. Get woke, go broke!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@warriorwoman91 The bay area sucks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Toure https://t.co/Zw5D031xNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 Black people are extremely racist!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @Toure @RichardMThomps1 https://t.co/Gs2MS53zX4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid https://t.co/BUIMH9OYui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRevAl https://t.co/AEr9rc7GBI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoriBush https://t.co/ZzFXOCp2Es]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @AttorneyCrump https://t.co/fCFPCQohk1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMclearan https://t.co/Ok8tKc9OgW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoriBush So you claim the US is so bad yet you still live here? Black on black crime is your biggest danger. Where are you gonna go to get away from that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AttorneyCrump #whiteexcellence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Nope, the demoncrats are though]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MsLaToshaBrown And demoncrats ignore black on black crime???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews Black on black crime strikes again!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoriBush Black supremacy strikes again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Why aren't people who refuse to wear masks dying? We should have been dead a long time ago but NOPE! SCAMDEMIC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @JoyAnnReid Black supremacy strikes again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Toure Black people suppress black people. If a black person talks educated then their fellow black people call them an uncle tom. Gotta wear them Js and have a grill to keep it street. Feel me! Black ethics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@couchfish1 @henriziolkowski @JoyAnnReid @DeanObeidallah https://t.co/SEu9wmSrBT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@couchfish1 @henriziolkowski @JoyAnnReid @DeanObeidallah https://t.co/z58nU6k9f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Morons that play stupid games win stupid prizes. He's not a victim. Another black man trying to run from the police!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SiCk_DiAbLo https://t.co/J97Sq9XWiE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@womanistwriter Blm is a perfect example of dividing.  That's why I say #AllLivesMatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Blm is extremely racist but I don't see you calling them out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Why would blm terrorize the country and you still call it peaceful?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AttorneyCrump #AllLivesMatter #whitelivesmatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I mean, who plays the victim card because she's black?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicoleArbour https://t.co/DXkv2EGG8T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMclearan Burn, loot, and murder? Buy Large Mansion? Fuck the racist BLM!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfessorCrunk So a black girl running at another black girl with a knife is justified.BUT a white cop using lethal force on her is the problem?What did you think that girl was trying to do with the knife,butter some bread?How about we raise our children better so lethal force isn't necessary!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid So a black girl running at another black girl with a knife is justified.BUT a white cop using lethal force on her is the problem?What did you think that girl was trying to do with the knife,butter some bread?How about we raise our children better so lethal force isn't necessary!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemelehill So a black girl running at another black girl with a knife is justified.BUT a white cop using lethal force on her is the problem?What did you think that girl was trying to do with the knife,butter some bread?How about we raise our children better so lethal force isn't necessary!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @AdamSerwer #AllLivesMatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemelehill The NBA is racist. Not enough white people.  Affirmative action]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Black supremacy strikes again!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Like pelosi getting inside tips on stocks and trading?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Where ya at blm??? https://t.co/5DW1xU2jIt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SavysuzyRises @MichaelSteele @semperdiced Im pro white, pro trump, anti blm, anti antifa!!!! Funny how the left is systematically racist given their past.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichaelSteele I love it. I have white pride and I'm not racist. Im just pro white so boom.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NYCPDDEA: This morning, NYPD cops were attacked with Molotov cocktails during a car stop.  Detectives: This shocking video is a reminde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Chris Cuomo thinks more white people need to get shot and Maxine Waters wants more violence in the streets.  And the mai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: Maxine Waters says that Chauvin premeditated the murder of George Floyd and that if Chauvin is not convicted a crime he wasn't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @breeadail: Rep. Maxine Waters (D-CA) to BLM protesters in Brooklyn Center, MN:  [Protestors] got to stay on the street and get more ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ So is being white]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Black supremacy strikes again!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid In a world full of blm'ers, be the Kyle Rittenhouse America needs and deserves!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid We need more Kyle Rittenhouse's in America to stop the mobs of BLM from burning down our cities and looting from the neighborhood stores! Black supremacy is real]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoriBush @POTUS That's black supremacy talking right there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealMkA20: Has anybody ever thought that the problem in this country is bad parenting and not bad policing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Toure: Imagine thinking heres what that 13 yo kid or that 19 yo kid should have done differently rather than heres what that grown as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WayneDupreeShow: Media: We've had "45 mass shootings in the last month"  America: We didn't have that under Trump.... #JustSaying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Black people kill black people more than any other race. Blacks kill blacks more than policemen do. 50% of all crimes come from black people.  Black supremacy is real!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Black people arent ready to admit that the biggest threat black people face is black violence.  Black people kill black people more than any other race. Black supremacy is real!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats Knives kill more people than guns! Remember that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Are liberals aware that black on black violence kills more blacks than anyone else? 13% of the population creates over 50% of all crimes in the US. Time to look in the mirror and reflect on that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AyannaPressley What about those who couldn't afford college so they were never able to attend? Will they get free college now?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Like this? https://t.co/sj4VyZLmN1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brian18376040: Fuck BLM, NFAC and Antifa and any other hate groups. I feel better now . Thank you all for listening to my tirade.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid So quick to call Twitter police on me when you're against the cops. Smh, go figure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid https://t.co/uroED6NHV0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I'm fed up of blacks killing blacks at an alarming rate and blacks attacking Asians!!!! What about you? Black supremacy is real]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Yet you're not worried about black on black violence? Smh, typical racist!!!! News flash,  blacks can be racist you POS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/J5uRHJdiav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nuMQzTW8ss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cBqRPeOHHL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JU43dqtvID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/egYBvbvAAz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7RGjtmPMv6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/owk5UZbpNK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/02siRR3ZLq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xM90y57TYq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Black supremacy strikes again.  God, you couldn't be any more racist. You're pure evil. Keep showing your true colors you racist BITCH!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemelehill You know you're a loser when your on AOCs side. I thought you knew about competition? Apparently not!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid You're blind. You're bias. You're a disgrace to America. Liberalism is a mental disorder!!! You represent pure evil upon us TRUE AMERICANS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib https://t.co/mcUtQNZNM1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AyannaPressley @ChuyForCongress https://t.co/ah1V4ahSKM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid https://t.co/xQNS2zTsCI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill https://t.co/jQWB7X7Hoe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: Breaking: James OKeefe of Project Veritas has been suspended by Twitter. This is pure censorship for political reasons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Only blacks? If you forgive student loan debt then you should allow every American who couldn't afford to go to college attend for free!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Keep making excuses on the cheating, lies,  and deceptions. Liberalism is a mental disorder!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @RepMaxineWaters @RepMaxineWaters is a dumb joke. F THAT B!TCH!!!!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>