<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[I've been out campaigning across the country for @Conservatives candidates in tomorrow's elections.  A vote for the Conservatives is a vote for lower taxes, investment in local communities  a plan to build back better from this pandemic.  #VoteConservative https://t.co/zD0rDxG00x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEngland: Today is International Day of the Midwife!   Thank you to all our incredible midwives for the care, compassion and support]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BenHouchen: Tomorrow is Election Day   Its going to be a very close election and every vote is vital - so make sure you vote for me!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Jill Mortimer has a fantastic plan for Hartlepool. Shell work with me to deliver more quality local jobs, extra investme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEastEngland: Today we for #IDW2021 @hastings_vickie, a community midwifery team leader at @NNUH shares her experience of being a mid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives:  Your vote is crucial to help us deliver on your priorities  On Thursday May 6th #VoteConservative https://t.co/oarKHP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GSK: As industry leaders in applying functional genomics, we welcome @GOVUK  @MattHancock's new investment into functional genomics. I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve backed UK science from the very start of this pandemic.   This multi-million pound funding for a state-of-the-art vaccine testing facility at Porton Down will enable us to further future-proof the country from the threat of new variants.  https://t.co/HWeEdHQP90]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: Today Prime Ministers @BorisJohnson and @NarendraModi agreed a 2030 Roadmap for UK-India relations.  Here are some of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimBethell: THANK YOU: to today's roundtable on how we can ensure our massive investment in clinical trials and data isn't "all about t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VACCINE UPDATE:  - 65.7% of adults have been vaccinated once for COVID-19 - 29.4% of adults have had two vaccines  The vaccine is saving lives so when it's your turn, come forward  get the jab.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @andy4wm: I saw standing for Mayor as a job interview but to millions of residents  Now I'm standing for re-election, so you could say t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives: 48 hours to go  Vote Conservative  https://t.co/0pAvn5uMhk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Thanks to the extraordinary effort of everyone involved, 50 million doses of the COVID-19 vaccine have now been given to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDalyMP:  50 million jabs delivered is absolutely huge. But it is so important that people continue to accept the vaccine when it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bren4Bassetlaw: An incredible achievement! Well done to all those involved ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reaching this milestone of 50 million vaccines shows how far we've come in our fight against this virus  I want to pay tribute to everybody involved in this huge achievement - the NHS, armed forces, volunteers, councils, scientists  the British public  A huge national effort  https://t.co/3du70l5lAP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve just delivered the 50 millionth jab across the UK!  Massive achievement from the team.   These jabs are saving lives and helping us get back to normal.   Thank you to everyone who has played their part in our national effort.    When you get the call, get the jab. https://t.co/BlSWwVGma6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Thanks to the help and generosity of @boconline, last night a delivery of much-needed oxygen cylinders was sent from the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: My message on Northern Irelands centenary year. https://t.co/x5giX4bMwT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: We are playing our part in the fight against the coronavirus surge in India:   Sending 1,000 more ventilators to hel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As a close friend of India, we've felt the harrowing scenes  are determined to do all we can  This support, sending 1,000 more ventilators, will help save lives  support India's healthcare system  In the battle against COVID, were all on the same side  https://t.co/zyUZzDX6lU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm delighted that the 15 million most vulnerable people have now been vaccinated twice.  The vaccine protects you, it protects those around you  is our route out of this pandemic. https://t.co/5O9gqHwdJT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VACCINE UPDATE:  - 15 million second doses have now been administered across the UK  - Yesterday, the team delivered over half a million doses  A huge thank you to the whole team involved  to everybody coming forward to get your jab. https://t.co/j0HeYa3UGa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: "It only took eight minutes in total - it's really simple. It's a triumph of science."  Earlier this week, @MattHancock got]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're getting a great reception on the doorstep for @Conservatives candidates across the country.  #VoteConservative on May 6th to build back better. https://t.co/VRiiqITwHW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At every stage of this pandemic, the British public has stepped up  made huge sacrifices.  This new pilot could help shift the dial in our favour by offering a viable alternative to self-isolation for people who are contacts of positive Covid-19 cases.  https://t.co/DmuSLzaltO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScotTories: There is only one way to stop indyref2 and get all of the focus onto rebuilding Scotland  use your peach party list vote f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fantastic that 50,000 women, organisations, clinicians  carers have responded to our call for evidence.  We're calling for all women  those with experience or expertise in womens health, to share their views.  Help us shape the women's health strategy.  https://t.co/FetE1DSN4J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccine is safe, effective  is our route out of this pandemic.  Thank you to @LennyHenry, Lydia West, @davidwalliams, Navin Chowdhry, @ElizabethHurley  @eltonofficial. https://t.co/PVSsfeE9QA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im so glad that Covid cases have come down so far, so its now safe for residents to be able to leave care homes for low-risk visits  I know how important this is  The vaccine roll-out is enabling us to cautiously but irreversibly ease from restrictions  https://t.co/Dz6Zr6GkGs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you get the call, get the jab. https://t.co/RBDHqNHxqX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to have a pint with @BenHouchen in Middlesbrough to talk about investment in the Tees Valley.  Thanks to the vaccine roll-out we can look forward to a great British summer.  #VoteConservative https://t.co/3u3UL5JXpv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives: Domestic abuse is an abhorrent crime that destroys lives. We have passed new laws to protect victims and punish offender]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VACCINE UPDATE:  - 65% of adults have now been vaccinated for COVID-19 - 27.6% of adults have had two jabs - Yesterday, the team administered 610,953 vaccines  This mammoth team effort is protecting our country from this virus, so thank you to everybody involved.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to all the Londoners who have come forward for their vaccine.  I had my first jab yesterday  I urge everybody to get your vaccine as soon as you are eligible, so we can beat this pandemic together.  https://t.co/tP4MJ4CGiv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimBethell: Terrific response from voters in Tees Valley, campaigning with Tilly for @BenHouchen, our amazing mayor.   So impressive to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A huge thank you to everyone playing your part to protect our country against this virus.  This data is hugely promising  shows that our strategy is working. https://t.co/ll4gspjQZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is staggeringly good data showing that 94% of adults have received or would be likely to accept a COVID-19 vaccine.  Thank you to everybody coming forward to get your jab - this is our route out of this pandemic. https://t.co/icdhf1ZQki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: "If we fail to act on antimicrobial resistance, modern medicine as we know it may cease to exist."   @MattHancock explains h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK is determined to use our presidency of the G7 this year to bring partners together  take bold new steps onAMR   In my view, its an existential threat as great as climate change.  Read my speech here   https://t.co/nFpDn24OzA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Global health is at the heart of the UKs G7 presidency. No one is safe until were all safe.  We look forward to working with @CEPIvaccines to speed up vaccine development, creating a global solution to ensure were better prepared for future pandemics.  https://t.co/RWY6S3lkxs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Building on the excellent progress of our vaccine roll-out, we're now opening up vaccinations to 40  41 year olds in England.  I got my jab yesterday  I urge everybody eligible to book a jab to protect yourself  your loved ones from COVID-19.  https://t.co/Kbr4aI8GHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were running ground-breaking clinical trials, we're treating COVID, were vaccinating our way out of this pandemic.  My speech on transforming the UK into a life sciences superpower   https://t.co/BXiAPJLmmq https://t.co/ywozJ42WHz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A fantastic day of vaccinations yesterday, with 597,025 doses being administered across the UK   Thank you to the whole team for your hard work.  This is our route out of this pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Through his steadfast leadership of @NHSEngland Sir Simon Stevens has supported NHS staff throughout this global pandemic.   Thank you for your formidable 7 years of service in transforming healthcare in England and best wishes for your future in @UKHouseofLords.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im delighted @suenaidoo73 has been appointed to be CNO of Wales.   Massive thanks to Sue for your incredible work and Im sure youll do a fantastic job.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im feeling great now Ive had my first jab.   Massive thanks to JVT for administering my Oxford / AstraZeneca vaccination  doing so much for us all through the pandemic.   When I got the call, I got the jab. https://t.co/nmDCwCg5qX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sciencemuseum: We're delighted to be supporting @NHSEngland with a vaccination centre here at the Science Museum! https://t.co/PZctkK45]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEWS: We have record numbers of doctors  nurses in the NHS  - 11,200 more nurses since last year - 6,300 more doctors since last year  We're on target to deliver 50,000 more nurses by the end of this parliament https://t.co/kzE3fRAoZu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brilliant! Got the jab. In  out in 8 minutes. Didnt hurt at all.   Massive thanks to JVT  the @sciencemuseum team.   When you get the call, get the jab! https://t.co/dPhUwkGEYB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delighted Laura Trotts Bill to ban invasive cosmetic procedures in children will become law today.  Thank you Laura for your tireless work to make this happen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: The Vaccines Taskforce has secured an extra 60 million doses of the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine.   The extra doses will he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KensingtonRoyal: 10 years    Chris Floyd https://t.co/fPunbUz3VL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 in 10 adults have Covid-19 antibodies.  This is the vaccination programme in action. https://t.co/kZWjYluk9S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve secured a further 60 million doses of the @pfizer/@BioNTech_Group vaccine that will be used, alongside others, as part of our booster programme later this year.  The vaccine is bringing back our freedom  we must protect this progress. https://t.co/02LOkQ2IT0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccine protects you, it protects your loved ones  it is the way out of this pandemic. https://t.co/R0vrvkVzze]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @G7:  1/2 This #WorldImmunisationWeek , we are highlighting how vaccine confidence  is critical to ending the pandemic  protecting c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @10DowningStreet: Watch today's coronavirus press conference live on our channels at 5pm. https://t.co/3AhHqU95pK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Helen_Whately: The healthcare system needs to work for everyone and this shows exactly why  If you're a woman with learning disabiliti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OliverDowden: The Ministerial Declaration I am encouraging @G7 leaders to sign today will align with the 10 Tech Priorities I set out f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Helen_Whately: Pleased to join 33.8 million people across the country in getting a first dose of #COVID19Vaccine. Thank you to the thou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delighted to have received my text inviting me to book my vaccination.   This feels like a huge personal step towards normal.   I got the call, Im getting the jab. https://t.co/G2FCBxiAD9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Vaccines have saved thousands of lives so far and now this data shows they could also protect others by cutting transmiss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These latest @ONS stats are very encouraging - shows the protection vaccines are giving in practice.   When you get the call, get the jab. https://t.co/71UQLKPu0x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vital supplies from the UK are arriving in India.  Were working with our Indian friends in these tough times.  My thoughts are with our Indian friends  everyone affected at this deeply difficult time.   ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEWS: A new study shows one dose of the vaccine can cut the risk of household transmission by up to 50%.  This is further evidence that the vaccine protects you and those around you.  When you get the call, get the jab.  https://t.co/UFQ6iimEL8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jochurchill4: A fantastic milestone that 25% of UK adults have now received 2 jabs.  My thanks to the teams working so hard to roll-out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ben_Everitt: Brilliant progress on second jabs  https://t.co/f67Lmd6Hdv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: A quarter of UK adults have received 2 doses of a COVID vaccine, giving them maximum protection against the virus.   This]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimBethell: So many friends and relatives so relieved they've had their 2nd jab. It was really noticeable speaking to them last weekend]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEWS: 25% of UK adults have now received 2 jabs.  This milestone shows how far we've come as a country in our fight against this virus.  A huge thank you to the whole team working so hard to roll-out the vaccine. https://t.co/zxoYcDR921]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I urge anyone who is eligible for a COVID vaccine to come forward  book your appointment here.  The vaccine is our route out of this pandemic.  https://t.co/ryh2OLPJ9a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm very excited to open up vaccination to 42 year olds - standing by my phone awaiting my text... https://t.co/A0kYnyjbtP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are now inviting anyone aged 42 or over and those who will turn 42 before 1st July 2021 to book a COVID-19 vaccination.  Thank you to everyone who has contributed to our national effort.   When you get the call, get the jab. https://t.co/OCxJNRTDKA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We stand side by side with India.  I had a very constructive discussion with @drharshvardhan.  We discussed the impact of variants and made clear the U.K. will support our friends at this time.    https://t.co/G3u2DM8SyL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShaunBaileyUK: Sadiq Khan promised to build 80,000 homes a year. He has failed to deliver 40,000 homes in 5 years.   Londoners need hom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nadhimzahawi: Watch this short film with sound on!  https://t.co/TDaGlwKHtr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_RobbieMoore: The vaccination rollout continues across #Keighley #Ilkley #Silsden the #WorthValley and the wider area at speed.  Well d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CWhittaker_MP: Brilliant advert for the vaccination and what an incredible success story for the UK. We need to keep vigilant still and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lucyallan: Every vaccination gives us hope https://t.co/I4q2I9GZK3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @redditchrachel: We've reached another milestone in the COVID Vaccine rollout with 60% of all adults in #Redditch having received their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Helen_Whately: Over 1.1 million #socialcare workers have now had their first #CovidVaccine which is fantastic. A huge thank you to ever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: It's #WorldImmunisationWeek and there's never been a more important time to be aware:   Vaccines are safe   Vaccines are e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCHQPress: Official figures show Labour councils are the worst in the country for recycling our rubbish   For councils and councillors]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delighted to launch our new campaign today.  Every vaccination gives us hope.  When you get the call, get the jab. https://t.co/2x2ikJ2Jc3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tariqahmadbt: The UK  is sending medical supplies urgently to help India  deal with a second devastating wave of Covid-19 in the co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the millions already vaccinated to protect yourself and those around you.  Every vaccination gives us hope. https://t.co/CHY0FMYepQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great news that after a huge few days for vaccinations we're able to open up to everyone aged 44.  The vaccine is our route out of this pandemic, so when it's your turn, come forward  get the jab.  Thank you to everyone involved in our national effort. https://t.co/bv3xQkYJjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to the team who administered 640,645 vaccines yesterday across the UK   I'm hugely grateful to everyone coming forward to get the vaccine. This is our route out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The heartbreaking scenes in India show that this disease isn't over yet.  We've been working this weekend to put together a package of support.  We'll keep on working with colleagues around the world to try to save lives from this awful disease. https://t.co/bXdX9KpMpD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Conservatives: On ANZAC Day, we remember the sacrifice of our closest allies, Australian and New Zealander soldiers who fought with cou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: This is the story of the UK vaccine rollout which has already saved thousands of lives.  A huge thank you to everyone inv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nadhimzahawi: Great to meet Mohamed Omer today at the Gardens of Peace pop up clinic in Hainault to see how faith leaders are supportin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimBethell: So proud.  Such progress.  Lets keep going.  https://t.co/pX8Ut85GUQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trussliz: Great news  https://t.co/0TYdxk8h8W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theresecoffey: Great progress on vaccinations https://t.co/w4LafsoZ3u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertJenrick: An amazing achievement! https://t.co/sPQxQidVmY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On May 6th, #VoteConservative to help our country build back better from this virus.  @Conservatives candidates will deliver on the people's priorities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These incredible photographs show the heroic efforts of thousands of vaccinators  volunteers in every corner of the UK who have given so much to protect the most vulnerable in our society against the virus.  https://t.co/MToXf4DhS7]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>