<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @HouseDemocrats Didn't democrats shut down restaurants 13 months ago?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RubinReport: Lebron's political views in video form.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealLathan Thats the only j song I actually like.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LibertyLockPod: 80 million people voted for this guy!? https://t.co/P6t2F4ej11]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @madisongesiotto: Media Narrative 101 https://t.co/MIosvJQgxa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CalebJHull: Shot... chaser https://t.co/5hPBrxE8mY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@endofanerajc A filling will cost like 80 to a hundred to get filled without insurance.  Dentists also have club plans; buy a "membership" with that office for a year to get discounted rates.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreckledLiberty Wait, why didn't she just wear it in the first place?    Ppl are dumb.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@morganisawizard Wow, who the fuck bringing our average down?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MagnusPanvidya Why did that dude take out his phone to harass someone, no one cares about that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bocxtop Bro, did you fail 2 years or what?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinVic @Darkstar4555 @JillEngel12 @aslavitt46 Tested vaccinations.   Also, no one forces you into the military, and school choice is a thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Johnny_Joey Who makes these steam punk version?  Woah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CyrusBaird I thought of "30-30"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IsleyResistance Nice hat you commie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtgreenee: We must stop paying people not to work in our country.  The real goal of extended shutdowns by the Dems is to make people pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Beer comes from hops. Beer has always been plant based. Fuckin loser.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Pretty easy when democrats killed 10s of millions of jobs last year.   The republican governors are the ones creating the jobs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MILFWEEED Dogs at airports are almost always smelling for explosives, not "dat loud"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirhottest Rats don't know any better]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MILFWEEED Because of your persona, my mind automatically read "dank" instead of "dark."  I was like, aint you always in a dank period though?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ATillmanBester @RashidaTlaib Have ypu seen this girl?  She was not little.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MosquedaHannah @RashidaTlaib She wasn't protecting herself, she was chasing the other girl. Check the law, that isn't self defense anymore.   I live in a state that has lenient gun laws, but if som1 is in my front lawn threatening me, and I ran OUT of my house with any weapon to attack them, id be in troubl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@solanacrystal @RashidaTlaib He did.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@humb1ed_ These signs have been up for at least 4 years...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@milkncooks She probably never has had a boyfriend with that attitude which is why gender doesn't matter to her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LarkinWilder Never been pregnant. Have accidentally peed myself multiple times.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@featuringJANE I am in this liquid state every day at my desk job. Body is there and clocked in, mind is elsewhere.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NebbyMcNebulous @featuringJANE As an adult, go to sleep.   As a child, go to 7-11 to get a slurpee and have a cig/ have more sex.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedcruz Can you help please  https://t.co/MYvkTtG6eA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dreaming9to5 @DenzelGarner1 @hxlytrin Sure, but not every situation is the same. Policing is the only public job that we scrutinize and shout "more training!" at. Why don't we do this for every public office?    Id start with congress, then onto the DMV.   Analogy, if someone who has never done your job tells you how]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dreaming9to5 @DenzelGarner1 @hxlytrin Warning shot?!?  That goes against the 4 rules of gun safety.   I doubt a taste would do anything to someone in that weight class.   They verbally told her to stop. She was a psychopath with a deadly weapon. Abre tus ojos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PetiteNicoco @RRR0BYN Dress for the job you want not the one you have. I dont agree with OP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brazen_unicorn @xccoaster @briantylercohen 40 percent is still a minority. In no world of math is 40 percent every a majority when comparing 2 sides that equal 100 percent.   Vast is also subjective, not an objective mathematical term.   We also aren't discussing legislation, so thats a straw man.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brazen_unicorn @xccoaster @briantylercohen 40 percent is a minority. Lol.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theMRC: CNN mocked Donald Trump when he suggested violent rioters were throwing things like cans of soup at police officers.  So guess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@morganisawizard Hope you're enjoying our April snow.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TweetsByBritt Ever notice how mass shootings happen where one can assume people are unarmed....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AyannaPressley You had enough money for a haircut though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mecuh What app do u use?  I haven't found an easy one to put USD into.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AOC So what youre saying is, illegal aliens voted for biden?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@endofanerajc Uhaul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Squirrely007 @JoshuaPotash I'm guessing you dont shoot handguns and any sort of distance in any sort of duress.   Also, a bullet wound in a leg can still be fatal. Abdomen area can still be fatal. Bullets are designed to rip apart the inside of tissue and typically cause hydrostatic shock to organs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrewHolden360: THREAD  Today, President Biden announced his intention to end the war in Afghanistan, to great media fanfare.  You may]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rongeisler I'm sure you were referring to the action of standing up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@featuringJANE I've been worn down all the way to LOL.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays The problem with this survey is that I dont drink coke, ever, so I would have to answer "no," thus, skewing the intended results.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roastmalone_ Jnco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PPathole @elonmusk @SpaceX @Tesla Thats coincidence, not irony.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders What?!  No, it doesn't.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PetiteNicoco @heckyessica Vitamins will make you sick if taken on an empty stomach. Especially zinc rich ones.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Iatenitethot What is this, 1917?  Who uses clips regularly anymore? #magazine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@featuringJANE NSFW onlyfans cookie ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseSymotiuk @VGanMisanthrope @RBReich Blacks are committing crimes at about 2 times the rate of whites when you take into account population (per capita) https://t.co/FwsXo69Uej  https://t.co/69QnF20Zjl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseSymotiuk @VGanMisanthrope @RBReich B) If you wanna talk numbers, maybe ask why there are more blacks in jail.. https://t.co/TSDlpHAxCc  https://t.co/ejIXH1R8wk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseSymotiuk @VGanMisanthrope @RBReich A) you ignored my point entirely.  You said that cops killing blacks is a huge problem and to ignore anecdotal evidence that suggests otherwise. I agree on the anecdotal part, which is why I showed imperical data. 235 out of 2 mil is a statistical 0 as a "major problem"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseSymotiuk @VGanMisanthrope @RBReich 2 million blacks were arrested in 2019  235 blacks shot and killed by police same year.   Larger trend looks like cops aren't killing blacks in droves.   Only took two Google searches, one for each stat.  ANalYSis https://t.co/FwsXo69Uej  https://t.co/S4JLwc8bcV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slooterman You should avoid eating charcoal altogether...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roastmalone_ Only boys use tinder.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@g0th_gh0ul Nah ill stay healthy.   Facts aren't "shaming" anyone  https://t.co/jidYuF6nIi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MILFWEEED https://t.co/tsbpfKya05]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cernovich I didnt register my car for 3 years. Got one $40 dollar citation. Came out 300 dollars on top.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mags_mclaugh You could be a doctor, a dentist, a teach... wait a min on that last one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@endofanerajc Compromise and cry at work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Boogiiqueen Iowa did.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NakedSavior: DMX getting the mostly white Woodstock 99 audience to repeatedly shout the n word https://t.co/UhQOghf4cE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@flippedhatnupe Rental car agencies sold a lot of their stock last year, now supply and demand is just fucked for their business.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justinuul @charlie_steele @endofanerajc I thought her comment was clever. Hence, my question.  Not sarcasm.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlie_steele @endofanerajc I think youre referring to @AOC ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlateauUkok @actshually By working a w2 job that taxes are taken out. Workaround is working through temp agencies.  I worked in a place that was mainly alien staffed and thats how they did it.   Temp agency set it all up, paid the taxes, and then gave employees cash remainder.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@endofanerajc How are you not wifed up yet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GregAbbott_TX: Biden is threatening our 2nd Amendment rights.  He just announced a new liberal power grab to take away our guns.  We wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Check out our handy assault rifle diagram, then get the poster: https://t.co/iWvMJtGkGU https://t.co/5ZdWTsG3GK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@True_Canuck1 I encourage everyone to buy a firearm. Just because you broke the governments rules shouldn't disbarred you from being equal to everyone else.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@morganisawizard Artifacts of a past time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@featuringJANE Guys, I think she wants to play pathfinder with us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TacoSalad85 @PetiteNicoco I'm not Korean, but ill take the higher ground.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timcast Where is the other toe?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tinahseattle @AriBerman Have you ever had something grilled with charcoal?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FunnyBoydston @featuringJANE Nerds usually do anal before DnD.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AZFakeLawyer Lol in the store that sells cigs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PetiteNicoco I like how all "white people" dress like "50 year old white women"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheKanehB:  https://t.co/c6Zv7pwrvq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@writeden @roastmalone_ If you wanna see the top of the line...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirhottest I think her first policy is "being black"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidFite: This is how government works. Remind me why we need it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cheesetrader1 We had an 8 lb turkey in Thanksgiving for 6 people, with leftovers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yeeterboi24 Its called #tool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jimgeraghty: Texas Covid cases and deaths are down since the state rescinded its mask mandate.   https://t.co/0LXe6H6lxM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CureHipHop: https://t.co/nYgE9NrZ8R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kathy4Truth: I'm Kathy Barnette and I'm running to become the first Black Republican Woman elected to the US Senate. Ill be the voice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Leaders in both parties should work together to make it easier to uphold our right to bear arms.   Fuck a tax stamp #ATF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirhottest Every damn day man.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyCaller: WATCH: CBS and @60Minutes excluded context from Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis in which he explains the steps his government to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@waltercool11 @toastofcoast88 @disclosetv @SpiritAirlines Doubt she's following orders. She doesn't understand her own company's policy and just wants to exert power over the white people.   Policy is in "plane" language... hehe.  https://t.co/eLKbJsGi0E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jmpalmieri @HillaryClinton She is the bully.   #deplorables]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottWGonzalez @7thtemplar @mansoortshams Actually, the m16 was the military version.   #facts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlobalJitterbug @Japtain_America @mansoortshams Per capita, cars are more deadly.   About 3x as many guns in the US but vehicle deaths are around 30 to 50 thousand/ year, slightly less than gun deaths.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KBucRay @tentacle_pup @mansoortshams Lol so when you shoot at one then actuate the action while the rest attack you... assuming you hit the first...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Joanne68jojo @RubyWatch63 @mansoortshams And it failed miserably in vietnam.   Lr308 would have served better (as proven by adoption of Asian militaries), and no one wants to ban those lololol.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>