<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeffreytran @pjamesdf NKS was fun to think about in graduate school, but its really only the Mathematica coding that Ive carried forward (and perhaps the general NKS emphasis on plotting for understanding separate from specific concepts).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@openidtry Mapping of BCR sequence to antigen is super complex and Id think this would be difficult. However, it would be a really interesting research question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeffreytran @pjamesdf I use Mathematica for rapid prototyping and most of the analyses that I post to Twitter. I use Python for bioinformatics and JavaScript for interactive visualization. Id prefer the broader reproducibility of doing analyses in Python, but Im still much faster with Mathematica.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BallouxFrancois @pjie2 @marcotrizzino Ah. Yes. That's definitely the theoretical expectation. Will be interested to see the preprint. Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justthefacts85 We need to be doing the immunological and clinical work to develop and bring to market updated boosters. We need a candidate targeted at B.1.351, at P.1, etc... After initial vaccine rollout, if a variant continues to spread, distribute boosters targeting variant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BallouxFrancois @pjie2 @marcotrizzino I think this "fitness decay" is mostly due to rising tide of population fitness. B.1.1.7 may be ~50% more transmissible than wildtype+D614G, but with growth of B.1.427, B.1.429, B.1.526, etc... it's no longer 50% more fit than other viruses circulating.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@K_G_Andersen Totally. The relative competitiveness is really only clear once two lineage are at higher frequency. In NY, we initially saw both B.1.1.7 and B.1.526 expanding at the same logistic growth rate, but once in direct competition, B.1.1.7 has gained the upper hand.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julietast2 @vnminin The analysis above relies on variant frequency estimated from genomic data to be representative of a state as a whole in order to partition state-level case counts. For CA, there is likely more of a geographic split in what's getting sequenced than in other states.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vnminin The NS3 surveillance sampling should be pretty decent at getting a random sample from within a state. These are a fraction of positive specimens from large testing entities. That said CA may have an issue that other states largely lack with difference in north/south circulation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@K_G_Andersen Agreed here about distinguishing introductions and community transmission. I discounted P.1 trend when looking a couple weeks ago because the raw frequency was still low. Now however we see still see a strong trend in states like Illinois with close to 30% P.1 frequency.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pjie2 This would be good to test. Cumulative cases is not a perfect proxy for proportion of the population infected, but should be largely comparable across states.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Growth of P.1 alongside probable decrease in vaccine effectiveness suggests it's all the more important to get as many people vaccinated as possible as vaccination can still suppress circulation of P.1; it's just that the bar for herd immunity is higher. 13/13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mutations in P.1 suggest partial escape from antibody binding, which is borne out in drops in neutralization titer. I would expect P.1 to show some decrease in vaccine effectiveness, but remain largely effective. Figure from Wu et al (https://t.co/Oy7DtCHxQA). 12/13 https://t.co/FQtTiidBUQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination will continue bring down overall transmission rate, where I expect transmission chains of non-variant viruses to largely die out in the coming weeks. Variant viruses B.1.1.7 and P.1 raise the bar for the level of vaccination required to control the epidemic. 11/13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking at this same data on a log-scale makes the absolute growth of P.1 cases in CA, FL, IL, MA, MI, NY and WA quite clear. 10/13 https://t.co/egeaZ1qRP9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can use the same approach with state-level case counts and frequency data to estimate case counts for B.1.1.7, B.1.351 and P.1 variants. Here, we see that P.1 is still a minor (but growing) contribution but where some states like IL and WA have a larger P.1 share. 9/13 https://t.co/1wi971Srwv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[However, plotting partitioned case counts on a log-scale clearly shows the continued growth in absolute case counts of P.1. 8/13 https://t.co/raMmZ66aeu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To address this we can take these frequency estimates alongside case counts from @CDCGov and use frequencies to partition case counts by variant. Doing so results in this plot for the US, where the large majority of the epidemic is due to B.1.1.7 and non-B.1.351/P.1 viruses. 7/13 https://t.co/JV0ZTfkiUS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Given that P.1 frequency is growing rapidly, but overall cases are generally falling, the question becomes are vaccines and other control measures enough to curb spread of P.1 in absolute case counts? 6/13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The observation of faster logistic growth of P.1 compared to B.1.1.7 suggests that P.1 may have a transmission advantage over B.1.1.7 in the US and may continue to gain ground even as B.1.1.7 comes to dominate the virus population. 5/13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We generally see more rapid logistic growth of P.1 across individual states as well. These 9 were chosen as those with the most data. All these plots only go to Apr 14, as there is a necessary lag to the genomic data as samples are processed. 4/13 https://t.co/8ImsE87rau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm plotting this with the unusual "logit" y-axis (with 1%, 10%, 50%, etc...) because a straight line in logit space is indicative of logistic growth. This sort of plot makes it easy to compare logistic growth rate of frequency between lineages with different frequencies. 3/13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here, using data from @GISAID, we see that in terms of frequencies across the US, P.1 has been undergoing more rapid logistic growth in frequency than B.1.1.7, while B.1.351 has been slower than B.1.1.7. 2/13 https://t.co/jPXUC6nxiE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just as we can decompose the US #COVID19 epidemic into a B.1.1.7 epidemic and a non-B.1.1.7 epidemic, we can further partition by variants of concern B.1.1.7, B.1.351 and P.1, where it's clear that P.1 has been gaining ground. 1/13 https://t.co/vl3l1JT3ZD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JPWeiland @DrEricDing @NYCHealthCommr @davechokshi You're right. This is important and would flag Illinois as a place to watch closely. https://t.co/543GP3mFAa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 And maybe to clarify slightly: The rapidly growing fraction of P.1 across the US (https://t.co/GnlDIzwqv3) is an critical data point that tells us it's an intrinsically fit variant. However, for assessment of local control measures I think one should quantify absolute P.1 cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 I think important to approach this with counts rather than frequency. Here, I did something similar to https://t.co/6fjeL9VT8y and split cases in New York state (not NYC) based on P.1 frequency to estimate P.1 counts. They were increasing, but have potentially slowed in April. https://t.co/WgVV0baQzU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chicken3gg @firefoxx66 You have to be careful with the most recent days in https://t.co/UxxQ4aVNIK as theres often little data to compute frequencies and few sequenced genomes may not be representative. Im only comfortable estimating lineage frequencies in India to the very beginning of April.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RonenV Thats lovely. I was expecting this to be a quote, but if so its not obvious from Google.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@akageleiry I was trying to use the phrase contribution of B.1.1.7 to avoid a causal interpretation (as opposed to B.1.1.7 lead to X more cases). I think you can approach this question as: if all the B.1.1.7 imports were non-B.1.1.7, how much smaller would their transmission chains be?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TWenseleers @JDarn6 @my_helix Thanks for this Tom. I was using a data cutoff of April 11 to account for lag in genomic data availability.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EliasHasle Yes, other lineages (particularly P.1) are growing rapidly, but they are still low frequency. There are two major epidemics in the US: B.1.1.7 and non-variant viruses. In this framing, there are separate epidemics of P.1, B.1.351, etc but these are still relatively small.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BenStillerSux69 @quantumVerd The former. Both B.1.1.7 and non-B.1.1.7 spreading in non-vaccinated population, but instinsic contagiousness of B.1.1.7 has made it spread faster in this population.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dave_andersen Thanks for this. Case data was directly from CDC, but this would make sense.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@geodesicvoyager Yes. Good point. The data cutoff here was chosen because genomic data is necessarily lagged. Recent declines in case counts may indeed suggest this inflection point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@quantumVerd Based on neutralization titer data we expect both vaccine-derived and natural immunity to work against B.1.1.7. The transmission advantage of B.1.1.7 appears to be from non-immune escape factors (I believe primarily higher viral load resulting in greater chance of transmission).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That said, there are multiple factors that should be resulting in continued improvements to the US COVID-19 epidemic (vaccination, continued build up of natural immunity from infection, improved seasonality). It's unclear to me how much of a wave from B.1.1.7 to expect. 10/10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is consistent with what's been seen in the UK and in Europe and supports a transmission advantage of B.1.1.7. Thus we see that the same conditions that can lead to control of older non-B.1.1.7 viruses and Rt &lt; 1, can still result in growth of B.1.1.7 and Rt &gt; 1. 9/10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Again, plotting non-B.1.1.7 cases (in gray) and B.1.1.7 cases (in blue) on a log scale makes the separation of growth and decline more obvious. 8/10 https://t.co/EA2H3KPH30]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can see the same pattern repeated in individual states with growing B.1.1.7 epidemics on top of a largely resolving non-B.1.1.7 background. Some states like California have less of a B.1.1.7 epidemic and some like Colorado and Michigan have more of a B.1.1.7 epidemic. 7/10 https://t.co/z2v96ddAva]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plotting each on a log scale makes growth and decline more obvious. Without the contribution of B.1.1.7 there would have been ~32k cases on April 7 rather than the observed ~65k cases. 6/10 https://t.co/3FBAp37ckE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is showing B.1.1.7 cases in blue stacked on top of non-B.1.1.7 cases in gray, where it's clear that non-B.1.1.7 cases have continued to decline, while B.1.1.7 cases have continued to increase. 5/10 https://t.co/c1anRPp4G8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can use the estimated frequency of B.1.1.7 to split cases reported by @CDCGov (https://t.co/8QBo2Mfspp) into non-B.1.1.7 cases and B.1.1.7 cases. In the following I've applied a 7-day smoothing to case trajectories. 4/10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This pattern is repeated across individual states. These six were chosen as states with plentiful genomic data and to provide geographic diversity. B.1.1.7 is dominating throughout the US, except for New York and surroundings where B.1.526 is co-circulating. 3/10 https://t.co/h3Xe4LS15g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If we look at virus frequencies in the US using data in @GISAID, we can see that the 7-day weighted frequency of B.1.1.7 has been growing consistently since January and is now over 50% in the US. 2/10 https://t.co/bz7o9YQfxR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are effectively two #COVID19 epidemics in the US at this moment; one largely resolving epidemic comprised of non-variant viruses and one growing epidemic of B.1.1.7. Together they have resulted in a near-plateau of cases throughout much of the spring. 1/10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@quipupe Were now estimating logistic growth rate in the latest versions of the ncov workflow. This highlights clades that are increasing in frequency. Discussion surrounding parameter choices etc can be found here: https://t.co/rF00ttNE5u. Really nice work with your analysis here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WesPegden @sarperotto Yep. Im assuming slow down of B.1.1.7 and B.1.526 is all due to competition between the two now that they are both common.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@video4me https://t.co/ORiVmZxWD2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WesPegden @sarperotto I believe that most of the effect is from "rising tide" where overall population fitness is increasing from multiple competing lineages and so lineage in question has less relative advantage. See for example B.1.526 and B.1.1.7 in New York. https://t.co/8svAtPj13J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarperotto Sorry about this. I've been fitting logistic growth rates to the past 45 days of frequencies (as they tend not to be fully constant over time). I've now cleaned up the plot to emphasize the fit is just over these last 45 days. https://t.co/FMaOpGl3uJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scottleibrand @MHowell55189 My anecdotal hypothesis is that the main driver for emergence is passaging through a partially immune population. Hence why we didn't see emergence during initial wave. Seattle has relatively low seroprevalence and so I'd see lower risk for emergence here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kevinpurcell @elaine_hali And we're (really @wcassias) has been keeping an updated @nextstrain view up to date at https://t.co/HHsDFufasW.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kevinpurcell @elaine_hali WA DOH is putting out the following document every week: https://t.co/Jiy3Bv3Z9h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LongDesertTrain Part of this may be due to repeated introductions from Bangladesh where B.1.351 got a good start and is now quite prevalent, but it's still an important observation. Would be good to assess consistency of competition across geographies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elaine_hali Groups are working on this (and this is happening in Washington State). I agree it's incredibly important.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As both B.1.617 and B.1.1.7 further increase in frequency they will be more directly in competition and it should become clear which lineage has the evolutionary advantage. 5/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It appears however that B.1.617 was at a higher starting point in January and so frequency at the end of March (we lack data for April) is highest for B.1.617 at around ~45% frequency. 4/5 https://t.co/3zWJHHj8lW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can fit a logistic growth model to the full genomic dataset from India for these three lineages, where we see logistic growth as "linear on a logit scale". Each of these lineages is estimated to have similar logistic growth rates of ~0.3 per week. 3/5 https://t.co/90u7rtVAJh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is a @nextstrain view of @GISAID data that focuses on viruses from India and highlights emerging lineages B.1.1.7 (in blue), B.1.351 (in green) and B.1.617 (in orange). Interactive version at https://t.co/gOkc6zxxgG. 2/5 https://t.co/tTEq3NPfiQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's hard for me to infer the degree to which new variants are driving the surge in cases in India, but we are seeing rapid growth in frequency of multiple viral variants. 1/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZacharyCohn Very roughly it's a moderate increase in capacity but large shift in prioritization in academic labs and DOHs plus the CDC coming on board (they weren't really sequencing prior to Jan).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZacharyCohn There was actually a lot of sequencing before Jan (not as much as now obviously but much more than 100-300 genomes per month). The issue was sample prioritization where prior to Jan there wasn't a push to sequence very recent samples.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[International investment is incredibly important here. I'd so much prefer an additional 1000 genomes from South America or Africa to an additional 10,000 from the US or Europe. 14/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sequencing throughput has been increasing in Africa and South America, but now lags behind the US and Europe due to recent national investments in sequencing capacity in the US and Europe. 13/14 https://t.co/4KqYQ59h69]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Work by South African and Brazilian scientists to quickly identify and share data on B.1.351 and P.1 did the world an enormous favor. 12/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[However, SARS-CoV-2 variants are emerging throughout the world and only focusing on improving genomic surveillance within national borders is short sighted. The primary goal of this surveillance is to be to able to formulate vaccine updates with sufficient lead time. 11/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Other countries have also been increasing sequencing throughput in response to the emergence of variants of concern and we see the US now matching sequencing throughput of the UK and the rest of Europe when considered separately. 10/14 https://t.co/00Zrup6ifi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With ~30,000 genomes in the past 30 days, we can reliably catch variants at a 0.02% frequency threshold in the US (geometric distribution with 99% probability of detection). Again, this is remarkable. 9/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this case, having a very large volume of sequences with good turnaround time should be sufficient to characterize variants while they're still at low frequency. 8/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[However, for variants in particular, analysis focuses on frequency, where we particularly care about variants that are increasing rapidly in frequency across different geographies. 7/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Much attention has focused on proportion of cases sequenced, where in the past 30 days the US has sequenced about 1.7% of cases, behind countries such the UK (30%), Switzerland (5%) and Germany (2.5%). Data from https://t.co/IRP3Q2xInd. 6/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This increase in sequencing has been driven by the CDC and by non-CDC groups (mostly academic labs and state lab health departments). 5/14 https://t.co/AP2wJpb0UC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[However, with investments in sequencing capacity, the US had rapidly increased this count, ramping from 100-300 in Dec 2020 to over 30,000 in April 2021. This is a remarkable achievement and I'm no longer worried about novel variants escaping detection in the US. 4/14 https://t.co/qaXzmAwiPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Throughout the fall, the US had just 100-300 genomes available that were sampled, sequenced and shared in the previous 30 days. 3/14 https://t.co/gGUNT9kmjO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My favorite metric for genomic surveillance is the number of cases that have been sampled, sequenced and shared publicly to @GISAID in the previous 30 days. By incorporating both sequencing volume and turnaround time, it tells you how much is known about current circulation. 2/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When variants of concern were first identified in late Dec, the US was not where it needed to be in terms of genomic surveillance. However, with considerable ramp up by the CDC, state labs and academic groups, we now have a remarkable genomic surveillance system. 1/14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@knahra1 This would be my first pick at the moment. But possible ranking will change in the coming weeks / months. B.1.526 would be my second pick at the moment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TonyBurnetti Definitely agreed here. But recent evolution has shown that the virus is malleable in terms of antigenicity and would suggest that selection primarily for antigenic drift would likely be effective.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gsgs2 Yes. This is important. Much of selection has been to increase replication which increases viral load which increases transmission. Antigenic impacts are largely knock-on effects. But that doesn't mean selection for antigenic drift in the coming years won't be effective.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TonyBurnetti @sarajean323 Well put. For flu, the common pattern is pandemic followed by seasonal circulation due to continued evolution. This is my expectation for SARS-CoV-2 at this point. Another seasonal respiratory virus thrown into the mix.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@czarinaflo @devm2025 @paulg Well summarized.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocJeffD That would be my (surface) reading, but it would good to have modeling to back this up. If  a dosing strategy reduces incidence relative to other strategies it will at least somewhat counteract promotion of evolution by partial immunity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VerrethRebecca @chris60323690 I don't think we have the genetic data for 1918, but 2009 flu pandemic did not show this sort of remarkable evolution despite infecting 1/3 of the world in its first year. Generally some viruses are more antigenically evolvable than others, but I don't know what makes them so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@3DiMMUNE A partially immune population (through vaccination and natural infection) would necessarily tilt transmission somewhat to B.1.351 vs B.1.1.7 relative to baseline favoring B.1.1.7. I don't know whether partial immunity is enough to flip to favoring B.1.351 however.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@3DiMMUNE https://t.co/uz2mEz46Mh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmeshAA This may shift with increasing population immunity, but the best data point I have here is that B.1.351 failed to invade in the UK when B.1.1.7 was predominate, despite having ample opportunity. This suggests B.1.1.7 has higher transmission rate in this setting. https://t.co/aLiJCtDff5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanPaulman You've likely had asymptotic or pauci-symptomatic infections every 5-10 years in your adult life. Or at least, this what serology data tells us. https://t.co/L1hEc9BlNM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thorntonrules In the continued evolution scenario, it would mean flu-like voluntary annual vaccination. I would not support non-ending mitigation measures.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottVMeyers If true, I'd expect another seasonal "flu-like" respiratory virus to circulate every year. Pre-existing immunity will limit spread and disease, but there could be a "COVID season". Response should be vaccination (like with flu) not lockdowns.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(Sorry I've been absent during the past ~2 months. I needed a break from Twitter. I'll try to provide more frequent updates going forward.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This continual cat-and-mouse scenario is what plays out with seasonal influenza, where new viruses emerge and spread, but leave a wake of population immunity that creates pressure for further evolutionary innovation. 15/15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On the other hand, currently selected mutations are arising in a context of population immunity engendered to original "wild-type" viruses and immunity raised to antigenic drifted viruses like B.1.351 may push evolution in a new direction. 14/15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On one hand, convergence would suggest that in ~1-2 year's time SARS-CoV-2 will have arrived at its destination having stacked up all the relevant mutations that are currently emerging. 13/15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The million dollar question here is, of course, whether this pace of evolution will be sustained year-after-year. I don't have a good answer to this. 12/15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As discussed previously (https://t.co/le1IacQYcX), the currently observed rate of evolution in S1 is rapid compared to the equivalent domain in influenza virus owing to accumulation of S1 mutations in the VOC viruses. 11/15 https://t.co/bNAeSHCFbn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Though there haven't been obviously superior competitors to B.1.1.7, variant viruses are continuing to emerge across the world. Genomic surveillance should also be global in its endeavor. 10/15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Examples of competing lineages of note include B.1.525 (with spike mutations Q52R, 69-70del, 144del, E484K, Q677H and F888L, common in Nigeria https://t.co/SXRSl2i00W) and B.1.617 (with spike mutations E154K, L452R, E484Q and P681R, common in India https://t.co/09N6dor1TC). 9/15 https://t.co/X1zeGP9YZI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since January, there has been frequent emergence of competing lineages with large numbers of spike mutations, but by-and-large B.1.1.7, B.1.351 and P.1 have remained at the forefront. 8/15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The point here is that it's not that B.1.1.7, B.1.351 and P.1 have unique mutations not present in other circulating viruses, it's that these VOC lineages have acquired some of the most extensive suites of spike S1 mutations seen in circulating viruses. 7/15 https://t.co/bwnOGNToRs]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>