<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rob_Ruadh Same blocked just now. Guess she doesn't like to be called a snitch.  Sounds like a great Cafe to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FlashVvV All for a QR code. Disgusting. Yes, she's a low life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@palma_edyta Same. Can't believe she named them. Bitch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out this snitch. Can't stand these people. https://t.co/Fw7pEpEZeI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jillastark snitchesgetstitches. Can't believe you named them. Low life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bach_mp: Minister Tierney mistakenly emailed me her Budget press release today, with comments from Labor spinners!  Labor doesn't even]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GayleRobMurphy Same here. I follow you, but your tweets don't seem to come up on my timeline ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tonytardio Look at @michaelobrienmp go  good to see him fired up!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elizabethrosie  so true. I'm a pro now at wiping a nose on the go. Gone are the days when we can be sick and spend the whole day on the couch watching movies ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@palma_edyta My son definitely seems to deal with it better than me. He's always full of energy despite having a cold. I'm just forever tired haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elizabethrosie And they seem to deal with it well. My son's still on the go, I think it effects me more, old age ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@francton Yeah not sure if it's true or not. But apparently it's what many Indians believe. He said he's got a lot of family over there saying trucks with supplies are being delayed on purpose ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisHaworth368 @thorsome1 A few more 'snap lockdowns' and he'll change his mind. I hope he's loving the masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ronInBendigo: Culpable.  @DanielAndrewsMP: Culpable @JennyMikakos: Culpable @LisanevilleMP: Culpable @MartinPakulaMP: Culpable @JamesMe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leighsales Typical responses by the #IstandwithDictatorDan cult ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simmogoesracing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PWBBOOMER Probably had it 4 times already. We've all had the symptoms multiple times.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rob_Ruadh Everytime he gets snotty, I think here we go again  I mean he literally sneezes and coughs in face, so there is no way I'm not getting sick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dissin Thank you. I actually bought some zinc + and omega fish oil this afternoon. I thought I had a great immune system, clearly not ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dandanstk We are lucky, his childcare is relaxed. All the kids are snotty, cough and sneeze and they don't say anything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had one cold all last year, this year my son started childcare, I've had one cold a month  first world problem I know, just annoying.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An Indian taxi driver told me what is happening in India is all political. Apparently their Federal Government has been blocking ventilators  medical supplies to certain cities who are controlled by the opposition. The purpose is to make the opposition look incompetent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnforca Isn't it funny that tiktoc is Chinese, and the app is being used to push evil shit around the world.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AusMiray It's a big F*CK NO!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stevoB59: The #FigjamDan effect. Foley claims Victoria has the best ambulance service in the country. Gold standard? AMAs Whitelaw s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_davidlimbrick: Proud to stand by my colleague @TimQMLCNorthVic today who introduced the Victorian Liberal Democrats first private memb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The politicians outraged about the border closure with India don't give a sh*t about them, just like they didn't give a sh*t about anyone impacted by the Federal  State border closures since March 2020. It's all political, it's all a hoax  we are being sucked into it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@navychick1993 @NattyEyece Best answer ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boongburg @michaelobrienmp @MatthewGuyMP ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelobrienmp: Its shocking that Victorians are forced into an Uber because they cant get an ambulance when they need one.  Labor h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AusAntiLeft I see it was a stampede.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SubinthePub @AlboMP I'm pretty sure he would have said "you've got this Victoria".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: BREAKING. Bill and Melinda will no longer be fucking each other, but will continue to work together to fuck the rest of us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VicGovDH Do people realise the trial for these vaccines end in 2023? Anyone who gets it is basically part of the trial. Except you don't get paid and no one can be held accountable for ANY side effects you develop in the years to come. All for a virus with 99.98% recovery if under 70.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VicGovDH https://t.co/mwASXh4Jif]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sassyausgirl She's a sell-out. Been talking up the vaccine for a while.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AllanRaskall Can we also have a photo of you getting your prostate checked? What about the flu vaccine? Any selfies getting them?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimSmithMP @abcnews They are all disgraceful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnforca Part of me feels very sorry for her. But the other part just thinks she's a f*cking idiot. She did this to herself. It's not some unfortunate accident, it's a risk she decided to take as a mother.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez They are all frauds. Silent all last year, so this is just political.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigKellyMP: Dr Zelenko nominated for Nobel Prize - and what a worthy winner hed be.   https://t.co/sd2k6839Zi  Hes saved thousands]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Layanaround @DMasa @15woody20 @SteMac81 @VictorianCHO So for a virus that is new, they already know long term effects.  What about the flu? People who got influenza sometimes take up to 6 months to fully cover  hmmm sounds like long covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dobbo67b @VictorianCHO ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VictorianCHO https://t.co/bxuhqh9saX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caseyphoenix @VictorianCHO Then you'll never feel safe. Because most of the population won't be having it. Worry about yourself, your vaccinated then why do you care if others aren't?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lolita4813 @PRS1611 @VictorianCHO What if it's you who got the wrong opinion? Maybe you should get a second opinion.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Layanaround @DMasa @15woody20 @SteMac81 @VictorianCHO Long covid  ahhh they got you good.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Redback @DMasa @VictorianCHO Look up the meaning of "long term".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@craigphase8 I'm guessing you have to sit on the floor  they are so cute ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@monica_2978 Exactly. Why wasn't everyone outraged when they first closed the borders and we all became prisoners in our own Country. They are 14 months too late with their anger.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@monica_2978 Cheers Monica ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MRobertsQLD Thank you Malcolm ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MRobertsQLD: We have opposed Digital Passports from the start  will support your bill Craig when you introduce it.  Digital Passpor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BabaBoon17 @LekkaMercedez @BurlingSharon Same, it's really annoying. I always check comments and make sure it's legitimate. It's happened a lot of times.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OzraeliAvi None.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez @BurlingSharon Montreal had a protest, but it's a lot smaller. I think that is in the US. Old photo.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez @BurlingSharon I don't think that's Montreal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AusHumanRights Here you are 14 months after our rights have continuously been trampled on. You are useless and should be ashamed of yourselves.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @umustrise: India  The Truth. A must watch clip. Wuhan 2.0 X 10. Long Live the Truth  https://t.co/xYkDG7XyTB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @G_P_L_M: #Lyon anti-government protest #1erMai  https://t.co/sghexKvQB8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iainAclark: @HaydnNuff @Plandemic10 This one is good. https://t.co/xsNNcosSzj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaiKate108 It's insane. Borders should have never closed. I remember when Victorian's were not allowed to return to their homes. It's all criminal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe if everyone was this outraged with the borders closing back in early 2020, we wouldn't be where we are now, with Australian citizens still stuck overseas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @R_S_P_H: It's #WorldImmunisationWeek and we want to know if you'd be in favour of needing proof of having a Covid-19 vaccine (vaccine p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez Unfortunately I think they needed a negative test to enter. So it's not freedom.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigKellyMP: Following the publication of the latest peer-reviewed study on Ivermectin, I call on the head of Australias National Cov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@daisymay4263 It's a bodysuit, so clips from that area.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NathanWVR They sure do ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NathanWVR Unfortunately I can't imagine anyone blasting ride the lightening these days. They'd only be offended.  Love Metallica.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On my way home from dinner. Car next to us, windows down, car full of girls and guys blasting One Direction, perfect. What happened to blasting trance or techno? Or am I showing my age ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @monica_2978: worst Premier in Australia?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JulesBackup8 @BabaBoon17 @AusMiray @dnforca https://t.co/qNTV7wqs55]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BabaBoon17 @JulesBackup8 @AusMiray @dnforca I'm hurt man https://t.co/zFEi40s9i0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JulesBackup8 @BabaBoon17 @AusMiray @dnforca https://t.co/2VHtNHRTHP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JulesBackup8 @BabaBoon17 @AusMiray @dnforca You said I was the best  I see I'm tossed to the side now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shravaka:  G'day patriots. New patriot worth a follow... Give a warm AusTwitter welcome to @skunk_cheeky  https://t.co/sG2zEHu8B5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Evadregand @AlboMP  as what? Minister of Transport or Foreign Affairs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bubblytest @AlboMP Read up on the Australian criminal justice system. It's Police who investigate alleged crimes, not politicians.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PazzaDons2012 @3AW693 I must be extremely selfish. I've never worn a mask. And I'm definitely not going to wear one to make you feel safe. Your health is your responsibility, not mine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamanthaBarba10 @bfriendmyles @PeterDutton_MP Ahhhh yes, almost forgot about those.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bfriendmyles @SamanthaBarba10 @PeterDutton_MP Don't be mad Myles, it can be confronting hearing the truth at times. Goodluck with all your businesses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bfriendmyles @SamanthaBarba10 @PeterDutton_MP You'd be destroyed in Court buddy. Run along to your businesses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamanthaBarba10 @bfriendmyles @PeterDutton_MP His legal team ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bfriendmyles @PeterDutton_MP Myles you sound like a 5 year old. Get a life mate. And you are wrong. He has a lot of supporters, including me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JWSpry: Pandemic and climate change share a connection  Both are useful pretexts for mass social control, while both are essentially,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: Vitamin D Hydroxychloroquine Ivermectin Budesonide Hugs and smiles  Experimental mRNA Experimental chimp virus Mas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CraigKellyMP https://t.co/bxuhqhr32v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JacinthaGeia21: A moment I won't forget https://t.co/SWYsGn0gZR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke Happy Birthday to your Dad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Make no mistake, this will not be a short term thing, and it will not be reserved only for international travel.   Unless w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@freethought202 This is being said and done to push people into taking the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine passports are here! https://t.co/Qmcstb1gkg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CovidBlindWife Very sorry to hear this. I really hope her vision improves. Must be a nightmare for her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidBlindWife: No improvement in my wifes blindness today   12 days on steroids   48 days going blind  52 days since #AstraZeneca #va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KirralieS: Parents and concerned citizens are fed up with the aggressive gender agenda. The push back has begun.  https://t.co/ZtSEU7WI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Carmilla5: #India https://t.co/qbAH1dh9eM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnforca Had to do that for months in Victoria. I hated it. Eventually people stopped asking. But I think your mask mandate should hopefully end on Friday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CoDWHroyiB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tigertuffmark @abcnews It's really embarrassing. Read some of the comments, some people are really into this article ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abcnews An article about a girl getting her period  #DefundTheABC NOW! I don't want to pay for this rubbish.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>