<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Asap_Rockit @Tutsy22 Lie Lie. Haba! FIFA 21 wey dem never crack? Haba nah bro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make it a daily habit to wear a mask to avoid being infected with COVID-19. Stay responsible, by protecting yourself, and your loved ones. Stay masked, Stay safe.  #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether #MaskOnNaija https://t.co/LWcYUw9FNN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whenever you are in public, wear a mask and you can save a thousand lives by that simple action. Whether its to the grocery store or a simple walk, mask up to reduce your chances of contracting COVID 19.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/lw84aSk1pA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're not out of the storm yet, your mask is still as important as ever. Make sure you have it on in public places to keep yourself and your community safe  #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether #MaskOnNaija https://t.co/hDhNpQdsn7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whether it's for groceries or a simple run to the filling station, make sure your mask is on you at all times.  #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether #MaskOnNaija https://t.co/vM7g4YPGBP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No let person deceive you, COVID -19 still dey around. Shine your eyes, use your face mask and dey wash your hands well well make you no contract the virus.  #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether #MaskUpNaija https://t.co/GKmF7RsGjx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make this holiday season special and COVID free by spending it indoors with your family and loved ones. Their safety is your responsibility and you can avoid contracting COVID-19 by social distancing and wearing your mask if you need to go outdoors. #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether https://t.co/OEa5W5KeGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 numbers are rising again and it's important you stay in the clear by following  simple health guidelines. Wear your mask in public places and use hand sanitizers regularly to avoid contracting the virus.   #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether #maskup https://t.co/UHSheOwo3x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 is still very much around. With numbers rising across the country, it's important to keep yourself and your loved ones safe by masking up. Your community needs you, mask up today and let's fight the pandemic together.  #MaskUp #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether https://t.co/rgB7YGo7yC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hangouts are back! And they can remain safe as long as you wear your masks and maintain social distancing in public. Stay safe and keep the fun going!  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/2cxccsoaNn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Naija, the wave is not yet past us. Join us in normalizing the simple act of wearing a mask. We can make Nigeria a pandemic free nation, #MaskOnNaija!  #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether https://t.co/JNW8RHFo22]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the brainchild of our massive nationwide rally to provide adequate healthcare facilities in the face of the pandemic, Ganduje assured the donated facilities would be adequately utilized.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have flattened the curve of the pandemic in Kano State. These words, quoted from a speech given by Kano State Governor, Umar Ganduje, summarizes the entire goal of CACOVID. Speaking while commissioning the Dangote Isolation Center,  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/Owb220oHEu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we celebrate 60 years of Nigeria's unity today, we ask for the same unity against a pandemic that has threatened our existence and the efforts of our heroes past. Happy Independence Day Nigeria! Let's keep staying alive together.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fight for Independence was a struggle we made as a people, united against the shackles of colonialism.   #HappyIndependenceDay #StayingAliveTogeher #StaySafe https://t.co/4udaIB4oMk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Receiving his states share of the donations, Governor Hope Uzodinmma of IMO State, echoed our thoughts and lauded the contribution we had made so far. The state received over 172,000 bags of essential food materials like Rice, garri, pasta and more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When we began the distribution of palliatives to communities across Nigeria, our goal was simple; to alleviate the vulnerable in the society from the effects of the pandemic.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/4L0Z1oDO2W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adequate and balanced diet is very important in building the immune system in order to effectively fight any form of viral infection. Be sure to eat healthy meals so as to keep safe this period.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/UwCwe61dM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Edo State has joined the long list of states benefiting from our Palliatives scheme. The culturally rich state received a total of 252,000 essential food materials shared across 36,295 homes.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/XxEdJ9QIXk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The importance of social distancing can never be over emphasized. Always avoid crowded places, whether its a trip to grocery store or a simple walk to the filling station.  #StayingAliveTogether #StaySafe #Cacovid https://t.co/qORodhsgSc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nasarawa State Governor, Abduallahi Sule recently commissioned the distribution of CACOVID palliatives to the vulnerable people in his state. The distribution saw over 21,600 homes receive 148,000 food materials as part of the palliative program.   #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid https://t.co/rRR7uieFFV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You do not need to panic whenever a person coughs. It might just be a cough. As long as your face mask is on and you wash your hands regularly, youre less likely to contract COVID19.  #StayingAliveTogether #StaySafe #Cacovid #StayHome https://t.co/GpHEr8e0I1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As part of our ongoing palliatives scheme, CACOVID has disbursed essential food materials to up to 50,000 homes in Benue State including cartons of noodles, salt, pasta, rice and other important materials.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/0A4zsGEOtq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cleaner your hands, the safer you are from COVID-19. Wash, sanitize and keep your hands away from your face to reduce your chances of contracting the coronavirus.  #StayingAliveTogether #StaySafe #Cacovid #StayHome https://t.co/BaM4f4ggjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our battle to containing the pandemic was birthed by the need to defeat humanitys greatest threat in modern history. Journey through our short but rich history to gain a full understanding of the strides we have made since we started.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/h0WpuHaRZe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Although it might get drowned in the headlines, COVID19 has a 90% survival rate and is not a death sentence. Avoid stigmatizing infected persons and instead work with them to keep others safe and healthy. #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid https://t.co/blNgU7CZnr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Governor commended CACOVIDs continued efforts to pull resources across industries to fight against COVID-19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[37, 000 homes in Enugu State have received essential food items in our nationwide palliatives program. Executive Governor of the State, Ifeanyi Ugwuanyi received  the items which included bags of rice, Garri, pasta, sugar, salt and others  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/YNC23l6PB5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As schools are set to resume and our children get back to the classroom, its important we adhere to safety guidelines to ensure their security. Teach them to mask up and wash their hands regularly to avoid contracting COVID19.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/eWvUVyLvRc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whenever you are in public, wear a mask and you can save a thousand lives by that simple action. Wether its to the grocery store or a simple walk, mask up to reduce your chances of catching COVID19.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/1ss093YTIa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let us continue to wash our hands and wear our masks so we can all stay alive together. #StayingAliveTogether #StaySafe #Palliative]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CACOVID remains steadfast in its bid to reduce the effects of the pandemic on the most vulnerable in our society.  38 trucks containing a total of 200,000 essential food materials were donated to the state of Yobe as part of the ongoing #CACOVIDPalliatives scheme. https://t.co/DLeZhIgPfl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Water is life as they say, so always be brimming with it. Replace your soda drinks with water and add an extra layer of protection to your immune system. Stay hydrated, stay safe.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/okOkeMW3FX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Governor Mohammed Badaru of state explained that will go a long way in complementing our efforts of supporting the people at the grassroots level #StayingAliveTogether #StaySafe #Cacovid #Palliative]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jigawa State received a total of 35O, OOO different essential food items for a total of 49,941 homes in the #CACOVIDPalliatives scheme. https://t.co/vWfCZseyaz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[as we bounce back from the effects of COVID19.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe #Palliative]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[50,000 vulnerable citizens in Borno State were assisted with over 300,000 different essential food items. The palliatives, including cartons of noodles, bags of rice, sugar, pasta, salt, and garri, are expected to serve as a salve to recovering people in the society https://t.co/rFdH5J9p2T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sleep well, relax when you can and make sure your stress levels are not spiked. Your immune system can take a knock if you overwork yourself continuously. Keep your mind healthy and stay safe.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/Kv7UZDnnQI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going to the store? Dont forget to mask up to protect yourself from COVID19. With masks, you reduce the chances of contracting the virus, thereby securing the ones you leave at home. Stay safe, wear a mask!  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/ezzIl6BMNF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When we all mask up, we reduce the spread and in the longer run, save thousands of lives. Let us work together to kick COVID-19 out of Nigeria! Coro Must Go!  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/cG4MiFyOZ7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your mask is your first shield against COVID19 and its important that you always have it on in public. It is only together, as one masked community, that we can reduce the numbers to even, nill. So mask up and let us bring COVID19 down!  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/0sM0IL349P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow updates on todays #CoroMustGo sensitization train on our Instagram Page! https://t.co/nkXaODlpJx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets make Nigeria a COVID19 free country by masking up and following the outlined safety guidelines. Masks will serve as our first aid against COVID19 and its important that we all adhere.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/XzjPMcy0O9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wear a mask, keep your distance and wash your hands regularly! These are the simple things we imbibe and lockdowns are eased gradually.   A COVID19 free Nigeria is possible, but only if we do it together.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe #WearAMask #WashYourHands https://t.co/XJYoXTJrGh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A total of 48,528 households enjoyed reprieve in the form of essential food items including Rice, pasta and even garri. We continue on our quest to make life easier for victims of the COVID19 pandemic and ask that you join us too in our journey.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Executive Governor of Delta State, Dr. Ifeanyi Okowa flagged off the #CACOVIDPalliatives Scheme recently and was full of praise for the effort shown by private stakeholders in the country to create a soft landing for vulnerable persons in the society. https://t.co/voZilKwNOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What state do you think wed spotlight next?    #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perhaps one of the culturally rich states in Nigeria, Ogun State paid host to CACOVID as our palliatives scheme rolled out. The state saw the donation of 44,710 essential food items to serve households hit hardest by the COVID19 pandemic.  #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether https://t.co/wcogz1sCgK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ekiti State, youre on the spotlight today for the #CACOVIDPalliativeScheme  Where are our wonderful Ekiti followers at?   Reply with your Local Government below  https://t.co/qI7QSFm8ue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Which State will we showcase next in our Palliatives Scheme?  #Cacovid #StayingAliveTogether]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is in line with our continued work towards the creation of platforms from which states can rebuild from the challenges of COVID19.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the battle against COVID19 still raging on, Anambra State got succor as the CACOVID palliatives scheme kicked off in grand style. 47,368 households will benefit from the alleviation project which will target the most vulnerable in Awka and other parts of the state. https://t.co/M08sG6GZnV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the donated essential food items, we expect a soft landing for these families as we all seek to rebuild from the travails of COVID19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kano State, another beneficiary of our palliatives program saw a total of 112,005 households receive 224,110 cartons of rice, 112,055 bags of sugar, rice, pasta, salt and garri.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/wi3ws7CH0Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The essential food items including bags of rice, cartons of noodles, salt/sugar and other products, will serve as salve to homes as we continue our fight against the pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As part of our mission to reduce the effects of COVID-19 in Nigeria, 38,333 households enjoyed the recent kickoff of palliatives distribution in Kogi State.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/9aCBewn6Au]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The importance of wearing a mask can not be overemphasized Wear your masks with pride! Style them your way, staying safe can be fashionable as well. Slay safe.  #CACOVID #StaySafe https://t.co/H8FXgw1BMw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who says you cant have fun with social distancing? Stick to the guidelines and you can have a amazing hangout with your friends. By keeping your distance, disinfecting your surrounding and avoiding external interactions, you can have a COVID19 safe get together.  #Cacovid https://t.co/GS7eEFFZbj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[would be given priority on the distribution. Each household would be receiving 1 bag of 10kg rice, 1 carton of pasta, 2 cartons of noodles, 1 bag of 5kg of sugar, 1 bag of 1kg of salt and 1 bag of 5kg of garri, semovita, and maize.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A total of 42,312 households benefited from the CACOVID palliatives scheme which kicked off in Jigawa State. State Governor, Badaru Abubakar in flagging off the distribution explained that people with special needs, such as the physically challenged, pensioners, orphanage homes, https://t.co/lfHKWJgOaP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[269,350kg of rice, 100,500kg of maize, 320,000kg of beans, 795,000 pieces of spaghetti, 400,000 pieces of Indomie, 16,000kg of salt, 292,934kg of sugar, 11,950 litres of palm oil, 150,000 pieces of Maggi cubes and 406,900 kg of millet.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[which include; bags of rice, maize and flour, millet, sugar spaghetti vegetable oil among others. According to Senator Bala, the relief materials received by the state Bauchi state government from CACOVID and other Federal government agencies include]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senator Bala Abdulkadir Mohammed of Bauchi State launched the distribution of palliatives to help protect the vulnerable against the effects of COVID-19. The flag off event which held at the Bauchi State Agricultural Programme, BSADP, saw the distribution of essential food items https://t.co/AHavpojzzp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The event will be graced by experts and frontline workers as they all share their experiences and challenges faced in combating COVID19. Click https://t.co/jys0mCsyof to register.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join Zouera Youssoufou, CEO, Dangote Foundation, for an in-depth look at Nigerias response to the health crisis in modern history in the Lessons from COVID Epicenters webinar holding on the 14th of August, 2020. https://t.co/UtUeXyBs5Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shes developed a book packed with amazing practices for the health savvy and is grateful for the opportunity to turn her lemons into lemonade.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drbimfit had a weight loss story that she knew could help a lot of people and used the lockdown to create a business out of her passion.  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/dk6U7shQfR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not all blessings come in the way youd expect. For @proudly_southsouth, he used the lockdown as an opportunity to pray, plan, refocus and re-strategize.  Have an #IsolationBlessing? Share with us via DM or tag us to get featured on our page!   #CACOVID #StayingAliveTogether https://t.co/shEFAZovR5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Send us a DM and we could feature your story on our page.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adeyemivictorayo used the lockdown as muse in the creation of his second book titled Chronicles of Quarantine. According to him, he had a hard time publishing a second book since his debut in 2015 and used the stay at home order to cook up a masterclass.  #MyIsolationBlessings https://t.co/MJ5FxrPRgn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 on the less-privileged in the state. The Governor, in his speech, lauded CACOVID for deeming it necessary to pull resources together to make the donation which was aimed at ameliorating the plight of the downtrodden in the society.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CACOVID unveiled the Delta State arm of its palliatives scheme at an Event Centre in Asaba. The scheme, inaugurated by Governor Ifeanyi Okowa of Delta State, will help in mitigating the debilitating effects of  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/3PpXD1djcz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have taken delivery of about 80% out of a total number of 56,454 cartons of noodles; 28,227 bags of 5 kilograms of sugar; 28,227 bags of 10 kilogramme of rice; 28,227 bags of 5 kilogramme of maize/semovita; 28,227 cartons of pasta and 28,227 bags of KGs of salt, Buni said.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CACOVID also improved the testing capacity of NCDC by donating of over 100 thousand test kits and various personal protective equipments (PPE). The Executive Governor Yobe State, Mai Mala Buni, on behalf of the people also appreciated the effort of the coalition.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The private sector-led Coalition Against COVID-19 (CACOVID) has donated essential materials to the State Government of Yobe to help in the fight against the COVID19 pandemic. 38 trucks of food items were handed over by Mr. Marcus Dibel, @efirstbank Business Manager, Damaturu. https://t.co/wxbUJaSYzU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KDHSSD: Kaduna State has been slated to receive 131 trucks from @cacovidng. 108 of these trucks have been received and warehoused for d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CACOVID remains steadfast in her mission to not just combat COVID19 but to serve as the platform for the advancement of Nigerias medical industry. We are open, our data is public and we are ready to answer all your questions so do not hesistate to ask. We will always answer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At the moment, CACOVID has spent a total of N23,147,266,506.40 on the palliatives programme.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The allocations for each state was decided upon by the Nigerian Governors Forum and oversight is currently being carried out by our partners at @PwC https://t.co/YWVdPgaWHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have Isolation Centers functional across all 36 states of the country, equipped with state of the art equipment that will cater for everybody who comes down with COVID19. These facilities are stocked with the essential tools to aid the management of the pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To balance our efforts and ensure efficiency, were still running a sensitization campaign to make sure everyone understands that COVID19 is deadly, not propaganda and can infect anybody.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CACOVID is majorly comprised of private sector individuals, with the aim of serving as a buffer for the effects of the pandemic. With this in mind, we can assure that there are no political affiliations needed to benefit from the Palliatives scheme.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is no data to calculate the exact effects of COVID19 on states as such, we agreed with the Nigerian Governors Forum to share 5% of the palliatives funds across each state.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At the moment, were flagging off the palliative scheme across the country. For every family that benefits from the scheme, we will be handing over the below essential food materials. https://t.co/iK1tMBSV64]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 600,000 test kits have been ordered for the country. In Yaba, Lagos alone, we recently unveiled an Isolation Center that is currently managed by the Lagos State Governement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And were off! Today we will explain in detail the efforts of CACOVID in combating the ripple effects of the COVID19. Join us and if you have questions, you can send them in with #StayingAliveTogether https://t.co/pflMIETHwj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still unsure of what the Private Sector Coalition Against COVID-19 has been up to? Catch us on Instagram live today by 11am and come bearing questions as we will provide answers to all your concerns and inquiries. https://t.co/BvEFsITdPZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Share with us via dm an inspirational experience that will motivate someone during these testy times and you could feature on our page!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A wise man once said, the best things in life are free. @patrickdonaldlee definitely took this to heart as his biggest #IsolationBlessings was the opportunity to spend more time with his children.   #MyIsolationBlessings https://t.co/JDQC9sFLGf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Share with us via dm an inspirational experience that will motivate someone during these testy times and you could feature on our page!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mega_salesfor_u found a surprising silver lining as the lockdown situation forced most learning to take place at home. This saw a sharp rise in the sale of their android tablet for children.   #MyIsolationBlessings https://t.co/Phg1qtpUw9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Share with us via dm an inspirational experience that will motivate someone during these testy times and you could feature on our page!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nmaclothingco decided to pivot at a crucial moment during the lockdown and it paid off superbly. The production of medical apparel to help support health workers has transformed the outfit which before the pandemic, was focused on regular wears.   #MyIsolationBlessings https://t.co/7Cf82oazV6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This short film will help explain the struggles our brave health-workers face everyday as they fight against the scourge of COVID19. Sit back, enjoy and learn from the experiences of some of the bravest people you could ever meet. #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe https://t.co/GviZZ77HFv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Westrol Fruits and Veggies got a big boost during the lockdown and heres her testimony. According to her, the lockdown allowed her gain new customers who flocked the store to purchase fruits and vegetables. #MyIsolationBlessings https://t.co/jNZOzx1twZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Through a unitary decision to social distance, we have succeeded in giving ourselves a chance against the pandemic. Why stop now?  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nurse Cherish Samuel has seen families reunited with laughter. She has heard awful stories from around the world on the potency of COVID19 and is grateful that Nigerias case is not similar. https://t.co/fEEFVEFImP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we all adhere to the guidelines set out for the ease of the lockdown.   Share with us via dm an inspirational experience that will motivate someone during these testy times and you could feature on our page!  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Funke Bankoles biggest #IsolationBlessing is the decision by private entities and stakeholders to intervene in the fight against COVID19. According to the sterling health worker, our sacrifice to slow down the pandemic can only pay off if https://t.co/bPXS5YV1zH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can she trust in you?  Share with us via dm an inspirational experience that will motivate someone during these testy times and you could feature on our page!  #StayingAliveTogether #Cacovid #StaySafe]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>