<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@WorkingBrother @KCChiefz @russs3lll @jesus_jimz Your swimming is everyones swimming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SiemensUSA: Amid this COVID-19 pandemic, another healthcare crisis looms large: #AirPollution now contributes to 7 million global death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrentTerhune Yeah, no way Alex Jones is an actor/controlled opposition.  Totally believable anybody could do what he does and not get sent away for a long time and not get suppressed.  I mean he was on brogan, that guy is legit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cher Acting tips definitely.  Dont know why people choose to accept these scripted events as real]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@malexgomez1981 @SteveRustad1 Wait till they find out about medical malpractice deaths in the USA.  And how often science changes in academia.  And that Louis Pasteur was a fraud.  That ScIeNce and science are different.  How can they have a vaccine for something they dont know how its spread. https://t.co/97hfHUBG1o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RussellOkung So the banks can have more control.  You crazy to thing people fall for this much longer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its cancel time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eToroUS scam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RudyHavenstein @_whitneywebb Who is imAndrewBustamante... lol, definitely rogue CIA agent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_whitneywebb written and approved by the ruling class?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope Elon Musk can convince Donald Trump to simulate the Great War with China.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Great War with China should be fought in space on planet madeup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There no parties in sci-fi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalGovForum: It is estimated that by 2025 the number of people living in regions with absolute water scarcity will have risen to som]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_whitneywebb Bernie sanders asking if you your fed up with Wall Street.  Whitney, find some courage and go after Louis Pasteur.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crypto_bitlord7 Troll lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The piles of homeless people in the street are mounting.  Filthy hands after filthy hands, why cant they be like the clean ones who live?  Dirty hands means bad person.  Dont do anything sheep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FibHunter @DrTomFrieden Theres piles of homeless on the street in DC.  All have dirty hands.  The few live ones I see are walking around with hand sanitizer.  One drank so much she now has the antibodies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FibHunter @DrTomFrieden 1 year in.  Yeeks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FibHunter @DrTomFrieden These people have no idea what a virus is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FibHunter @DrTomFrieden Fib, no showers without a shower and without a means to pay rent the big banks they take your shower.  This will happen in mass soon enough.  How can you not see this.  Theres no excuse for having mush brain.  Unmush your brain.  Also homeless arent dying fool.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTomFrieden Doctors know so little about the body its not even funny.  They are worse than cops.  Google will tell you they dont KNOW how the virus spreads.  Bechamp will tell you because your an idiot who is a sucker for a scam.  Pasteur, fraud.  Frieden, fraud with a blue check on twit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Thomas_Binder does your body produce viruses? When does it?  What is your take on Bechamp vs Pasteur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GhoshSirsh why was he instrumental in PayPal's success?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SsanceNetwork: @walruswhisperer @RussellOkung Then theyll call you to say good job baiting the working class into technocratic distopi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SsanceNetwork: @walruswhisperer @RussellOkung This is the third time theyve run this play around holiday season.  Whales flood market]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timothysykes Its not the suits its the ruling class]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Craig_A_Spencer Get your eyes checked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mwiner123 @HudsonInstitute Guys wwii was so Israel could exist and then later be destroyed, to fulfill the prophecy which we likely wont see fulfilled in our lifetime, all this other stuff is misdirection.  Like Jews rule the world lol.  Buzzword.  Buzz buzz.  Revelation ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTomFrieden Dr. Our health professionals are unhealthy and incompetent.  See 250000 medical accident deaths  each year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTomFrieden Doctor Louis Pasteur and his handlers have you fooled.  Your body produces viruses.  The system is going to throw up some nasty truths.  Good luck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@keshinil @SegravesNBC4 @MayorBowser @nbcwashington Hey, your democracy doesn't exist.  Its a sharade put on so the peons of the world to feel like they are as important as their masters.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SegravesNBC4 @MayorBowser @nbcwashington There is one party, and you simps are fooled by the two party illusion.  Trump, your nemesis was a Democrat.  It comes across as retarded, those that thing credentials will save them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SegravesNBC4 @MayorBowser @nbcwashington When will people figure out that false flags are planted in the media all the time, i.e. Reichstag Fire.  Public safety, terrorism, buzzwords that have been planted to justify draconian rule.  This is madness.  There's no way that the storming of capital was authentic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FluorescentGrey @_whitneywebb Webb retweets you.  You guys blew her cover.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_whitneywebb these seems like another planted story, such as Wikileaks.  Gotta get good at identifying controlled opposition in 2021.  Who buys that the laptop was actually stolen?  Why would this story be in the news so soon.  Webb is caught in that of others.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTedros Since there is so much uncertainty surrounding the virus and unknowns its outrageous that no one is calling for the ruling class to get vaccinated first.  These are the most valuable members of our society from which everything else trickles down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me what a patriot is?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@postlocal @capitalweather They dont even know if COVID-19 is transmissible through the air.  How the hell can you trust the vaccine to work if its a novel virus with so much unknown.  Find a new Pasteur to base your fraud off of, this should make you furious]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MayorBowser Why the hell would someone get a vaccine if they dont get to change there behavior.  This is obviously a war on the general populations body.  There is a long game here.  They cant tell you if Covid-19 is transmissible through the air.  But they kno all else abt it  Google it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realjunsonchan @TX_WalkerRanger @anonpatriotq A populist movement lead by a blackmailed, see Sec. Ross, bankrupt billionaire, who begs for Roy Cohn, you really dont get how this works maybe you have mush for brains]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ComeOnSense4 @almostjingo Give them a half truth and they will chase it.  Dawg what evidence do you have that both parties arent working together.  Wheres the wall smash, your vote is meaningless, the ruling class mocks you with it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow @MayorBowser Cells in your body getTogether to produce viruses as part of immune system response when extra response is needed. They see cleansing agent, like soap, to isolate and carry away damaged cells.  Hence, google cant tell you if Covid is spread via the air or not but get vaccinated]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realMarkHohe @Bearocalypse @ClimateDepot @MayorBowser Anybody trying to politicize this has no idea about the one world banking system, two party deception, one world medical system.  The ops pick thesePeople, passionate and simple, to focus on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@msroberts0619 @Bearocalypse @ClimateDepot @MayorBowser The flaw in the pcr tests should be common knowledge at this point.  The creator of the test says it will find anything in your body if you run it enough.  Complete lack of understanding of the body at the least by todays medical professional fraudsters.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow @MayorBowser Does closing testing sites while the media is reporting skyrocketing infection rates seem like evidence of a pandemic or Plandemic?  It will be fine.  Research the fraud that is the father of modern medicine.  Louis Pasteur.  Then research Anton Bechamp.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pidgeon_peter @SarcasmStardust @realDonaldTrump Also. Asante is controlled opposition who operates for 20 years.  Real opposition isnt elevated in msm, they are suicided]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zoeharcombe the key to exposing the Plandemic is to go back to Louis Pasteur and the first Plandemic.  Pasteur was a fraud and there is a reason that he is elevated and there is a reason that people with blue checks are allowed to provide "resistance", at least thats what the script allows]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BTCEchoz @walruswhisperer @RussellOkung There is no easy way to avoid transhumanism, but putting your entire life online is a great way to get lost in the matrix.  They built the network that you are trumpeting and they can shut it down at will.  Gold/cash, cant do that with press of a button.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@walruswhisperer @RussellOkung This is the third time theyve run this play around holiday season.  Whales flood market in bitcoin build hype when people go see their families so word spreads everywhere.  Then soon after holidays whales sell off and take all the hypebeast hard earned money]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@walruswhisperer @RussellOkung Then theyll call you to say good job baiting the working class into technocratic distopia.  Cash is tangible and can be hidden anywhere in the world.  Bitcoin is stored on the digital network created by criminal ruling class.  No way they built backDoors into it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RichardDawkins People with credentials saying things]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Independent Great reporting by the cia.  The media are no different than the writers for wwe.  #operationmockingbird]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danmccrory6 @va_shiva The only way out of this is to go back Pasteur the entire paradigm of modern medicine is a scam.  They dont plant anything about this on here.  Theres plenty of stories about masks, testing, etc.  this is what will blow it up.  Bechamp, terrain theory.  Marx, similar thiefs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Craig_A_Spencer Holy cow this Is what passes for science, is the church accepting new members]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@internetsociety creators of this plandemic have same bloodlines as the creators of the internet and all the many backdoors that the elites have into THE FEED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@internetsociety and acknowledge that the creators of this plandemic have the same bloodlines as the creators of the scamish Rockefeller paradigm of medicine and the last plandemic.  All to distract and justify totalitarian transition to cashless society..transhumanism will be here soon enough.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drdavidsamadi David, I mean Ella, nice burner account]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@va_shiva @DRockWolf1 All the worlds a stage for you suckers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drdavidsamadi Lets retrain all medical professionals.  Wouldnt know medical fraud if the banking system took Louis Pasteurs hand and smacked you in the face.  Audience, this guy is controlled opposition ala Snowden, Jones, rogan, sanders, etc.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_whitneywebb Report on Pasteur and the complete fraud of modern medicine, bechamp, terrain vs germ theory.  This is the fucking answer, not tiptoeing around the edges.  You need a new editor, stop reporting on the misdirection unless that is your role.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alan2102z @_whitneywebb @elleprovocateur What brand misdirection piece, with a half true or two, does this one have for us.  Epsteins totally real, not story planted by elites.  Lets do crypto fraud next lol.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drdavidsamadi we need to PREVENT disease]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JenMax57 do you have a better source?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RufusKings1776 Fox poll blah blah blah Trump blah blah blah...THE WORRRST..blah  hsehs shesh hsehs sheesh.  SHEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEESSSSSSSSHHHH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JodieHMoss @mkraju team blue?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevinBardosh: The heavens....? https://t.co/KVZs98V7fJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kakaysb @2LarryJohnson7 If this year should show you anything.  There is one world government, one world banking system, one world healthcare system.  Countries are the tools of the ruling class.  Place focus on ruling class not China.  Ruling class gains Money, power and control from war.  Misdirection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYYGT3 @2LarryJohnson7 Its not about money, its about control.. of your body and genetics.  Get familiar with the TRANSHuman movement and agenda 2030.  This is a great reset setting the stage for technocratic totalitarian rule.  They print endless money if you havent noticed on whims and get richer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper @ajamubaraka @jimmy_dore We really hope we have democracy.  Your vote doesnt count.  From ruling class perspective,You are livestock given politicians(not usually ruling class), usually blackmailed actors, And the wrestling match storylines are gobbled up.  Tenet, Illuminati influenced, May add insight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WolfieSmith5: "Don't be stupid. As if they're gonna fake something as big as Covid" Me: https://t.co/DJ9yAqAe70]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jasonhu10530544: Most of the world was EXCITED about a sci-fi future watched on TV or on a gaming console. Little did they know that c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MayorBowser I wear a butt plug for the safety of my grandma.  Farts are superspreaders, and I can smell yall through my mask.  Plug it up for Grandma, and throw some ski goggles and ear muffs on.  I want to yell sometimes, your not plugging your orophusus correctly, murderer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarinCAtrades @Forbes @NickJFuentes i.e. the confusion with masks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KuzyBeCackling @MayorBowser @_DCHealth notice how easily they got permits.  The Proud Boys are paid actors.  They put on live performances for the media.  The DC government is a small piece to this plandemic puzzle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[mrna vaccination is just another kick of the can down the road.  digitial id is just another kick of the can down the road.  Movement and Sex will be restricted to the point that reality will undoubtedly be hell.  VR will ease pain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rockefeller paradigm of medicine must be destroyed if rapid speciation is to be avoided.  That is the goal if the Great Reset and the plandemic.  To ensure that the working class is no threat tp the ruling class.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'd bet 75% of health professionals have no idea about Germ Theory, Louis Pasteur, Rockefeller Medicine, etc.  The antidote to the PlanDemic is finding clear scientific evidence that dispells Germ Theory.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I believe that there are many scapegoat options prepared for this psy op.  Gates, Fauci, Trump, there are many potential scapegoats presented to you in the media.  They will not scapegoat "Germ Theory".  This is where the holes lie in this psy op.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The key seems to be in what few are talking about on Twitter.  I doubt that there is a money trail that these actors playing journalist can find.  There are many pushing you down this direction, with the Epstein angle intertwining with the Gates story and Dark Winter, EcoHealth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a lot of half truther's pushing and shillling out there to draw you away from the full truth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a lot of half-truths surrounding the COVID narrative, but I am confident in my senses enough to say that there is 0 evidence of a novel, pandemic causing, virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TLAVagabond Your missing the bullet where the truthers find the Alt media reports of.5trth, give them trust, and look less intently, even though they clearly aren't really censored and are shilling for the same msm rulers.  "Groundbreaking" Canadian Epstein and you guys are right on it.. ok.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing Wait until this idiot learns about medical malpractice deaths in the United States.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billbarhydt I dare not venture deep into Crypto Twitter again, but the majority of these scammers promoting crypto are poor at indpnt think and are desperate to speculate their way to the top in a system designed to crush small investors.  Rest are bots.  ruling class prints all over twitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billbarhydt This environment is a scammers paradise.  What is best for the sheep is to have tangible money that they can hide from the IRS.  Stick your chest out a little further on your next tweet. https://t.co/L2IuJgYomB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tepperleen @TulsiGabbard DEMOCRATS are DEMOCRATS.  Two party illusion is see through.  Trust your eyes.  Narrative...Tulsi is the only Democrat with (courage?integrity?) to stand up to Clinton.  Real story...dropped suit soon after, sharade to gain trust attention and $$$ from fauxgressives for DEM PARTY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @saferphones: "High exposure to RF-EMF produced by mobile phone base station towers was associated with delayed fine and gross motor ski]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HegKong @med1cinewoman Very clearly setting up for eugenics movement that ends with crispr eliminating natural birth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@inspiteoffires @yourvokalnews They are all insiders.  Think for yourself.  People fighting Team red vs. team blue are Painfully embarrassing.  To sum it up its one big club and you arent in it, At All.  Time for a real populous movement outside of the illusions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mspennygoodman The controlled opposition fools the majority.  I hope you begin to see through their illusions.  They too are entertainers who care nothing about you, evidenced by their inability to act outside of one party illusion, failure to attack banking class]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JerseyBoy43 @Robert25162833 @tschak @jimmy_dore Where in the book on capitalism is their anything on living wage numnuts.  The wage is set by the market, opportunity cost.  The big players set the market receive handouts from banks all the time.  See how small business kod and corporate, where little actually gets done, excel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth Dont take my play on 3dgoggles.  I screenshot so if I first I Credit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth Everything isnt blue vs. red.  These people Want a show so bad Id guess they put on 3d goggles withTheir muzzle, ear, nose and butt plugs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: If you believe 81 million people voted for Biden, I've got a pandemic with a 99.8% survival rate I want to scare you i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SsanceNetwork: Hey, Anne Frank is a made up person.  Her biography was written by a creepy old man.  How she even has a mural is a test]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey, Anne Frank is a made up person.  Her biography was written by a creepy old man.  How she even has a mural is a testament to Zionism, which many want you believe is Judaism, but it isn't.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews First off, Anne Frank isn't even a person she is a character of fantasy written by a deceptive, creepy old man.  Second off, this like every story is there for a reason.  This is likely staged and its not interesting enough to talk about.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Politicsinsider this is what the illusion of democracy looks like?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adamfarren2 Yes that is the narrative/illusion presented and there has been ongoing cozy relationships between banking class and China predating Mao.  USA is also working w/ China in almost every area.  Countries are the tool of the elite and populist/elitist..red, blue drama Is seethrough]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>