<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Tony #Fauci to @ACPinternists on #COVID19 stress for HCWers: "The standard way that we treat this kind of stress doesn't work..." "We have to be very creative" in dealing with "this unprecedented experience that our healthcare providers have been through." https://t.co/tNlKvxsCUi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @WhiteHouse wants 70% of Americans vaccinated by July 1st, including teens, and today announced a long list of efforts to make it ultra-easy and free to get a #COVID19 #vaccine. https://t.co/QOkIwTumzS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's a thought, Tucker Carlson -- does "the right to choose" in your calculus include birth control, Mifeprex (mifepristone) and Cytotec (misoprostol)? Or do favor government interference in those cases? Just working on the range of the rage.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The variants are old: "multiple #coronavirus infections in China  the USA harbored the progenitor genetic fingerprint in Jan2020  later, suggesting the progenitor was spreading worldwide months before  after the 1st reported cases of #COVID19 in China." https://t.co/jo7EzF8OgF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker's decided that "his" Americans should refuse #COVID19 #vaccines "This is a question of free will...a fundamental American right: the right to choose which medicines you put in your own body. Until recently, all of us assumed that we had that right." https://t.co/2L2DxE6CFX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: The first images of a mutation on a COVID-19 variant of concern have been captured by University of British Columbia researc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RonBrownstein: Two Americas: The WaPo ranking shows that all 21 states where the highest % of adults have received at least one #vaccin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations to both @Yamiche for landing the prestigious slot, and the @PBS for having the wisdom to give the helm to Alcindor. https://t.co/KM2U1Q7tfv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrianLehrer: LIVE: 24-hour subway service will return on May 17. But, citing pre-pandemic complaints, Gov. Cuomo said he wants the MTA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: We are living from oxygen cylinder to oxygen cylinder.  At least 10 people, possibly as many as 24, died in India after a ho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: Our covid times  by @BillBramhall https://t.co/EWub0vvzF7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Razarumi: Bill and Melinda Gates announce their divorce after 27 years of marriage: "we no longer believe we can grow together as a cou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zainrizvi: @gregggonsalves @apoorva_nyc @JenniferNuzzo @noahweiland @SharonLNYT The US has more vaccines sitting in freezers right now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No private parties have a greater impact on global health than @BillGates  @melindagates . So the announcement that they are divorcing is sending shock waves through the entire field, @WHO @gavi @GlobalFund @PATHtweets and much more. https://t.co/PiZrcVUZYq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wise @KFF analysis of policy options for @WhiteHouse efforts to increase global access to #COVID19 #vaccines  https://t.co/km2EEDTYyW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another smart @trvrb thread, this time on the #SARSCoV2 variants' race in the USA, with P.1 (Brazil) rising faster than B1.1.7 (UK) -- which could be a big problem if people don't hurry up and get #COVID19 vaccinated. https://t.co/JksCzUVTzX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Oxygen should be treated as an essential utility, as vital as electricity or water." #COVID19India https://t.co/g432RHEXpo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here, Mitch, is the book I'd add to the high school curricula of all American teens -- and for every adult in the country to review. It shows how the entire economy of the American east coast, from Argentina to Maine, rested on the slave trade.  https://t.co/kNMp3pBf4X https://t.co/D9rpQWynvv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, because why teach children that the @WhiteHouse was built by slaves, the entire cotton and tobacco trades of the South rested on slavery, enslaved Africans grew  harvested sugar cane and processed the sugar in NY -- that the ORIGINS of American colonialism = Slavery? MORE https://t.co/jnVsAYPGV2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pissing match betwn @NYGovCuomo  @NYCMayor continues. DeBlasio vowed to reopen NYC on July 1. So #Cuomo trumps him: "capacity restrictions for businesses, restaurants  cultural venues wld be lifted by May 19th...will affect retail, gyms, Broadway, museums,  bars," etc. https://t.co/7y3bDAglgD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In two weeks? New York City back to near normal? Wow. https://t.co/ss2gHmJYjQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is making the rounds -- I have no idea who started it, but it's just plain brilliant.        Bravo to whomever. https://t.co/IW4pfoEgXB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @NewYorker 's #PeterKuper nails the @CDCgov #COVID19 masks guidelines. https://t.co/6ePPB5T83Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone mailed me a huge book manuscript -- loose pages, no title or author page, no note. It seems a very good pandemics book, but I have no idea where it came from, and I get so many book requests that I can't guess. If it is you, please contact me ASAP. https://t.co/4tWRr2DCc7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worse: "New Delhi ordered 21m vaccines from the Serum Institute, which is making the @AstraZeneca...An additional 110m doses were ordered in March when infections started to climb." Point is, #Modi thought he'd defeated #COVID19  never ordered vaccines. https://t.co/bYPOfIWfB6 https://t.co/sCXu7xeFrY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI the #NobelPrizeSummit is now on @YouTube -- including the session I hosted with @ProfPCDoherty #JenniferDoudna  #TonyFauci -- "A Pandemic Guide to Solving Problems with Science". 30 mins of insights, #COVID19 #pandemic  https://t.co/aGy4kO2U44]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #vaccine shortage in #India is not about patents or WTO -- India is the world's #1 vaccine maker. It's about the incompetence of the Modi govt  failure to order #COVID19 vaccines, according to CEO of India's Serum Inst.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India's Serum Inst. is the world's largest #vaccine maker. According to the CEO, Adar Poonawalla, the #Modi government never ordered stockpiles of #COVID19 vax for the people of India. Officially, only a couple of 100 million doses were ordered  &lt;2% of the population is vaxed. https://t.co/2rQkHY3hd6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wonder if, given Michael Lewis' new book, @CDCgov will finally close its reporter blacklist (I was on it under #Trump folks) and allow its scientists to speak to reporters without restrictions. https://t.co/4sfcPREfeT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: Finally got my first dose of #COVID19 vaccine!  (Moderna.) Vaccin (et majeur)! https://t.co/s4Cs8VJyTa #vaccination ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSNews: LET THE MUSIC PLAY: Thousands attended the Strawberry Music Festival in Wuhan, the Chinese city where COVID-19 first emerged l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With all the horror out of India  Brazil and the optimism about vaccination in the U.S. it's easy to lose sight of the fact that the U.S. still has by far the largest #COVID19 toll in the world. https://t.co/Wsko1swjuk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were at a moment where science has the potential to make a difference on issues of social justice and inequality, she said. I know my students are increasingly concerned about these questions, and I think rank-and-file scientists are too. https://t.co/vLdIj4nxOl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @voxdotcom: Vietnam was one of just a handful of countries to seal its borders as the coronavirus spread around the globe in early 2020.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @harvardmed: Dr. Aditi Nerurkar of HMS gives insight on the most pressing issue in India being oxygen, not because there is a lack of it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelthiaRicks: So. Africa is receiving its 1st of 4.5M Pfizer vaccine doses. Health Minister Zweli Mkhize said ~325k doses were schedule]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelthiaRicks: India launches massive effort to inoculate all adults against Covid https://t.co/6AWRHQFJiC via @medical_xpress]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is such a valuable interactive site from @nytimes showing every step in manufacture of mRNA #COVID19 #vaccines. https://t.co/EyMM2kfBZE As you watch, you can see dozens of places where supply shortages of DNA or RNA processing chemicals or enzymes can slow things down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If "long #COVID" persists indefinitely in a substantial % of #COVID19 survivors, how will societies cope with the largescale social, medical and productivity costs? This is especially concerning given the majority of "long haulers" are young adults. https://t.co/sX8GLBU32u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very tough #COVID19 situation continues in Ontario and Toronto.  https://t.co/FDe1B9cUaN https://t.co/K1fSOWQuxA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: After vaccination, the "breakthrough" rate of covid infections in San Diego County among &gt;1 million vaccinees is 0.02% 234 c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: What may we expect from vaccination of 10-15% more of the US population? 7-day averages compared with UK and Israel shows a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTomFrieden: Covid killed 1.8 million people in 2020. At the current rate, it could kill even more people in 2021. But this isn't inev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seemingly overnight the death rate in #Brazil quadrupled, with the nation having witnessed more than 400,000 #COVID19 deaths. This catastrophe can be laid at the feet of #JairBolsonaro  his cronies. https://t.co/3GdRUTJsiW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hard to believe it's been ten years..... https://t.co/wqK0ilsMva]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelthiaRicks: How SARSCoV2 hijacks human cells to evade immune system: The viral genome gets tagged w/ a special marker by a human enzy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Prime Minister Narendra Modi's Covid-19 task force didnt meet for months. His health minister assured the public in March tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SPRING IS HERE! Brooklyn Botanic Garden today. https://t.co/Xve38CAnuW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dbguy1999 No apparent danger. When I've been in Reykjavik seems like the volcano is about a 2 hour drive, maybe 3. Good news is low cash, so no repeat of eruption that blocked European air travel a few years ago...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An elderly woman with dementia walked put of a store, forgetting to pay &lt;$14. Police threw her to the ground, fracturing an arm and pulling her collarbone, then left her cuffed in a cell for hours in pain, confused, no calls to family or lawyer. https://t.co/T7HCutDZfF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: 100 million Americans have been fully vaccinated, almost 40% of adults, as concerns grow about reaching those who have not got]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenBranswell: .@WHO has given an emergency use listing  its equivalent of @US_FDA's emergency use authorization  to Moderna's #Covi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow. https://t.co/QzBidiMiDk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Utterly heartbreaking #COVID19India https://t.co/J1t1a8tO4d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is great, New York, but we have to do MUCH better if we want to reopen #NYC on July 1: "45.6% of NYers have completed at least 1 #COVID19 #vaccine dose. To date, NY has admin'ed 15,170,850 doses with 33.4 of NYers completing their vaccine series." https://t.co/Ar6VshgGRN.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @animalculum: Sea Level Rise Driven by a Crucial Ice Sheet Could Be 30% More Than Predicted https://t.co/UKMh8xf1UI #ClimateChange https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: Nepal facing deadly Covid wave similar to India, doctors warn https://t.co/ejaHsr80PB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NYCComptroller: Natural wetlands act as a spongesoaking up storms that could lead to major flooding and devastation.  New York should]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardiannews: Figures on Covid deaths post-jab show vaccines success, scientists say https://t.co/wsHvRXe0NG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Risk from virus variants remains after first Pfizer COVID-19 vaccine, UK study finds https://t.co/5OkXgb32fC https://t.co/uSdJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. spending @Medicare Part B spending on drugs? 80% of the cost to taxpayers is for just 50 patented drugs that lack price competitors or generic formulations.   https://t.co/KZ9RhImyYz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yeah, that's me, dead center sitting solo, taking in @NYPopsUp jazz that was a world class wonder, performed for free -- unannounced -- in my neighborhood park. All of us were filled with joy  feeling relief from #COVID19 dread. Sing it: "I  NY!" https://t.co/FAhQb1IgMW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These days in NYC you never know when you may turn a corner or step into a park  WOW! The best of music, dance, theater is right there. Artists are doing PopUps, coming back from #COVID19 with joy  passion. Last week I heard a jazz sax outside, ran down to the park  went wild. https://t.co/rgrE4oTFdz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTomFrieden: Our current vaccine infrastructure cant be relied on to meet the needs of the world. Countries with excess supply can ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTomFrieden: Indias surge is a reminder that the virus is learning about and adapting to us faster than we're learning and adapting t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bearing witness to the suffering and agony of #India's #COVID19 catastrophe can, of itself, be painful. This @LionsRoar blog tells you how to push that pain aside by helping  . https://t.co/g7700kxkf7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KriteeKanko: India is now a "chamber of horrors". I haven't experienced suffering so deep  paralyzing! In this @Lionsroar piece I shar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEWS: "On the advice of @CDCgov  the Administration will restrict travel from #India starting immediately.  The policy will be implemented in light of extraordinarily high #COVID19 caseloads  multiple variants circulating in India...will take effect Tues, May 4."  @WhiteHouse https://t.co/DdkJIMqzoT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impressive: Number of children in custody at the U.S./Mexico border drops by 84%.  https://t.co/xDeTxKJ2Ix https://t.co/vbhbavBLQT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/KYIGTs9b9G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: France detects first cases of Indian COVID variant -ministry https://t.co/LQml48dQJ1 https://t.co/HojGKGrGWZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: The Covid crisis in Latin America is taking an alarming turn for the worse. Last week, Latin America accounted for 35% of all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: The death of Marvin David Scott III in Texas has been ruled a homicide by the Collin County Medical Examiner. Scott died after bei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSNews: JUST IN: Brazil surpasses 400,000 coronavirus deaths https://t.co/EZwRf3BVcJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You have got to be kidding............ #COVID19India https://t.co/uxqjYfQru0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[O.M.G. https://t.co/SgzYCrzwv5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And WHO provides this very helpful chart on vaccine efficacy versus the variant #SARSCoV2 strains. https://t.co/YJDeWhZRwL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHO notes which variants are of concern, versus "of interest".. MORE https://t.co/QkjTI6PifU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @WHO has provided a #COVID19 variants rundown,  underscoring uncertainty about just how significant a role the B.1.167 "double mutant" is playing in the India surge. MORE https://t.co/3SwyXMePyX https://t.co/1LOyyaqzI2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These #pandemic images are amazing -- bravo to al of the students that made these erstwhile @NewYorker covers. https://t.co/S7s3284hLl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FORTY YEARS. The anniversary of discovery of AIDS is June 5, when the first case report appeared in MMWR. https://t.co/dwK47BZITb At least 75 million people have been infected since then, and 32 million have died of AIDS.  To date, #COVID19 has infected 150M and slain 3.1 million https://t.co/gKgVQcXHam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SamCowie84: G1 reports that Brazil has reached grim milestone of 400k Covid-19 deaths. 100k deaths recorded in the last 36 days. April]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll be on @MSNBC w/@NicolleDWallace @DeadlineWH in a few minutes -- talking, of course, about #COVID19 .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A year ago many financial wizs were predicting a downfall for the U.S. economy, thanks to #COVID19 .  They couldn't be more wrong, says @FT expert @martinwolf_  https://t.co/o2Zm70NE4X https://t.co/Nb3NpGRckr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three months ago scientists in India were claiming such high rates of asymptomatic infection had occurred in the nation's largest cities that they had achieved herd immunity. Then the ghastly surge in cases and deaths happened. What did they get wrong? https://t.co/NiHTHCHdAE https://t.co/SmIIOAPEhv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nowthisnews: Lets end cancer as we know it. Its within our power  Pres. Biden said we should invest in health the same way we inve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: While New York City will fully reopen on July 1, the office people remember is very different from the one they will return]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @channelstv: Indias COVID-19 Crisis Could Happen Anywhere  WHO https://t.co/pNlIPRvQLW https://t.co/GIY6ZK8DJJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbremmer: Big Colombian protests against a proposed tax reform... despite a court order ruling the marches be postponed because of a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jaw-dropping. And still, the government is allowing political rallies in many States. https://t.co/IQ5yDeOZHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelthiaRicks: Medical investigators at @IcahnMountSinai in New York City are studying and developingcancer vaccines. They're also wor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020/21 might turn out to be turning point years for Science. The #COVID19 lockdowns, often w/lab shut-downs, have forced 1000s of scientists to spend less time rushing small lab experiments for publications, and more time thinking big. #ScienceMatters https://t.co/O4QllMegXR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOPE https://t.co/ElXGDJAdhU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Speech to Congress, @POTUS @JoeBiden : "The autocrats will not win the future. America will. I have never been more confident or more optimistic about America. We have stared into an abyss of insurrection and autocracy  of pandemic and pain  and 'We the People' did not flinch."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's possible to give #COVID19 to your pet cat. A UK vet study found two house cats infected by their owners: one was asymptomatic, the other became mildly ill. https://t.co/9H1jFPTFjF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Study in UK of @pfizer  @AstraZeneca vaxes shows just 1 dose cuts spread within households by 50%. https://t.co/4jEfiUi2sG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Independent: Senator Ron Johnson questions why US should vaccinate everyone, so Fauci gives him 567,000 reasons https://t.co/keewErp1J2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: "W/current technology...we can capture at least 6,700 PWh p.a. from solar  wind, which is &gt;100 Xs global energy demand. The collapse in renewable costs in the last 3 yrs means that 1/2 of this solar  wind tech  now has economic potential" https://t.co/gUFvWamaf5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hildabast: Phase 3 immunogenicity  safety trial registered for CureVac  flu vaccine together in people aged 60+. https://t.co/fAOUn7U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelthiaRicks: Is a variant to blame for Indias deepening Covid-19 crisis? Doctors, the public and the media are citing anecdotal  but]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>