<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Ive been saying this as a broken record for more than one year now.  Please repeat after me: T-cells are our unsung heroes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vitamin D has crucial role in reducing infections. Imposing lockdowns/restrictions to stay at home is denying people such simple solutions. Not a single scientific evidence exists that people infect each other in public places. Lockdowns kill. @narendramodi @nitin_gadkari @ndtv https://t.co/533aOqa7YP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vitamin D has crucial role in reducing infections. Imposing lockdowns/restrictions to stay at home is denying people such simple solutions. Not a single scientific evidence exists that people infect each other in public places. Lockdowns kill. @priyankachopra @akshaykumar #Mumbai https://t.co/533aOqa7YP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zerohedge: Evidence Reveals That Military Team Collaborated With Lab Where COVID-19 Pandemic Originated https://t.co/SEujqp4urD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @justin_hart: As noted below in the chart, people between the ages of 15 and 24 were 10x more likely to commit suicide than die from #CO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gbdeclaration: We are pleased to support the Collateral Global project that has begun, and will continue to, analyse the global impact]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: New Peer-reviewed in International Immunopharmacology  "A comprehensive update of immunological mechanisms underlying positiv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@politicalcomic Watch this from Nov. 2020 if you haven't. YouTube pulled it down. https://t.co/xGao8skuaZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @the_brumby: Why were lockdowns never advised pre-COVID?  Compare age 15-64 mortality Sweden vs US  Sweden: below avg death throughout 2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please listen. Pathologist Dr.Roger Hodkinson, his company sells covid tests. https://t.co/1uxVnuJdoi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: Three popular lockdown skeptic accounts suspended by Twitter, and where you can find them now:   Robin Monotti (@robin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aginnt: .@GovRonDeSantis understands the perverse nature of political power with authoritarian COVID law and how it is counter to the l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidjthunder: --THE FUTURE OF DEMOCRACY IS IN OUR HANDS--  A harsh flu season will be enough to set in motion the wheels of tyranny, b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Mumbai #indiacovid  https://t.co/N4U824d81V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Carmilla5 Thanks for sharing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffreyatucker: 1) Herd immunity does not mean the virus "goes away." It means it becomes endemic. 2) 70% immunity is the pharmaceutica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffreyatucker: Pathogens in One Lesson, Courtesy of Sunetra Gupta https://t.co/2HQehZwzMW from @aier]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Francis_Hoar: And contrary to international human rights law (Article 13 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights), for good reason]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Data clearly shows that no matter what you do, the virus will take it's course. Notice the low fatality rates. Let it take it's course to help develop herd immunity. Extreme measures do more harm.  #CovidIndia @swaminomics @chetan_bhagat @ShekharGupta @NandanNilekani https://t.co/8Mbu4a03Hi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Data clearly shows that no matter what you do, the virus will take it's course. Notice the low fatality rates. Let it take it's course  let us develop herd immunity. Extreme measures will worsen the problem.   @narendramodi  @nitin_gadkari  @htTweets   #Mumbai    #CovidIndia https://t.co/i7zC9bChhN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: #BoycottMSM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: A wise lesson I had learned from my late mother at a young age was never to care what others think of you. External validatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Chris Whitty: From now on there will be no more lockdowns - and the UK will treat Covid like flu.  Hes right. From no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ankurchandra123: By imposing weekend lockdowns, the PM and CMs are robbing the poorest of Indians - the hawkers, the shop workers - of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MLevitt_NP2013: Yes, all who said early 2020 that COVID-19 was flu-like were right.  List includes Tony Fauci 28-Feb-20, John Ioannidis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Francis_Hoar: Thanks to the incredible @laworfiction, this reached the High Court today. https://t.co/hw3AjvIusn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's not the super congested Dharavi Slums in India,  not the poor who are dying. It's the more media consuming  middle class and affluent of India who are affected by covid.   https://t.co/uQzOHnqIju via]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's everywhere. https://t.co/gZRqDCYjDO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhaskinscabrera: Universities used to be a benevolent presence in a community; now they enforce the woke orthodoxy.  In my county, near]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aginnt: "So whats the actual reason flu went away and hasnt come back?...No one really has a great answer. But we can absolutely, wit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: "Academics must urgently counter the very real danger of groupthink ... At least politicians are explicit about their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pratistha25: I want to ask the same to media channels. Most ppl in India have mild to moderate covid symptons. Because of your fear mon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YonSolitary: THREAD on What is happening in #INDIA  ***A) Dead Bodies Piling Up, Mass Cremations:***  Give the discredited RTPCR test t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: https://t.co/VWjrFyYxh1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stevetrian Decreasing case fatality https://t.co/twagYvqqp5 won't like it. Fear mongeres won't like it. https://t.co/EV9C6qlmig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shame on media channels, clips that u show of bodies piling up  full crematories in India are old images. Crematories are crowded even on a normal day. More than 20k people die everyday due to various causes. Ur hunger for TRP is driving mass hysteria. @narendramodi @AmitShah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shame on media channels, clips that u show of bodies piling up  full crematories in India are old images. Crematories are crowded even on a normal day. More than 20k people die everyday due to various causes. Ur hunger for TRP is driving mass hysteria. @PrannoyRoyNDTV @htTweets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shame on media channels, clips that u show of bodies piling up  full crematories in India are old images. Crematories are crowded even on a normal day. More than 20k people die everyday due to various causes. Ur hunger for TRP is driving mass hysteria. @nitin_gadkari #India]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YonSolitary @ColSanjayPande Truly, Ivermectin has been proven to be very effective. This is what happens when we use extreme measures to any problem. Lockdowns,  masks, social distancing etc. took away all the attention  resources, while there were easier solutions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone else had similar experience? https://t.co/cgGpulh1GQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelPSenger: Its long past time for leaders to pick a side:  Team FreedomDeSantis, Noem, Ioannidis, Sweden, Lincoln, Churchill, Wa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: Their disproportionate and sustained efforts to make something stick (masks, vaccines, passports...) show that they are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eYLVEZl7Os #CovidIndia #CovidIndiaInfo #MumbaiCovid #mumbailockdown #endLockdowns]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India has to stop repeating the lockdown, masks, restrictions. They increase infections, deaths  trigger panic that creates health system chaos. Open everything and provide targeted protection only to those who are most at risk. @_Aaj_Tak @nitin_gadkari @NITIAayog @narendramodi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: LOCKDOWN IS OVER FOR GOOD!!!   Right? https://t.co/qXUIcCJ2Hz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YonSolitary: Oxford Astra Zeneca "vax" is same as Covi-shield in #India  It is under Phase-3 Double-Blind Randomised PLACEBO-CONTROLLED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: Almost 10 million people die in India every year. Almost 27,000 die every day. C. 3,000 died with Covid-19 yesterday. Why]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TOIIndiaNews @TOIIndiaNews You'v done heavy damage by your fear mongering. Lockdowns have killed  harmed many more than covid. U never reported that 13.6 Million ppl. have also recovered from covid. Sweden,Florida, Texas etc. were open always and no covid disaster happened in such countries.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YonSolitary: Dear Indians  There's a group of people driving demand for lockdown, crackdown, mandatory jab, panic-mongering  These are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YonSolitary Monumental task to beat the overwhelming panic spread by the privileged class, the "educated" pseudo moralists who deny all data  evidence put before with a fake line -"but ppl are losing loved ones". Piece by piece we'll have to cut through all the fear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YonSolitary: The use of RTPCR test to declare any dying patient as covid patient and then to deny the person their last rites as per th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @galexybrane: There is no evidence that mask mandates have reduced covid cases, so at this point masks are just symbols of submission to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Francis_Hoar: 850 deaths out of 27,000 a day in India. And the pressure is for India to impose measures that will divert its limited re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@nytimes @BBCBreaking @ndtv @PrannoyRoyNDTV You should be ashamed for the hysteria you have built up in India by cherry picking news and manipulation...You are abetting crimes... https://t.co/u2WfNfjAxQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MHilltobe @talkRADIO @JuliaHB1 @Iromg @kylenabecker @naomirwolf @Francis_Hoar Thank you for sharing this...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaysanchezdorta: I asked a doctor in India (a fellow who is on the ground and not compromised - unlike most of those reporting on what]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WWakeUpTime: @Francis_Hoar 2,000 die of diarrhea every day. This is a letter from a Doctor there. Essentially they stopped using IVM fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CovidIndiaInfo #MumbaiCovid #Mumbai https://t.co/5wxkCAZlIT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mygovindia: Rumours claiming that new strains have made the virus deadly are FAKE! Do not fall prey to misinformation being spread onli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Francis_Hoar: The preposterous reporting of this in the UK and elsewhere really takes the biscuit. https://t.co/m5JB6Uui5A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Francis_Hoar Biggest battle right now is to fight the fear... Doctors putting teary eyed dramatic videos, BBC showing  cherrypicked images and videos....its a long list of fear tactics being used....Friends who are given evidence call us morons and nutcase.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: "With so many COVID19 deaths, it is now obvious that lockdown strategies failed to protect the old. The blame game for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want to ask the same to media channels. Most ppl in India have mild to moderate covid symptons. Because of your fear mongering, they've rushed to hospitals and led to shortages  black marketing. How do u sleep at night? @PrannoyRoyNDTV @BBCIndia @narendramodi @htTweets #Mumbai https://t.co/fA8HWj0Vha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media should be ashamed of itself for being so fake. and spreading fraud. Journalism is truly DEAD. London protests. https://t.co/LLBQZ8Fa7P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Francis_Hoar: It must have been over 500,000. That makes it the biggest since the Iraq War march 18 years ago; bigger than the Brexit d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MLevitt_NP2013 Sir India too has shown decreased case fatality rate since May 2020. More people might be positive but deaths have fast declined. Note that after May, tightest lockdowns also started easing a bit. https://t.co/ABoTnmgyMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AFranzsen @covid_london @MLevitt_NP2013 @AJEnglish @BBCWorld BBC thrives on such scary reports cherrypicked to spread panic. Did BBC tell you that 13.9 million ppl have recovered  many at home with basic medication. India is 1.4 billion ppl. In panic, ppl with mild to moderate symptoms freak out  get admitted. TB kills many more/year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: I cannot believe that after the last fiasco on Easter weekend  that went viral globally  the thugs from @CalgaryPolice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ronnocm2: Brilliant just brilliant  https://t.co/0Yq9wzP4ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: Death and injury following vaccination in the USA.  "Over 211 million doses of COVID-19 vaccines were administered in th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LockdownLazarus: Pure joy https://t.co/C4Yx0IwSqc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: A year ago, there was no evidence that lockdowns would protect older high-risk people from Covid. Now there is evidenc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieDarwin99 @covid_london @MLevitt_NP2013 You don't have a single evidence of deaths being undercounted, u've just read it in media headlines. Infact ,  deaths have been overcounted. Famous Actor Satish Kaul was admitted in hospital for last 10 years. But when he passed away, media headline "passed away due to covid".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@covid_london @MLevitt_NP2013 It's the panic triggered by lockdowns,  the widespread fear mongering by media, politicians and even doctors that's led to health system shortages. Not the virus. Less than 0.1% of India has been infected or dead from or with covid till today. 13.6 Million ppl have recovered.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MLevitt_NP2013 It's 1.3 billion people. And considering the fault PCR base test results, cases are actually miniscule. As for deaths, till today less than 0.1% of India has died with or from covid. It's the panic triggered by lockdowns that's causing health system shortages.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @galexybrane: It should be a huge scandal that so many early covid patients died on ventilators. Doctors intubated people prematurely an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJKayWriter @hagilani @MartinKulldorff @UCLA @WSJ I think when media tells 'crashed', it's defined so. This crisis is a castle of lies, 'word of lies'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: "One lesson that should transcend ideological differences: Dont put one illness above all other problems in society,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its crucial for doctors to stand up against the tyranny  fear mongering. Its the oath you took of doing No harm. Once the public looses trust in you when they find out the govts., media have been lying, then you will loose your job. #mumbailockdown #CovidIndia #MumbaiCovid @ndtv https://t.co/l56gELf8Te]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: World Medical Assoc Declaration of Geneva ratified after WWII atrocities demands every MD globally consecrate their "life to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drmikehart: Many doctors are now facing a challenging dilemma, do I say what's right and ethical, or do I comply with the governing bod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TOIIndiaNews WHO chief needs to answer : Q1. Out of 1.34 billion, covid has killed &lt;0.1% of India. How is it deadly then? Q2. 13.6 Million ppl have recovered from covid. How is it devastation then? How much more fear mongering will he do ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lockdowns increase infections  deaths by creating panic  forcing people indoors where viruses spread more. As per data, every place in the world that used lockdowns saw increased deaths. Maharashtra has proved this again. End lockdowns  the chaos will end. #Mumbai #CovidIndia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lockdowns increase infections  deaths by creating panic  forcing people indoors where viruses spread more. As per data, every place in the world that imposed lockdowns saw increased deaths. Maharashtra has proved this again. End lockdowns  the chaos will end. @OfficeofUT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Francis_Hoar: I am acting in this case. Interim injunction application next Friday. Statement of Case and submissions here: https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffreyatucker: How many people know the core facts on survival rates from Covid? How many media outlets have even reported on this whi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnculvenor Thanks for sharing  that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: I can't believe some people are putting so much effort into fighting to deny patients life saving treatment.    https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danielkotzin @speedster1857 @tlowdon Everytime cases go down, it's becoz of govts., life giving healthcare workers. Everytime cases go up, it's our fault.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India needs to stop this panic theatre using test case numbers. Till today 13.5 Million ppl. have recovered. Case fatality rate has been declining since last May 2020. It's now just 1.2%. Masks are only to keep ppl scared of the virus. #CovidIndiaInfo #COVID19India @htTweets https://t.co/n4zdonrk0n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sannesunshine1: After loving living in nz for 8 years, I can say that after what I've seen this last year from the smiling dictator Jac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrclaims Yes. I have no doubt that they don't work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear @narendramodi lockdowns send an overwhelming panic message to general public. That's whats led to healthcare shortages. Please urge the doctors, politicians  particularly media to not convey panic. Till today, covid has killed &lt;0.1% of India. #StrategicBlunder  @SrBachchan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lisakeb007 Ma'am actually its nothing. Everyday &gt;27,000 ppl die in India due to various causes. TB kills millions every year. The panic mongering by media, doctors and politicians has led to the health care burdens. Ppl with moderate and mild symptoms have rushed to be admitted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India is proving this true. Lockdowns imposed in past weeks have increased infections. Lockdowns and panic messages by doctors, ministers and media are the biggest strategic blunder that has compounded the problem. #CovidIndiaInfo @ShekharGupta @narendramodi https://t.co/Oakhlmx7Jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13.3 million people in India have recovered from covid. Not even 0.1% of the people are infected or dead. Media should be ashamed of the panic mongering. It's the fear  not virus that's led to chaos in healthcare systems. Lockdowns send that panic message. @nitin_gadkari @ndtv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13.3 million people in India have recovered from covid. Not even 0.1% of the people are infected or dead. Media should be ashamed of the panic mongering. It's the fear  not the virus that's the cause of the chaos in healthcare systems. @aajtak @akshaykumar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13.3 million people in India have recovered from covid. Not even 0.1% of the people are infected or dead. Media should be ashamed of the panic mongering. It's the fear  not the virus that's the cause of the chaos in healthcare systems. @ShekharGupta @narendramodi @kaushikcbasu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13.3 million people in India have recovered from covid. Not even 0.1% of the people are infected or dead. Media should be ashamed of the panic mongering. It's the fear  not the virus that's the cause of the chaos in healthcare systems. #COVID19India #CovidInfoIndia @JM_Scindia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Carmilla5: Covid Deaths Audit  Covid19 Assembly https://t.co/nmwLcy1zqG]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>