<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaO888: Three End Games for these fascists: Depopulation Slavery for those that remain Immortality through AI, Transhumanism and Clo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaO888: The Singularity is Near: WEF's agenda for AI and Immortality  Artificial intelligence and the future of humanity by inventor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaO888: Michigan State Economics Prof Mark Skidmore:  $21 trillion Missing Money from the Department of Defense (DOD) and Housing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaO888: $30 trillion: Official debt $115 trillion: Unsupported adjustments $120 trillion: Underfunded Medicare and Social Security]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cordeliers: The 5th Annual Vatican Conference, beginning May 6, will promote mRNA COVID vaccines and CRISPR gene editing technology. Mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: "Hancocks big project - 28,186 people euthanised in care homes and hospitals. 38,000 doses of midazolam and morphine a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @claude_roumain: This is part of a transcript from a document which outlines planning details before lockdown. When Dr Evans says "a goo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mercola: NIH sued for hiding dangerous virus engineering program. https://t.co/ATuAxVHLqd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikolovScience: Dr. Richard Urso, MD is the 3rd physician I've heard to testify before the TX Senate Committee on Health  Human Servic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StockShaman: The Clearest image of mars ever taken!!! NASA https://t.co/J2Sc8yfOhU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @squawkying: https://t.co/aTAAgEyaF2  Br Alexis Bugnolo Arrested for praying the Our Father  in public without a mask in front of St Mar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fall will bring the Windows Vaccine #CovidPoliticalGames https://t.co/CTPvRXgS98]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @igorsan88: @FiatLuxGenesis mRNA Is gonna change all of your cells.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sonicstout: @FiatLuxGenesis @Prosecco20 The winter could be so bad in the UK, it is an unimaginable horror. So many deaths would lead t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @csu_daniel: @FiatLuxGenesis The fall will bring the Windows Vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BobbyDoubts: @FiatLuxGenesis An then "they" will enforce us to take another massive vaccination with a sudden fast super effective new]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClodoOvalle: @FiatLuxGenesis The vaxxinated deserve it. They literally started this with their zombie sheeple obedience so let them suf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SlankardAndy: @FiatLuxGenesis https://t.co/cu8NtuLs3L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sleeverless: @FiatLuxGenesis This is what happened with animal testing of CV vaccines...the ferrets died when exposed to wild virus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @K_interfectrix: @FiatLuxGenesis Ive heart that too. The study on ferrets showed more than 1/3 died after later exposure. That was SARS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewJ97591595: @FiatLuxGenesis @FishEaters What happened in previous trials, a phenomenon called Antibody Dependent Enhancement (ADE)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COREYFSHARP: @FiatLuxGenesis Yes, its gonna be bad. The spike proteins their bodies are producing are going to attract virus like min]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Smtapu1: @FiatLuxGenesis Maybe. One thing is for certain and that is no one knows for sure what the long term side efects may be .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KateOBoyle2: @FiatLuxGenesis Thats what general McInerny said. That a new strain of virus will come out that well primarily affect tho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kobe_sylvester: @FiatLuxGenesis I am more worried about my woke elderly relatives dying from the vaccine than by covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobM777: @FiatLuxGenesis Will this actually occur ? Who knows. I pray that it doesnt. Some brainwashed people I personally know took t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KarolinaCrowley: @FiatLuxGenesis This is my worry too. My in-laws have all got it. They refused to listen to anyone who wasn't either o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arribas_june: @ranger_viking @FiatLuxGenesis Some people only learn when it affects them personally. Unfortunately.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CorneliusXavier: @FiatLuxGenesis What happens to the social order when 50% or more die?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CorneliusXavier: @FiatLuxGenesis Exactly right. Only an idiot would think that a billionaire who has a passion for depopulation would h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goodsuccess132: @FiatLuxGenesis R u seeing the thousands of women saying their cycles are messed up too just being around vaxxed people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Qygax: @FiatLuxGenesis well, there are studies that show post vaccine exposure to wild-type cov induces pulmonary inflammation: https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fighthefall: @auxiliumsolider @FiatLuxGenesis That's what I'm saying. If you're going to gladly hand over your God-given immunity, righ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Nucleic acid injections in animals led to auto-immune failures in many lab tests.  Of course this will happen to those stupi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: I know.  I know. https://t.co/OjDOxFY1xp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: "I wouldn't support Hitler if I lived in 1940 Germany."  Litmus test:  https://t.co/4KebhFZtfh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rothfarms: @want2Bholy @HicksonMaike But what we have here is decades of so-called shepherds that have been feasting on the flesh of th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JRBombadil: @Sharonand8 @HicksonMaike There are many false churches, only one founded by Christ.  This is only yo confirm that the Chur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: #Woelki promoted this man as late as 2017. If the Holy Father does not accept #Hesse's request for resignation and urges]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: The new revelations about Cologne are so appalling - both about #CardinalMeisner but also #CardinalWoelki. The leniency w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kathrynlopez: Pray that the Lord raise up models of holiness and great intercessors in the Church today. #homilytweet #PiusV https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: Very akward interpretation of can 1395. Because the minor (a male prostitute) was not UNDER 16 (but 17), a priest could s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: I bet St. Joseph and St. Peter are already carving some nice millstones for the bishops, who fail to be shepherds, protec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: While the Hohenzollern cheered for #Hitler, the Wittelsbacher rejected him. A fantastic documentary in which Duke Franz a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: Just when you think it couldn't get worse in #Cologne. The #Cardinal lied through his teeth - and knew that he promoted a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: Looks as if the Cardinal of Cologne has promoted two priests who had both abused minors ... and knew about it.  #Catholic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jack20190420: @HicksonMaike Yes it is.  I go to work normally and do not wear a mask at work.  Go to church normally.  I also refuse to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HicksonMaike: My question: who profits from this fearmongering and shutting down of our public life and economy? Why is the country whe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HicksonMaike: A report from a German living in China: restaurants and schools are open, vaccines not a topic, many are vaccinated, othe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @obianuju: Do these people know something that the rest of us dont? Are we in some sort of bio warfare? The world is only just recoveri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CortesSteve: The seven worst states in America for Covid hospitalization. All blue states, all mask mandates.  Source: WaPo data https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ulrichlehner: #Cologne priests abuse male prostitutes who are minors - but then the diocese  conveniently "cannot find them" -  assumes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HicksonMaike: Biden said he inherited a nation in crisis, "the worst attack on our democracy since the Civil War." What about the Biden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArchCordileone: Those who reject the teaching of the Church on the sanctity of human life and those who do not seek to live in accordan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaMeloni1: Yes! I once prayed for a sign re: the conversion of a slowly dying person who had never practiced the faith. One day, he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HicksonMaike: Here LifeSite's report on the new statement by @ArchCordileone on why pro-abortion Catholics should receive a public corr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HicksonMaike: Indeed, he [Fr. Amorth] states, One day Padre Pio said to me very sorrowfully: You know, Gabriele? It is Satan who ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KnLIJUME8z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: And if anyone doubts the first sentence of my above header:  https://t.co/b3oillN8we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: A feast day with chocolates and a jab derived from cell lines of a little girl dissected while alive for her kidneys.  No wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: The catechism of the Council of Trent is the only catechism ever declared by a Pope to be infallible. Therefore, to write pu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Instead of the purifying laver of Baptism, the Covid religion proposes the vaccinethe bearer of disabilities and deathas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: At 15k followers, I'm not a public person.  I use Twitter to show conservatives they aren't crazy for not following communis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Taking the jabs seems to me symbolic of all sindestroying yourself and judging those who wont.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Extremely wise Greek Orthodox priest here in this MUST-WATCH 11-minute video on C19V and totalitarianism and the book of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: These guys are all pumped to remove the face-muzzle for less than 30 seconds  https://t.co/FX9FXQPE5J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: This is a full communist coup.  But it's health-communism, not economic communism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrLeanaWen #NaziCovidPolitics #EvilCovidAgenda https://t.co/MwrPHj38aO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sachinettiyil: Catholic priest FatherFidelis Moscinski was arrested by the police in Manhasset, Long Island, on April 24, for refusing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tyskienow: @1ThessCh5 @garethicke That's just a label they give alternative open minded free thinkers searching for the truth! It makes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VinnyLadd: @1ThessCh5 Anyone who questions the official narrative is labelled a conspiracy theorist. When in actual fact all their doin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gonzo24Hare: @1ThessCh5 Embrace it, we are the ones who question things and look into it, instead of just watching msm n believe the go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DurhamUKGB: @1ThessCh5 https://t.co/izVhTKkJ8i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteDaniels84: @1ThessCh5 You're not a conspiracy theorist. You just know what's going on isn't right! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bigoneosv: @1ThessCh5 We been conspiracy theorist  we been covid idiots we been anti vaxers they been sheep from the start  being led l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1ThessCh5: This time last year I was a conspiracy theorist for saying the vaccine would be mandated worldwide, now Im a conspiracy the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: The CV mask covers the face.  The CV nucleic-acid jab "covers" the human genome.  The face and genome are the the two most i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: 2 baptized pro-abort "Catholics" and a woman who raided the home of a pro-life activist trying to expose the slaughter and s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Joe Biden just asked "every priest and minister" to talk about the importance of "the mask and the vaccine."  10-4.  Please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Did you know the true definition of pandemic includes "equal casualties across all age groups"? The Internet has scrubbed th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: God often gave the most astonishing miracles to the saints who said the scariest things about hell (the Apostles, St. Vincen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: https://t.co/YGBkFBF1az]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Because communism always trashes the poor while the rich-elite get richer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: https://t.co/Yiy9JlGphl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Trump tweets so mean but Biden is a gentle moderate for our country: https://t.co/mkfw0RUNt3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: Ok, so the picture was NOT doctored as people suspected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @daviddaleiden: Im preparing to testify at the PA House Health Committees hearing on Fetal Experimentation this morning.  Watch the he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: The Roman Martyrology says on 6 May, "In Rome, the feast of St. John before the Latin Gate.  Being bound and brought to Rome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrDaveNix: The only apostle not martyred was St. John.  But here in the FSSP Ordo this week, there is an optional third class feast of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aTAAgEyaF2  Br Alexis Bugnolo Arrested for praying the Our Father  in public without a mask in front of St Mary Major Rome #ItalianPoliceThugs #PoliceThugs #PoliceScum #GlobalistPolice #NaziPolice https://t.co/rOgVSeswiC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanStFrance: https://t.co/6sxXVBB7e8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanStFrance: Nothing is far from God.  St. Monica https://t.co/nNjVLNkm15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IanStFrance ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LifeNewsHQ: Iowa Constitutional Amendment Would Declare Theres No Right to Kill Babies in Abortions https://t.co/DGaoaU0EYp https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanStFrance: At 98 yrs old, Friar Roberto Maria de Maracana was the oldest Capuchin in Brazil and still genuflected fully. When he was]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pegobry: I know Republicans are incredibly stupid, but they cant be stupid enough to nominate a dude in a dress for an election.   Nar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LifeNewsHQ: Abortion is NOT health care!  Abortion is NOT health care!  Abortion is NOT health care!  Abortion is NOT health care!  Abo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AfDimBundestag: Pressestatement: Dr. Alexander Gauland zu Freiheiten fr Geimpfte und zum #Klimaschutzgesetz-Urteil des Bundesverfassun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CesareSacchetti: Renzi, allegedly involved in Spygate and Italygate, met on December 23 Marco Mancini, a member of the Italian secret s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CesareSacchetti: new appointments of the Italian intelligence.Renzi seemed to be very worried for these appointments because of his all]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>