<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[We must act now to stop the spike. With cases continuing to rise, we have no choice but to take serious action now or jeopardize putting the health system at risk.  #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike https://t.co/KNzNqqUcw6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So please, follow the health guidelines.   Get vaccinated when its your turn. If youre eligible now, please dont wait any longer.   Summer is just around the corner  and what that summer will look like is up to all of us.   14/14 #COVID19AB #StoptheSpike https://t.co/uCOckn06U6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The good news is we have vaccines on our side. They are already working wonders and are finally arriving in larger numbers.   We will soon be able to begin vaccinating Albertans over 16.   The vaccines will catch up to the virus and defeat it.   13/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike https://t.co/AM2VuOrB6d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats why the fines for violating public health orders are doubling from $1000 to $2000. The maximum fine for serious offences is $100,00.00. We will not tolerate those who endanger the health of their fellow Albertans.   12/14 #COVID19AB #stopthespike https://t.co/4ZrN1tQvd5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know this is all discouraging.   Nobody wants to be here after 14 months  multiple waves of this global pandemic.   But our commitment to the health and safety of Albertans must come first.   11/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Those who can work from home must do so. Masks are required at all indoor worksites unless workers are distanced from others.   10/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Further, outdoor sports and recreation will be limited to household and close contacts only.   Youth and adult performance will close.   9/14 #COVID19AB #stopthespike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Health, social,  professional services  such as massage therapy, physicians  dentists, accountants, and lawyers  are available by appointment only.   Indoor fitness remains closed.   8/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At 11:59 on May 9, personal  wellness services, like hair salons, tattoo parlours, tanning salons,  nail salons, will close for 3 weeks.   In-person dining at bars  restaurants, including outdoor patios, will close, being open for take-out only.   7/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike https://t.co/Ubxj4CkNZc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Outdoor social gatherings, currently limited to 10 people, will be limited to 5  with a strong recommendation that people limit gatherings to two family cohorts.   Sadly funerals, currently limited to 20 people, will be limited to 10.   6/14 #COVID19AB #stopthespike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Retail services must limit customer capacity to 10 per cent of fire code occupancy.   Places of worship, currently limited to 15% capacity, will be limited to 15 people, as they were last spring.   5/14 #COVID19AB #stopthespike https://t.co/fcdVDNr7sD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Effective immediately, Workplaces with COVID-19 outbreaks will be mandated to close for 10 days, with exemptions for critical workplaces.   All post-secondary instruction will move online.   4/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting Friday, May 7, K to 12 classes will move to at-home learning until Tuesday, May 25, after the long weekend.   This two-week reset will allow schools to come back for in-classroom instruction for the rest of the academic year.   3/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike https://t.co/8S3KHN9I0b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We must not, and will not force our doctors and nurses to decide who gets care, and who doesnt.    That is why we must act now to stop the spike and protect lives and livelihoods.    2/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike https://t.co/LEfqbZGj6D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Like most places around the world, Alberta is fighting a third wave of COVID-19. Weve hit record case numbers, and ICU admissions, driven by highly transmissible variants.   We will not permit our health care system to be overwhelmed.   1/14 #COVID19AB #StopTheSpike https://t.co/WF2BVVZft1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Taking questions from the Premiers Office  https://t.co/vT7YMynGZc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Effective May 7, all K-12 classes are transitioning to at-home learning for two weeks to protect the lives and livelihoods of students and teachers.  Find out more: https://t.co/NNGAHBvala https://t.co/YZOtKM5lz7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Announcing new public health measures to limit the spread of COVID-19. https://t.co/G3TH5k4WOQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Despite the delay in Janssen vaccines, Alberta will deploy 20,000 additional vaccines to support the Regional Municipality of Wood Buffalo and Banff.  Albertans 18 years of age and older in these communities will be eligible. https://t.co/thBDQIrzw9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enhanced public health restrictions are in effect in Fort McMurray, Red Deer, Okotoks, Airdrie, Grande Prairie, Calgary, Rocky View County, Lethbridge, Strathcona County, Edmonton, and St. Albert.   Learn more: https://t.co/kGlKWAwob5 https://t.co/Vkak75OrL5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1067REDFM: Today we celebrate our 8th Anniversary. Thank you Premier @jkenney for your greetings. https://t.co/SDZrb4oPyb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting May 4, Alberta teachers, early childhood educators, and support staff can start booking their shots.  By offering them the vaccine, we are making schools, daycares and communities safer throughout our province.  Details: https://t.co/3Degt7LPD8 https://t.co/qyStGpcjNc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Between May 4 and 10, Calgarys Genesis Centre clinic will stay open until 11PM to make COVID vaccinations easier for Albertans observing Ramadan.  Book your shot if you are eligible: https://t.co/t6gSnmlWUJ  https://t.co/NfBPyqZMja]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Update on COVID-19 and Albertas vaccine distribution strategy https://t.co/6q5irsVKSi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impressive work by Alberta biofuel start-up that helps turn waste into jet fuel.   A great example of commercializing research for the benefit of the broader public.  https://t.co/D1NSdjWZNi https://t.co/KLVAKyS01w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RicMcIver: Thank you to all of the volunteers who took part in the 45th annual highway cleanup on Saturday.  You've shown Albertans' co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jasonluan88: Today marks the beginning of #MentalHealthWeek. Albertas government is proud to stand with @CMHA_NTL and all of Canada to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New measures apply to municipalities or regions with 350+ cases per 100,000 people and 250+ currently active cases.  This includes Edmonton, Calgary, Red Deer, Fort McMurray, Grande Prairie, Airdrie, Lethbridge, Strathcona County  St. Albert.  Details: https://t.co/kGlKWAwob5 https://t.co/esoWj2WMAR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RishiKNagar: @jkenney inaugurated @1067REDFM this day in 2013. Happy 8th anniversary! https://t.co/y339wz2ruM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JasonNixonAB: The Legislative Assembly is adjourned for the next two weeks. All other government business, including Cabinet meetings,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I again implore Albertans to get vaccinated when it's your turn and to follow the rules in your area. To those of you already doing this, thank you. To those who aren't, please smarten up. The more people we have flouting the rules, the longer this pandemic will last.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If we do not begin to bend the curve, our health care system could very well be overwhelmed in a matter of weeks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats the opposite of what these folks are doing.  The reason we are at this critical stage of the pandemic in Alberta, with record high daily case counts and intensive care numbers, is precisely because too many Albertans are ignoring the rules we currently have in place.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On a personal note, I'm angered and saddened to see so many people selfishly put themselves ahead of others. Rodeo is celebrates Albertas Western heritage, a key part of which is our community spirit and looking out for others, especially the vulnerable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not only are gatherings like this a threat to public health, they are a slap in the face to everybody who is observing the rules to keep themselves and their fellow Albertans safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are all sick of this. We all want it to end. Thousands of Albertans are following the rules, sacrificing travel and social gatherings to do their part to stop the spread of COVID-19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is disturbing and to see large numbers of people gathering this weekend at Bowden in flagrant violation of COVID-19 public health measures.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting May 3, all junior and senior high school students in hot spot municipalities and regions will shift to online learning. K-6 students will continue in-classroom learning unless approved by Alberta Education to shift to online learning. https://t.co/KPMWGYJM3e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Easter to all Eastern, Orthodox and Apostolic Christians celebrating the resurrection today.  Christos anesti! Christos voskrese! https://t.co/qOPa32BeTm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertas oil does not get the credit it deserves.  https://t.co/Buyx2ZpkPp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank-you to the Muslim Association for inviting me to participate in a virtual #Ramadan #Iftar tonight, w/ MLAs Muhammad Yaseen  Mickey Amery.   Thank-you to Muslims in Alberta who are making sacrifices to observe Ramadan in a way that respects COVID-19 public health measures. https://t.co/2hKcn8pqUc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A good summary of our Alberta 2030: Building Skills for Jobs strategy.  https://t.co/TrUYLF2SKC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ottawas vaccine shortage has caused the worlds longest wait between the doses.  For Albertas government, protecting the vulnerable is a priority  and we have prioritized COVID vaccines for cancer patients because they shouldnt wait four months.  https://t.co/eitlJZeHmp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta will work with Ottawa to lower child care fees in the province, but any deal with the federal government must respect and uphold the range of child care choices Alberta parents have right now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here, our Childrens Services Minister Rebecca Schulz does an excellent job explaining Albertas position on the the $10/day child care program in the federal budget.   https://t.co/hWASGZE1JZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have partnered with @albertacancer to provide $15 million to launch CAR T-cell trials in Alberta.  Offering this therapy in Alberta makes treatment more convenient for patients, and making CAR T-cells locally helps reduce costs and turnaround times. https://t.co/oysFca6QNn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Line 5 must stay open.  There are literally thousands of jobs on both sides of the border which would be lost to idled refineries if the pipeline is decommissioned.  https://t.co/sNQKl4Yyh5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GoAHealth: Calgary vaccine clinic expands hours during Ramadan. The Genesis Centre vaccination clinic in Calgary has expanded its hours]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ambitious goals set with Alberta 2030: Building Skills for Jobs strategy. We are building a system that is highly responsive to labour market needs and will support post-secondary research and its commercialization to ensure Albertas long-term success.   https://t.co/TaKyywOAn6 https://t.co/46S1Gei0MN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination bookings are now open to all Albertans 50+, and all First Nations, Mtis  Inuit 35+.  With expanded eligibility, more than 2.8 million Albertans are eligible to get the vaccine.  Book your shot at https://t.co/t6gSnm4lw9 if you're eligible.  https://t.co/8QL8zYNZBP https://t.co/PPqfvpDlmL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great work at @calgarystampede kitchens to help Albertans in need!  https://t.co/MIWlqkFy2r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Update on Albertas COVID-19  https://t.co/2oYM0FRBY1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best of luck to Alberta's own @Hubbard_RMN as he prepares for the #NFLDraft.   An exciting step in what is sure to be an incredible career!  https://t.co/08AgATrtHl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dropped by the Calgary Covid-19 rapid vaccine clinic at the @CTCC_Calgary to thank the staff, and see what a great job theyre doing.  They can do up to 10,000 vaccinations a day here. If youre eligible, please book your appointment at https://t.co/t6gSnmlWUJ or call 811. https://t.co/sllzGCvSWH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @demetriosnAB: LIVE: Alberta 2030: Building Skills for Jobs initiative https://t.co/aDJyMLW40I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As part of Budget 2021s historic investment in health care, Albertas government is investing $59 million in Calgarys Rockyview hospital. This and other new health care projects will mean world-class care, when and where Albertans need it.  https://t.co/JjFuKIYBva https://t.co/i9CMwPaYVU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A promising tech collaboration between Albertas @altaml_com, @Attabotics, and @amiithinks that brings AI  robotics together to revolutionize supply chains with vertical warehouses.  Great to see Albertas tech leaders come together to grow and innovate.  https://t.co/mmyVnXx172]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This innovative cancer treatment is now available in Alberta, and first Albertans received the treatment last month at Calgarys Tom Baker Cancer Centre.  There are numerous benefits of having the cells crafted in Edmonton rather than abroad  https://t.co/iqrRfqSFPN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Budget 2021  Investing in Calgarys Rockyview hospital https://t.co/wGQacZEX2m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UCPCaucus: Today, on the #NationalDayofMourning, we take time to remember all those who have lost their lives, been injured or fallen i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A great collaboration between @doefs Greenhouses  and @EnerMerge producing electricity, heat and CO2 to grow high-quality produce right here in Alberta.  Happy to see the expansion moving forward.   https://t.co/1itn6g6dmg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An important legal win for Alberta today in our strategy to protect the value of our resources: https://t.co/9tBmNTGjuO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A friendly competition where all Albertans win!  https://t.co/K9sTWbUfKF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pandemic and the public health measures have taken a real toll on seniors living in nursing homes.  Thanks to the prioritized vaccinations of residents and staff, we are now able to allow indoor visits of up to 4 and outdoor visits of up to 10 people. https://t.co/pgA7d6WmEu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertas government is offering vaccines to workers at meat plants to protect them from COVID and prevent outbreaks.   Starting today, more than 15,000 Alberta meat plant workers will be able to get their vaccines under Phase 2C.  More details: https://t.co/xAXDGUfEwI https://t.co/sZqgKVT6Q7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone loves Kananaskis Country for its beauty.   Unfortunately, Alberta parks are suffering from increased littering and vandalism with record-high visits.  Please follow the rules to help keep our parks clean for yourself and others.   https://t.co/0t8WA9ILMD https://t.co/DmZy1p0KzN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta is expanding vaccine eligibility for youth. Those born in 2006-2009 with underlying health conditions are now eligible.  This decision is based on emerging research showing vaccines safety and efficacy in this age group  the NACI recommendation.  https://t.co/xAXDGUfEwI https://t.co/k9lT1YstsX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a beautiful Alberta love story  Kudos to this Red Deer man for taking the time to learn how to curl his wifes hair, because she isnt able to do it herself.   And thanks to @delmarcollegeAB for helping him out! https://t.co/3abAycQ0J3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Removing the requirement for healthcare provider oversight will reduce the burden for businesses while freeing up health care capacity when it is most needed.   The program will maintain strict eligibility requirements, safety protocols, and oversight.  https://t.co/3Oa6S2fQU1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta is expanding rapid testing to make it easier and less expensive for organizations to deliver COVID tests and help prevent outbreaks.  https://t.co/nICwL7bLpj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Update on Alberta's Continuing Care Centres and COVID-19 Vaccine rollout https://t.co/TPUsnfLoed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertas aerospace and aviation sector is full of opportunities to grow, diversify the economy, and create jobs.   Good luck to Team Artemis on winning this contract.   https://t.co/8lwUWlFvXh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great entrepreneurship that helps protect Albertans!  https://t.co/ns9LTPcRPV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AHS_media: Limited AstraZeneca appointments are still available throughout Alberta and can be booked through our online booking tool: h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its terrible to see the suffering of the Indian people during this variant-driven wave of #Covid19, with thousands of people dying every day  hospitals completely overwhelmed.  I hope  pray for this crisis to end soon.  https://t.co/i856nhHPVA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: On @TheRoyGreenShow to talk about Albertas Energy and the federal budget https://t.co/PqHtSDavJ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To help struggling veterans get back to normal life, Albertas government has provided Homes for Heroes $1.1 million to support the construction of 20 modern furnished units.  The construction starts now and the houses are set to open in October.  https://t.co/OPuHcvzVtB https://t.co/aCerbLJXpg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news for Albertas forestry industry.  Many mills were shut down during COVID and inventories have been depleted.  Albertas forestry industry did not face shutdowns in either the pulp and paper side of the business and the lumber side.  https://t.co/xrCx0u3dWi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We remember the victims of the Armenian Genocide that began on April 24, 1915.   Let us call to mind the eternal souls of those who were murdered in the genocide, while being grateful to their survivors and descendants for safeguarding their memory.  https://t.co/o79Dr6zGUj https://t.co/C7BjYvEVkf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CAR T-cell therapy, a promising new cancer treatment is now available right here in Alberta.   The province's first treatment program using the product is now open in Calgary and will be launched at two additional sites in the future.  https://t.co/HNHaK8uuxW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertas government is committed to improving public safety.  Bill 61 will make it impossible for dangerous criminals to hide by changing their names.  We are calling on other provinces to harmonize their name change laws with ours.  Read more: https://t.co/B2VMYApm4h https://t.co/xLkqu4MHit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta is full of ancient treasures. Great find, Austin!   https://t.co/EobOYNr6BX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta now has 3,000 tech companies  more than double of what we had in 2012.   Such rapid growth provides a great momentum for Albertas recovery.   https://t.co/WcTunOT4GO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting today, Albertans can access AstraZeneca vaccinations on a walk-in basis in Brooks and Medicine Hat.   All Albertans aged 40 and over are eligible, regardless of where they live.   More ways to get your shot: https://t.co/t6gSnm4lw9 https://t.co/Ebz44TsECQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shandro: We continue to prioritize protecting those who are most vulnerable to severe outcomes, and we'll keep rolling out vaccines as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shandro: Its disappointing that we have not received confirmation of any future shipments of AstraZeneca arriving in Alberta.   We con]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shandro: With approximately 112,000 doses remaining at pharmacies and AHS sites, and over 100,000 appointments booked in the next 14 da]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shandro: Weve seen a remarkable uptake from those wanting AstraZeneca. Alberta has administered more than 48,000 doses in the last thr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shandro: Todays recommendation from NACI on offering the AstraZeneca vaccine to those age 30 and older is welcome news in Alberta.  We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This round of applications is open until May 31, with a budget cap $350 million. More details: https://t.co/wG2W3jywtC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Help is available for businesses struggling to make it through the third wave.   Starting today, eligible businesses that have experienced revenue losses of at least 30% can apply for the Small and Medium Enterprise Relaunch Grant to receive up to $10,000. https://t.co/e7wbVg3eNJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are doing everything to make vaccine bookings easy and accessible to protect the health of Albertans.  To reduce barriers to getting the COVID-19 vaccine, Bill 71 provides a paid, job-protected leave to all Alberta workers regardless of job status.  https://t.co/sIGDLn6nnq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shandro: LIVE: Making CAR-T treatment more accessible for Albertans facing cancer https://t.co/immXfG0NwQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[. @FlyEIA has become the worlds first airport to join The Climate Pledge to go carbon neutral by 2040  at no extra cost to passengers.  Great work!  https://t.co/KaAY9buxNp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta has lost one of our greatest builders  entrepreneurs.  Stan Milner personified the spirit that built post-war Alberta. He was an energy industry pioneer, created thousands of jobs, and gave back massively to our community.  I was proud to call him a friend. RIP. https://t.co/G9nwlHoyqk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news for all law-abiding firearms owners in Alberta.  Congratulations to Brooks-Medicine Hat MLA @michaelaglasgo on successfully passing this private members bill through the Legislature. https://t.co/XvJytvEyWX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glad to receive my first dose of Covid19 vaccine today at Edmontons Rapid Clinic.   The whole process, from booking online to the clinic, was seamless  convenient. Thanks to AHS staff for their great work!  Please get vaccinated if youre eligible to keep yourself  others safe https://t.co/FQntRUoCdZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AHS_media: The Telus Convention Centre walk-in vaccination site in Calgary is at capacity and is no longer accepting walk-ins today. We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have also introduced financial literacy to Albertas draft K-6 curriculum to teach practical skills in finance across all grades in an age-appropriate way.   Read more: https://t.co/xWLOaJLtWb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting this fall, junior and senior high students will be learning financial skills to succeed in todays world.  To expand learning opportunities for students, @YourAlberta is releasing a call for grant proposals to create financial literacy programming. https://t.co/QeHBccg1zN]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>