<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@VMaledew You are right Vic.  It is all about getting rid of the masses and pushing the ones left back in to a miserable existence of work and poverty they will be digital slaves. It is coming and fast now they know they can brainwash the sheep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bee42681881 @boblister_poole @EarlswoodWarw Will end up like all the rest as the bent money worm will find its way in from Kill Bill and co.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boblister_poole Is it ever actually going to start up and broadcast any thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 OK thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@serendipity_14_ ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 No haven't seen it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HBiggus Lucky you, will it be awash with muzzled sheeples]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 Vote for nobody]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lovely blue sky here this morning. If it was not for the scamdemic it would be a great day. But no its Groundhog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 Shows all this stuff and the ideas behind it have been going for years just below the surface]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very interesting find from V F N 1999 cartoon https://t.co/qjFkfyVrOl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 Looks like a Chinese cartoon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 Yes and NWO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jennyrickson They won't, London is lost.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pavlos80322302 There are a lot of references to covid before the scamdemic started.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaveBritainUKIP: VOTE UKIP #VoteUKIP https://t.co/oOiVF3vo8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ToniaBuxton @JuliaHB1 The powers at be don't like anyone who is not a bent career Politician.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VMaledew Victor being English is even more of a problem. But I like to say I am English as much as I can. As that is the country that I come from.  I am a proud and English and from YORKSHIRE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bee42681881: This is what nature produces without interference. Beautiful. https://t.co/0BCibGiqpv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kingybcfc @MattHancock Predictive text made lying in to living. Perhaps the phone knows best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what all the globalists keep pushing. All very dangerous stuff https://t.co/iQAMlIFHx2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @boatratbown: yes it is if you want to change this vote David Kurten or Lawrence fox https://t.co/kRrQoJDKds]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HerdImmunity12 I think they will try to have another lockdown. The reason being the sheeples just blindly comply. They are on track to bring in all the new world order agenda. The plan is kill all independent business, control the masses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TenbyMosque JC was a much better Labour leader then the worm Kier]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyExposeNews Every thing to do with this scamdemic leads back to Kill Bill. He is truly the most dangerous person in the world.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Towler @serendipity_14_ @reformparty_uk Yes, will be this and much worse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kingybcfc @MattHancock Stop living Matt Stop harassing people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @luckyma_man: @MattHancock Good morning Matt, many thanks to you and the team These 10 minute updates on the vaccine roll out are a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VMaledew @Conservatives I think voting for an independent is my only option as I can not vote for any of the main political parties as they all seem to be one of the same NWO Globalists]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Steve_Laws_ Neither. Both are untrustworthy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thewle Is this so they can be twice as much of a threat to world health]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jen70717630 @petersingh206 @Legitscrutiny Bill the most dangerous man on the planet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike has the handle on this https://t.co/yYqfAbU4yy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0hmate Eastern Block of Yorkshire the rain has gone now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @molliepug2: Please share  Miniature Cockapoo stolen last night in Whitestone outside Spar has a distinctive heart-shaped nose. She]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrTardigradeUK @mmjblair @JohnWil15033691 Zoom probably is used to spy on what we are talking about.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thewritingcham3: Why did the golfer need new pants? Because he got a hole in one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@petedjackson @nigelastrong You are so right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @petedjackson: If it was about health, there would be:   No Alcohol being sold   Cigarettes banned   Fast Food Restaurants Closed ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bee42681881 @brownsauc Not Sly its a lefty globalist organisation that hates us white people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SimonPearson961 Are they going back in time to the 1930s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tonypierson2: Have you had the jab? A retweet would be appreciated thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Iromg Looks nice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what is wrong with most of the brainwashed sheeples https://t.co/nU8g2EvKd9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndrewYesudian @MartinDaubney @LozzaFox @SadiqKhan Khan is an idiot pretending to be a politician. Politicians in the main are clueless and just in it for the easy money.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamTLowry @MartinDaubney @LozzaFox @SadiqKhan Nothing wrong with cars Its the Eco loons that is the problem.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinDaubney @thedoctorxxx @LozzaFox @SadiqKhan Its all about driving the little guy out of buisness and also to kill any last little bit of fun that may be left. I use to go to London in my motorhome and stay at a campsite. I could use the train to get to the city no problem. The Idiot Khan became Mayor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@enuffsa1d @Alliance4Unity George is a good guy I hope he does well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KismetandHope: Perspective of life has changed so much recently I wouldn't be surprised if the sun was a lightbulb on a timer in a seri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LozzaFox  Thats dog for you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajorityRules2 @georgegalloway A very good move vote for George]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SimonPearson961 Have always called it that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASoftstar Run it is Chris Whitty come to give me the killer jab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@a_webb Yes, but I don"t as they would not listen as they love being Boris slaves]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fathoms_deep A very early Atlantan I remember them and the old Sunbeam trollies just.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@edthewatch @VernonF31630714 Up's "Caravanning"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@edthewatch @VernonF31630714 Well I have given up carving never liked tents and my Bike needs a new tyre. Still rains on me But I stay home Bank hols if I can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@serendipity_14_ Have only been to Jersey but I love it so much I must now have been around 15 times Would have been going last year but the scamdemic put pay to that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SimonPearson961: Im beginning to wonder about Hancocks figures. Frankly, I dont believe him. So lets check:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@serendipity_14_ Snap I love going to Jersey. Go most years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nice bank holiday weather. All the sheeples will be out in their soggy face nappies. The sheeples all follow each other face nappies are a must and Eco caravan and camping holiday weekend are a must. Also a drive in to the country with the bikes strapped on to the car is a must.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LozzaFox: Especially given that there is a cycle lane in Hyde park 20 metres to the right.  @SadiqKhan has spent five years waging war]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LozzaFox @SadiqKhan Every thing that is now going on with Puppet Boris and the likes of Starmer is not for our good they are in the pay of the globalists. We are in dangerous times]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HBiggus @SirPyecroft In our house we often watch the Sweeney. Gritty stuff and proper old school policing. I do just remember Dixon of Docgreen. But have not seen since I was a litlle lad. No TV channel showes it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mmjblair: https://t.co/adkMoOYmnl @natureandlandsc @noreward_norisk @NewtonClarkeUK @moolie61 @SamPamby @SteveG06322664 @ovni1969 @ovni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have a look at the link this is a good article an is on the money https://t.co/P4I0BpjMPw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very realistic the dead body is smoking a fag https://t.co/W2ERWA6iOJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WinterOakPress: Just one more thing... https://t.co/0KQCSqNsYB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_rumster1965 Looks like it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajorityRules2 @Peston Boris is just a big c0ck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mexico1978R: BBC = Bullshit https://t.co/rfrQiLOcbn https://t.co/GBfLbiyCkV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theorphanmoon68 Because they want socialism. They want all for use with nothing while they live of our money and efforts. Same old think keeps coming back Always a failure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love this tweet https://t.co/7K7eqgkz0J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maryjon48413793 Hi there, I think one of my words is invisible  " is anyone out there "]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More woke weirdoes. Needs to get out more. Wait for the abuse now https://t.co/b8imEgRLMm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Starfighter_X1 More real than you it wouls seem.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFreds Just a thought, has the phone got any good juicy numbers or emails]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Godnose @rospay15 Not really. We had real jobs and it was day release. All part of being an apprentice. In my last 2 years at college the hours where 8:30am to 9pm. Cant see the youngsters doing that now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TykeGrumpy @caroldecker Is she thinking that looks a bit like me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My motley crew back in the 70s at Trowbridge technical college this was the engineering student's https://t.co/AwuJXmC5yJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Think I am an invisible Eagle today. Is any out there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Invisible_Kid_8 @caroldecker Must be it is as ugly as him]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caroldecker: I made this myself out of a potato and a pencil . Kids today have no idea how to entertain themselves  https://t.co/zoxv4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caroldecker Thats a scary looking thing Carol. But you are right the kids of today are not inventive.  Should have seen our bike creations made out of scrap bikes back in the 60s Also I use to do a lot of art.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HopkinsBRFC A funny canoeing idiot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sunny Sunday here in Beaverland. Me and the sniffer hound are of out to check on the sheeples soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Andyrhno1 Yep ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadyNoo22 They are. But I think its working more on the older people from what I find. I despair at my friend that are my age they have all had the jab, they all wear masks. So I dont bother much with them. They have become unfriendly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TenbyMosque @Conservatives Conservatives and Labour are now as one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeteJacksonGMP: @JenWilliamsMEN @AndyBurnhamGM Between 2017  2020 I provided over 60 pages of docs to Andy Burnham re GMP being rotten]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: The invasion continues in Dungeness this morning, see exclusive footage of this beach landing.  They even needed a large]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadyNoo22 Dont you think they are trying to brainwash the young through the sport. I am probably someone who is in the minority as I mostly hate watching sport and always have.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Walkabout24 Funny I was all so born at a hospital that was once a work house it closed as a workhouse in 1939. So 19 years before I was born]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillScrotum I dont follow idiots like him. Also I am not an anti-vaxer just some one who does not want gene therapy for what is just a cold bug. Also who in their right mind would want to be lab rat and not even get payed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadyNoo22 Sky are probably the worst of the bunch Noo. Its all getting ridiculous now. Watching a bit of tv this evening. Every add has blacks. What can I say]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GROUNDHOG DAY agin as so many sheeples and still no normality #scamdemic  #NWO #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/PH1b7YKMuX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi Been busy out  about today few sheep to dodge, but just they way it is now. This afternoon project fitting  a little DAB converter to wife's car, so she can listen to her favourite stations. Can't believe how good it works, impressed. Tinny thing with stick on aerial.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFreds If I had a pub he would not get a pint from me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jimbothebull @SkyNews Nothing is normal now is it. and this was not.  The great scamdemic]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>