<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gates prenup may have EXPIRED  and their divorce could parallel Bezos split, lawyerclaims https://t.co/pZrls97WFd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stacey Solomon fears burglars will target her 1.2m Essex cottage as she tightens security around dreamhome https://t.co/AdJwBjkHiu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Widow, 78, cancels lifelong doorstep milk delivery after being told to orderonline https://t.co/uf9bVzvYiA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keir Starmer cannot shirk his lions share of the blame for Laboursmisfortunes https://t.co/gBJDLfith4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is Conan OBriens networth? https://t.co/G2O4NTClJq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian latest  KUWTK star shocks fans with bold bleached brows and peroxide blondehair https://t.co/T3vCGlZWyv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Washington Capitals Tom Wilsons girlfriend TaylorPischke? https://t.co/M3iljt9OHX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gemma Collins insists she looked like a MAN and her dad said she looked awful before having her fillersremoved https://t.co/kMFdrnD2Gw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Bill and Melinda Gates divorce as mega rich couple set to battle it out over 93bnfortune https://t.co/9ujJU3KumS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Styles shares a passionate kiss with The Crowns Emma Corrin as they film new movie MyPoliceman https://t.co/iKPUOJo8f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesy Nelson reveals breaking point that made her go on strict diet to lose weight before Little Mix videoshoot https://t.co/MNIkUowyVc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not buckling up your pet in the car could land you with a maximum fine of$1,000 https://t.co/ajMQBQWff0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi posts sarcastic ad looking for non-threatening female to replace Liz Cheney in House GOP after she rippedTrump https://t.co/ZwPldChFln]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Jennifer Lopezs mother GuadalupeRodrguez? https://t.co/g03AkxeK6v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pro-Trump Christian pastor claims its a sin to refer to Easter Bunny Biden as prez and insists hes ajackal https://t.co/nU0ItuguXb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Teen Mom star Kailyn Lowrysdad? https://t.co/F22YrjczNP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Local elections 2021: Get ready for the fall of the Red Wall2.0 https://t.co/7lQAh7UXvj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman confesses she lit a house on fire with people inside and pulled up a chair to watch itburn https://t.co/ND2FcA5grz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Kat Timpfs husband CameronFriscia? https://t.co/p9oB82Xhm3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesy Nelson reveals she broke down in tears in terrifying panic attack on video set before quitting LittleMix https://t.co/nP3iBWrfzD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Garner and John Miller back together nine months after split as actress ex Ben Affleck spends time withJLo https://t.co/IWVtgiedqx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who are the richest women in theworld? https://t.co/hn7ZCmTXyn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New 29.3m Porton Down labs to help future-proof Britain against Covidvariants https://t.co/LTFxg5ni3f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian DENIES she attempted to import stolen Ancient Roman sculpture after customs seized $750,000shipment https://t.co/LGLiYyQ7RW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Machete-wielding teen, 18, storms nursery slaughtering 3 babies  2 workers as staff hid terrified kids in changingroom https://t.co/Co4FyhCHs3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Piers Morgan slams hypocrite Meghan Markle for kids book on father-son bond after ruining Harry and Charlesties https://t.co/bWCyLjS56U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tristan Thompson mistress Sydney Chase slams reports NBA star is suing model for claims he cheated on KhloeKardashian https://t.co/QAcCe4pX7d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police urgently searching for missing Rebecca Goold, 14, who vanished on way toschool https://t.co/4kroUCeL5B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Keegan proudly shows off super healthy dinner of just fish and veg as she insists itstasty https://t.co/LDlghG11Xp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Restaurants Facebook post shames four gobs****s who ran out on bill into returning with the cash and apologynote https://t.co/rAYzosHXeP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ultimate guide to Thursdays local elections  what seats are up for election and how can Ivote? https://t.co/XX8v0C1fjV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good Samaritan in his 30s is stabbed to death trying to help another victim as five teens aged 13-16arrested https://t.co/t7JehuVnVE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RHONY fans label newbie Eboni K. Williams best addition ever as she reveals terrible credit led to car beingrepoed https://t.co/5w4wqj6SzV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man, 63, arrested on suspicion of murder after woman dies from serious injuries at home inOldham https://t.co/gmWS5U5pOR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LeAnn Rimes, 38, flaunts toned body in tiny yellow swimsuit on vacation with husband EddieCibrian https://t.co/tqPXjvBbHQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Model Hunter McGrady, 28, reveals her brother has died at the age of 23 as she wonders if she can live lifeagain https://t.co/FCtqGS9fDO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian latest  KUWTK star slides into Insta DMs of Sydney Chase who claims she slept with TristanThompson https://t.co/hmWGCxbSMf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman faces hate-crime charge for calling 911 on black Amazon delivery driver and called himN-word https://t.co/nccyy4Jxdk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love Islands Lucie Donlan stuns in white-lace lingerie with suspender belt for glamorousshoot https://t.co/7wrhMXUpI0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats happening in Colombia? Latestupdates https://t.co/P42sXyaJ9z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Devastated Michelle Collins reveals her mum has died after cancerbattle https://t.co/KUFvWeFpcz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Local election results: When will the winner beannounced? https://t.co/Lsgdvw6Sb3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK weather forecast LIVE  Mini-heatwave RETURNING with warm 20C temperature evenings perfect for pub beergardens https://t.co/YGnfVnCCaB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Candace Owens interview: Former president all but CONFIRMS 2024run https://t.co/zfrKXIUZrq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Josh Duggar arrest latest news  Fans urge Anna to leave husband amid troubled stars child porncharge https://t.co/eJ7Cg2GmaV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gates divorce latest: Couple to split property according to separation contract as they had NOprenup https://t.co/MA73hjbL1w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heartbroken boyfriend pays tribute to partner killed and eaten by black bear as he calls her love of mylife https://t.co/EiVNhAsnlW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Beckham kicks off his birthday celebrations with pie and mash lunch and visit from hismum https://t.co/r83SzLI1My]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Democratic Rep. Charlie Crist running for governor ofFlorida? https://t.co/7aXAVueUkS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden latest: President wants 70% of adults to have one Covid shot  160 million fully vaccinated by July 4holiday https://t.co/IrJcu42471]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marilyn Mansons alleged abuse victim Game of Thrones star Esme Biancos lawsuit has police planning to reachout https://t.co/BsNbmGfLbo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Little Mix fans react to timing of Jesy Nelsons exit interview and Leigh-Anne Pinncocks baby news just hoursapart https://t.co/CdEEyEEvBd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Chris Taylor hinted romance was on the rocks before shock split with MauraHiggins https://t.co/Wf43dIJHnP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mom-of-four, 35, dies from blood clot in brain 11 days after getting Johnson  Johnson Covid vaccine, familysays https://t.co/U3i7fcvriE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not buckling up your pet in the car could land you with a maximum fine of$1,000 https://t.co/sgpxABifPj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Noel Clarkes production firms 1.5m in debt  as disgraced actor is axed from jobs after sexual misconductallegations https://t.co/U8TnNWiML4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Views Joy Behar boasts a great catch is on the market after Bill and Melinda Gatessplit https://t.co/xb5EYiLG07]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran releases horrifying fake propaganda video showing the US Capitol blow up as GOP sen pushes Biden to takeaction https://t.co/7lwAtgkkTY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billie Eilish wore over $80k worth of diamonds on British Vogue cover while showing off curves in stunningphotos https://t.co/tTjPyI0W2T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man who sexually abused his young relative for years faces 312 charges of incest  one for each week he abusedgirl https://t.co/pyEqUXnkms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Widow, 78, cancels lifelong doorstep milk delivery after being told to orderonline https://t.co/6yGzYFPspd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keir Starmer cannot shirk his lions share of the blame for Laboursmisfortunes https://t.co/LOyO2zee3P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Bill and Melinda Gates divorce as mega rich couple set to battle it out over 93bnfortune https://t.co/Q9QTQup9OZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesy Nelson says she didnt know she could be this happy after leaving LittleMix https://t.co/L1atBSrTIQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brit Awards 2021: The Weeknd signs up to perform after shock Grammyssnub https://t.co/iW5U7Bqvu0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi posts sarcastic ad looking for non-threatening female to replace Liz Cheney in House GOP after she rippedTrump https://t.co/FBf7i3WJUv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When will Paul Sinha return to TheChase? https://t.co/vQpMuZ1oRE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Mark Labbetts ex-wifeKatie? https://t.co/EQs80iG5hu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Ann Winblads husband AlexKline? https://t.co/P37gG4V54Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Garner and John Miller back together nine months after split as actress ex Ben Affleck spends time withJLo https://t.co/6DImyqBQGt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tristan Thompson mistress Sydney Chase slams reports NBA star is suing model for claims he cheated on KhloeKardashian https://t.co/4ruX5M76wB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All over-50s to get a third Covid jab in autumn to stop third wave and tackle threat of newvariants https://t.co/Std9PJFXb1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who are the richest women in theworld? https://t.co/TdeomEXX5l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Gates divorce could see him lose secret status as Americas biggest owner of farmland with 242k acres up forgrabs https://t.co/vBSfRHCwK9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bidens and Carters photo goes viral as camera illusion causes President and First Lady to look likeGIANTS https://t.co/9AgRDmK7iO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK weather forecast LIVE  Mini-heatwave RETURNING with warm 20C temperature evenings perfect for pub beergardens https://t.co/RcSh5UT6T3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calls to end the witch hunt of veterans as trial of OAPs for killing IRA gunman 50 years ago collapses infarce https://t.co/vzcYCQtnMp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump gives STRONGEST hint yet hell run again in 2024 telling Candace Owens fans will be very happy withannouncement https://t.co/Icoc7XpMJ5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RHONY fans label newbie Eboni K. Williams best addition ever as she reveals terrible credit led to car beingrepoed https://t.co/mt1LA0RuPw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How does America celebrate Cinco deMayo? https://t.co/xTNC6Lfh3l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McDonalds customer horrified to find burger wrapper covered in poop as she sues fast-foodgiant https://t.co/adAxAD0JL0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Model Hunter McGrady, 28, reveals her brother has died at the age of 23 as she wonders if she can live lifeagain https://t.co/0uWx4ZBWh0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LeAnn Rimes, 38, flaunts toned body in tiny yellow swimsuit on vacation with husband EddieCibrian https://t.co/8T1aNHVmFZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian latest  KUWTK star slides into Insta DMs of Sydney Chase who claims she slept with TristanThompson https://t.co/DRVCCmAYo9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Josh Duggar arrest latest news  Fans urge Anna to leave husband amid troubled stars child porncharge https://t.co/E9hJhTq8q1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson blasts CIA recruitment video and describes cisgender millennial star as the Kim Philby ofwokeness https://t.co/OdYFAl9oBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gates divorce latest: Couple to split property according to separation contract as they had NOprenup https://t.co/sjqe87kx1F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Candace Owens interview: Former president all but CONFIRMS 2024run https://t.co/E8inecYQ9p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Democratic Rep. Charlie Crist running for governor ofFlorida? https://t.co/oJEDPcHuKZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden latest: President wants 70% of adults to have one Covid shot  160 million fully vaccinated by July 4holiday https://t.co/VOSILC7tof]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Views Joy Behar boasts a great catch is on the market after Bill and Melinda Gatessplit https://t.co/7nQCYRe5Zc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesy Nelson reveals she broke down in tears in terrifying panic attack on video set before quitting LittleMix https://t.co/OGjWYO0KXA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Kat Timpfs husband CameronFriscia? https://t.co/rJZvpWNiCb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Beckham kicks off his birthday celebrations with pie and mash lunch and visit from hismum https://t.co/Sw04wwM7Du]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mom-of-four, 35, dies from blood clot in brain 11 days after getting Johnson  Johnson Covid vaccine, familysays https://t.co/NdswguXvwf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marilyn Mansons alleged abuse victim Game of Thrones star Esme Biancos lawsuit has police planning to reachout https://t.co/wHTbuOBDTk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran releases horrifying fake propaganda video showing the US Capitol blow up as GOP sen pushes Biden to takeaction https://t.co/Q1DZicJoj8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Little Mix fans react to timing of Jesy Nelsons exit interview and Leigh-Anne Pinncocks baby news just hoursapart https://t.co/kGD2t9Pos3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Chris Taylor hinted romance was on the rocks before shock split with MauraHiggins https://t.co/CyecMte7oi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man who sexually abused his young relative for years faces 312 charges of incest  one for each week he abusedgirl https://t.co/pRqvwQhF0V]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>