<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine protectionism. Welcome! https://t.co/fZMyOUITMr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UKCovid19Stats Cry more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dutch Government introduces a curfew (20:30-04:30) for the first time since World War 2 to curb the spread of the UK variant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SilverVVulpes I made a little mistake in the tweet above, but these are the samples per time point, week after week:  1/91 1/133 2/172 3/209 10/183 22/163]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Correction: Rt of UK variant in The Netherlands is about 1.19, 30% higher than the 'old' one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@avanzuuk The latest OMT update.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Outbreak Management Team (OMT) in The Netherlands expects a new rise in cases in March due to the UK variant.   Harsh measures are probably needed 'until seasonal effects change and enough people are vaccinated'. https://t.co/FBfuXlhwMi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reproduction rate of coronavirus in The Netherlands:  'Old', most common strain: 0.95 UK variant: 1.30]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK variant in The Netherlands, random sampling:  Week 49: 1.1% Week 50: 1.1% Week 51: 1.4%  Week 52: 5.2% Week 1 (data not complete yet): 11.9%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[About 200 cases of the UK variant have now been identified in The Netherlands, up from 100 cases on tuesday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: A person in The Netherlands has tested positive for the coronavirus mutation first found in South Africa.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Situation in the UK looking bad:  In the last 7 days:   - 366,435 people tested positive (+47,6%) - 2,547,320 tests were conducted (-15,8%).  - 14,987 patients were admitted to hospital (+19,7%). - 4,228 people died (+24,5%).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_nickdavies: @i_petersen UK scientists originally interpreted this as the variant spreading (slightly) more easily among children than]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GuptaR_lab: Data on the N501Y mutation in pseudotyped virus bearing SARS-CoV-2 Spike, with and without delta69/70. The 501 appears to r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["A whole ward full of children with COVID-19". https://t.co/ZgqpHkjLYu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/pjmAvq4bSH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RussianEmbassy: Gamaleya Research Centre Director Alexander Gintsburg: Combination of #SputnikV and @AstraZeneca-@UniofOxford #va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NCoVAfrica Christmas backlog?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: The U.S. reports first case of UK variant in a person without travel history.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@truthsbytammy K bye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@silversynergy @paysupplystaff @MailOnline  https://t.co/dedu8lP99Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK variant in The Netherlands:  - 5 cases in region of Amsterdam - 5 cases in region of Rotterdam - 1 case in region of Nijmegen https://t.co/qZSvtNaPxc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The outbreak at the primary school has already lasted for over a month.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Research shows that 5 people in Rotterdam have been infected with the UK variant. They are linked to a cluster of infections in a primary school.  A total of 11 people have now been infected with the UK variant in The Netherlands.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeorgeJGal Not many worrying mutations, but these are.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: UK mutation VOC 202012/01 found in Northern-Ireland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marko010583 @rivm No, just today it became clear both persons haven't been in the UK.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cases have been detected in the region of Amsterdam.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: The two cases of VOC202012/01 (UK variant) in The Netherlands may be a result of community spread, health institute @rivm says.   Both persons with the infection haven't been in the UK recently and are not connected with each other.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mjsayed Agree]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The UK has recorded another 36,804 confirmed cases of coronavirus - the highest daily increase since the pandemic began.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: VOC202012/01 (UK variant) has not yet been identified in the US. - CDC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirgainsla It is an easy name to use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The Netherlands reports one more case of the UK variant. The person hasn't been in the UK recently.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@firefoxx66 Hey Emma. I was wondering if this new UK variant still has the potential to mutate even more? I don't see any reasons why it couldn't, so is it worrying if this variant which has already seen a lot of changes mutates even more? Thanks in advance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: EMA recommends the Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine for use in the European Union. The European commission will take a decision on the vaccine tonight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/SXk79J122A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The 501-variant of Sars-CoV-2 which is now spreading fast in England "may alter antibody binding".   More research needed. https://t.co/bpmi7rAbVD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Travel restrictions are among the measures under discussion, one source suggesting govt. could even restrict travel between the South East and other parts of the country".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: UK PM meets with senior ministers on Friday night to discuss how to contain the new variant of Sars-CoV-2. The evidence that the new strain of the virus transmits more easily has 'hardened up'. - The Telegraph.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: South Africa Health Minister announces new COVID-19 501.V2 mutation is circulating in the country and suggests 'that the current second wave we are experiencing is being driven by this new variant'.  // https://t.co/GCl0zUL5gF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: EMA will meet on 21 december (AFP), first vaccinations in Europe could be given before the end of 2020. https://t.co/EaihBLN0iA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarrySpoelstra: Belgium does have a special  #SarsCoV2 clusters spread. Question, does this translate into any different #covid19 epide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: German health minister says EMA could approve Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine as soon as 23 december.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mamamia1823 @MarionKoopmans @MarcBonten Maybe @BogochIsaac or his colleagues know something about it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lolette____ Yes almost certain, although it still has to be confirmed in a lab.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Or in Belgium @vanranstmarc?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0gzkIZt0Yp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So there does circulate a new mutation in England, which may lead to faster transmission there. Is that specific mutation also known to circulate in The Netherlands? Asking because transmission suddenly went faster, and experts didn't seem to know why @MarionKoopmans @MarcBonten]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QaAa8YpAJ7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING.The Netherlands to go into hard lockdown: all non-essential shops, barbers, museums, theaters, cinemas and schools will close.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Earlier today, a record 6854 new cases were reported. https://t.co/RYedlQbyU5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Netherlands to close all pubs  restaurants to curb spread of #coronavirus - NOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The Netherlands reports 16 new deaths due to #coronavirus, the highest amount of deaths since May 30.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The Netherlands reports 431 new cases of #coronavirus, the largest daily increase since May 7.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoxanneRoks It sort of is, but the Dutch added one medicine and it seems that it is very effective.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Dutch researchers find treatment that lowers the death rate of #coronavirus in severely ill patients by 65%.   https://t.co/Z2mWjjStol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nemoproheta https://t.co/fltySYo05B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ngyojiw Highest amount of cases in more than a month]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The Netherlands reports a record 144 new cases of #coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just in: Governor Kevin Stitt of Oklahoma tests positive for #coronavirus.   He is the first U.S. governor known to be infected with the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US has officially left the World Health Organization. https://t.co/01glbeNISi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@szabo_jon Yeah, sadly. They have to go back into lockdown!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[0 #coronavirus ICU patients in Toronto. https://t.co/6V1YCUTg3h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The U.S are close to 3.000.000 cases now, infections rising fast again..  What to do?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember Europe having only 10 cases of #coronavirus?   So strange. https://t.co/g7gRl8C8XY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember North-America having only 4 cases of #coronavirus?  It has been a rollercoaster since.. https://t.co/SeyBj0ru0A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[London. https://t.co/B3kbHf7jcO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Australia: cases surging. https://t.co/JtVt297Okv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/5v6MT3ndDC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The Netherlands reports 0 new deaths due to #coronavirus for the first time since March 6.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hydroxycholoroquine does not prevent #COVID19 in those who were exposed to the infection - research https://t.co/WhJgiBIQhA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YdhgxUCyF1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The U.S. cuts ties with @WHO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Spain reduces amount of deaths caused by #coronavirus by nearly 2,000.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Three more people in The Netherlands have been infected by minks, @rivm confirms.   Total mink-human transmission: 4  #coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: According to Dutch minister @carolaschouten, a mink has infected a human in The Netherlands.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Singapore ends lockdown on June 1.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oxford vaccine not really effective https://t.co/QG4ZQaAKmY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 patterns in countries around the world. https://t.co/b9Ibt7Ym1A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/2cjqYKzm6O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/0f0lZux3wV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Bangladesh reports record breaking 1,162 new cases of #coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Singapore reports 884 new cases of #coronavirus. https://t.co/YaJeVvVE1p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People can't wait for their cruises  https://t.co/Yij6B7fy7A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: #Coronavirus reproduction rate in Germany is back above 1.   @rki_de reports it now is 1,1.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Qatar reports 1,130 new cases of #coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Korea: 40 new cases of #coronavirus linked to a nightclub, 27 in Seoul. https://t.co/kL0Ye1v7ii]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Russia reports 10,699 new cases of #coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Brazil reports 9,888 new cases of #coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pakistan lifts lockdown, on the same day the country has reported the largest daily increase in cases (+1523).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Singapore reports 741 new cases of #coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Czech Republic reports 4-5% of population tested positive for #coronavirus antibodies.   27-38% of people with antibodies were asymptomatic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: New Zealand reports 0 new cases of #coronavirus for the second day in a row.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today in Amsterdam:  More and more people heading towards the city centre each day, but most of the time people do keep 1.5 meters distance from other people.   #coronavirus https://t.co/4JUAzAyK2d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Primary schools to reopen in UK on June 1 - Telegraph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: The Netherlands reports 97 new hospitalizations due to #coronavirus, again an increase. - 2 May: 97 new hospitalizations 1 May: 85 new hospitalizations 30 April: 84 new hospitalizations 29 April: 76 new hospitalizations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: US germ warfare lab creates test for pre-infectious #COVID19 carriers - Guardian]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Singapore reports 932 new cases of #coronavirus. https://t.co/2fRKEdD8zU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Today, Texas has lifted a lot of restrictions  State parks, retail stores, malls, restaurants, movie theaters, museums and libraries have reopened -&gt; with limited capacity.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>