<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Just one in 300 secondary school pupils tested positive for Covid in March.  GP Dr Renee Hoenderkamp tells Julia the "massiv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @n_plowman: My daughters class was asked today to put their hand up if their parents had had the #CovidVaccine . She is in 2nd class. SE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Parkin3Claire Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinWhitney The grown ups in the room do not come out of this looking good do they....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Retired paediatrician Dr Ros Jones thinks healthy children do not need a Covid vaccine.  "As a society, adults are responsib]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think if the last year has proved anything it is that the teaching unions do not have pupils welfare at heart. https://t.co/XC93FmF6MI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: Amazing interview with @mrmarkdolan on @talkRADIO today with his guest, Dr Ros Jones, a retired consultant paediatricia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If anything it's deeper than this suggests.  A failure to challenge has been compounded by the shaming of the few daring to do so and the cloaking of the whole thing as "caring" (when in fact it's often "harming").  The impacts for our children are ongoing, and catastrophic. https://t.co/9aZQdGgYUJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AllysonPollock @sunilbhop Yes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @allisonpearson: Angel! https://t.co/EOlKTY9unR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apsmunro: People keep trying to suggest children are just as susceptible and infectious as adults (or even more!)  There are so many st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EnergzdEconomy: @JenniferSey People outside of the US are seeing this picture and suddenly realizing that America has lost its mind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KathyConWom: In vaccinating children, we are conducting the riskiest medical experiment in all history. This experiment is unnecessary.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TiceRichard: VACCINATING healthy children, those not at risk, with vaccine  approved on emergency basis  still in trial phase, is wron]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sw1chg: Children have been weaponised. Not happy with the word but it sums up the awful situation as we fight #Covid_19... the virus AN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very interesting article questioning the use of emergency use authorisations for the Covid vaccine for children. https://t.co/4R5ZUHOPkV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristineBrett8: Yes when in fact it highlights that what is unsafe about schools now are the measures imposed on children by adults]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: They cannot say it, but I will. @Sacha_Lord  @hughosmond brought a legal challenge to restrictions placed upon our industry,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kthodgson_h Done!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KirstieMAllsopp: There is a real divide opening up between those who are afraid of Covid, and want others to be equally afraid, and tho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlotteCGill: It feels quite a lonely club - being one of the people wondering why, when the vaccine roll out is so tremendous, we ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Covid poses an incredibly low risk to children.  https://t.co/h2VekLuLGR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I don't think many parents could have imagined this, and far from abating it's getting worse.  I am genuinely astounded as to how the world got to this point. https://t.co/b4kTMKGc1z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How utterly spineless of the court - yet another state institution failing when it matters most.  My, how the faultlines in our democracy  have been exposed. https://t.co/e0H4tJhXDP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GavinWhitney: As ever, @lensiseethrough is absolutely right. Horrifying that we are even considering this. What have we become?   Healt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @13orangesbc: @SomersetCCC @PeterWanless @NSPCC NOTHING on the lockdown harm to millions of kids  NOTHING to the harm from muzzling (+ t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @13orangesbc: @SomersetCCC @PeterWanless @NSPCC @UsforThemUK @thelucyjohnston @lensiseethrough @janekin24 @Pondleg @KirstieMAllsopp @Ton]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @t20racerman: @Telegraph @lensiseethrough Excellent article and one this teacher entirely agrees with. Making kids wear masks for hours]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@t20racerman @Telegraph Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristineBrett8: I really cant understand people like @sarajcox saying they havent seen elderly parents since 2019! The fear of passi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @allisonpearson: On @BBCNews massive pessimism about opening up. Then the embarrassing fact -1 Covid death!   The disconnect between the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@d_matcham @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston @talkRADIO Thank you so much.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @d_matcham: @lensiseethrough @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston You were great on @talkRADIO earlier, clear, sensible with a kee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_InThisTogether: @alanvibe @lensiseethrough @UsforThemUK There's no "we" children are being harmed by the State. The vaccines pose a ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatePal12621605 @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston Thank you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellethejambo @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston Thats a cheap and pretty meaningless smear to throw against someone who has had all their vaccines (as have my children). The issues are fundamentally different when children themselves are at no risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Telegraph:  "Children are at negligible risk from Covid. These facts are blessings. We must not squander them by asking children to sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TonyHinton2016: @lensiseethrough @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston At least 2 children out of just over 2000 in the US Pfizer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterDain1: @lensiseethrough @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston https://t.co/GKq41RG0TA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@d_matcham @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston @talkRADIO Thank you. Yes I thought the flippancy was surprising given the issues at stake.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm disturbed we are talking about rolling out the vaccine to children - at what point did we reverse the idea that adults are meant to protect children, not the other way around?  My comment piece here.  https://t.co/ZONrRDCRRz   @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: Asking children to do something that does have a risk when there is no benefit to them is unethical. Lets be honest about w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rwjdingwall: @ShamezLadhani @SusieCoughlan @MAbsoud Main concern is creating an expectation of vaccination for children with zero evide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thelucyjohnston: @david_colquhoun @realdoll03 @rwjdingwall @NSPCC_Press @lensiseethrough @UsforThemUK @EstherMcVey1 Nhs not organised f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Grant_KenneTT: @PoliticsForAlI @Telegraph Why are we vaccinating children? Genuine question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ekaitzsaies: @thelucyjohnston @zoeharcombe @rwjdingwall @lensiseethrough @UsforThemUK @YoungMindsUK Instead of lockdowns, governments s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @n_plowman: @ElizAthertonSop @thelucyjohnston @rwjdingwall @lensiseethrough @UsforThemUK @YoungMindsUK Yes. We need a really good intros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SueC00K: These dire egregious ads. 320m. Of our money. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And lets be explicit about why we would even think about this: to use children as human shields for adults. Simply wrong. https://t.co/w29UVV2jVx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another brilliant article by @thelucyjohnston which exposes the devastating collateral damage caused to our countrys vulnerable young - children - by indiscriminatory lockdown policies.  It is a valid question to ask could this have been avoided. https://t.co/lPCjugsbZl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GuidoFawkes: Fox  Tice Plan Running Free House Pub With No Covid Restrictions https://t.co/JWBDkwk8jM https://t.co/rtOOZdjMNk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IsabelOakeshott: Apparently the PM has only just discovered how ruinously expensive childcare is in this country. So he tried to get a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TiceRichard: SUNNY SIDCUP with @LozzaFox and great team of supporters loads of enthusiasm https://t.co/0WjSrRYf3v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UsforThemUK: May 1st. The countdown is on to the promised end of masks in class on 17 May.   Time to let our children breathe.   @Boris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OliviaUtley This is so true. Particularly when dunked in luke warm tea.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@benjrooney That may well be true in your case - great if so - but we have seen countless cases where parents have struggled to get exemptions. Neither should it be for children to have to exempt themselves from a harmful policy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MAbsoud: Will schools in England still have to enforce masks in class??   https://t.co/QgdTVEgca0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: So frustrated that Im being called anti-vaxx when Im just pro-ADA, pro-HIPAA, pro-Equality Act, pro-First and Fourth Am]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeterDain1 @reformukwales Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NettieMarieJ: Excellent column exposing the UKs (and probably every other nation that forces children to wear masks) utter disregard f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @leoniedelt: @Francis_Hoar Primary duty of all educators is safeguarding of the children. Not the staff. Not their coworkers or staff. T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Telegraph:  "Children must be able to take off the masks, immediately, and they must be able to do so without being accused of putting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @usforthemcymru: Teacher speaks out about new normal in school.  We need clear exit strategy and we need it URGENTLY. @fmwales @wgmin_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsForAlI:  | NEW: A 12 year old girl is suing her school for "requiring or encouraging" pupils to wear face masks. She says they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sw1chg: @Telegraph @lensiseethrough spot on again.  Masks on kids always wrong but given what we know now its abuse.  @NickGibbUK sho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StuartBirkett2: @sajadah @lensiseethrough @Telegraph @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston Assuming they are asleep for 10 hours t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @armdale: @BBCNews @itvnews @Channel4News @SkyNews @GMB @thismorning @loosewomen @RuthieeL @nadiasawalha @Schofe @hollywills @benshephar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is unforgivable that a measure requiring children to cover their mouths and noses for 7 hours a day has been rolled out without any harm assessment.  My piece on the saga which shames our politicians here.    https://t.co/BM3nBWGrqV  @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Back on Twitter after a weeks suspension for posting a link to a public record. Warned that my next violation of the rule]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jblovatt: Dear  @NickGibbUK My kids hate masks. Do you wear one all day?   Also, do you sit at a table to eat lunch, or are you made to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toadmeister: When a meeting on mask-wearing in Arizona schools was cancelled by the school board, concerned parents took matters into t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @plumfairy72: @thatsmanderley The kids dont mind. Dont they @NickGibbUK do you wear one all day? Appalling answer. Detrimental to lear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fox_Claire: Who knew? We all bloody knew.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: No evidence to show masks in schools were necessary and now clear evidence that testing school kids through up more false posi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LexyTopping: Government minister in recognition that #SharedParentalLeave "is not working" Klaxon ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iamalisonperry: Hey Boris, please can we also have free pre-school for 3  4 year olds (and while were at it, heavily subsidised child]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfSarahJLewis: The Governments lawyers said that relaxing the requirement for children to wear masks would be unpopular - so gov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thelucyjohnston: Mask harms - new review. Drop in o2, fatigue, headaches, breathing probs. Long term - increase risk of blood pressure,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @13orangesbc: This is brilliant from @mamasaurusMeg who knows what she is talking about  @GavinWilliamson - where is YOUR evidence that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden's generous package for children and families puts our Government to shame.  My piece in todays @Telegraph on the crying need for reform of how we do families in the UK.   https://t.co/Z0wkxg3iEy  @EduPolicyInst @EducEndowFoundn @playingout @playengland @LexyTopping]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RachCarrell: Why is looking after children still seen as a private issue, rather than a public one?  Today, we launch our call to arms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RomanieThomas @DrPragyaAgarwal ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SusieCoughlan @jowilliams293 Exactly - we appear to be wilfully myopic (once again).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MAbsoud: Also missed opportunities to diagnose #LanguageDisorder  A common and important yet under represented neurodiverse condition h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great read by @jowilliams293   What I find contradictory is that whilst we jump on the precautionary principle to shield kids from things unlikely to harm them, for those that might - e.g. lowering of local speed limits - we must wait for harm to occur before action can be taken. https://t.co/vhcPk2gdex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great piece by @LexyTopping and good to see this issue gaining coverage.  @BorisJohnson if you really wanted to thank the working parents of this country you could start by overhauling the parental leave system.  It doesn't work for men, women or children.  @joshglancy https://t.co/zu5nySf7pj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wise words but grown-ups aren't exactly leading by example at the moment. https://t.co/mp0jvClIun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @beverleyturner: This crowd snaked all the way down the embankment. It was huge. And still NOT A MENTION on @BBCNews ! I honestly didn't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alexiskeech: At what point did wearing a crappy #SingleUse facemask supersede a far more superior #Reusable washable TypeIIR to get the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I agree.  The packaging the tests is such a tragic waste (as is the fact they are so inaccurate to be unfit for purpose). https://t.co/mFZ2VgvHn1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is upsetting.  "Last year, despite the global downturn triggered by the pandemic, tropical deforestation was up 12 percent from 2019, collectively wiping out an area about the size of Switzerland." https://t.co/tqcOjlkno5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BenGoldsmith: Single use plastic consumption in the NHS during the time of Covid (up ten fold my doctor reckons). Discuss? Do we dare?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSun: Anyone with more than one child can relate https://t.co/1fsoeekiq3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BenGoldsmith @BenGoldsmith do you think you might be able to follow me so I can DM you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristineBrett8: So sad tonight. Elderly relative died and her husband who has seen her every day during their 58 year marriage wasnt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karamballes @UsforThemUK Yes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TiceRichard: BBC BIAS: disgraceful @BBCNews zero reporting of one of biggest demonstrations in London in recent years, today, the Freed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karamballes @UsforThemUK I'd agree; the current plans need to be scaled up by an order of magnitude and we'd support smaller class sizes as part of that. Focus on creativity, sport, music and looking at where the current tutoring programme is failing would be a good start.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karamballes @UsforThemUK Yep - funding cuts at this point esp for disadvantaged children is the exact opposite of what is needed.  So far very underwhelmed by the catch-up proposals and funding allocated to those.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laworfiction:   -         Court proceedings on behalf of a child have been issued. We]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>