<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 8/8  Rule of thumb, for everyone: outside  either (a) 2m distance or (b) mask. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/4bu0rxNYGv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 7/8  Even better news (though just a start); More vaccine is starting to get to the places that need it most. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/LbCmbs1iaq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 6/8  Good news: First dose vaccination is expanding. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/hTrePBgOK1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 5/8  Ontario hospitals are transferring more patients to other centres  sometimes very far away from family  than ever before.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/2Yy4KHKA9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 4/8  ICUs are under incredible pressure  theyre still rising, even as hospitalizations crest. Were backlogged 257,536 surgeries. We cant deal with the backlog, until ICUs start to clear up.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/1WqwZJndIr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 3/8  Combo of vaccine and public health measures is driving COVID down. Were close to Yellow now, Green would get us back to February numbers by late May  but that means pushing down hard. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/cBu9oOqGJD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 2/8  Were moving around less  great But too many of us are still going to work. #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/2wlurtzZob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario update 1/8  The curve is cresting, but just This is a good start. We have to keep driving COVID19 down. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/SvKXliScOu https://t.co/aXvYCBxgwA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our current modelling, which we're now presenting at a news conference you can follow on CBC Newsnet, CP24, CTV News Channel and CPAC (to 4 p.m.) #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/5ZRt222XfH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We'll be presenting our updated modelling in a live press conference at  3 p.m. (Toronto time) today. You can see it at CPAC Canada Responds https://t.co/ez8M75OLs6, or your favourite news network... #COVID19Ontario]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave, because it's an ethical imperative. Doing this right can heal our communities, deepen trust between Ontarians  those making decisions for us, and fight a disease that we all share  but not equally. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/9eoUF4FkLb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave because the federal benefit pays too little, takes too long, runs too short  has too much red tape France, Ireland, Australia, Spain, the US  our Yukon cousins have more effective systems. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/9eoUF4FkLb https://t.co/OAy0D1PJT8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave because more than half (!!) of Ontarians must work onsite, often in jobs that have no sick benefit,  pay less than $50k per year; so every single cheque counts. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/9eoUF4FkLb https://t.co/JZEmNt34Ov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave to end the Third Wave. Most of Ontarios outbreaks are at work. In the US, effective paid sick leave -- the Families First Coronavirus Response Act (FFCRA)  actually cut COVID-19 spread in half. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/9eoUF4FkLb https://t.co/Mh7OSQ5ShU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave to protect employees  businesses. It reduces absenteeism, increases productivity (by preventing workplace outbreaks)  supports businesses  especially sm biz w/ tight cash flow  through COVID. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/9eoUF4FkLb https://t.co/m3YFZEeVNE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/6 Ontario needs EFFECTIVE sick leave. Looks like this: 1. You call your employer, 2. Employer keeps paying you (enough) 3. Government pays employer (fully) 4. You get better and go back to work. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/9eoUF4FkLb https://t.co/lKa9R8FocA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is an early, early sign -- we seem to be heading in the right direction. Rt for Variants of Concern (95% of our COVID now) are &lt;1. It's 0.94 to be precise. We have a long (long) way to go, but this is the right start. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/Rh1DKrZNRD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/2 Two things fight COVID faster than vaccine: masking  distancing. But a year+ in, its hard  even harder to help the people around you stick to it. Behavioural Science offers an important guide to this critical work. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eB1PigZTjE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/2 Were all in a position to help our neighbours, family, co-workers and friends stay safe from COVID. Our behavioural scientists have this guidance for shaping a safe environment where you work and play. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eB1PigZTjE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/3 Focusing on hotspots protects all of us, because vaccines also stop transmission. When we immunize essential workers, we also protect everyone around them (and around them,  and them, and so on...). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/nDX9zsC2XM https://t.co/9gAMxLY5Wz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/3  Just by targeting vaccines on hotspots, we can prevent 20% of SARS-CoV2 infections in folks 16-59 years old -- and 18% infections overall (!!). (This assumes 50% of our vaccines are for anyone aged 16+ in hotspots). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/nDX9zsC2XM https://t.co/5jhkYTYHKC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/3 Speeding up COVID-19 vaccination in hotspots and for essential workers will cut SARS-CoV2 infections, hospitalization, ICU admission and death. (Hotspotting is an effective way to target many essential workers.) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/nDX9zsC2XM https://t.co/iOlPszjeoA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OntariosDoctors: @Ontariosdoctors strongly support #COVID19 Science Advisory Tables way forward statement. #onhealth   https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OntHospitalAssn: The six steps outlined by @COVIDSciOntario will require consistent and effective government policy and guidance, combi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OntHospitalAssn: The OHA strongly supports these recommendations from Ontario's independent COVID-19 Science Advisory Table -- a clear,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Science Advisory Table statement: Ontario is now facing the most challenging health crisis of our time. If we want to bring #COVID19Ontario under control, protect our health system and reopen as quickly as possible, this is the way forward: https://t.co/xN7zHCWi10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imp't for MDs administering #Tocilizumab in Ontario. It's in short supply; here are clinical guidelines on how to manage supply in clinic. Pls read  share with colleagues. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/cfUdSmKmKx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Age limits on Astra Zeneca have changed in Ontario. If you are eligible for AZ, PLS GET IT. (while supplies last, as they say.) #COVID19Ontario]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7/7 But we can stop COVID much faster than vaccines can. Vacc takes weeks to work; staying home stops COVID in its tracks! COVID explodes when we move around. Please, please stay close to home. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/QnithG1VCz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6/7 The payoff from targeting our vaccines on those who need it most. Offering it younger, in targeted hotspots, almost doubles the effectiveness of vaccine. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/O3X2aXb5kG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5/7 Places that least need vaccine are still getting more than those that need it most. Ontario is working to change this, but we all have a part to play. Get it when its your turn, help others get it when its theirs,  wait your turn. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/IgaZrD0jby]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4/7 Please, get your vaccine now if its your turn; help others get theirs when its their turn; and please wait your turn. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/rsc8Alim1T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/7 Were facing 18,000 DAILY new cases. This isnt a curve  its Mum and Dad. Our daughters  sons. The person you love most in your life. Every person has a family, a story, a future. We can still stop the very worst from happening. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/GRbjsWZzgG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/7 Notice this, please. Ontarios hospitals, YOUR hospitals  some of the best in the world  are cracking. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/LTmn8IElnA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/7 COVID will keep growing exponentially as long as Rt&gt;1. Were in that zone on both VOCs (now dominating in Ontario) and on the original. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/eQ2lGrjLKG https://t.co/655thpu1qs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi everyone, sorry for the radio silence over the last few days -- we've been working... News conference today at 1 p.m. (Toronto time). Please join us here: https://t.co/sdWYCqjdn3 (or at most other Canadian news channels) #COVID19Ontario]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excellent all-in-one-page summary of clinical guidelines for COVID therapeutics. Clinicians: please read  share w/ colleagues. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/VQydJfNJrQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most of our homebound elderly live in Ontarios COVID hotspots. Heres a plan to bring vaccine to THEM. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/2K89EsMwCt https://t.co/X8QfB0u5TP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 25% of Ontarians older than 75 havent even booked a vaccine appointment  but most want it. The gap: Homebound elderly, who cant get to an appointment. Heres a plan to bring the vaccine to them. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/2K89EsMwCt https://t.co/wwcWG05hgN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Third wave update -- we're focusing on Variants, which are now the main COVID in Ontario (B117 is so much more infectious, we may as well call it 'new COVID'): Rt of Variants is 1.25. They're now 67% of spread. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/3pjEcUMGHS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For ED  inpatient health professionals: More clinical guidance on Astra Zeneca related clotting: pls read  share with colleagues https://t.co/Muz0lVBLlh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For outpatient health professionals: More clinical guidance on rare cases of Astra Zeneca related clotting. pls read  share w/ colleagues #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/TwFXSIphIh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Payoff 3/3: Saving schools! This is so important. Hitting this third wave hard will protect our schools, and our kids. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/p9rN0mvjMg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The payoff 2/3. If Ontario hits back hard NOW, we save our health care system. (Green Line). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/e0UBTJdx1Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Payoff 1/3. If Ontario hits back hard NOW, we bounce back sooner (green line). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/leWWsDV6Tz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays briefing  final thread: The Payoff (in three parts) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What we can do now 4/4: Spend time OUTSIDE with friends / family. 2m apart; masked if you have to be closer. (Dr. COVIDSciOn does 2m in a park w/ friends. Works nicely for coffee  losing at badminton not so good for chess, admittedly.) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/8HVuIBZPtE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What we can do now 3/4. Get vaccine into the highest risk neighbourhoods.  Highest risk areas are 1-3; for ages 80+ and below 60, theyre LESS vaccinated than lower risk areas (8-10), This hurts everyone. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/1RTZxSmd5v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What we can do now 2/4. Get your vaxx now, if you are eligible. And help others get theirs  book their appointments, help them get there. Any vaccine that Ontario makes available to your group is safe for your group. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/Jbt4rGftZQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What we can do now 1/4: Help essential workers stay home when they are sick. Workplace spread is a critical driver. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/wSdGfPqdra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays briefing  Third thread: What we can do now (in four parts) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Understanding VOCs 2/2. Lets call it the new COVID: Hits younger #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/quGEulUGcZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Understanding VOCs 1/2 Lets call it the new COVID: causes more hospitalization, ICU  death #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/nkbG6FVAlL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays briefing -- second thread: Understanding VOCs (in two parts) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our Third Wave 4/4 the longer this continues, the longer it will take to rebuild our health care system. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/pZ8py6mpIV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our Third Wave 3/4: Our hospitals are getting slammed. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/LKZrSE7uhv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our Third Wave 2/4: The provincial curve is climbing quickly. VOCs are 40% more contagious. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/QC4b0h8Sg1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our Third Wave 1/4: VOCs are driving dramatic surge in SARS-CoV2 across the province. VOCs are 40% more contagious. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR https://t.co/CyBB9LFlqR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First thread: Our Third Wave (in four parts) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were tweeting todays briefing a bit differently  theres so much to share Four threads: (1) Our 3rd wave (2) Understanding VOCs (3) What we can do now (4) The Payoff #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/WO1Q8CGGWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different. 7/7 Vaccines Work. If youre eligible, please get vaxxed NOW. If you know others who are eligible, help them make and keep appointments. Any vaccine approved by Health Canada is a good vaccine. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/acV1xJooBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different. 6/7. We CAN do more: BE OUTSIDE. Risks are far lower. If you can take it outside, pls do. While outside: stay 2m apart, mask if you need to be closer. (Always mask if you must meet or work w/ others inside). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/acV1xJooBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different. 5/7. Were not reacting the way we did before. We already have more ICU  hospitalization than we did when we locked down in December  off the same # of infections we had then. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/acV1xJooBj https://t.co/kpdDPHnUkL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different. 4/7.  This time we know exactly whats coming: VOC hits hardest 15-28 days after infection; Rising infections today are a clear map to more ICU and death within four weeks. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/acV1xJooBj https://t.co/6BpchWn7dG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different 2/7. Ontario is in more danger than before. New data: VOC are now dominant and lead to 62% higher risk of hospitalization, 114% higher risk of ICU; 40% higher risk of death. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/acV1xJooBj https://t.co/dlzJSKJX4A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different 3/7. COVID is hitting YOUNGER.  New data: with VOCs now dominant, 46% of ICU admissions (March 15-21) were younger than 60.  #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/acV1xJooBj https://t.co/66xomzGeqq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Is. Different. 1/7. Yes, weve been at this for a year;  were exhausted; weve heard it all before. Today, our news is different. The situation is more serious. We also have options. Pls read these 7 tweets  share.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/acV1xJooBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were facing a tough moment. VOCs are 68% of our SARS-CoV2, ~1572 cases as of today; Rt = 1.36. Standby for a full report on VOCs here later this afternoon.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/u8yQDGtbyT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Astra Zeneca benefits outweigh its risks. We have a good QA for non health professionals here.  #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/CYSzPMfVFh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Astra Zeneca AE clinical guidelines: If youre a health professional (espy primary / emerg / pharmacy) pls take a moment to read  share w/ colleagues. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/ZX1lkbOptI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontarios pandemic today: VOC are an estimated 1042 new cases (first time above 1000. They account for 58% of the spread and have Rt of 1.28. Watch that orange line (below). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/XPjulU4GmL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontarios Variants: Could this curve get any steeper?! Variants Rt is 1.25 (March 18) and theyre about 56% of Ontarios pandemic. This line is the message #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/3zTf8k2NPR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great weather coming up this weekend (unless youre in Thunder Bay or Kenora; rainy Sunday, sorry). Get outside if you can  be careful. Latest R on VOCs was 1.34. Variants now 54% of our SARS-CoV2,  were approx 830 cases as of Thursday.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/QNAdzT5w4T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest Rt for VOCs is 1.35. Todays estimated count of VOCs is 797 cases; 53% of the provinces SARS-CoV2. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/o7Sa2QA8ek]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontarios front line workers trace roots back to everywhere in the world, and deep into this territory. Wherever home is, this St Paddys Day message from our Irish friends may resonate.   https://t.co/Ez1j8flEqc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/3 We used open-source data to blueprint this for TO; any community in Ontario can develop the same plan. We offer some guidelines on how to do it. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/dKyLmn3psl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/3 Naturally Occurring Retirement Communities  buildings that have many elderly residents, but arent LTC homes. We used open data to pinpoint 256 in TOs high-risk zones; home to 41k seniors. We can bring vaccine to them! #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/dKyLmn3psl https://t.co/hL855HxhNY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/3 To beat COVID, we urgently need to vaccinate elderly Ontarians living in high-risk zones  but may older people cant make it to a clinic. Heres how Ontario can bring the vaccine to them! #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/dKyLmn3psl https://t.co/orM7EPW7QE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your daily R  VOC update: Rt on VOCs was 1.38 March 12 (takes a couple of days to calculate because math). VOCs are now ~53% of SARS-CoV2 in Ontario; that's estimated 778 cases. https://t.co/MN2BxNW43b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sadly, we are in fact all in this together. Ontario is organized into 34 public health units; almost two-thirds are now experiencing exponential growth of SARS-CoV2.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/gjmYYKPY5b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So, here we are: Ontario's Third Wave. This isnt a model..  Blue line is overall SARS-CoV2 spread; Orange line is VOCs -- now almost half of the pandemic and driving the growth.  (The two lines are now parallel). #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/i8hcod9XAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tough news for today: 733 daily cases of Variants of Concern = 49% of all COVID in Ontario. Yes, spring is here; yes, vaccines are coming; yes, weve been fighting for a long time  but this is NOT over yet. Stay safe til its safe.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/HuGfeJ6B4J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This variants of concern curve is getting close to vertical. Yes, vaccines are coming  but we are NOT out of this yet.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/j58HNkmzda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1.41 Thats the current estimate for Rt  (effective transmission rate) with variants of concern.  1.41.  The early variants are back above 1 too. Both well up from last week. Were heading in the wrong direction, Ontario. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/9xmRGdTB9C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID Update 7/7: Our behaviour is key too  Stay Close To Home! ("Our blue line isn't looking great, IMHO," says Dr. COVIDSciON) #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/DZQgwhidzA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID Update 6/7: Vaccines protect more than just you; evidence from Israel is that they also stop spread. (This is a big deal!!) #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/q6R18kjjCD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID Update 5/7: Vaccine speed is key: PLS get one as soon as youre eligible!! More than 1m Ontarians already have at least one dose. Chk your hospital / pharmacy / municipality / health unit.  #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/ybqnf4OmRT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID Update 4/7:  just when we need hospitals most #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/3o9zTH4vhc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID Update 3/7: which would slam our hospitals (YELLOW again) #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/Ln9EGFNZcj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID Update 2/7: And this new pandemic could get bad (check out the YELLOW line) #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/tRIIP68If7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID update 1/7: New variants are creating a new pandemic (look at the red chart) #COVID19Ontario  https://t.co/NcCK6nQO8I https://t.co/j4BWpPArAN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best evidence that we can turn the curve on Variants? We've done it before! (This is what we've done to the early COVID variants, which now account for ~58% of the virus in Ontario.) #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/XZrCVKu3UV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you check the Leafs / Sens scores every day, dont do that  itll drive you nuts. Check this instead: you CAN do more about Rt than about bad penalty kills. Distance, mask, stay home if youre sick.  Push Rt on VOCs to below 1!! #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/nbkBAKdmdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rt is the effective reproduction number  how many additional infections one infected person causes. It's 1.24 now on VOCs, but changes constantly based on our actions  immunity.  We need to get this below 1 by distancing ( masking).  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were now publishing Rt  how fast COVID is spreading in Ontario  every day. Check this like youd check the weather. (Except this isnt a forecast. It's real.) We need to get below 1 to stop the spread. Today were at 1.24 on VOCs.  #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/U6F16usw2A https://t.co/MNqkrh1NaA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our LTC findings show how important it is to first vaccinate populations who have especially high risk of SARS-CoV-2 infection, COVID-19 hospitalization and death. Doing this the right way will save more Ontarians, more quickly. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/1BVhNiRz76]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AND -- this is important  vaccines work best in the context of public health measures, until the whole population has vaccine-based immunity. So we have to keep our guard up while we roll out vaccine!  . #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/1BVhNiRz76]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Data show dramatic drop in death by COVID in Long Term Care homes. A sign of how powerful these vaccines are. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/1BVhNiRz76 https://t.co/L4B2mVFIKQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bravo Ontario!! Deciding to target Long Term Care homes for the first COVID-19 vaccines substantially reduced infections, hospitalizations,  deaths among LTC residents and health care workers. #COVID19Ontario https://t.co/1BVhNiRz76]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jyangstar: NEW: The province is taking the Science Table's advice to prioritize vaccines based on age *and* area.   My story last week]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>