<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: In an open letter, the Association of American Physicians and Surgeons asked universities to reverse mandates before]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRightMelissa: Bill  Melinda Gates are getting a divorce but the bigger news is what their foundation is being accused of around t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: You cannot imagine how badly I want to be wrong about what's happening in the world right now. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Towler: Please don't say you were not warned. @reformparty_uk https://t.co/IsltIgNWyE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GroundedGoddess: I'll just leave this here.... https://t.co/VgNoSkdIk6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: This is the article they want you to forget.  You should read it. https://t.co/SNZCaSpW2p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: This is the video they want you to forget exists.  Did this science change or did the propaganda slave machine change?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: Critical race theory was created to divide us by race and create racism in America...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: More than 500 people admitted to hospital with coronavirus after getting vaccinated.... Nothing to worry about though a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: India, New Delhi  This video tells a completely different story than what the MSM is feeding everyone https://t.co/tFb4ejNc61]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WinterOakPress: The #GreatReset (aka Build Back Better, 4th Industrial Revolution etc) is an attempted global capitalist coup on a scal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: They have no end date to all this.  Double mRNA injections just to act like sitting close to humans is still deadly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Shannon96574094: It's all part of their plan  https://t.co/LTrhWZCuuk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mkibbe: We are not debating if you should get vaccinated. We are debating if they should impose a national surveillance system, control]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Matthew_4_Trump: Remember, the elites will still eat beef whenever they want, fly in private jets, live in big mansions, enjoy their fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WinterOakPress: Here are Ten Things We Have Learned During the Covid Coup:  1. Our political system is hopelessly corrupt. Virtually al]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: 1/  Hello, my name is Gal,  I am an Israeli citizen, and I want to convey this urgent message to the world: Contrary to what y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: As an experienced multidisciplinary research scientist, having studied this in depth, I am certain that: All their measu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisdriver3: More than half of the new cases of covid are people who have been vaccinated.. Dr. Harvey Risch Yale university.. https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LevanaLomma1: A vaccine "passport" will do NOTHING to stop the spread of COVID-19. What it does do is create a platform for a new world]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: MUST WATCH + RT: @billmaher calls out media for pushing COVID panic porn + poll showing Dems are wildly off when i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thorsome1: India is waking up fast to the plandemic  https://t.co/VcWxqLbonp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MDFairweather: @AlexBerenson New York Post claiming people that sadly passed away 11 months ago, have now sadly passed away due to Covi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: 1/: Dear #ZeroCovid fanatics, I sometimes wonder whether you are aware of what you are causing with your attitude. You mock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrMoeOthman: Ahh the Covid fear propaganda campaign continues.  #fakenews   The world's a stage, and i'm just trying to pull you all ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeighStewy: The unluckiest Women in India.    First she died in the street during a gas leak in May 2020.    Now she's dead again in th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: We have seen nothing yet.  Get ready for what's coming next winter or possibly before......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @seanmdav: I can't believe this even needs to be said, but the CDC has zero legal or moral authority to tell you to do anything, and its]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ez_dee: Relatives in India: Yeh, it's all bullshit, we're all fine. Just turn the TV off.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: New CDC mask guidelines are a hostage negotiation to demand you get a COVID vax. Ppl who continually abided by these g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: The new CDC guidance is not designed for normally functioning Americans. It's for the zombies in D.C., New York City,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ev0l: I am in Ontario.  I can only buy the things the government says I can.   I cant drive out of Ontario.  I am not allowed to prote]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ToniaBuxton: And not a WORD on the telly or any MSM. Journalism is DEAD. We will spread the truth. https://t.co/cPr2Cow9TA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karma44921039: Watch this https://t.co/mOEXbcpWjE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @american_ka: Listen carefully! https://t.co/CBCLmNODnn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomiLahren: If you wear a mask outside- especially alone- you are a sheep and an idiot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @444_Yeshua: PLEASE LISEN TO THIS NURSE   https://t.co/rZ3NIDYbUs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: Bill Gates owning more farmland than anyone else in America should be a much bigger story. No one person should control]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JRNyquist: Why are all these people on about the same thing? https://t.co/jIB5MK0BZv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Bill Gates owns 242,000 acres of American farmland and now Joe Biden wants to cut our beef consumption by 90%. They want]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @awakenedbrooke: If you havent researched Event 201, Clade X, Agenda 21, Agenda 2030, New World Order, Great Reset, Gematria, Bill Gate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: 1/20: Giving people false hopes while leaving the population in a permanent state of fear creates the best possible conditi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Boris is conspiring with his Davos Globalist buddies (and girlfriend) to inflict the low carbon, high tax, 25/7 survei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: We are at a very serious crossroads. And it could probably go either way.  There is a tiny window still open.  We need]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheoFleury14: Hey everybody the next phase in the youll own nothing and be happy phase is you guessed it........ CLIMATE CHANGE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: Don't worry about Chauvin or LeBron or whatever new shooting suddenly gets too much coverage. These are distractions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SikhForTruth: How Vaccine Passports Will Actually Work.  #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere   https://t.co/Ryk42f13W2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WinterOakPress: More and more people are latching on to the fact that something is not quite right in all this, that we have been play]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Lockdowns + Medical Tyranny + Race-based media narratives + Climate Change restrictions = Game over for prosperous Ame]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WhitlockJason: We're all being played by the globalist elites. We're being pitted against each other and pitted against all institution]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: Dr Mike Yeadon: Former VP, Allergy  Respiratory Head Pfizer  Chief Scientific Officer Pfizer Allergy  Respiratory Res]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: First, we warned about never accepting masks and lockdowns. Then it was the coerced vaccines and the vaccine passport. Next, i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Thomas1774Paine: EXCLUSIVE: Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Drops New Bombshell  Bill Gates Coronavirus Vaccine Will Pay Out BILLIONS in Profit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @2LarryJohnson7: The fact the American public cant see past their own fear to see how all of this going to go down, then they deserve t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fatchancemate: Russia  Epic TRUTH, from A Russian Colonel, who duscusses Coronavirus and it's true purpose. Let me tell you now, it's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: Forced or coerced vaccination is medical rape: a crime.  We need a medical #MeToo movement now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ash007Truth: I love the military https://t.co/fPTFiTokvk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Meanwhile in Texas...  38 days since dropping Covid restrictions and mask mandates Full capacity sports Business o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: 2 people died with COVID in England today  Meanwhile... 450 died of cancer 4.6m on the NHS waiting list 18 ppl o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Once an epidemic has spread widely in a population or around the world, theres no chance you can eradicate the virus comple]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Stratford_: If youre under 60 and taken the vaccine, Im sorry, but you dont now get to oppose the passports or status certifica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JesseKellyDC: Im glad youre catching on to Dr. Fauci and the gigantic COVID lockdown scam.  If you had caught on BEFORE we reordered]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: Research on SARS-CoV-2 RNA by scientists at Harvard and MIT has implications for how mRNA vaccines could permanently a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikhail86439176: This is The Only Way to END Pandemic #Tyranny https://t.co/0lKbTvkJzC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: This guy is a hero - he is an American Pathologist - watch his COVID lecture:  https://t.co/JR5POJiTqL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Do. Not. Comply. #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @2LarryJohnson7: https://t.co/MF357CTVlE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fractalwatch: 2 minutes of red pill,that will save  lives. Watch till the end! https://t.co/pb9qS6P0Ei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Last summer, without a vaccine, we could travel freely; masks were not mandated for shops until late July and guess what:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thebradfordfile: Dr. Fauci has disagreed with every single thing Dr. Fauci has said in the past year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: The only reason, THE ONLY reason the putrid sack of dung would say something like this now, at the point we've reached, i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: Professor Mike Yeadon explains why we don't need new vaccines for Covid variants, plus a bombshell comment at the end of the v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Reminder: Complying with the moving goal posts doesnt end the pandemic, it keeps it going.  America isnt semi-free b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: I'm just checking that people know that vaccine passports were planned before Covid-19? (document was last updated Q3 2019]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: There are people just hoping Florida, Texas and other states Covid data doesnt continue to go down. IF it does, it smashes fu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robert_spalding: I dont think most people realize the COVID vaccine has not been approved by the FDA. It is under experimental protoco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Ive been warning Americans about how vaccine passport is the end of human liberty/ will be tied to your income. NZ Prime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Sick. Sociopathic. Bastards.  https://t.co/3aKKCv0Y8a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: My latest article: Keeping us masked forever? The Davos sets dystopian ambitions are very clear https://t.co/LkURNUm68b #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: There are 492 hospitals in Ontario. There are 496 people in intensive care units from Covid-19. They each have a hospital t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Spare_Me_Ur_BS: Pfizers Former Vice President Sounds Multiple Alarms NEW LINK  https://t.co/XmMyFE5yOe https://t.co/xyi6kOjTYj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlisonBlunt: 1) "The Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation and an assortment of high-profile figures and policymakers are pushing for unreg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: I hate to say it but its time for the opposition parties in UK, CN and yes, US, to demand investigations into all possible]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: Just ask yourself: why has no journalist in America been allowed to ask Dr. Fauci why the NIH supported "gain of funct]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stillgray: Patience has run out. https://t.co/TJfUYKswoV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AxelSavage4: The real conspiracy theory:  Complying with tyranny will lead to freedom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @End_TheFederalR: It's the other way around  https://t.co/SOqFhx73pD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RupertLowe10: Don't call them vaccine passports.  You don't need a passport to go to the pub or the cinema.  Vaccine papers.  They want]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Why did Fauci send millions of dollars to a lab in Wuhan??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: China is buying massive amounts of land in our country through Bill Gates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Notyour28981739: Since the vaccine manufacturers admit that you can still get AND transmit covid when fully vaxxed,  then vaccine passp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: Here clown-like actor Boris Johnson is cynically pushing #VaccinePassports as your ticket to freedom. He says businesses will e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffsekerak: Start sleeping 9 to 5. Start eating once daily. Start doing push-ups at dawn. Start praying or meditating. Start cancellin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ericmetaxas: I'm not getting the vaccine. I have no objection to others getting it. But it's not for everyone. There are too many quest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFreds: I still see people using the term conspiracy theorist, hoping it still works as a slur. Theyre inability to look around th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimKennedyMMA: This is a dystopian nightmare.  You dont get to use freedom as a carrot.  You dont get to incentivize me with freedo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DickDelingpole: The shit were going through is being played out with only slight variations in every country. And its being orchestra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: 1/ Nothing to see here, Moderna edition: Like the @pfizer vaccine, the @moderna_tx vaccine led to more pregnancy loss in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: China pulled off the most successful psy op in world history, crippling the free world into submission and an embrace]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: Fuck her and fuck all these people.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>