<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol https://t.co/3v7X73rhNK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank God! https://t.co/2OUFDVdPu5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Word  https://t.co/OcrNKuA77I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Children "take a mental picture , here is the face of a two faced hypocrite ". #shiftyShorten #auspoI #COVID19au https://t.co/4yp7A47Jjx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Biden #masks #Covid_19 https://t.co/m0bq8VM8h2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jane9873: Ray Hadley is the first commentator I have heard speak sensibly about the pause on flights from India! Jacinda stopped then t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Climate #GreenEnergy #auspol #auspol2021 https://t.co/PgdR7urjn7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RitaPanahi: Cheek. https://t.co/PotbE5P4QB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hmmm! https://t.co/b8BshRTbTx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Agree. Stand up and be counted parents.  Protect your healthy  children from unnecessary vaccinnnnes! #Covid_19 #vaccine https://t.co/RrGfB6P0xy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol https://t.co/5G2kWKNua0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol #auspol2021 #PortofNewcastle https://t.co/xYpjpOD3w4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guilty!  Now charge them and have immediate resignations.  #auspol #auspol2021 #coatesinquiry #Victoria #danandrews https://t.co/PwumbyV36L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElaineM11584892 Morrison!  How disrespectful are you left wing nut jobs!  You must be totally daft to think the Prime Minister of Australia would not have appropriate legal aid. #auspol #auspol2021 @ScottMorrisonMP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Trump https://t.co/EZtDXhMvTi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DonaldJTrump #thedeskofTrump #Trump https://t.co/CbpDlGIrxT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShilohStarrs @CherylABrown3 @kelly_rdc 2/ Underground movements are preaching the gospel in all of the countries you mention.   Yes billions don't RECEIVE Jesus, and yes many have not heard the gospel preached YET, but they ALL WILL have that opportunity in their lifetime. Plse Read your Bible  pray for those nations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShilohStarrs @CherylABrown3 @kelly_rdc That is just Not true. If I have heard of their gods, for sure they have heard of mine - seeing Christmas and Easter are known throughout the world. Ask yourself why these governments of these countries literally persecute  kill any Christians amongst those nations?  1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JaromeBellVA: Raising the refugee cap while ignoring the suffering of the homeless veterans already in this country is a perfect way to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ouch! https://t.co/hRDBgDOZ0y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 https://t.co/dTY85Ys0zC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol #auspol2021 #DarwinPort https://t.co/2pOb4Rg1di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MPedenRacing: @Therese_Rein @ScottMorrisonMP Can you confirm delivery of Pink Batts while you're at it please Therese?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol https://t.co/2eEmnxsy7r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Julia clashes with International Trade Secretary Liz Truss: You have battled for freedom and liberal values all your politi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WindaWester: @Reuters Like Microsoft's products, updates not always compatible with current versions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DELETETRUMP9: @Reuters I hope she tells the truth when the divorce is over.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alexgibson3d: @StillR0ckin @Reuters Word.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StillR0ckin: @Reuters You simply cant Excel at everything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mj_slats Can't agree with you Slats.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PartyReality: Because Zali is not a person to take on substantive issues . Another waste with @SenatorWong @KKeneally]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CherylABrown3 @ShilohStarrs @kelly_rdc Not yet! Whoever these bush tribes may be?  However, God reveals Himself in the very nature around them as well.  Every group of people were looking for a god of some kind throughout history. It's innately in man's nature to believe in something higher than themselves.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShilohStarrs @CherylABrown3 @kelly_rdc Absolutely not a bot. You made claims that are incorrect. In those scriptures you will see all will be given a chance to have Him revealed to them. It simply is a free will choice in the end.  Anyway I will leave this convo now  God is not withholding His love from ANYONE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not to be opened whilst she remains in governance.    #jacindaardern https://t.co/snOlBf1bYi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shame #jacindaardern https://t.co/SdxfHrlniQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Iyervval: Any surprises that Jacinda bugs bunny Ardern is funded by Chinese communists?  https://t.co/qW3OZ8l6TI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShilohStarrs @CherylABrown3 @kelly_rdc Read Romans 1:18-20 wrath of God is revealed..so they are without excuse.   Acts 4:11-12 Jesus is the stone that was rejected by you,..and there is salvation in no one else..  Deut 4.29 ..seek the Lord your God and you will find Him   Math 7.7 ..seek and you will find..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DigitalCurrency https://t.co/hMZZSSjUUc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking News  https://t.co/KR21b73X0N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Vintagedrummer7: I noticed that hed gone woke a few years ago and getting worse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShilohStarrs @CherylABrown3 @kelly_rdc Read your Bible.  YES they will.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol2021 https://t.co/bmq1857zKo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Victoria #danandrews #danielandrews #PortofMelbourne #auspoI #auspol2021 https://t.co/dGGp16bhcE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#danandrews #DanielAndrews #coateinquiry #Victoria #auspoI #auspol2021 https://t.co/MSUJl53cSB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol2021 #auspoI https://t.co/1s6mTybBbM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reveal company names. #auspol2021 #PortofMelbourne #danandrews #DanielAndrews #Victoria https://t.co/J4klULawh5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DefundTheABC How much longer @ScottMorrisonMP will you make taxpayers support the trash from @ABCaustralia  #auspol2021 #auspoI https://t.co/U6YE9tSVKt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@warnerbrosau Nope]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PREMIER DAN ANDREWS rape and bashing allegation! Read all about it!   Why are the media so quiet for such a big story? #DanAndrews #danandrews #danielandrews #auspoI #auspol2021 #Labor @SkyNewsAust @RitaPanahi @pm_live  @rowandean @7NewsAustralia @9NewsAUS https://t.co/Wf4As6NcPE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol2021 https://t.co/bOs4MG6TQo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Socialism #Communism #LeftAlternative #auspol2021 https://t.co/AGRHuVXdqF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GrumpyOLSoldier Was it called "A tale of Two Narcissists"?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catedempsey I'd go.  Look from afar if you have to -  at least to pay your respects.  Trust your gut when you get there if you want to take it further.  It must be hard on you.  Guilt is never an alternative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kate3015: @mattjcan It appears to me that is exactly what they are trying to do. I would have thought in your position, you would be en]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspoI https://t.co/giFZbBVQGG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SydneyLWatson: Free people don't need permission.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilMarsom: @GrumpyOLSoldier So they hammered Morrison for exactly what albo is doing...go figure!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MittRomney #Trump https://t.co/q89TwFxJDm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toddstarnes: Mitt Romney seemed offended by the booing and heckling. You know what else is offensive? Siding with the Democrats against]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: North Korea has dismissed Nuclear talks with the United States, says Biden's approach is "intolerable"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: Navy SEALs killed Osama bin Laden 10 years ago today.  Never forget that Joe Biden was against the mission.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol2021 https://t.co/sFToLwqTui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KKeneally @ScottMorrisonMP Verbal diarrhea from a screeching banshi!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspoI https://t.co/jD5Sm5VwRX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@oldgrandman  condolences]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol2021 https://t.co/HtR1Fya7R3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrMackay5 Yeah I wonder how many of his haters believe in horoscopes, clairvoyants, crystals, reiki etc or are fine with other religions such as Buddhism, Hinduism etc What is it about a Bible reading, church going Christian that gets everyone so upset?  Hmmm!   #auspol @ScottMorrisonMP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dandanstk: I hear McClown is up shit creek again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 https://t.co/kxJvaK1zm9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackJsherebkin: @Ladymondgreen1 Understand your sentiments Daisie..  But INDIA is Not "COVID Ravaged" its BS Got it first hand from res]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol https://t.co/7GySKRbczD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellymelly I can't take anyone seriously when the do the pronoun thing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. He is one nasty man. https://t.co/lMv7m4UjxG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnCharlesTwe2: @stixlives Sounds like more MSM bullshit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 #covidmania #COVID19India https://t.co/WQK2vXustk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @down_wet: @stixlives Yes .. 10's of millions must be tested a day .. where are the test centers .. who's producing the billions of kits]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 https://t.co/2LDSfzeTh8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dandanstk: @stixlives Impossible lol, their health care system has been non existent for years, they wouldnt be testing many people in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stixlives Why not give them #ivermectin to treat them cheaply? Anyone?  Anyone?  #COVID19India #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19India #COVID19 https://t.co/Dyf9EVBSJV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fricken unbelievable!   Really! Unbelievable!  #covidmania https://t.co/nTITGMVRTg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanWil62993886 Preach Ryan preach!  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes of the same ilk.   Media - the new enemy within.  #auspol https://t.co/lidmP10Owz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteamboatLion Imagine the complaints if Covid broke out again  they did not take this new threat seriously? Do you complain when your own countries states are shut down  banned from entering because of 1,2,3 etc break outs?  Shut up  sit down   #auspol #COVID19Aus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#auspol https://t.co/ZtPdteWPaq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes that was a shocking decision.  #auspol https://t.co/jL3KW3Ihk2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woo-hoo YES!  #auspol https://t.co/ndfL1I6RP7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanWil62993886 Clennell blocked me for picking him up on his clearly political preference, instead of being an unbiased political reporter.  He hated that the PM put his arrogant butt in its place  clearly used his contempt for him to try and get him back publicly. Jimmie boy is an Albo 2.0!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chasbarter Did they pray to Him, like she did?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HISGLORYME: Florida 8-Year-Old Starts Petition to End His School's Mask Mandate https://t.co/LK5CSYiEzM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: "Oppressors can Tyrannize only when they achieve the following.. A standing army, an enslaved press, and a disarmed popu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ROO3sixty @burrosavic @TheBatman1961 Yes it has finally awakened some sheeple ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well played.    I don't go to work to hear what your political, societal or sexual preference is - whilst on the clock.  That's after hours chit chat. https://t.co/nVU4VNEsn1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iosonoilmatrix: @ScottAdamsSays Do you remember those good old halcyon days, when you went to work, STFU and did your work and then wen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fscarfe @MrMackay5 All addictions!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GreenEnergy #ElectricVehicles #greenscam #auspol https://t.co/MRyQcGBQtk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBatman1961: So @AdamBandt  you approve of say Bio mass, you know the burning of trees to make electricity?? And you approve of burni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnRHewson No doubt you would have equally whinged  complained if the government allowed them in or put them somewhere for quarantine purposes. Pfft! #LaborLosers #LaborWhingers  #auspol #COVID19Aus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kingYacob1: "Every War in the past 50 Years is a Result of Media Lies" ~ Julian Assange  Stop the FakeNews about Ethiopia Stop the Fake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GingerGano I pray in all situations.   1Thes 5.16-18 Rejoice always, pray without ceasing, give thanks in all circumstances; for this is the will of God in Christ Jesus for you.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>