<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScienceisGlobal: @GenomeBC a special tribute to these extraordinary #WomenInSTEM for their contribution to the pandemic. Many of their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FLGenomics: Join our COVID  #Genomics Online webinar at 3PM.   Topic  #COVID19 #data sharing    Register: https://t.co/2N3c9jKfFm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GenomeBC: During session 2 Sharon Peacock from @CovidGenomicsUK, @clopezcorrea and @bronwynmacinnis are talking with @ScienceisGlobal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["...what COG-UK was doing had never been done before.  Prof Sharon Peacock caught up with @JuliaBradshaw_ at the @Telegraph to discuss how Britain leads the world in #SARSCoV2 sequencing   https://t.co/8IsaHI5GnB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HDR_UK: With over  20 well-known speakers + varied programme talks  discussions, #HDRSciCon will connect the #HealthData community ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FLGenomics: Join our last webinar in the COVID  #Genomics ONLINE series, as we will hear from experts how the pandemic has shaped our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uob_bear: Great to see one of the BEAR team recognised for making a difference! ^DC https://t.co/L9GgvDb3Gl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BioEmformatics: An insight into what makes the enigmatic Rads tick. The COG-UK consortium is lucky to have him onboard! https://t.co/ym]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StevenJDunn: So great to see rare photographic evidence of the legendary Rad.   When hes not saving the UK through covid genomics, he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In our new blog series, we meet a few of the countless people working tirelessly behind the scenes at COG-UK    Today, we meet Radoslaw Poplawski from the @unibirmingham @MRCClimb team   "...this project made me feel like I was making a difference"   https://t.co/86h1RCfKaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Professor Sharon Peacock caught up with the @NakedScientists and discussed the #COVID19 situation in India, variants and more    Listen now from 05:00 onwards   https://t.co/3KlhOJTi8N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't worry if you missed @AsiaSocietyHK's event, "Coronavirus Updates: Facts from Hong Kong and Beyond"   Featuring @ravgup33_ravi and Prof Sharon Peacock    You can watch the full recording here   https://t.co/iLIMcZoGVq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jcbarret: This is a good article about what we currently know about SARS-CoV-2 variants in India. Really important that it has on-the-g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sangerinstitute: Why India's Covid crisis matters to the whole world  @BBCMorelle @BBCNews   @jcbarret @CovidGenomicsUK #COVID19India]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @clopezcorrea: So much looking forward to the #GenForum21 A real honour to share the stage w/ Sharon Peacock from @CovidGenomicsUK  w/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is a new variant driving India's coronavirus catastrophe?   Prof Sharon Peacock and @jcbarret shed more light on this in a recent article by the @FT    Read more   https://t.co/ywMvuHLvsN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's next for COG-UK, after one year in operation?   In our latest blog, Prof Sharon Peacock reflects on the past year and outlines the consortium's plans for the next 12 months   #SARSCoV2 #COVID19    Learn more   https://t.co/pCxuyp4rnY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss @AsiaSocietyHK's event, "Coronavirus Updates: Facts from Hong Kong and Beyond"   Featuring @ravgup33_ravi and Prof Sharon Peacock   TOMORROW @ 1PM GMT / 8PM HKT / 8AM ET    REGISTER NOW   https://t.co/7kkGbotMOb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: "The Quadram Institute helped us to develop an efficient process to rapidly deliver the positive SARS-CoV-2 samples we had]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bioinfomatt: My talk from Tuesday's @HHMIJanelia science of COVID-19 seminar series is now on youtube. https://t.co/X12VKPLfIS - Check]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wil_rowe: Last day in the @pathogenomenick lab today - proud to have contributed to @NetworkArtic  and @CovidGenomicsUK over the last t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKCICstudy: Are you registered for #UKCICconference? Just 5 days to go!  Those already registered will be receiving information on how]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss @AsiaSocietyHK's upcoming event, "Coronavirus Updates: Facts from Hong Kong and Beyond"   Featuring @ravgup33_ravi and Prof Sharon Peacock   Tues 27th April, 1PM GMT / 8PM HKT / 8AM ET    REGISTER NOW   https://t.co/Sv4BnsAos5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKCICstudy:  One week to go until #UKCICconference kicks off!  We're so excited to 'see' you all online next week  Join us for our tw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidGenomicsUK: What's next for COG-UK, after one year in operation?   In our latest blog, Prof Sharon Peacock reflects on the past y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's next for COG-UK, after one year in operation?   In our latest blog, Prof Sharon Peacock reflects on the past year and outlines the consortium's plans for the next 12 months   #SARSCoV2 #COVID19   https://t.co/pCxuyoMPZo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emblebi:  Sharing raw sequence data   The Platform has driven the release of 85% of global viral raw sequence data into the public dom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sangerinstitute:  "[The Indian variant] may not be as problematic as other variants of concern [...] it may not be as transmissable as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PostdocPat: A preprint with examples of our @UoNLifeSci  @CovidGenomicsUK SARS-CoV-2 whole genome sequencing work in Nottingham with N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss @bioinfomatt from @SheffBioinfCore discussing subgenomic RNA expression in #SARSCoV2 as part of @HHMIJanelia's Science of COVID-19 Seminar Series   TOMORROW at 16:00 GMT / 12:00 ET     https://t.co/d6zqikE5YJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GenomeBC: Registration is open for our Annual Genomics Forum! #GenForum2021 will be held over three days, and will include a wide range]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @clopezcorrea: Have you registered for @GenomeBC Genomics Forum ? Super excited to share the stage with a great group of #WomenInScience]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: Quadrams powerful analysis of local #COVID19 outbreaks has made it instrumental in contributing to the national picture]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nextstrain: You can find the new sequences from Switzerland (64), Turkey (92) and the United Kingdom (1283) below.  (Thanks to @unil Ce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nextstrain: Check out the new sequences from Spain (206), Sweden (16), Switzerland (46) and the United Kingdom (1105) below.  (Thanks t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nextstrain: You can see the new sequences from Switzerland (151), Turkey (66) and the United Kingdom (5905) below.  (Thanks to Viollier]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ComputerWeekly: How the Covid-19 #Genomics UK Consortium of universities and other institutions has harnessed datasets, analytics and c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cardiffuninews: A great read on the work of @CovidGenomicsUK, featuring @tomrconnors work sequencing SARS-Cov-2, the virus that causes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScienceisGlobal: Dont miss the fantastic line up of our @GenomeBC https://t.co/y4AeHTSVrN #Covid-19 a moment of importance in #genomic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: Were only just getting started on this, its got massive potential. --  @SJ_LS @PHE_EoEngland   In our reflections of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can travel restrictions help stop the spread of #COVID19?   In a recent study, COG-UK examined &gt;4,000 #SARSCoV2 importations over the summer of 2020   @DrDAggarwal outlines what we have learned from the study and how we can utilise the insights    https://t.co/HEg6AaHIH4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MyMicroreact: great to see @myMicroreact being utilised to interpret epi-linked sequence data @NorwichResearch, @NNUH, @NHSuk, @CovidGe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Has everyone in Kent gone to an illegal rave?"  The @guardian are exploring the variant trail with the #COVID19 detectives - featuring @meera_chand, @pathogenomenick, @erikmvolz, @jcbarret  @neil_ferguson   https://t.co/H90c14Pn7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShefUni_IICD:  Were hiring   We have a vacancy for a #Research #Technician working with @Thushan_deSilva  #covid19 #SARSCoV2   ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: In their biggest individual week, our @CovidGenomicsUK team sequenced an incredible 1,900 #COVID19 samples   Between Oct a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sangerinstitute: 'Has everyone in Kent gone to an illegal rave?': on the variant trail with the Covid detectives   @sarahboseley @gua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CVRinfo:  You can now watch the @CovidGenomicsUK Science Showcase, where from 53:11 @robertson_lab chairs a session discussing #SARSCo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Williams_T_C: in just over a year @GISAID has reached the impressive milestone of 1M submissions   testament to the incredible hard, an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @malariagenomics: New blog: Dr @cristina_ariani reflects on moving from #malaria to Covid #genomicsurveillance during UK lockdown and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: UK variant hunters lead global race to stay ahead of COVID. The Quadram's @andrewjpage features in the @MailOnline and @AP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cambridge_Uni: Why do we need to worry about #COVID19 variants?  Prof Sharon Peacock is on the lookout for mutations that change the wa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COG-UK's Sharon Peacock is a keynote speaker at today's COV-IRT research symposium:  https://t.co/yvh9K00QXt https://t.co/tQx7eKU7lL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CGR_UoL: Another couple of @opentrons robots to help covid response and environmental genomics @CovidGenomicsUK @NERC_EOF May need more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sangerinstitute: UK variant hunters lead global race to stay ahead of #COVID19   @DailyMailUK @AP @CovidGenomicsUK   https://t.co/Ge6QG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The recording of Friday's Science Showcase is up!   New insights into molecular tests and massive sequencing  #SARSCoV2 variants: distribution, detection and prioritisation  #SARSCoV2 variants: patients and prevention   https://t.co/HC0Xp6h1nx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: We're proud to be a partner of @CovidGenomicsUK, delivering large-scale, rapid whole-genome sequencing of SARS-CoV-2   One]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MattBashton: It's been amazing to be part of this project for the last year, sequencing SARS-CoV-2 as part of @CovidGenomicsUK with the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nanopore: Over a year at the forefront of #SARSCoV2 genomic epidemiology, @TheQuadram reflect on the collective effort of @CovidGenomic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @msinnott123: It was a pleasure to be able to speak, many thanks to the @CovidGenomicsUK organisers for a great afternoon of talks! http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't worry if you missed the #COGScienceShowcase   We will be sharing a recording of the event next week   So watch this space ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A huge thank you to all our amazing speakers and chairs    @catherineludden @CLongstaff @templeton_kate @DrLMJackson @robertson_lab @AineToole @msinnott123 @alecarabo @judith_breuer @_nickdavies @wendybarclay11 Dr Sally Corden  Prof Sharon Peacock   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next up, we have @wendybarclay11 from @imperialcollege discussing #SARSCoV2 variants, vaccines and immune escape   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now, @_nickdavies from @LSHTM (@CMMID_lshtm) is exploring whether the B.1.1.7 #SARSCoV2 variant causes more severe disease   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next up, Dr Sally Corden from @PublicHealthW introduces @judith_breuer from @ucl, who will be discussing #SARSCoV2 variants and what we can learn from the HOCI study   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now, @alecarabo from @Cambridge_Uni will be speaking about prioritising #SARSCoV2 mutations and variants   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next, we have @msinnott123 discussing #SARSCoV2 mutation and variant surveillance at the @sangerinstitute   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Up next, @robertson_lab introduces @AineToole from @EdinburghUni who will be providing an overview of the global epidemiology of #SARSCoV2 lineages of global concern   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now @DrLMJackson, Scientific Project Manager at COG-UK, will be discussing non-sequence based molecular methods to detect #SARSCoV2 variants   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next up, we have @templeton_kate from @EdinburghUni speaking on #SARSCoV2 mutations and diagnostic test accuracy   #COGUKScienceShowcase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Up first...  @catherineludden introduces @CLongstaff from the @sangerinstitute who is discussing lessons learned from large-scale #SARSCoV2 sequencing   #COGUKScienceShowcase  https://t.co/H4O2NniML8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ STARTING NOW  https://t.co/POHWvuYDgs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CVRinfo:  Don't miss the @CovidGenomicsUK Science Showcase Event!   Today (26 March) at 1 pm.  1.55 - 2.40 pm: @emcat1 will be chairi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MRC_Outbreak: EVENT: don't miss the @CovidGenomicsUK Science Showcase Event  Molecular tests  sequencing Variants distribution  d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EsteeTorok: Its #OneYearOn since the @CovidGenomicsUK began sequencing SARS-CoV-2    Join the anniversary showcase event today at 13:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuadram: Since COVID-19 hit the UK in March, we've been at the forefront of genomic sequencing  sequencing over 18,000 samples.  Ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss our Science Showcase event TODAY at 1pm!    New insights into molecular tests and massive sequencing   #SARSCoV2 variants: distribution, detection and prioritisation   #SARSCoV2 variants: patients and prevention   Register now   https://t.co/H4O2Nn1bmy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MRC_Outbreak: Marking one year of incredible work by @CovidGenomicsUK   Together with 16 academic partners  other stakeholders the tea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofGMVLS:  #OneYearOn, we celebrate the efforts of our #CVRCovidResponse. MVLS is proud to be part of @CovidGenomicsUK   Find out mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cardiffuni: This week marks #OneYearOn from the launch of @CovidGenomicsUK to deliver large scale, rapid sequencing of the genome to ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roslininstitute: One year ago we joined @CovidGenomicsUK - a whole genome sequence alliance to map how the novel coronavirus spreads an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EdinburghUni: To mark @CovidGenomicsUK 1st anniversary we'd like to thank our colleagues @SBSatEd @arambaut  Dr Kate Templetons team]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its #OneYearOn since the COG-UK consortium first began   Today, we look back at key events and milestones the consortium has seen over the last 12 months    Explore our first anniversary timeline    https://t.co/iiaMxY7S52]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @publichealthni: Last year, as part of the response to the pandemic, we joined @CovidGenomicsUK  Sequencing the genomes of viruses isola]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @P_H_S_Official: Public Health Scotland and our COG-UK partners are marking one year of the pandemic response. https://t.co/S3l4z3I476]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NorthumbriaUni: At the beginning of March, Northumbrias Professor @DarrenSmithdx was appointed as one of four new Deputy Directors of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NorthumbriaUni: Northumbria is proud to be a core academic partner of @CovidGenomicsUK, a national effort to map how #COVID19 spreads a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MRC_Outbreak: PUBLICATION @nresearchnews on transmissibility of #SARSCoV2 lineage B.1.1.7 in England.  Read the full paper here https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShefUniNews: One year of @CovidGenomicsUK and thousands of #COVID19 genomes sequenced, our scientists @ShefUni_IICD, @neuroshef and @sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CVRinfo: #OneYearOn meet the scientists involved #CVRCovidResponse @CovidGenomicsUK  Dr Ana da Silva Filipe (@CVR_Genomics) I lead t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CVRinfo: #OneYearOn #CVRCovidResponse is proud to be part of @CovidGenomicsUK   Did you know, COG-UK is made up of over 600 members ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oxmartinschool: 6/7 Dr Moritz Kraemer (@MOUGK) has also been volunteering time towards @CovidGenomicsUK as well as working to develop @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oxmartinschool: 5/7 Other members of the programme like @sabrinalyli, @nmrfaria and @JaneyMessina have been analysing the #pandemic sit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oxmartinschool: 4/7 Researchers @aezarebski  @laduplessis have been part-seconded to @CovidGenomicsUK. Their research has shown how #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oxmartinschool: 3/7 Prof Oliver Pybus (@EvolveDotZoo) is a @CovidGenomicsUK PI for the @UniofOxford. He contributed to the discovery of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oxmartinschool: 1/7 #OneYearOn we are so proud of the hard work that has been done and continues to be by our Pandemic Genomics team. S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss our Science Showcase Event TOMORROW at 1pm   Featuring @catherineludden, @CLongstaff, @templeton_kate, @DrLMJackson, @emcat1, @AineToole, @msinnott123, @alecarabo, @judith_breuer, @_nickdavies, @wendybarclay11  more!    Register now   https://t.co/k1NaoSGSfk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShefUniNews: This week also marks one year of @CovidGenomicsUK   Our scientists have played a key role in the consortium to further our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bdi_oxford: 1 year ago, BDI researchers helped launch @CovidGenomicsUK - a rapid, national effort to generate critical genetic knowle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @unibirmingham: This week marks the one year anniversary of @CovidGenomicsUK and colleagues here at Birmingham have been instrumental in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week, COG-UK turns one   For us, the past year has seen herculean efforts of hundreds of people within the consortium   In this open letter, Prof Sharon Peacock reflects on the past 12 months and thanks all who have contributed to COG-UK   https://t.co/Owf1N3LLtP]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>