<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The EU is the most open market in the world.  But openness rhymes with fairness.  Today we propose to tackle distortive subsidies granted by non- countries, with new enforcement tools.  Our goal: ensure a level playing field in these challenging times and support our recovery.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our updated Industrial Strategy also supports the green  digital transition!  We tailored it to our EU-wide targets for 2030, especially the Climate Law.  And it will help equip our workers and SMEs with the means and skills they need to thrive in the transition.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our Industrial Strategy will boost our recovery.   Today we propose:    A Single Market Emergency Instrument for free movement of goods, services  people  An in-depth analysis of our dependencies  more diverse supply chains  New industrial alliances in strategic areas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La vaccination sacclre en Europe: nous venons de dpasser les 150 millions de vaccinations.  Un quart des Europens ont dj reu leur premire dose.  Nous aurons suffisamment de doses pour vacciner 70% des adultes de lUE en juillet. https://t.co/0ateOt7B9E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Das Impftempo gewinnt in der gesamten EU an Fahrt: Soeben haben wir die Marke von 150 Millionen Impfungen berschritten.  Ein Viertel der Europerinnen und Europer hat schon die erste Dosis erhalten. Im Juli werden genug Dosen da sein, um 70% der Erwachsenen in der EU zu impfen. https://t.co/3XsjRwyfks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination is gaining speed across the EU: we have just passed 150 million vaccinations.  A quarter of all Europeans have had their first dose.  We'll have enough doses for vaccinating 70% of EU adults in July. https://t.co/j5ZdOukSrg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Polands recovery  resilience plan.   It focuses on key areas for  economy: innovation, businesses  labour market reform; green  digital transition; clean transport  stronger health system.   Our goal: to have #NextGenerationEU funds flowing by the summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Otrzymalimy  Krajowy Plan Odbudowy.   Koncentruje si on na kluczowych obszarach dla gospodarki: innowacyjnoci, przedsibiorczoci i reformie rynku pracy; transformacji ekologicznej i cyfrowej; ekologicznym transporcie i wzmocnieniu systemu opieki zdrowotnej #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Freedom of press in the EU is often taken for granted.  It should not.   We have had recent, painful reminders.   On #WorldPressFreedomDay, let us remember that democracy cannot work without free and independent media.   We have to protect journalists at all costs. https://t.co/BElyfnElQA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The EU stands by India, as I told Prime Minister @narendramodi today.   More aid - oxygen cylinders, ventilators, medication - is channelled to  from Czechia, Denmark, Spain, Netherlands and Germany via the Civil Protection Mechanism.   This is global solidarity in action.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to revive  tourism industry  for cross-border friendships to rekindle - safely.  We propose to welcome again vaccinated visitors  those from countries with a good health situation.  But if variants emerge we have to act fast: we propose an EU emergency brake mechanism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is clear momentum to strengthen our strategic relations on trade, digital, climate change  multilateralism.  I'm encouraged by the prospect of intensifying our trade  investment relations.  This would tap into a huge potential to the benefit of our businesses  citizens]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good call with Prime Minister @narendramodi in preparation of the EU-India Summit:  Team Europe stands in deep solidarity with our democratic partner India.   We are providing rapid support and are delivering assistance to fight COVID19. https://t.co/xeQAUCYC68]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On this #WorkersDay I pay tribute to healthcare workers around the world.  You put the safety of others before your own.   You spent endless days and sleepless nights saving lives and caring for our loved ones  We will never thank you enough. https://t.co/LzzvyYhIUZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nous avons reu le plan de relance et de rsilience de la Belgique, avec 6 grandes priorits :   Climat, durabilit et innovation ; numrique ; mobilit ; social et inclusion ; comptitivit; et finances publiques.   #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We hebben het herstel- en veerkrachtplan van Belgi ontvangen, met 6 kernprioriteiten:   Klimaat, duurzaamheid  innovatie; digitaal; mobiliteit; sociaal  inclusiviteit; concurrentievermogen; en overheidsfinancin.   #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wir haben Belgiens Aufbau- und Resilienzplan erhalten.  Die Schlsselprioritten: Klima, Nachhaltigkeit  Innovation; Digitales; Mobilitt; Soziales  Inklusivitt; Wettbewerbsfhigkeit; ffentliche Finanzen.  #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Belgiums recovery and resilience plan, with 6 key priorities:   Climate, sustainability and innovation; digital; mobility; social and inclusiveness; competitiveness; and public finances.    #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prejeli smo slovenski nart za okrevanje in odpornost, ki je usmerjen v prihodnost: zeleni  digitalni prehod; pametna, trajnostna  vkljuujoa rast; zdravje  blaginja vseh.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Slovenias recovery and resilience plan.  It is built for  future: green  digital transition; smart, sustainable and inclusive growth; health and welfare.  #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wir haben heute sterreichs Aufbau- und Resilienzplan erhalten.   Der Plan sieht Reformen  Investitionen in die Bildung und in einen grnen und digitalen Wiederaufbau vor.  Wir streben an, dass die Mittel aus #NextGenerationEU bereits im Sommer flieen knnen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Austrias recovery and resilience plan.  Austrias plan includes reforms and investments for the green and digital recovery, education, skills and innovation.  Our goal: to have everything in place so #NextGenerationEU funds can flow by this summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vi har modtaget Danmarks plan for genopretning.   Den har til forml at gre dansk konomi mere modstandsdygtig, grn og digital.   Vores ml er at have #NextGenerationEU  midler aktiveret allerede til sommer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abbiamo ricevuto il piano nazionale di ripresa e resilienza dellItalia.   Comprende riforme e investimenti per la transizione digitale e verde, innovazione, competitivit, cultura, istruzione, coesione e salute.  #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Italys recovery  resilience plan   It includes reforms and investments for the digital  green transition, innovation, competitiveness, culture, education, cohesion and health.   #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jointly with @EP_President Sassoli and @eucopresident Michel, I condemn in the strongest possible terms Russias unacceptable decision to ban eight  nationals from entering its territory, including @EP_President  @VeraJourova   https://t.co/jcOL3t7Hpd https://t.co/tIu6J0mSTR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nous avons reu le plan de relance du   Le plan  s'articule autour de 3 piliers: la cohsion et l'inclusion sociale, la transition verte, et la numrisation, l'innovation et la gouvernance.   Notre objectif: que les fonds de #NextGenerationEU soient disponibles ds cet t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Luxembourgs recovery and resilience plan.  The  plan is built around the 3 pillars of cohesion and social resilience; green transition; and digitisation, innovation and governance.   Our goal: to have #NextGenerationEU funds flowing as of this summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Spains recovery  resilience plan.  #NextGenerationEU will finance the countrys recovery, with projects linked to the green and digital transition, cohesion and gender equality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hemos recibido el plan de recuperacin de Espaa.    #NextGenerationEU contribuir a financiar la recuperacin del pas a travs de proyectos vinculados a la transicin ecolgica y digital, la cohesin y la igualdad de gnero.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received  recovery  resilience plan   The RRF will finance  recovery along 6 priorities: the green and digital transitions; health care; equality; economic transformation  the rule of law.   Our goal is that #NextGenerationEU funds start flowing already this summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Esam samui  Latvijas ekonomikas atveseoanas plnu.  #RRF finansjums plnam pieirts saska ar 6 priorittm: za un digitl transformcija, veselbas aprpe, vienldzba, ekonomikas prveide un tiesiskums.  Mris #NextGenerationEU ldzekus skt izmantot ovasar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Denmarks recovery  resilience plan.  It aims to make the Danish economy more resilient, green and digital.   Our aim is to have #NextGenerationEU funding flow by the summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spannende Diskussion mit @ABaerbock ber die nchsten Schritte beim #EuropeanGreenDeal den Fortschritt der EU-Impfkampagne und den Neustart in den transatlantischen Beziehungen.   Die groen Herausforderungen unserer Zeit lassen sich nur europisch lsen. https://t.co/uO5uhO3nF9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im grateful that @Europarl_EN  Council agreed privacy-friendly rules allowing companies to continue detecting and reporting child sexual abuse content online.  We will now work on preparing a permanent legal framework. https://t.co/nvj6DgqP2I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good first meeting with @albinkurti   Wish his government success in advancing reforms in Kosovo, including in the rule of law, and normalisation of relations with Serbia.  EU will continue support for Kosovo, including with vaccines to fight the pandemic. https://t.co/nLf70qMQhV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dostali sme od  narodny Plan obnovy a odolnosti.   Je dobre, ze obsahuje klucove priority pre buducnost : zelenu ekonomiku, vzdelavanie, vyskum a vyvoj, zdravotnictvo a e-government.   Ked bude odsuhlaseny,  moze ziskat az 6,3 miliard v ramci progamu #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Slovakias Recovery  Resilience Plan.  Good to see that it includes key priorities for  future: green economy, education, RD, innovation, health  e-government  Once the plan is green-lighted, Slovakia could receive up to 6.3 billion under #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guter Austausch mit @ArminLaschet zu Klima, Pandemie und der Erholung unserer Wirtschaft.  Wir sind uns einig: Europa soll beim Klimaschutz vorangehen.   Das ist gut fr die Umwelt und birgt groe Chancen fr Deutschlands Wirtschaft, die stark istbei sauberen Technologien. https://t.co/I97s86Hiol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India  needs our support and solidarity.  Im very grateful to France, Italy, Austria, Finland and Ireland for sending oxygen, medical equipment such as ventilators and COVID medication under our  Civil Protection Mechanism.  We are in this together.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Frances Recovery  Resilience Plan.  It aims to make the French economy more resilient, green and digital.  After our assessment, France could receive up to 40.9 billion under #NextGenerationEU.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nous avons reu le plan de relance et de rsilience de la France.  Il vise  rendre l'conomie franaise plus robuste, verte et numrique.  Aprs notre valuation, la France pourrait recevoir jusqu' 40,9 milliards d'euros au titre de #NextGenerationEU.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will have the EU gateway up and running by June, while supporting the timely rollout of national systems.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @Europarl_EN adopting its position on a Digital Green Certificate is a key step towards free and safe travel this summer.   Now negotiations with @2021PortugalEU can start.   We will support and facilitate a swift conclusion of these discussions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women against #COVID19!  Happy to meet @CZacharopoulou, co-chair of #COVAX.  Were fully behind #COVAX, which aims to deliver 1.3 billion doses to 92 countries by end of 2021.  With almost 2.5 billion, #TeamEurope is the one of the lead donors to #COVAX. https://t.co/HRdNTCN1bO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[                   , , ,    .            30,5 .   #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Greece's Recovery  Resilience plan.  Good to see that it focusses on strategic areas for the country's future: green  digital, jobs, skills, private investment and reform.   After assessment  could receive up to 30.5 billion under #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wir haben heute den deutschen Aufbauplan erhalten.  Wir freuen uns, dass er unsere gemeinsamen Prioritten unterstreicht- vom Klimaschutz bis zur Digitalisierung.  Unser Ziel ist es, dass Europa im Sommer mit den Investitionen starten kann.   #NextGenerationEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have received Germanys Recovery  Resilience plan under #NextGenerationEU   Glad that it includes reforms  investments linked to EU-wide priorities: climate action, a stronger health system, digital.   We will now assess it. Our goal: to have everything ready by the summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays #COVID19 response meeting focused on:    Epidemiological situation in   State of play of vaccinations and vaccine deliveries in the EU  Coordinated approach to travel restrictions  The alarming situation in India and #TeamEurope support https://t.co/mbS5BRv7bi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I warmly welcome the @Europarl_EN vote in favour of the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement.  The TCA marks the foundation of a strong and close partnership with the UK. Faithful implementation is essential. https://t.co/aTU7cOB5Ck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[C'est une phase cruciale pour la relance.  Les pays de l'UE finalisent leurs plans de relance pour dbloquer 750 milliards  sous #NextGenerationEU.  Nous travaillons avec eux pour que ces plans rendent l'Europe prte pour l'avenir.   C'est l'occasion du sicle pour l'Europe. https://t.co/cdCfVuyffm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unsere Erholung ist in der entscheidenden Phase.  Die EU-Staaten finalisieren ihre Wiederaufbauplne; via #NextGenerationEU stehen 750 Mrd. bereit.   Wir arbeiten gemeinsam, damit die Plne Europa zukunftsfit machen.  Dies ist die Gelegenheit des Jahrhunderts fr Europa. https://t.co/fzygdfFTtJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have entered a crucial phase for our recovery.  EU countries are finalising their recovery plans to unlock 750 billion under #NextGenerationEU  We work closely with them to ensure these plans make Europe fit for the future. This is the opportunity of the century for Europe. https://t.co/dNlgms5msQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The EU stands with India.  A first shipment of urgently needed oxygen, medicine and equipment will be delivered over the coming days under the EU Civil Protection Mechanism.  I want to thank      for their solidarity.   expected soon. https://t.co/CN0niOY5Lz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glad to meet @eduardheger.  The EU stands with Slovakia in the fight against #COVID19 and support on vaccines.   We discussed  draft recovery plan - I welcomed its focus on reforms - and the countrys digital and green transition. https://t.co/ruXqumxcw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We know it will not always be easy and there is a lot of vigilance, diligence and hard work ahead.  But while todays vote is obviously an end  it is also the beginning of a new chapter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And it will focus minds on finding pragmatic solutions where they are needed  most urgently around the Protocol on Ireland/Northern Ireland.  The next step is to mutually agree on compliance paths, with concrete deadlines and milestones.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This agreement protects the rights of our citizens and the integrity of the Single Market.  It will give us the tools we need to ensure full and faithful compliance with the obligations, which both sides signed up to.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today @Europarl_EN is voting on the Trade and Cooperation Agreement with the UK.  It represents the unity, responsibility and solidarity within the EU to protect the interests of our citizens and our Union.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Outre lgalit homme-femme, la dsescalade en Mditerrane orientale doit se poursuivre.  La Turquie doit accepter les arrts de la CEDH.  Ce sont nos conditions pour renforcer notre coopration sur lconomie et la migration avec la Turquie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Als Spitzenpolitikerin kann ich jederzeit das Wort ergreifen und mir Gehr verschaffen. Aber was ist mit den Millionen von Frauen, die das nicht knnen? Frauen, die jeden Tag berall auf unserem Planeten gekrnkt werden, aber sich nicht wehren knnen. Fr sie mssen wir aufstehen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bei meinem Besuch im Pfizer-Werk in Puurs durfte ich zuletzt zlem Treci treffen, Mitbegrnderin BioNTech und eine sehr starke Frau.  Dank Persnlichkeiten wie ihr legt unsere Impfkampagne Tag fr Tag an Tempo zu.  Bis heute wurden in der EU 129 Millionen Impfdosen verabreicht.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We'll table legislation to prevent and combat violence against women and children, online and offline.  Because we have to make sure that women and girls are adequately protected in Europe.  As US @VP Kamala Harris said at the UN: the status of women is the status of democracy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Ankara I reiterated my deep concerns about Turkey withdrawing from the Istanbul Convention. This is a terrible signal.   Yet to be credible we also have to act at home. Several EU countries have still not ratified it. Some are thinking of quitting.   This is not acceptable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My visit to Turkey showed how far we still have to go before women are treated as equals. Always. Everywhere.  My story made headlines. But there are so many stories of women, most of them far more serious, that go unobserved.   We have to make sure these stories are also told!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccination has helped us beat many diseases.   It can be the lasting way out of the #COVID19 pandemic.   Today, at the start of European Immunization Week, we reached 129 million vaccinations in EU.   We'll have enough doses to have 70% of adults vaccinated in July. https://t.co/4pWxhJIWJF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glad to meet @predsednikrs. We discussed:   Fight against #COVID19  Economic recovery  Accession process where we need to continue to see positive developments in Rule of Law  Belgrade-Pristina dialogue  Belgrade-North Macedonia railway  which we are ready to support https://t.co/Hi4i6Mol9V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alarmed by the epidemiological situation in India. We are ready to support.  The EU is pooling resources to respond rapidly to Indias request for assistance via the EU Civil Protection Mechanism.   We stand in full solidarity with the Indian people! https://t.co/Pv8ezFPdS3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @selenagomez!   Europe  is committed to bringing the world together to end this pandemic - and prevent future ones!   We want to make the world stronger and more prepared to deal with health crises.  For this we count on global cooperation and solidarity! #VaxLive https://t.co/HR5hMZU1LV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The story of #COVID19 vaccines is that of groundbreaking science.  Pioneering spirit. And a miracle of manufacturing.  Our vaccination campaign is gaining speed.   I am confident we will have enough doses to have 70% of adults in the EU vaccinated in July. https://t.co/8a4aMeFgQX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important to exchange with President @sandumaiamd on the political situation in Moldova.  I expressed full support to her efforts for reform and for ensuring respect for the rule of law.   Solutions to political differences must be found within the framework of  constitution.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good meeting with  Prime Minister Viktor Orbn tonight.   We discussed various issues including:  COVID situation   Economic recovery efforts  national recovery plan  Implementation of the #EUGreenDeal   RoL Report   Global Affairs  Western Balkans https://t.co/c3mm4pKjAc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Together with @eucopresident Michel, I will be happy to greet US @POTUS Biden in Brussels for the EU-US summit on his next trip to Europe in June 2021.  We have much to do together, from climate change to health, from trade and multilateralism to geopolitical challenges.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A year ago, the world came together and created the @ACTAccelerator.  To fight a virus that knows no border.   We need the @ACTAccelerator perhaps even more now, as the pandemic is not over. And it needs funding.   I invite all governments and the private sector to step up. https://t.co/PAFrMbJRDJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liebe zlem Treci, danke fr Ihre groen Leistungen!  Sie haben den ersten Impfstoff gegen #COVID19 entwickelt, der in der EU zugelassen wurde.  Ein wissenschaftlicher Durchbruch, eine Revolution in der Medizin.  Die Welt kann glcklich sein, Sie zu haben! https://t.co/tgEv68oogS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dank aan de medewerkers van de @Pfizer site in Puurs voor hun fantastische werk, de klok rond.  Zij spelen een belangrijke rol bij het bereiken van ons doel om in juli 70% van de volwassenen in  te vaccineren.  Ook dank aan @Alexanderdecroo en aan Belgi , vaccingrootmacht! https://t.co/bVPfBLPDqa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This site is also a symbol for the  fairness  openness.  Europe is producing vaccines for Europeans  the world.  We have exported 155 million doses to 87 countries since December.  We take pride in this and invite others to join us. Well only be safe when everyone is safe. https://t.co/1V4F5M02a3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 1 year, the Puurs siteis producing1 billion doses.  @EMA_News just approved the increase of this sites production capacity by a further 20%.  This will make it one of the biggest vaccine fill and finish sites in Europe. https://t.co/1zuTgdUkIX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Puurs site was the first to produce mRNA vaccines at large scale in   Now we are leading worldwide on this technology.  We are negotiating a new contract to secure 1.8 billion doses for 2021-23.  For booster shots and protection against variants. https://t.co/ZV69H2bsmO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ravie de visiter le site de @Pfizer  Puurs.  Grce  des partenaires solides et fiables comme @Pfizer et @BioNTech_Group, la vaccination s'acclre en Europe.  Je suis convaincue que nous aurons dj suffisamment de doses pour vacciner 70% des adultes de l'UE en juillet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ich bin froh, heute den @Pfizer Standort in Purrs zu besuchen.  Die Impfungen in der EU schreiten dank verlsslichen Partnern wie @Pfizer  @BioNTech_Group zgig voran.  So knnen wir bereits bis zum Juli 70 Prozent aller Erwachsenen ein Impfangebot machen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glad to visit @Pfizer's Puurs site.  Thanks to strong, reliable partners like @Pfizer and @BioNTech_Group, vaccination in the EU is speeding up.   I'm confident we will have enough doses to vaccinate 70% of all EU adults already in July. https://t.co/m5sLiQwSo0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is so good to have the US back on our side in the fight against climate change!  Together we can get faster to a climate-neutral, prosperous and equitable future.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @POTUS @JoeBiden for convening the #LeadersClimateSummit   Europe will be the 1st climate neutral continent. But it does not want to be the only one.  Let's all commit to ambitious emission reductions by 2030, on the way to net-zero by 2050.   https://t.co/xi1gk6icfv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #NewEuropeanBauhaus is about hope and new perspectives.  It aims to reach peoples hearts and souls.  So the necessary transition towards a climate-neutral Europe becomes a true cultural movement.  Tune in to the #NewEuropeanBauhaus conference!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our goal: to cut greenhouse gas emissions by 55% by 2030.  In June, we will revamp our energy  climate policies to make them #Fitfor55.  To get there, we had a good 1st College debate today. And I will be glad to present our  climate goals at the #LeadersClimateSummit later. https://t.co/MK8rUBIbHA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[O nosso objetivo: ter tudo pronto este vero.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ acaba de apresentar o seu plano de recuperao e resilincia.   Sado este importante marco na implementao do #NextGenerationEU para que a  saia mais forte da crise.   Continuaremos a ajudar os Estados-Membros a apresentar planos de alta qualidade.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ just submitted its recovery and resilience plan.  I welcome this important milestone in delivering #NextGenerationEU for the  to emerge stronger from the crisis.  We will continue to help Member States deliver high quality plans. Our aim: have everything ready this summer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New EU taxonomy criteria will define activities that best contribute to fighting climate change and to guiding the massive investments needed.   Other measures will ensure companies provide reliable information on sustainability.   The EU leads the way on sustainable finance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #EUGreenDeal is our growth strategy. Climate neutrality, our horizon.   To reach our climate goals, we need businesses fully on board.  Today the College agreed on measures to help companies shift further towards more sustainable business models.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today we also present a Coordinated Plan, to outline the reforms and investments we need to secure our position as a leader in #AI, worldwide.  With almost 150 billion for digital investments - 20% of its budget - #NextGenerationEU will help reinforce the  excellence in AI.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is a fantastic opportunity for Europe.  And citizens deserve technologies they can trust.  Today we present new rules for trustworthy AI. They set high standards based on the different levels of risk. https://t.co/EuzaIUBW9i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I welcome todays decision by the German Constitutional Court.   The EU stays on track with its economic recovery, following this unprecedented pandemic.   #NextGenerationEU will pave the way for a green, digital and more resilient European Union.  #StrongerTogether]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I warmly welcome the agreement on the Climate Law.  Our political commitment to becoming the 1st climate neutral continent by 2050 is now also a legal one.  The Climate Law sets the EU on a green path for a generation. It is our binding pledge to our children and grandchildren.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mes plus sincres condolances  la famille du Prsident Idriss Dby et au peuple tchadien.  Le Tchad est un alli dans la lutte contre le terrorisme au Sahel.  LUE restera  ses cts dans cette priode difficile.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I welcome @EMA_News announcement on the safety of the Johnson  Johnson vaccine.   This is good news for the roll-out of vaccination campaigns across the EU. https://t.co/WenukxE8GR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The latest meeting of the Recovery and Resilience Facility Steering Board assessed the status of draft recovery plans.   The presentation of high quality plans, focused on achieving green and digital goals, is essential to allow #NextGenerationEU funds to start flowing quickly. https://t.co/8cjYsIuTaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today we invited experts  organisations to reflect on global cooperation, public health capacities and health security preparedness  response.  Their findings will feed into the preparation of the #GlobalHealthSummit on 21/05.  For a  better prepared against future pandemics. https://t.co/VbaO7ArqhP]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>