<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@steamboateldaw @LegendaryEnergy And you were right to do so. He was awful 15 years ago, as was Ann Coulter. Not Bill O'Reilly-bad, but pretty bad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 Rather, it means that he has a sense of humor. Unlike people who put pronouns in their bio.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paulg: The US, Canada, and all of Europe combined account for .87% of plastic emissions. The Philippines accounts for 36%. https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aic_drawings: Style of William Turner, Farmyard with Haystack and Pigs, 1800 https://t.co/QEGflzlRzy #artinstituteofchicago #museumarch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ableeyes3 @wimpdaddy @SammiSueWinters Sure thing, dude.  https://t.co/YwMbeBRW0n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit Did you see their recent woke video?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy OMG, OMG, Donald Trump just lit the Internet on Fire! Best POTUS ever amirite?????   (and yes, I'm so sick of it too. Keep up the good work, An0maly.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @philthatremains: Never turn in your guns. https://t.co/lft1Hk87p8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AccidentLiberty Those mountains were so beautiful before they put up all those stupid statues, here is Mt Rushmore before. Stop destroying stunning natural spaces for this garbage. https://t.co/vYuIp9OvIV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ggreenwald: Liberals and parts of the cultural left refuse to admit they have power -- they always insist it's the right who wields it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: People are realizing they lost a year of kindergarten, middle school, Freshman year, hyacinths, flirting, smiling, kissing,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Wakcedout @PaineReading @muzeiar @DrumChronicles It wasn't a standoff in the beginning, the police made it one. The proper thing to have done would be to tail the criminals from a distance and not confront them until there is an area where there are few or no innocent bystanders.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit IMHO, Trump's impact was grossly negative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RothchildChris @JackPosobiec Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PanzerkampfPyro I miss the early days of 8chan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_spookman @Peoples_Pundit @whois_John_Galt &gt;far left  I would say it's mostly a liberal/neoconservative belief. Most people on the left sans a few politicians like Bernie Sanders don't believe Russiagate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peoples_Pundit Btw, I just noticed how different the two questions are. The first one is so obviously true, the second one is much harder to call, so it's an even bigger shift.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peoples_Pundit I wonder how many remember that John Kerry was probably robbed in the 2004 election. Kerry didn't fight back at all, and seems to have done very well for himself.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull &gt;living vicariously through the victories of your little league team  Poor guy, I hope things work out for him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gone_too_far__ If they don't throw around terms like misogynist....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngryMomUSA You'll notice that a large and vocal segment of the population can't be bothered to remember hardly anything. They have to just go along with the narrative of the moment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WalkerMarcus: This is dystopian. https://t.co/CDkxRv8Re0 https://t.co/Y12hL8N2fG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aTeXan575 They can do somersaults now?? Okay, this is going to be a problem....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is no end goal other than abuse. Their online behavior is that of narcissists and psychopaths. https://t.co/4PszrOp2hJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy No, never. And I agree pretty much with every one of your criticisms of Trump. We would have been better off with Hillary.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EbrahimRaeid Liberals talk down to everyone while pretending they are the most empathetic people on the planet. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jleophodl @wrathofgnon The use of tax money is really a separate issue  debate. This advice also applies to private developers of low-income housing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaBugle In 1965, political dynamics were very different, and immigration was not a partisan issue. Republicans were almost certainly following their corporate supporters.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anarcho_Toad PSA: Liking transmen is gay, liking transwomen is not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @geol_uk: Russia is now breaking the Syria siege. Illegal US and EU sanctions are broken. https://t.co/AKuXLiyYYx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IAmN0tPaulAvery @NickJFuentes Okay, conservative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickJFuentes: I am willing to work with anyone who opposes the American regime. My placement on the no-fly list puts everything in pers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelmalice &gt;it encourages people to vaccinate  I just spotted something wrong.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog &gt;men and women can't be friends  Among other issues, this seems like a proposition from before the obesity crisis. Like, say, the 1970s.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Surabees Thank you. I was looking for some risque thing that he said, and couldn't imagine it was something that is so non-controversial. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit I guess it's hard to make Covid True Believers seem cool in any way. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VictoryIllinois @SwainForSenate I agree, but this is to stop it being a mandated part of public schools.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraHelena39 @CamelotGoldfish @CassandraRules Shouldn't be an issue unless it's particularly damning.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules Sorry, have to disagree. We need full transparency in all cases. Riots won't stop until whites in particular quit acting like doormats and stand up for themselves.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nealjclark1 @BonsoirAnna I don't think that's a good criterion, tbh. Art Nouveau is a  novel style, but it is based on traditional aesthetic values and forms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @disclosetv: JUST IN - Vaccine passports are officially outlawed in Florida now, the bill passed 76-40.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cheese12987 But there's no money in Ivermectin. You don't want these poor pharmaceutical companies to have a down quarter, do you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MintChipMusic That's not fair! To get real numbers, they'd have to do real journalism and not just read off press releases. You can't expect the NYT to make that kind of effort.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PomeloScooter @IllinoisOpen @MartyMakary The elderly are much more vulnerable to Covid-19 and coronaviruses in general relative to influenza viruses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zwergie1 @TheBabylonBee Wow, can't wait to hear all the people whining about their rights because it's too much work for them to wear a seat belt outside. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IllinoisOpen @PomeloScooter @MartyMakary Exactly. For the young, it's safer than the flu, and for those at mid-life, fairly similar. For the elderly in poor health, yes, it is scary, but they can take targeted, voluntary precautions on their own.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Assisted_Karma @iamungit There are some parallels with Kent State, as at the time most of the country shrugged it off  blamed the students, but it had a galvanizing effect on the American left and is one of best remembered events of that era.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit https://t.co/FoDBiq15l0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Assisted_Karma @iamungit I don't think it's fully dawned on most Americans the injustice that was perpetrated on Ashli Babbitt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Assisted_Karma: @iamungit most noteworthy, was the precedent set by Congress 'criminalizing' Americans invited by the sitting President]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rafael_MLDZ @jasontgist @JackPosobiec All you have to do in loss prevention for a case like this is inform that they are caught, they run the risk of a criminal record and so forth. Tell them that you're happy to give them a break if they promise not to do it again. Let them go, and all is well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IanMDesigns @JackPosobiec Decades of little accountability.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Kodos_ @iHeartSteroids @ggreenwald @Alyssa_Milano A lot of those people are stuck in the 00's when Fox was a sick mouthpiece for war and the Bush administration. Today, O'Reilly has been gone for years, and Tucker alone has more genuine dissident leftists on his show than the other news channels combined.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CTPatriot2006 @ggreenwald @rosemcgowan And the interview wasn't just a case of "let's get someone on to trash the libs." The interviewer genuinely admired Rose, and was effusive in her praise.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ggreenwald: It's very hard to choose one's favorite Rose McGowan moment, but if you force me to, I would likely select this masterpiece]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@luddofisherman Great video on guard dogs, btw. It typically makes sense for commercial farmers to have multiple breeds.  https://t.co/yXpjsbHpEg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@luddofisherman There is a really simple  easy answer for farmers in wolf-territory: dogs. Guard dogs have been bred for thousands of years to protect flocks. Numerous breeds for different situations.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JosephFordCotto Mildly. There is a marked shift among whites towards a group identity over the past several years, but this won't be relevant to politicians who don't help them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Awesome news! Let's keep the downward momentum going.... https://t.co/z9dizoxAp7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NabeelAzeezDXB: The Kardashianization of women is a problem.  So many have the exact same look.  And lost the features that make them u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CassyWearsHeels I know Florida has done the same, not sure what other states.  https://t.co/6N45JocQxb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CassyWearsHeels: BREAKING: The Idaho state House has passed a bill banning critical race theory indoctrination in the state's public sc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OhComfy In national politics, I'd say Thomas Massie. In regional politics, probably Ron Desantis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@doni_hypocrisy I would support giving them a copy of "Winners Aren't Losers" when they are bused back to the border and dropped off in Mexico.  https://t.co/uZSeRQ3g8b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JewcockLover @acurrie254 Exact quote. Nothing there that Islamists were specifically recruited for genocide. Try again.  &gt;1.5M Armenians were killed over 100 years ago by the Islamist Ottoman Empire.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skye_daddy Why, because she doesn't support BDS? Many critics of Israel do not. She supported 1A protections for BDS, and that is what matters.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JewcockLover @acurrie254 You're spinning in circles. That's like saying the Bush administration invaded Iraq, and the United States government and military had nothing to do with it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JewcockLover @acurrie254 Sure, but the discussion hinges on Tulsi's tweet. She never said the Young Turks either, she was referring to the Ottoman Empire.   https://t.co/MEqzVSU5ZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HollyBriden Ted Lieu is not the brightest....  https://t.co/mofwkqTgl5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarcasmStardust It has lost 44k likes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JewcockLover @acurrie254 If religion is so wound up in their identity that they are forcing conversions, that's not a secular society.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worth reading. A reminder that, like many other terms  in politics  religion, there is no strict definition of Islamism. Forced conversions would definitely qualify as a harsh fundamentalism by modern standards. https://t.co/dnVTtlDJiZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SDonziger: BREAKING: Judge Preska just terminated all virtual access to my trial scheduled for May 10th.   Chevron's plan is to finis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Vonnie932 @EdTruman3 Nothing to do with this case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoganOtaku @JurassicOtaku @drrollergator Yeah, my guess is TERFs as well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit No information as to how they contacted the church. While antifa doing this wouldn't surprise me, you have to  give a more solid account.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thevivafrei @elonmusk @nbcsnl @SpaceX They actually were genuinely funny decades ago.  https://t.co/E2MW18NSJY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeanMcCarthyCom And women slaved over hot stoves in the kitchen while guys got to have fun on these huge outdoor monkey bars. https://t.co/IgD9qXX4cU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@flippantflaneur Most people haven't heard of Clausewitz.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Esque_FL @trailduster6bt Sure, but I wish we had several more years. A lot was accomplished between 2010-2015.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Esque_FL @trailduster6bt I would much rather have flown under the radar for several more years at least. Bottom up instead of top down.  Does anyone else remember how good Youtube was prior to 2018?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Esque_FL @trailduster6bt They went hysterical over the idea, not the reality. That was worse than him doing nothing to stir things up. So much was happening below the surface before Trump, now it's much harder  so many voices have been silenced.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Esque_FL @trailduster6bt Outstanding article by Ann Coulter on Trump that sums up my point.  https://t.co/K6bapGVGjb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Esque_FL @trailduster6bt There was very little in the way of material challenges, Trump had no spine to follow through on anything where there was any resistance. He blustered, liberals went hysterical, and changed the internet to something semi-open.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheConservatar7: WTF is this?  This nonsense is getting way out of hand... https://t.co/DAhCOZ6YM9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BidenLs @pdabrosca With all respect, friend, you should have been done with him a long, long time ago.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@trailduster6bt People quickly forget how much less censorship there was prior to Trump's election. He made things worse in so many respects.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wrathofgnon @Gronold3 While I love roses, I tend to associate them with the UK. I think something like the daisy/sunflower family which thrive in the USA would have been a nice choice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit I'd say income taxes are much worse than capital gains. Low capital gains relative to income tax bolster the inequalities of financialism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@willpock @george_jazzcat @MarkChangizi You beat me to it! They would give him a whole face mask if they could. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanUhl: conveniently leaving out who killed him https://t.co/OvmNCkKCb7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @lhfang And this is true on every level. Poor and working-class pleasures like eating a chicken sandwich are destroying the planet, not the Pentagon and its endless wars.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit @joe_shipman I mean, how ideologically oriented are Facebook  Twitter that they can continue to destroy their businesses? We had several decades of an open internet, so closing that down entirely seems unlikely.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit @joe_shipman I also said losing all social sway. Meaning that what CNN says is truth means less than many other figures. That is true now, and will continue. The only thing they can do to stop it is censorship, and I think they are already having troubles escalating that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit @joe_shipman And even if these were more normal times, the pendulum in the 2020s is almost certainly going towards conservatism (generally 10-20 year cycles). The MSM are way over-extended on wokeness. Even putting aside Covid lockdowns, election, and so much more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit @joe_shipman Sure, they might be able to stay afloat from investors or different games like airports paying them, but we're in the midst of a long-term crisis in belief, to where Jimmy Dore already imho already has more cultural impact than Brian Stelter. That gap will continue to widen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joe_shipman @iamungit I doubt that dynamic will last past the decade. There is not a lot of stability or trust in this system, and media will be one of the first institutions to fall.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katewand: Do not be fooled: Covid has been used as the catalyst to usher in the Green Reich.  Climate change was a tough sell, still to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamungit In fairness, I think he was asking when will CNN, MSNBC, ABC, etc go bankrupt/lose all social sway, which is a fair question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HAv2RtrnVdeoTps: ShOoTiNg A kNiFe OuT oF SoMeOnEs HaNdS iSnT tOo HaRd. https://t.co/G04znCMmwR https://t.co/VLTtTK7kH2]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>