<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cryptogally @goddeketal @federalepolitie They've always existed,  now they're allowed to act out their sick violent tendencies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goddeketal @federalepolitie If there really was a dangerous virus, why pile on?? Why actually INCREASE contact?? All the police assaults (hmm I mean lawful arrests) would increase transmission, right?? https://t.co/OyHnEoHD7i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GillianMcKeith If there really was a dangerous virus, why pile on?? Why actually INCREASE contact?? All the police assaults (hmm I mean lawful arrests) would increase transmission, right?? https://t.co/Hl0ZanH0gR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 Even if it wasn't experimental,  even if it would be 100% safe, still dont want it.  Why have chemicals in your body you dont need against a 'virus' that isn't dangerous?? Its the hard sell that worries me the most, the propaganda,  the coercion..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HassanM91 @garethicke Another slur we have to deal with is "covid denier". I believe it exists but is not dangerous at all. I would TOTALLY shake hands with a 'covid patient'. Wash their hair, fluff their pillow,  give em a hug. No more dangerous than a cold]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsPollss Anyone who supports this, is guilty of child abuse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke Just a thought.  Sometimes the cultists spout cr*p such as "go work in a covid ward then" (without PPE). Thing is, maybe we should do exactly that, prove to the world its all a lie? No PPE, no tests, just helping poorly people and debunking the biggest lie of the 21st century??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke Never wear a mask, no vaccine,  not burning my skin with chemicals.. smiling and hugging it up. Feel fine, everyone I know feels fine. Most dont follow this scamdemic BS either. How lucky are WE not to catch 'it' during this terrible pandemic??? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FlaBandit @GovRonDeSantis Had 'covid' 3 x, never felt a thing. Am clinically vulnerable as well.  So either 'covid' is extremely mild or the test results were wrong 3 times in a row?? Never wear a mask or social distance either.  Im fine, everyone ive spoken to, touched/hugged is fine. Please wake up!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theboyjai @Demo2020cracy 'beg' is an understatement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 Yes, they're all wearing masks to protect others (her)  right?? NOBODY wears these face nappies to protect another.  Only to suit their own hypochondria. This poor woman]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic Disgusted with being married to a genocidal psychopath??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 At what point are they ready for shearing??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 Can't find it as he only wears it for the cameras]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice Always thought Brexit was a good idea in principle.  Who in their right mind is okay with strangers far away making decisions for you?? But Brexit or no Brexit,  you still have your life controlled by facists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesDelingpole Yes, its the hypocrisy that riles me. Always the same with these snakes, "do as I say' not as I do".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MckenzieJeffe17 @CharlotteCluca1 @BreesAnna Another disturbing trend is that sensible and insightful people are labelled anti vaxxers. Nothing is further from the truth.  Had plenty of vaccinations as a child,  mine had them, even the dog. Even if the vaccine wasn't experimental, why have drugs in your body you don't need?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MJackshiite Sleepy Joe gets lost in the night on the way to the bathroom,  goes in the garden??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MckenzieJeffe17 @CharlotteCluca1 @BreesAnna The real sad thing is that there are many people who have lost loved ones to this poison. Normal happy people being brainwashed on a daily basis believing we can 'get back to normal' by risking their life because government says its 'safe'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlotteCluca1 @BreesAnna Yes dying from an experimental unnecessary 'vaccine' will absolutely make sure you never get this 'awful virus'. 5 people close to me have died from this poison, they were brainwashed into believing this vaxx was the way out.  They're 'out' alrite ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DickPower369 Trust me, it'll fit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@insurgent2047 Yes, sometimes I'm grateful my dad never got to see this insanity that is the world today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI Any excuse to backtrack on the 'roadmap'!! Come on, hands up, who is surprised at this??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFreds https://t.co/Z1gad9mcdx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamHMUFC @Demo2020cracy Hero? Absolutely!! Out of a job?? Very likely ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BareReality Oddly enough this video keeps being taken down https://t.co/vNBxE2KQQ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhackyRacesPP @GillianMcKeith @BorisJohnson Was it Capone that eventually got done for tax fraud while for years getting away with actual murder? I get your point]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jumpforjoyless @CarolineCoramUK It reminds me of something a colleague used to say.. "well, that's another thing that has been improved beyond repair".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic No clue what you sound like... Im a 90's rock chick so your music probably not my cup of tea.  I follow you because you are a rare sane and kind voice  in an ocean of lunatics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic My daughter wears one going into shops. She knows its all BS but is scared of 'getting into trouble' if she doesn't.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice And another 'conspiracy theory' has come true...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nick_the_geek78 The same nasty weasels that call us freedom fighters 'selfish'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZoePrecious2020 Covid marshals.. nasty little weasels that enjoy bullying innocent people.  Hope they will get their just desserts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Catchthewind7 @CarolineCoramUK Sci Fi movies, conspiracy theories.. they affect each other.  But there have been many Sci Fi movies which are now uncomfortably close to reality.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @pcrclaims They feel it harms their case actually. They're not stupid and wouldn't reject it if offered.  But they feel demanding compensation 'cheapens' their claim.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dsbahia1 Hi, hope you know i was being sarcastic,  right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tedtalksoph @JamesMelville Yeah, the whole 'selfish' slur is sooo over used and absolutely incorrect.  Expecting the world to stop turning to suit one's hypochondria IS selfish though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dsbahia1 Oh, didn't you know that all those 'overworked NHS staff' deserve to spend 5 min () to enjoy themselves while patients are 'dying' and have no idea when they'll see their family again or ever?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Idonotconsent6 @GillianMcKeith "Oh these selfish anti vaxxers and covid deniers.  With their illegal super spreader mass gathering.  Idiots as we're nearly out of lockdown. They're gonna cause another lockdown". (SARCASM)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DazeJohnby @davidkurten @metpoliceuk Better be one step ahead of the spelling police.... 'skulls']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DazeJohnby @davidkurten @metpoliceuk Yes, thats what happened... Poor thing, only got to swing her baton a few times.  Hardly cracked any sculls at all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lyndonx Unfortunately many of us are very stupid indeed. Like lemmings off a cliff.. After a year of trying to educate these idiots I say let them jump.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @pcrclaims Dont think they want money, just the truth. Her husband has done a U turn again. At first he really believed it was covid but the last 6 months has opened his eyes.  He finally understands its all a scam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidkurten @metpoliceuk This is what really happened last Saturday.  Police was lying as usual https://t.co/jmN49V0mUe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thereds8 https://t.co/vNBxE2KQQ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IzzieMac1 @CarolineCoramUK Yep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Allycon3 Since December i have lost 5 clients,  2 of them under 60. All died within 2 weeks of the vaxx. Why do so many people blindly believe 1000's have died from covid but completely reject ANY deaths from the vaxx??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sapiofoxxxxxxxy P.s. I found this article very helpful https://t.co/G4QFegoCW2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sapiofoxxxxxxxy If being a intelligent,  responsible and honest person was easy..there would be more of us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeanWal33531685 @SusanMichie I seem to get the most grief from the blue hearts cult. Praying to the golden calf that is the NHS but have very little concern for others. Had my first block today, they preach but dont listen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mrsme17750698 @nurseannhughes @DailyMailUK My friend's sister died in childbirth,  heart failure and blood loss. Still put down as covid.  Many many more cases like this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK There's been plenty of bodies already  BECAUSE of lockdown, let people live again !!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanRallyOh Just been watching Friends.  Not much else can cheer me up after duelling with covid worshippers today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @pcrclaims The post mortem wasnt 'granted' because of covid rules. She was cremated against the family's wishes because of covid rules. So paid a solicitor to have that doctor prosecuted.  F*cking disgusting after what that family has been through already.  A baby that never knew his mother]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @pcrclaims Im not saying nobody died from covid. Im just saying that there are many more cases like this. The government is only just admitting what most of us have known for a very long time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrclaims My friend's sister died in childbirth last September.  Heart failure and blood loss. Put down as covid. Her family had to hire a solicitor to get it overturned by insisting on a post mortem. Millions of people have died and been fraudulently put down as covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrclaims @BigLebowski2018 Its so that 'covid death' cannot be contested]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xoxsteviexox1 @clare_eliza @MissBethanEJohn You wont be missef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xoxsteviexox1 @MissBethanEJohn Yes, i see you are a truly caring person. I bet you're real proud of yourself too??? Real nasty.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xoxsteviexox1 @MissBethanEJohn Im not the one perpetuating a lie that has half the population living in fear. Also im not that weak that i need validation from strangers on twitter to give my life meaning. NHS neglect last year is unforgivable.  And I do not think car accidents are contagious,  nice try though]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xoxsteviexox1 @MissBethanEJohn Work for 2 charities looking after the elderly. Help out at lunch groups, support groups, am a committee member for local charity,  again working for the elderly. Trying to fix damage done by 'scamdemic'.  Happy now?? What do YOU do apart from being abusive to key workers??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Eljay2602 Have been reporting these adverts as harmful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0067Joolz @RealCarlVernon https://t.co/HneitOjAs6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealCarlVernon Lemme guess... its the fault of those selfish anti vaxxers and covid deniers holding illegal super spreader gatherings??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson @BigLebowski2018 Two different taxi drivers have told me that funeral homes blackmail the muslim community into agreeing 'covid death' so they can have the body returned for a burial (within 24 hours).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abi_carey @MissBethanEJohn @DrNeenaJha @BreesAnna Im sorry you believe that. There is absolutely no proof that covid even exists,  let alone people being sick from it. If I had enough characters there is so much information to share. Cancer has killed more, car accidents have killed more, heart disease has killed more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PostAds2020 @Matsukaze1310 @DrNeenaJha AND asthma,  hay-fever,  chest infections,  colds, pneumonia.. Hoorah, all cured because of covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abi_carey @MissBethanEJohn @DrNeenaJha @BreesAnna Sorry to hear that. Due to a car accident I am now clinically vulnerable.  30 yrs of training and experience down the toilet. Had pneumonia twice, likely to get it again. But would not expect countless people to put their lives on hold for me. Because THAT would be selfish.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @defensesxdown No idea, blowing her own trumpet, "worked through the pandemic risking her life". One of them... So yeah, probably works in the canteen or something.  These kind of people are so ignorant,  its just not funny anymore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @defensesxdown Currently trying to have a conversation with a 'NHS worker'. Nasty cow she is, think they're god or something]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissBethanEJohn ?? Making shit up again are you? So sad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissBethanEJohn Same to you, working for the NHS doesn't make you a saint, it makes you complicit in the scamdemic. If you work to protect the elderly, work in a supermarket or as a delivery person, THEN you deserve respect.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissBethanEJohn Worked through the 'pandemic' have you? Was it nice to sit on your backside for a year and still get paid??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @defensesxdown During the summer its fine, can be refreshing.  But i remember an advert by the NHS (who else? ) recommending elderly people to open their windows in winter. It seems every trick is used TO make people ill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @defensesxdown So i can wash my hands outside, catch a cold and call it covid?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissBethanEJohn @DrNeenaJha @BreesAnna Its a cold, calm down yourself and hide behind your sofa and leave life to normal people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville I hate the mask fetishists, immune system deniers and selfish germaphobes who have no respect for the poor souls that have died from NHS neglect over the last year. Debts, suicides, emotional turmoil. Praying to the NHS golden calf. Thanks to the vaxx, yur gonna need them now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @elsadog_: @Dr_Drekkle Its here: the woman in purple, naked child and yellow taxi...  https://t.co/QaILl2kD56]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dr_Drekkle:  The psychopaths are desperate AND THE ACTING IS FUCKING AWFUL!  https://t.co/DIwv9nO2ah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dr_Drekkle @ZoePrecious2020 Reminds me of those scams they run in certain countries where somebody deliberately runs into a parked/stationery vehicle and claim they've been hit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChibaMadelaine @KJPoulton @JamesMelville Had pneumonia twice, developed from a cold. Was very ill, almost died,  wasn't covid. Not then, not now. Please do some research. Hayfever, colds,  asthma, chest infections, pneumonia still exist, none of it is covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Matsukaze1310 @DrNeenaJha Another lockdown was always going to happen. Fake numbers in 'cases' were always going to happen.  These protests prove there is no pandemic. I WOULD worry for my health if either of you were my doctor. Not a ounce of common sense between you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrNeenaJha @BreesAnna So for over a year, millions and millions of protesters have just been lucky not to catch 'it' then? Almost like the 'virus' doesn't actually exist??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wakeupfromcovid: COVIDIOCRACY! Credit: Another Frog: https://t.co/38OQ2xtyal https://t.co/2A1ripllyo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thegarymoore Exactly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@defensesxdown Been told to wash my hands with soap and water before entering my doctor's surgery tomorrow. So I asked what to do as i wasn't allowed to use their toilets. Receptionist said,  "wash them at home?" Hmm thanks, hadn't considered that ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville Now, if i was a germaphobe as well, wouldn't want to be touching that trolly after someone's bedding had been all over it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna Soo, HOW EXACTLY is the EU nothing like the Nazi's???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lisakeb007 Yes the sheeple suddenly 'care' for all those poor people in India.  Because the government spin suits their common cold phobia.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Griffin9c @Ausnahmezustan3 @dgventers @drdavidsamadi Passports no, being forced to inject unknown toxins into your body for the common cold IS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksr10sfan @drdavidsamadi Trust me, if i didn't already live in this sh*thole, I wouldn't want to go either.  Don't blame you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mindsetsasha @ZubyMusic Not insane, just a fact. No matter how much the feminazis deny it, men and women ARE different. If both sexes were the same, we wouldn't be able to reproduce and our species would die out. My husband can't breastfeed and I cant hang up a picture without swearing in 3 languages!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord It depends on what rules/restrictions these places expect me to adhere to. If they want me to be vaccinated,  social distance etc etc. They dont deserve my business.  But before booking, I WOULD check.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZoePrecious2020 Government actions/restrictions were never meant to save lives. They are meant to do the opposite.  To make us ill, mentally and physically.  To divide, for us to attack each other.  A very old and unfortunately successful tactic in achieving full blown facism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI If it doesn't happen, and i think it wont. He and the cultists will blame us 'anti vaxxers', the 'covid deniers' etc etc. And all 'super spreader protests'. We have been very very lucky not to catch this elusive 'virus' for a whole year!! Its almost like it doesn't exist??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna Sorry Anna, if you have a problem with Hugo,  i will have a problem with you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolineCoramUK Building it back better sounds to me.. Tearing down an existing structure, and replacing it with something different.  You could call it 'resetting'?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic Im a woman and i CHOOSE not to work in those sectors. Isnt that what equality and women's rights is about?? To CHOOSE rather than to be a tick in a box?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock People in India have had poor sanitation, poor diets and high amount of traffic accidents for as long as im alive. NOW you care when you can peddle your scamdemic??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@annaberu I remember a post from one of those cultists.  After a single 'unmasked' shopper (a normal person) was told to leave.  She demanded the whole shop including products be sanitised. SHE was told to leave too. How are we tolerating these lunatics in our world?]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>