<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@LogicalKangaroo @lisa_iannattone @sapinker Yes. Chapter 8 of #apollosarrow explains this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurahgiles Exactly. :-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JimNewsMorrison So true. @ErikaChristakis would agree too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KaseyKlimes Wins the internet today. ;-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In awful news, NYC public schools will abandon one of life's great pleasures, snow days, next year. Another casualty of the pandemic. https://t.co/xVxXR0aiZ9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PamelaParesky: An interesting take on safetyism: The more claims of feeling unsafe are honored, the more such claims proliferate, sa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mqdicer: Congrats to @chocophlan, #HumanNatureLab postdoc, on new paper: "Integrating taxonomic, functional, and strain-level profiling]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SincerelyData What question would you like to ask about this topic, and what model would you specify in order to address it with observational data?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The humane and ever-rational @conor64 pushes back at harmful hyperbole.   All cases [of police killings of minors] are tragedies. But most news coverage of these killings lacks vital context to inform good answers. End #policeimpunity  https://t.co/LpJxhPHCxH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These stories regarding the pluck shown by Australian surfers appear regularly. But, even by that standard, this one is impressive.  "The shark isn't getting its tooth back [and] I'm not getting my leg back."  https://t.co/glPM2A7tQa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickKristof: Tani is a reminder: Talent is universal, but opportunity is not. He was lucky that his homeless shelter was near a school]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SincerelyData Yes. Its crucial. Would you have done this analysis in some other way? What variables would you include as controls?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gurdur @LDBurnett @conor64 Plus, I came to her public defense when her episode first started. https://t.co/KK2aRk0v3A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LDBurnett @conor64 @jonathanchait @CathyYoung63 Lora: I came to your defense, publicly. Not sure why you see any inconsistency. https://t.co/KK2aRk0v3A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conor64 @LDBurnett @MichaelBerube1 @adamsteinbaugh Lora, I actually came to your defense, publicly: https://t.co/KK2aRk0v3A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really? "Linfield University president: I did not know there were rules for firing tenured faculty" https://t.co/IV8rBTT3AM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its shocking  and telling  that Pollack-Pelzner was forced out without an opportunity to defend himself, said FIRE attorney @adamsteinbaugh. President Davis has shown himself to be a bad actor, and this termination is a farce.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tenured professor abruptly fired after raising allegations of anti-Semitic speech by Linfield Universitys president https://t.co/2CQR8FLJrh via @TheFIREorg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Such an observant and entertaining book https://t.co/d7yJXwSYgq via @RoyaTheWriter Strongly recommended, as they say. https://t.co/s3ezMrsK3M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @singularityu: Listen to episode 10 of The Feeback Loop: Exploring the Impacts of COVID with @NAChristakis.   Available anywhere you lis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@45TheManchurian The controls are (truly) always the rub, arent they? Take a look at the paper and suggest a different way to tackle this topic?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LDBurnett @conor64 @jonathanchait @CathyYoung63 Im not (yet) familiar with this case, but Im sure Ive supported many professors in exactly this situation (small colleges firing professors who have criticized the institution, from the left).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news: after controls, a study finds no gender difference in promotion to associate professor in biomedical science, physical science, political science, mathematics  statistics, and engineering, but some evidence of difference (p&lt;.10) in economics https://t.co/F8PUiRZVeD https://t.co/pL1tvtRcyn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SCMPNews: Official Chinese social media accounts mock Indias Covid-19 crisis https://t.co/b2Uh69P6YA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zakkohane: Face recognition ML used in exactly the way feared @business https://t.co/CmDKoKAdgT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[About flipping time. End #policeimpunity. https://t.co/cEIDEU1WJD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More data: after vaccination, the known "breakthrough" rate of COVID infections in San Diego County among &gt;1 million vaccinees is 0.02% (234 cases, 55% with no symptoms). https://t.co/XeKRMYw6GQ via @EricTopol 5/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarioLuisSmall: Yet another reason low-income populations were more affected COVID-19: Locked down local business and organizations --]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@razibkhan Related and of possible interest: https://t.co/dTW3pIaJDi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@obaidomer Also good.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Making the rounds.  ;-)  h/t @DAChristakis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How it's actually going to be: https://t.co/CQDO0QvCOE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How you imagine the trolley problem: https://t.co/xyptl4hlHI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HopeJahren With VERMONT maple syrup of course. https://t.co/YOZTeaDe2d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Popehat It can never be wrong for a wife to tease her husband.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Placebos have traditionally involved concealment. But they can also work when prescribed transparently as open-label placebos," especially as a conditioned stimulus. RCT (N=51) finds post-op patients consumed ~30% less daily morphine. https://t.co/4N5fvPfcop  @PAINthejournal https://t.co/YNtLJ2N7m6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: We are fortunate that vaccines induce such a strong immune response and provide protection from all of the virus variants th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is wild: alien genomes can be found on Earth. Some viruses that infect bacteria use an alternative genetic alphabet thats distinct from the code used by nearly all other organisms. https://t.co/8q4DEnuVnA via @NatureNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saletan @ScottGottliebMD Of course it is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mcm_ct Um, on the basis of several large randomized controlled trials. Plus, now, several huge observational studies (eg from Israel) documenting efficacy and safety (over time horizon to date).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pkedrosky Discussed in #apollosarrow too. ;-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is mind boggling. This bird perfectly imitates the sounds of camera shutters and chain saws. Its the vocal equivalent of flamboyant bowers. https://t.co/t4tSulcwgK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mcm_ct Yes, of course there are delays (both in reporting and in accrual of bad outcomes, which are delayed with respect to vaccination). Do you have a citation for 'three months'?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mcm_ct I think it is unlikely you know something about the COVID-19 epidemic that I do not, but it is surely possible. Can you be more specific? Are you alluding, perhaps, to the temporal element (ie, 1 in 1M deaths, but just over 4 months  given current prevalence)? Tweets are short.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kal_muzaffer @docmilanfar @aminkarbasi Yes. Just like Greek baklava is the best. #baklavawars. ;-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Republicans calling Mitt Romney a communist is like Democrats calling Kamala Harris a fascist. The political extremes in the USA have lost their minds. https://t.co/4i6U2ThaKh We all have a role to play in enhancing civil discourse  in seeking compromise with political opponents]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For avoidance of confusion, let me add: Given one set of data issues here (e.g., likely under-reporting of asymptomatic cases), we can also calculate the CFR as 112/6,720=1.6%, which is at the upper end of consensus estimates of the CFR in unvaccinated people. 4/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RiverTamYDN Yes. (See comment about data issues.) We can also calculate the CFR as 112/6,720=1.6%, which is roughly in keeping with CFR (at the upper end of consensus estimates).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@imbernomics Yes. (See comment about data issues.) We can also calculate the CFR as 112/6,720=1.6%, which is roughly in keeping with CFR (at the upper end of consensus estimates).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The bottom line is that these vaccines for COVID-19 are miraculously effective. So far, only about 1 in a million people who are vaccinated have died from COVID-19. And reports so far show amazing safety, too. Get vaccinated. For yourself. For your family. For your community. 3/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you calculate the IFR of SARS-CoV-2 among the vaccinated using these (admittedly imperfect) data, you get 112/9,245=1.2%. This would mean IFR is higher than among the unvaccinated. But 45% of breakthrough cases post vaccination are among those 60. So maybe not.   But...  2/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 Breakthrough Case Investigations and Reporting | CDC https://t.co/GgtIwXvrLt via @CDCgov   95,000,000+ fully vaccinated 9,245 infections (0.01%) 594 COVID-related hospitalizations (0.0006%) 112 COVID-related deaths (0.0001%)  However...  1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GadSaad @EricTopol Ah I see. So sorry. I dont believe Im trying to curry favor with anyone. I do believe I was and am grateful for your support. I dont believe Im different in public or private. I have no memory of who I used to follow, but I do curate the list occasionally to maintain breadth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GadSaad @EricTopol So sorry! I read the thread and thought I understood. Can you clarify for me?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GadSaad @EricTopol While I strongly supported Biden, I had one brilliant friend who, unaccountably, voted for Trump. Many long conversations ensued. He pointed out just what you are saying: I don't agree with everything 'my' candidates say or do, so why should I expect him to do so?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The young in these 2 Varanasi villages started to die. Thats when Covid became real https://t.co/EPxF88rYXM via @ThePrintIndia  In the previous wave, we thought that this was some kind of conspiracy. But now its real. Even 30-year-olds are also dying.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look at this fresh treasure. https://t.co/MafDDiFcit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In any party of 6, its a mathematical certainty that there will either be a group of 3 people who all know each other OR a group of 3 who are strangers to each other.  Oh and: New Proof Reveals That Graphs With No Pentagons Are Fundamentally Different.  https://t.co/VJDMOD6CA9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPRK_News Did the pairs have shoes of dissimilar sides (left and right) or of the same side (left and left), more in keeping with juche?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GhassanAlRegib @docmilanfar @aminkarbasi That wins the internet today. But surely you know: https://t.co/sxSXpdNITN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @innocence: Almost exactly 18 years ago, Rosa Jimenez gave birth while wrongly imprisoned. Her son was taken from her almost immediately]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Polls have found that a majority of gun owners favor stronger gun regulations, as long as the basic right of gun ownership is respected. https://t.co/rwOwhLnQBr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickKristof: A far-right GOP Oregon legislator who let violent pro-Trump protesters through locked doors into the state Capitol buildin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the N-Word Became Unsayable.  As usual, no one and nothing is left off the hook or escapes @JohnHMcWhorter's brilliant, withering gaze, not least any racism in American society. This is a learned and humane man at work. Read and marvel. https://t.co/vMuICWFOw6 @nytopinion]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Policing must change. Police work for the citizenry, not vice-versa. "Serving on the jury has made him see how wrong it is that a person should be so afraid that a police officer could do them harm that they needed to change their behavior." https://t.co/hG5rjniGOj via @WSJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardTufte This application of Elo might interest you: https://t.co/JuoBGYFcB1 @sohamsankaran @jacob_derechin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulbloomatyale @ashleyruba Total. And hilarious.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulbloomatyale Your comment wins the internet today, as does the original post. ;-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paulbloomatyale: !!! (I've written at least 5 of these papers) https://t.co/8yiUPScSqg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatGeo: "Watching a creature dieone who is the last of its kindis something I hope never to experience again. It felt like watching o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apparently (and thankfully, albeit too late for McNeil), the New York Times has now revised its absurd policy that "intent doesn't matter" when it comes to racial slurs. https://t.co/SOQItDFStg Of course there is a difference between using and mentioning a slur!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zakijam: Not since Liam Neeson in Taken has someone had the particular set of skills, acquired over a long career, for an endeavor like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @incunabula: "The door opened, and Elisabeth discovered a long-hidden treasure: It was a unique moment in my life, an emotion without e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aminkarbasi @docmilanfar Yes. They are variants of concern.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@docmilanfar @aminkarbasi Exactly correct.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buddysage @cerebrodesatado I know. I dont believe there has ever been another similar case. For obvious reasons.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman in rural Mexico with no medical experience performs expert C-section on herself, after swigs of hard liquor, and both she and her baby, Orlando, survive. https://t.co/rxhPYzGV0N via @cerebrodesatado]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@megan_janas @jackofallthumbs Dont read this: https://t.co/rxhPYzGV0N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cerebrodesatado Oh wow.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nirav_mainecdc @UChicago @UChicagoMed Thanks for the reference and for the kind words. :-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FawksWatcher Yes. Also.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This trope in action movies (from Rambo to The Martian) has an actual precedent?! I should have known. Incredible. https://t.co/S0LUahszKn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conor64 This has happened at the peak of past bubbles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@R_H_Ebright Exactly. Nine days through the army went the arrows of the god. Until the tenth day when Hera took pity on the Greeks. For she saw them perishing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@R_H_Ebright This whole excerpt was on its own page at the beginning of #ApollosArrow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Before the pandemic, we used to cremate eight to 10 people (daily)," said Jitender Singh Shunty, head of the Seemapuri crematorium in eastern New Delhi. "Now, we are cremating 100 to 120 a day." https://t.co/jhWEJZEQYy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cesifoti: You've heard about audiobooks. But videobooks?! We translated How Humans Judge Machines into 30 short episodes. You can now w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Homer's Illiad, 800 BC, Apollo's plague upon the Greeks: "frequent funeral piles of the dead were continually burning"  India 2020 AD: https://t.co/jhWEJZWrQ6  It's awful to contemplate how India will suffer.  Plague is not new to our species. It's just new to us. #ApollosArrow https://t.co/S7AmV2JEFT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The irony of some losers vandalizing profound and ancient petroglyphs dated to the Fremont era that stretched from 500 A.D. to 1300 A.D. with white power is stunning.  https://t.co/ZofqA1UEX9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@natashajaques @Susan_Athey @maxhkw @aminkarbasi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @natashajaques: I couldn't resist. With contributions from @maxhkw https://t.co/3J7fz6dQut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfAbelMendez: The Radio We Could Send to Hell: Silicon carbide radio circuits can take the volcanic heat of Venus - IEEE Spectrum htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeffSharlet @VanityFair @clairehoworth @landsbaumshell Hey congrats! :-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VirusesImmunity @hmkyale @DaisySMassey @wade_schulz @Yale_LabMed Nice work, all. ;-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is ridiculous. Claira Janover clearly should not lose her job for what is clearly a metaphor, not a real threat of violence. She was making an argument. Don't like it? Argue back. Don't call for her to lose her job. Sheesh. https://t.co/NDuVQazs8Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even better, this case appears to hinge on the use of the indefinite article a in a statute. High school grammar teachers all over the nation should rejoice. https://t.co/jEGARDXNwx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilShubin @TJNear @DKiernanSkelly Ha!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@office_chick @TJNear @DKiernanSkelly @NeilShubin Don't ask me why I am friends with so many ichthyologists. No idea.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@office_chick bait for @TJNear @DKiernanSkelly @NeilShubin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bananahippyhat @TheBabylonBee @ATabarrok As I said: I have great respect for the CDC. And, I appreciate a good joke, too. ;-)]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>