<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[This #HandHygieneDay, we call on health workers  facilities to ensure effective hand hygiene at all points of care. #HandHygiene:  Protects health workers Protects patients Protect communities https://t.co/90I3ZOGN7t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Investing in access to water, sanitation  hygiene services is a simple  cost-effective way of saving lives!  #HandHygiene prevents up to 50% of avoidable infections acquired during health care delivery. #HandHygieneDay https://t.co/aOr31gEoza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is #HandHygieneDay - a reminder that "seconds save lives."   #HandHygiene is one of the most effective ways to prevent the spread of infections, including #COVID19. This year, WHO calls on all health workers  facilities to ensure safe hand hygiene at all times. https://t.co/y8PsuRupfW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOEthiopia: Its #HandHygiene Day 2021! Seconds save lives! #CleanYourHands #InfectionPrevention https://t.co/J4nCWQ2GQZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOBotswana: #DYK that #AntimicrobialResistance makes infections harder to treat or even incurable?  Don't abuse antibiotics. https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just nine days outbreak was declared in #Guinea, #Ebola vaccinations began with support of @WHO  partners. WHO is also supporting with medical equipment  supplies such as cold chain, testing  screening materials.   No new cases have been recorded since 2 April. https://t.co/lQUpJsDhQ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Ebola surveillance  preparedness are also being ramped up across #Guinea's six neighbouring countries  cross-boarder transmission remains a risk due to travel  trade.   Hundreds of Liberian traders use the Ganta crossing point to visit a weekly market in Guinea. https://t.co/FDYVIpa6QP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHO  partner organizations are also working with community leaders in #Guinea so they take ownership of the #Ebola response  support public education. Community involvement has proven to be critical in curbing Ebola. https://t.co/yN9JUXu5Gb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Guinea declared an #Ebola outbreak on 14 February after cases were confirmed in NZerekore. Health authorities swiftly mounted a response with @WHO support. Surveillance  screening networks have been set up to quickly detect  stop the spread of the virus. https://t.co/iIeZK5ZWzF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huge efforts have been made to curb #Guinea's #Ebola outbreak  building on expertise gained in 20142016 outbreak. Guinean health workers  community leaders have been at the forefront of the response with support of @WHO  partners.  Our photo storyhttps://t.co/pDd3xh7YaW https://t.co/HFBR0kMBks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHONigeria: Please DON'T self-medicate. If you feel unwell see a licensed medical practitioner.  #AMR https://t.co/1AHGp8RwD3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHONigeria: #DYK that #AntimicrobialResistance makes infections harder to treat or even incurable?  Don't abuse antibiotics. https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep yourself safe from #COVID19 this #Ramadan.   Wash your hands often  Wear a mask  Keep a safe distance  Avoid large gatherings or events #RamadanMubarak https://t.co/Zw2FwLvQSD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANTIMICROBIAL RESISTANCE. Its a global health crisis threatening 4.1 million lives in #Africa by 2050.   #AMR makes common illnesses untreatable as bacteria, parasites  viruses mutate  become resistant to medicines. #ResistAMR   https://t.co/iS0xAb5ZmA https://t.co/OWTEZPtXt6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: We cannot be lulled into a false sense of security. The devastating surge of #COVID19 cases  deaths in India,  increases]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOBotswana: Antimicrobial Resistance #AMR could kill 4.1 million people in #Africa 2050.   When we abuse, misuse or overuse medicines]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOSouthSudan: When we abuse, misuse or overuse medicines like antibiotics, antivirals, antifungals  antiparasitics, we risk bugs beco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr @MoetiTshidi shares an epidemiological update of the #COVID19 pandemic in #Africa  words of caution as risk of a surge in cases remains. https://t.co/UjdnspjhP7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: Heartfelt congratulations to the people of #DRC for ending the latest #Ebola outbreak! Huge credit to the expertise of l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: We have been pleased to support @MinSanteRDC's efforts to bring this outbreak under control, including contact tracing, tr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teams remain on high alert as #DRC health authorities monitor for potential #Ebola flare-ups in the months to come. @WHO continues to work with health authorities to tackle other public health problems, including outbreaks of measles, cholera  #COVID19. https://t.co/iYfM1hjYtn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #Ebola response was coordinated by the Provincial Department of Health in collaboration with @WHO  partners. WHO had nearly 60 experts on the ground supporting contact tracing, providing treatment, community engagement  vaccination. https://t.co/mGX37nNTfp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The latest #Ebola outbreak in #DRC has been declared over after just 3 months. Twelve cases, six deaths  six recoveries were recorded in four health zones in North Kivu during this outbreak.  @WHO congratulates DRCs swift response to this outbreak!  https://t.co/2gNHJR22B6 https://t.co/hNZ1moYLaT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antimicrobial Resistance #AMR could kill 4.1 million people in #Africa by 2050.   When we abuse, misuse or overuse medicines like antibiotics, we risk bugs becoming RESISTANT to the medicines used to fight them.  We must #ResistAMR  More info: https://t.co/iS0xAb5ZmA https://t.co/qBhoTAENG7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOOD NEWS from #DRC!  @MinSanteRDC has just announced the end of the 12th #Ebola outbreak in DRC  just 3 months after the first case was reported in North Kivu.  Congratulations to health authorities, health workers  communities for this effort. https://t.co/JeTs051A0P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keeping healthy helps your body to fight infections like #COVID19.   Quit tobacco Avoid alcohol Be physically active Eat a healthy diet https://t.co/pPEJXt390d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK that smokers are 1.5x more likely to get severe cases of #COVID19?   Say #NoTobacco  https://t.co/avkdjasf7u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People with non-communicable disease have a higher risk of severe #COVID19. The main risks of #NCDs are:   Tobacco.  Alcohol.  Air pollution.  Unhealthy diet.  Physical inactivity.    Let's #BeatNCDs. https://t.co/5LOSCDokFF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay active this weekend! The health benefits of a physically active lifestyle during adolescence include:    improved cardiorespiratory  muscular fitness bone and cardiometabolic health  positive effects on weight  Lets #Be Active! Lets #BeatNCDs! https://t.co/D8rkPZuTAs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK that #COVID19 is transmitted by droplets that spread when we talk, sneeze or cough?   Wearing a mask creates a physical barrier that catches these droplets. #MaskUp https://t.co/FrP8j3LH2o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Africa crossed a historic milestone when it was certified as free of wild #polio last year. Vaccination drives, reaching up to 220 million children multiple times a year, made a huge impact.   Dr Tunji Funsho shares lessons from ending wild polio https://t.co/5wmAXq8wHN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK Every $1 spent on childhood immunizations in Africa returns $54 in economic benefits.  Vaccines are a smart investment. #AVW2021 #VaccinesWork https://t.co/U92tWsXUgI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK in 2019, 20 million children worldwide  more than 1 in 10  missed out on basic vaccines?   In Africa, 1 in 5 children remain unprotected. Expanding access to vaccines is key for people everywhere to reach their full potential. #AVW2021 https://t.co/hm7Cv6hDTU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOMalawi: Access to immunization connects families with health care systems and brings us all closer to universal health coverage by 2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOEthiopia: Happy#GoodFriday. This Ethiopian Easter Festive, stay alert to protect yourself  others from#COVID19.  Your health]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is the final day of Africa Vaccination Week #AVW2021  a reminder of the power of vaccines.  Vaccines save 4 million lives every year  protect us from deadly diseases. #VaccinesWork https://t.co/EoTOsjrVAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The risk of #COVID19 resurgence remains high in several African countries due to poor adherence to public health measures, mass gatherings, low testing  vaccination rates. Essential health services are still reeling from disruptions caused by the pandemic.https://t.co/jxUEm0PbSb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leaders have the power to ensure that #HealthForAll remains a priority. Strong political will is key to deliver on the promise to reach everyone with life-saving vaccines.   This #AVW2021, share this message to call for more action on immunization! https://t.co/wl7qMG0w18]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #AVW2021, stand with us to call for a world where everyone has access to vaccines,  for a world where we can all be #ProtectedTogether! https://t.co/YHXKPeSz0V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What does #HealthForAll mean to you?   Access to quality essential health care services  Access to safe, effective  affordable essential medicines  Financial risk protection  Vaccines for all  Strengthening routine immunization is a smart investment! #AVW2021 https://t.co/4CXExdRZKv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 2020, vaccines helped end a deadly #Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo #DRC. Vaccines bring us closer to an Ebola-free Africa! #AVW2021 #VaccinesWork https://t.co/03zZKTgyzx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We are encouraging countries to prioritize the first dose, to reach more people, rather than saving supplies for the second dose. It is imperative that the available doses are used as quickly as possible." - Dr @MoetiTshidi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["@WHO is waiting on additional stability data from the Serum Institute of India to determine if the shelf life of #AstraZeneca Covishield doses can be extended from six months to nine months." - Dr @MoetiTshidi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["On Tuesday I met with Ministers of Health in the African Region to discuss key issues, particularly around expiring doses, supply shortages, vaccine safety  misinformation." - Dr @MoetiTshidi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["A WHO analysis of 46 African countries finds that almost half are facing a high risk of experiencing a surge in cases. Now is not the time to let our guard down." - Dr @MoetiTshidi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We cannot be lulled into a false sense of security as the continents case count appears stable. The devastating surge of #COVID19 cases  deaths in India,  increases in other regions of the world, are clear signs of the risk of resurgence in Africa." - Dr @MoetiTshidi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Join our @WHOAFRO #COVID19 press briefing. Dr @MoetiTshidi is joined by experts from across the Region, including Dr Christian Owoo  Dr Kaushik Ramaiya. https://t.co/n8AgDEAICT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines will help us end the #COVID19 pandemic so we can finally be closer to each other again.   #VaccinesWork to bring us closer. #WorldImmunizationWeek #AVW2021 https://t.co/1ltCuyPpaG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its #WorldImmunizationWeek!  Vaccination protects people of all ages against preventable diseases  is one of the best ways to provide children with a healthy start in life.   #VaccinesWork to bring us closer. #AVW2021 https://t.co/CYUGrCyyAC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here are some of the key lessons emerging from African countries that have made strong progress in #COVID19 vaccine rollout  including Angola, Ghana, Mauritius  Rwanda.  Early insights offer hope, inspiration  early, yet vital lessons. #AVW2021 https://t.co/1uBdEzyQ6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 4.5 million confirmed #COVID19 cases on the African continent - with more than 4 million recoveries  120,000 deaths cumulatively.   View country figures  more with the WHO African Region COVID-19 Dashboard: https://t.co/FKav40Cbdd https://t.co/68AGxBhVlh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one is safe until everyone is safe.   Equitable access to #COVID19 vaccines will help protect health  economic gains in all nations -  bring all of us closer to the end of the pandemic. #AVW2021 #ProtectedTogether https://t.co/IXsp7csn6x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: #HPV vaccine is highly effective. It can prevent 9 in 10 cases of HPV  the #1 cause of cervical cancer.  Yes, #VaccinesWork to br]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: The #HPV vaccine is available in more than 100 countries around, helping to protect millions of girls against #CervicalCancer.  Bu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO_Zimbabwe: How much do you know about diabetes   Watch to learn more about the causes, symptoms and how it can be treated   @MoHC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't miss tomorrow's @WHOAFRO #COVID19 press briefing. Dr @MoetiTshidi will be joined by experts from across the Region, including Dr Christian Owoo  Dr Kaushik Ramaiya.  Thursday 29 April 11AM (GMT+1) https://t.co/R1QBHzOw85 https://t.co/o4ZT7AWFAF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lack of access to quality data is a major barrier to addressing health the Region. The @WHO integrated African Health Observatory (iAHO) makes health information more available, accessible  easier to use.  For more info: https://t.co/g9BWWG7IDC https://t.co/Zrvd5sucgS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @WHOAFRO integrated African Health Observatory (iAHO) is a health information platform that provides a real-time overview of health in the  Region.   Check out the presentation of the newly redesigned iAHO earlier this month.  Watch here: https://t.co/Lu7yX7U7Od https://t.co/9nYbSWijj7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK that Africa accounts for 16% of the global population, but only 0.1% of the global vaccine production?   Advancing RD, manufacturing  distribution in #Africa will bring us closer to equitable protection from life-threatening diseases. #AVW2021 https://t.co/6aFBtHel98 https://t.co/lUSp55dp6m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Equitable access to safe  effective #COVID19 vaccines will help communities  economies thrive.   No one is protected until we are all protected, stand up for #VaccinEquity! #ProtectedTogether   #AVW2021: https://t.co/6aFBtHel98 https://t.co/24D8c0lhLI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 vaccines offer crucial protection against severe disease, hospitalisation  death from the virus. They bring us all closer to ending the pandemic. #AVW2021 #ProtectedTogether #VaccinesWork  https://t.co/6aFBtHel98 https://t.co/KubVnRPz4k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pandemic preparedness  response must be equitable to be effective. Join panellists including @WHOAFROs @Patuhebwe for this @harvardGH discussion on making equity a strategic priority in future health crises.  Thurs 29 April 3:00-4:00pm (CAT) https://t.co/Ho3gKeaiIb https://t.co/vYynLyMztm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: Farewell to my sister Micaela Marques de Sousa @UNICEF Representative in Congo. Appreciate the opportunity to thank you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @USAIDGH: Vaccines bring us closer to a more prosperous ! @USAIDs investments in #COVAX will play a critical role in reinvigorating ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gavi: The vaccine is cheap, safe and saves lives. We will not lose our lives because we are not vaccinated - Angola is celebrating th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here are some of the key lessons emerging from African countries that have made strong progress in #COVID19 vaccine rollout  including Angola, Ghana, Mauritius  Rwanda.   Early insights offer hope, inspiration  early, yet vital lessons. #AVW2021 https://t.co/aUWnaghVuQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: Productive meeting with @ChrisJElias last week on @WHOAFRO priority programmes  which have been advancing thanks to @gate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reflecting on #COVID19 in Africa: One Year Later with @VOANews Straight Talk Africa.  Join @WHOAFROs @Patuhebwe  other experts looking back on one year of pandemic response on the continent. #VOACoronavirusAfrica  Wednesday 28 April 3:30pm CAT https://t.co/nG6sgSqHyP https://t.co/j2KpjFRAO0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 4.5 million confirmed #COVID19 cases on the African continent - with more than 4 million recoveries  120,000 deaths cumulatively.   View country figures  more with the WHO African Region COVID-19 Dashboard: https://t.co/FKav40Cbdd https://t.co/bXBId46kso]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: Pleasure joining briefing today on #COVID19 vaccine rollout with Ministers of Health from the Region. Productive discussio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With most African countries rolling out #COVID19 vaccines, what are the emerging challenges seen? Join @UNICEF @GAVI @WHOAFRO  Health Ministries for tomorrows webinar on Africa's #COVID19 vaccine rollout.  28 April 10am12pm (GMT+1) Register: https://t.co/CVtDaIfAew https://t.co/jhhf1dzv9v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DRC's #YellowFever vaccination campaign is led by health authorities, with support of @WHO, @Gavi, @PATH, @UNICEF, @VillageReach  other partners.   It has taken more than a year of planning  was partly delayed due to the #COVID19 pandemic. https://t.co/uT4ql8jSCj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DRC just launched a preventive #YellowFever vaccination campaign targeting more than 16.3 million people, including nearly 300,000 refugees. This drive against the disease is the first in #Africa this year. #AVW2021  https://t.co/YqHEuyuUvm https://t.co/ZbBxgATua8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unlike most medicines which treat or cure diseases, vaccines prevent them. This helps keep people  communities healthy  reduces the strain on health systems.   This #AVW2021, speak up and advocate for equitable access to vaccines. #VaccinesWork #VaccinEquity https://t.co/Pl6AeoKqHM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 tips to ensure #COVID19 safety at places of worship  mosques this #Ramadan.   #RamadanMubarak https://t.co/6gDmnBl3B6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 4.5 million confirmed #COVID19 cases on the African continent - with more than 4 million recoveries  120,000 deaths cumulatively.   View country figures  more with the WHO African Region COVID-19 Dashboard: https://t.co/FKav40Cbdd https://t.co/7rhQR67JkW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOGAMBIA: #HappeningNow! Dr Desta Tiruneh, #WHO Representative in The #Gambia hands over the #Trachoma elimination letter from @DrTedr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK that 1 dose of the yellow fever vaccine gives life-long immunity against the disease?   We must push for high immunization coverage to protect people from #YellowFever  other vaccine-preventable diseases. #VaccinesWork #ProtectedTogether https://t.co/Iw9kny7pVU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OMS_Afrique: Rejoignez les leaders africains de la sant et les champions de la vaccination pour clbrer comment "les vaccins nous rap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines eradicate diseases, save lives  prevent disability  In 2020 the @WHOAFRO region was declared free of wild poliovirus, an inspiring sign that shows #VaccinesWork. With greater immunization efforts, we can fight against all forms of polio!  #EndPolio #AVW2021 https://t.co/WbTjMAk5Kk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Join African health leaders  immunization champions in celebrating how Vaccines Bring Us Closer. #AVW2021  https://t.co/a0qY2aFZ1I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #AVW2021 we call for more, better action to ensure every generation in #Africa is protected from vaccine-preventable diseases.   #COVID19 has significantly disrupted routine immunization services, leaving many at risk. #ProtectedTogether #VaccinesWork https://t.co/YOa775mHTV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Phionah Athuebwe from @WHOAFRO explains why the #COVID19 vaccine is still important even if youve already had COVID-19. #ViralFactsAfrica https://t.co/WwqM03yY2V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: #AskWHO on @TwitterSpaces:  #3 Session: How can we #EndPolio?  @Dr_HamidJafari  @NayyarUjala   12:00 PM CEST   #WorldImmunizati]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is the launch of Africa Vaccination Week live from Accra, Ghana with @MOHGhana and @WHOAFRO @WHOGhana.   Join African health leaders  immunization champions in celebrating how Vaccines Bring Us Closer. #AVW2021   10:0012:00 (GMT)  Live Streaming @WHOAFRO @mohgovgh https://t.co/pp9tLXlDMT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOGhana: #Malaria kills nearly 400,000 people every year in the African Region, yet it is preventable,  curable.   We must ensure tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOAFRO: Can we end #malaria as a public health threat? The simple answer is YES.   4 African countries have already achieved #ZeroMal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Innovations will be critical to speed up progress towards #ZeroMalaria.   So, we are excited that Ghana, Kenya  Malawi have delivered more than 1.7 million doses of the RTSS #MalariaVaccine - a promising additional tool in malaria prevention. https://t.co/As7FOLENY3 https://t.co/1JvvPNbYIC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cabo Verde is one of four African countries that have gone for three consecutive years malaria transmission.   The country is now eligible to apply for @WHO's certification of #malaria elimination. #WorldMalariaDay https://t.co/FTsBTWDSMn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today, we are celebrating 2 years of the #MalariaVaccine.   Lusitana was the first child in the world to receive the RTS,S malaria vaccine through routine immunization. She has now received all four doses  is fully vaccinated.   #WorldMalariaDay https://t.co/SLXr9lKdJO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we end #malaria as a public health threat? The simple answer is YES.   4 African countries have already achieved #ZeroMalaria status for 3 years. #WorldMalariaDay https://t.co/IrSxZxrG9d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 years ago, #Malawi became the first country to introduce the malaria vaccine into its childhood immunization programme.   Clara is one of many mothers who were eager to protect their children against #malaria, a major cause of death. #WorldMalariaDay https://t.co/zygYj3PZkk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the official launch of Africa Vaccination Week on Monday 26 April! Hosted by @MOHGhana, @WHOAFRO  @WHOGhana with African health leaders  immunization champions. #AVW2021 #ProtectedTogether #VaccinesWork  Monday 26 April 10:0012:00 GMT Live Streaming @WHOAFRO @mohgovgh https://t.co/UBUuUAzDsq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: Every #malaria case  death is preventable... It's unacceptable that almost 400,000 people in Africa died of malaria in 20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHONigeria: Today, @WHO joins the world to commemorate the #WorldMalariaDay2021 with the theme Zero Malaria - Draw the Line Against #Ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOBotswana: #vaccines are the easiest way for us to live fuller and longer lives! I take a stand to get vaccinated to protect myself a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoetiTshidi: #COVID19 has highlighted the enormous value of vaccines. We need global solidarity, political commitment, sustained fundin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOGAMBIA: Today is #WorldMalariaDay2021. @WHOGAMBIA joins the rest of the world to call on all stakeholders to "draw the line against]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO_Zimbabwe: The @WHOAFRO region is home to 94% of all malaria cases and deaths.   The more we invest in vaccines for preventable dise]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOEthiopia: It's #WorldMalariaDay    #DYK that #Malaria still kills 1 child every 2 minutes. Together we can #EndMalaria https://t.c]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>