<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: This is the second individual who is not a member of Congress to test positive in the congressional outbreak (Rep. Pressley's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: Latest update to @CovidWh's Congressional tracker includes 10 positive cases around the events of January 6. The most recent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We urge all members of Congress who were in the Capitol on January 6 to get tested and quarantine until they receive their results. We hope for speedy recoveries for those who are infected and wish that member of Congress would set an example for the nation by wearing a mask.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're back. As we begin to see more Covid-19 diagnoses from members of Congress, including many who were present in a room with maskless GOP lawmakers, we have tracked 9 cases since January 4. Follow along and see all cases in Congress here: https://t.co/Gl1CYMuqzn https://t.co/actLRMmkFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: We have now made the Congressional Covid-19 tracker available on @CovidWh as we begin to track what may turn out to be a supe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: New: Rep. Brad Schneider is now the 9th member of Congress to test positive for Covid-19 since January 4. He is the 3rd to no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: New: We have now tracked 8 Covid-19 cases in Congress since January 4, including 2 as a result of direct exposure from a lock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: Major update to our Congressional Covid-19 Tracker: We may be seeing the beginnings of a superspreader event in Congress as t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is a table separated by events. We are particularly seeking to obtain more information relating to last Friday's White House Christmas party, where Jenna Ellis was in attendance. https://t.co/tyD9uKwe2J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're back! With recent diagnoses of Rudy Giuliani and Jenna Ellis, we have tracked 35 contacts with 2 positive cases. 4 events are under investigation: Events in AZ, MI, GA and the Christmas party.  Follow: https://t.co/LPfi6TYhC5  Submit tips: https://t.co/XXkt8K92cj https://t.co/GFWibNgUJS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will work on tracking Mayor Giuliani's contacts and any potential links to previous iterations of our tracker. More soon. https://t.co/GXYQwZdkoG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: For the past few months we at @CovidWh have spent much of our work tracking Covid-19 infections at the White House, but what]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: We at @CovidWh have been tracking Covid-19 cases in the WH in 3 "waves." If we put all these infections together (and these a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest version of our tracker includes 3 new positives reported by @JenniferJJacobs: Andrew Giuliani, Donald Trump Jr. and Hannah MacInnis.  This round of White House infections is now up to 20 positives. Track it here: https://t.co/okBW5NfRr4 Submit tips: https://t.co/br3vuprd8H https://t.co/jUZwgCeMYb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferJJacobs: News: Don Jr, the presidents son, has tested positive for coronavirus. He escaped the virus when people around him go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The rapid influx of positive tests, many linked to the party, is not surprising, as 8 days have elapsed since Election Night and this is usually the time for the virus to incubate and individuals to develop symptoms. Here is an epi curve of the current positive tests. https://t.co/yOaFWANkGw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest update of our tracker includes 17 positives, 7 of whom confirmed to have been at the election night party. We are in the process of upgrading our dashboard. Follow along here: https://t.co/EObRTuiDUv  Submit a tip: https://t.co/br3vuprd8H https://t.co/WJKC2Iln2r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are on this list, get tested and quarantine to prevent further spread.  If you have a tip, submit it here: https://t.co/br3vuprd8H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Major update to our @CovidWh outbreak tracker  we have been working on listing all contacts from the election night party. Latest stats:  - 11 positives, 5 of whom were at the election night party - 51 total contacts (and counting)  https://t.co/okBW5NfRr4 https://t.co/yJS31ncdDL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: We are investigating if Mr. Bossie was present at the election night event. https://t.co/1MjsoH7MW6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest update of our chief of staff outbreak tracker includes 8 positives with the recent diagnosis of Secretary Ben Carson. Follow along at https://t.co/okBW5NfRr4.  We are currently listing all present at the election night party. Submit a tip: https://t.co/br3vuprd8H https://t.co/ZmmJmUlXOk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest version of our tracker reflects reporting from @maggieNYT and @JenniferJJacobs  the chief of staff outbreak is up to 7 positives. Follow along at https://t.co/okBW5MYg2u. We will be tracing through events Meadows attended.  Submit a tip at https://t.co/XXkt8KqD3R. https://t.co/jEBe6dtkq5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: Latest update of @CovidWh Round 3 includes 5 positives, as reported by @JenniferJJacobs and @maggieNYT.  Follow along here: h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus is back in the White House, this time around Chief of Staff Mark Meadows. Follow along here: https://t.co/okBW5NfRr4  Submit a tip here:  https://t.co/XXkt8K92cj https://t.co/scBD26vGuO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Round 3table coming soon. https://t.co/9YF9I8fhZ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: "He needs to be in quarantine," @ashishkjha says on the VP circle outbreak. "The evidence on this is overwhelmingly clear and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AnaCabrera: CNN has learned Zach Bauer, Pence's "body man," is one of the staffers who has tested positive for coronavirus. In his role]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferJJacobs: PENCE tested negative today, according to a statement from his office, the morning after his chief of staff diagnosed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have launched a new VP outbreak tracker on our website. Check https://t.co/Fni6rVqvlK for the latest updates. Most recent results are: - 5 positives - 2 negatives (VP and SLOTUS) - 1 contact  Tips welcome at https://t.co/CwVSyHFRcM. https://t.co/j5FpkrDlxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: First release of a new dashboard tracking the latest COVID-19 outbreak at the White House. Now tracking 3 positives, 2 negati]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhrenton: It's live! We at @Covidwh are out with a new website. See the latest version of the dashboard, learn more about the project a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White House COVID-19 Tracker update, 10/8:  We added one new positive case today  a member of the White House press corps. Total positives stand at 37; total contacts - 328.  https://t.co/Z78CZ9wILo https://t.co/u73ZupYBJx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news, per an internal memo https://t.co/UHxikpqvTJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ thanks to our first 1k followers. Humbled by the interest, saddened that this tracker is necessary at all.   Reminder that our tipline is open: https://t.co/CwVSyHXs4k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just a note for those interested in our data - we are adding only contacts that seem to be in the chain of transmission from the WH.  As such, these contacts would not be added.   We wish them a speedy recovery and hope their congressman gets tested.  https://t.co/2b2v1GGo3Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: Give us a follow over @CovidWh to stay up with the latest.  Our data: https://t.co/Nqumd20O4b  (mobile) https://t.co/6EI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: Final wrap-up  for this evening on WH COVID:  We end the day at 311 contacts. 34 positive, 75 currently negative, and 2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hats off to a journalist who happens to be a student - imagine what youll do once COVID no longer holds center stage.   Signed, The other two people running this account https://t.co/ofxAMZvu0q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: Update on the debate prep event: the tweet suggesting the Pences were there has been deleted.   As such, we're taking th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @democracynow: .@CovidWh, a tool created by @bhrenton, monitors the growing number of people in Trumps circle who were exposed or infec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: Obviously this is a huge shock - not yet added to our tracker, however.  No info yet on whether these cases were discove]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8pm ET Update  277 total contacts. Within the Administration, we have 80 contacts (13 pos / 24 neg / 43 unknown)  Stay up to date at: https://t.co/Gg1cIDTlpe https://t.co/YuGfQDqVpk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StephenMolldrem @COVID19Tracking @marganina Hey Stephen - we are not at all affiliated with the Atlantic. One of our collaborators also volunteers for the @COVID19Tracking, but there is no relationship there.  We are aggregating data from public news reports on the WH Outbreak. Thanks for taking the time!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: With Kayleigh McEnany testing positive, our positive count is up to 19.  The WH press secretary is the first contact we']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: Finally - we have a new home at https://t.co/8wDwPMvdkK. Visit our dashboards there for the latest, or drop us a tip at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterJ_Walker: Wrap up  on #whcovidtracker for the evening. Thx to everyone who has contributed to our public database or given feedba]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are currently 7 administration or other Republican leaders who have declined to quarantine following negative tests from the WH outbreak  #whcovidcluster #whcovidtracker   https://t.co/Z78CZ9wILo https://t.co/k4CU4JnVBk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[270 contacts in our database overall, 164 of which attended one of these events.  Far more unknowns than answers at this point from this #whcovidcluster   https://t.co/7MwopxHnGG to dig deep into this view https://t.co/5vTXMlnq3V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We'll keep putting out the most up-to-date data on the WH COVID outbreak thanks to our crowd sourced contact tracing.   Follow this account for official updates, and check the latest at any time https://t.co/Z78CZ9wILo https://t.co/PUrUBXg3To]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Positivity rate:  March average: 4.30% April average: 4.41%  Number of days above 5%: March: 3 April: 5 https://t.co/kBg0LcjzQa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@daleen_gerber Needs to rolled out effectively and quickly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How does Aprils stats compare to March's stats?  New Cases: March- 33 342 April- 33 053 289 more in March however April has a day less than March and 3x more public holidays https://t.co/3pHyzDUq1w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[April 2021 roundup for #COVID19 in SA:  - 33 053 Cases (High: 1 674, Low: 437, Avg: 1 102) - Average Daily Pos. Rate: 4.41% (High: 9.22%, Low: 2.71%) - 1 504 Deaths (High: 130, Low: 8, Avg: 50) - 53 778 Vaccinations (20 days- 0 administered  21 days less than 1000 administered) https://t.co/AQYuXg8N83]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SA #COVID19 Vaccinations Stats: 30 April 2021  First time 10k vaccines were administered in one day since 31 MarchFolded hands  Total Administered: 317 656 Administered Today: 10 065 Remaining: 182 344 https://t.co/lcFesD7gAM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/lew5Q36e67]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/lew5Q36e67]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/lew5Q36e67]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/lew5Q36e67]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hz8l3IeAT6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics: 30 April 2021  Spike in cases today with a pos. rate above 5% GP with more than 500 new cases Vaccine rollout seems to be ramping up  - 1 674 New Cases - 1 194 New Recoveries - 19 New Deaths - 21 240 Active Cases - Daily Pos. Rate: 5.61% https://t.co/UZcUhDDp2Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bhekisisa_MG: [WATCH] #JnJ fast facts: Store at -20 degrees for 2 years. Thaw for 2 hours. https://t.co/t0jkLbeiTR https://t.co/2Tq1737]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rajeev_The_King: All districts in Free State are third wave of infections now https://t.co/1UN4qhjjfH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/0pzPZC7Woa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/yrWRFSvLnj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SA #COVID19 Vaccinations Stats: 29 April 2021  Today South Africa surpasses the 300k mark for vaccines administered  Total Administered: 307 153 Administered Today: 9 438 Remaining: 192 409 https://t.co/YwTYLtHVLw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/0pzPZC7Woa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/0pzPZC7Woa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/0pzPZC7Woa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HQOrezaTK7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics: 29 April 2021  Seems like vaccines administering is ramping up KZN new recovery stats have been abnormally low  - 1 086 New Cases - 815 New Recoveries - 46 New Deaths - 20 799 Active Cases - Daily Pos. Rate: 4.69% https://t.co/6ctdqwJmGq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/bb7U4he4F1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SA #COVID19 Vaccinations Stats: 28/04  And we're back to vaccinating after a 15 day pause  Total Administered: 298 153 Administered Today: 5 530 Remaining: 201 847 https://t.co/ZjMw8e532Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/JlU2ofHIlW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/JlU2ofHIlW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/JlU2ofHIlW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/JlU2ofHIlW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaGailBekker Lovely news! Thank you so much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaGailBekker: Administered around 5000 today.....ramp up tomorrow. Some sites still finding their feet today after the pause but bac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Gi2TGZdBMs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics: 28 April 2021  Daily pos. rate back above 5% Vaccines back to being administered after a 15 day hiatus  - 1 250 New Cases - 625 New Recoveries - 48 New Deaths - 20 977 Active Cases - Daily Pos. Rate: 5.55% https://t.co/kOOSruMsBR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WesselsGreyling @LindaGailBekker @miamalan @TheSecretSarah Perfect Im expecting an update on vaccines administered tonight. Just wanted to what that 300k increased to.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VicusVd @LindaGailBekker @miamalan @TheSecretSarah Thats number of vaccines administered. Would like to know total supply so I calculate how many vaccines are remaining etc.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaGailBekker @miamalan @TheSecretSarah any idea of the total amount of vaccines administered and available? Would be useful for my vaccine chart. Last stat I was 300k https://t.co/pTgwnnMSo4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It would be great to see rankings for student satisfaction https://t.co/LFCk5m4mim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/dbvwFSCp4T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/dbvwFSCp4T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ih5UWWxi4V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics: 27 April 2021  Daily pos. rate back below 5% Should be expecting low numbers today and tomorrow due to the public holiday Vaccinations continue tomorrow  - 880 New Cases - 1 106 New Recoveries - 51 New Deaths - 19 977 Active Cases - Daily Pos. Rate: 4.04% https://t.co/3wMcv8Wgmf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: Does pausing covid vaccines lose lives? https://t.co/ufA5dgmPtq This epidemiological modeling with the AZ vaccine interrupti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HealthZA https://t.co/tRwkTlVJD5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrZweliMkhize https://t.co/tRwkTlVJD5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HardamJv @LeighMoon @DrZweliMkhize I've posted todays stats :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HglJN1dQap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics: 26 April 2021  NW(8%), FS(30%)  NC(16%) make up 55% of new cases despite only accounting for 14% of SA's population Last 2/3 days daily pos. rate exceeds 5%  - 849 New Cases - 695 New Recoveries - 38 New Deaths - 20 254 Active Cases - Daily Pos. Rate: 5.72% https://t.co/SFru8SRmNb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excellent thread and breakdown of the current and future vaccine situation by @miamalan  Check it out https://t.co/SFMYAqE49a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No Champions League. Not even Europa League. Were in a relegation battle.   South Africa in the mud pass it on https://t.co/HT8SRHHg6o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Writing a small paragraph about the acknowledgment of the upsurge in NC, FS  NW and people breaking COVID-19 restrictions does literally nothing in trying to combat these issues.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We seriously condemn some posts we have seen on social media depicting large parties and where youngsters make a mockery of super-spreader events, even boasting to host some of their own."  So you've seen it and taking no action although going against restrictions? https://t.co/7jVmvpdUbA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This did not need 2 weeks to decide on this. Valuable time lost https://t.co/3ViBNQrtvB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its nearing the end of April and we have not even vaccinated 300k people against #COVID19 https://t.co/wOfzpUtEYS https://t.co/PH95eZuM03]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>