<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear Plasma donors,  Here is something for you. It's time to be human for human. Thank you @yogitabhayana m'am :') https://t.co/GQPdZdXX5O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SonuSood bhaiya, kya aapke rahte hue bhi ye bachchi apne Maa ko kho degi? Kuchh kijiye na..maa papa dono blind hain. Sab Kuchh khud akele hi kar rahi hai bechari.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A daughter is crying to save her mother. She is not getting a bed in hospital. Her condition is critical.  Please help @SonuSood sir @DrKumarVishwas sir @OfficeOfDKV @DelhiPolice @IYC Contact - 99714 12654 , 7042908380 Add: 411/2/1 Gali No-7, A Block Laxmi Vihar, Burari, Delhi. https://t.co/gRV0thgwy8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A pathetic news is coming from Noida. NIIMS Gr. Noida is asking families to move their patients out as they do not have any supply of Oxygen.  We request your support and help @dr_maheshsharma @PankajSinghBJP @CeoNoida @noidapolice @dmgbnagar @TheLallantop @OfficeOfDKV @Uppolice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[   ,                       "   ,      "  #indifightscorona #BengalElection2021  @CovidPlasmaIn @covid19nz @TeamSOSIndia https://t.co/p8glxsQztb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Location : Delhi  Patient Name- Aditya Prakash  Age- 34 Attendant  - Nitin mehrotra  Phone Number - 9322841114 covid positive Oxygen Level -60 with cylinder Requirement- ICU bed with ventilator  @DrKumarVishwas @OfficeOfDKV @IYC  pls look into it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[       .. Urgent Need : Plasma (Any group)  Patient has given birth to a child 2 days back.   Patient - Priyanka 30 age Hospital-  Mata Roop Rani Hospital, Uttam Nagar west delhi.   Contact 8920973277 9891139623- ranjeet @DrKumarVishwas @ravishndtv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SumantTripath16 @myogioffice Get this injection in written by hospital and ask your CMO to arrange it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PankajMunjal17: @Urgentcovidhelp Need plasma donor B+ urgently for below patient      RACHIT VOHRA  Sarvodhya Hospital Sec - 19, Farida]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@varanasi_covid @ashutosh_vns @PreetamSinghBJP @NIKHIL__0111 @dmvaranasi2016 @myogioffice @myogiadityanath Please delete this number. We are getting unnecessary calls.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sdmsadartehsil @ravikishann @myogiadityanath Thank you very much for looking into it sir :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@uditsingh4 @Anshulsharma89 @CovidIndiaSeva @COVIDNewsByMIB Ours?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@supriti2910 @ravikishann @myogiadityanath @sdmsadartehsil Let us know your message please. Is it related to covid stuffs?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@supriti2910 @ravikishann @myogiadityanath @sdmsadartehsil What's your issue?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ravikishann @myogiadityanath @sdmsadartehsil Thank you sir :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[                   100                        @ravikishann @myogiadityanath  ,   .  #Gorakhpur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URGENT     - Shweta  - 24   -  Pahar Ganj New Delhi https://t.co/O2pUUlLrUV. - 8178025524    - 54-60 Hospital Name - RML, Delhi.  Requirement- Ventilator             .   @raghav_chadha @DrKumarVishwas pls help]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[            !  Need : ventilator bed Location: bhopal Suraksha thakur 32 year  Oxygen level-50 8770337032 #MadadKeHath @PIBBhopal @Bhopal @TheLallantop @saurabhtop @INCMP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please look into it on urgent basis. It's about someone's life. @OfficeOfDMAgra.  #madadkehasth   @DrKumarVishwas @saurabhtop @TheLallantop @divyanshisumrav https://t.co/iHN33AJtTz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ ,   icu          (  10:00 PM)  -   Age 30  - 85        -   - 6232115698     ,      ##madadkehasth @divyanshisumrav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patient Name: Sameena Age: 46 *Breathing Problem* Oxygen level: 58-60   Currently in Holy Family Hospital, Julena, Okhla.   *Need ICU bed in emergency*   Attendant : Amir Hamza +91 8750927572  #CovidHelp https://t.co/RIfuuFDDbn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ !  Remdesivir Injection required for patient at New R.S Hospital, Dubagga Lucknow.   Patient name Ali Ahmad Khan  Attendant Ahmed Bilal +91 82947 94685  #CovidHelp #Lucknow #Help Via : @lakhnauaa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Scene is so Realistic Now. Nayak movie was ahead of time.   #GetWellSoonPM #MannKiBaat https://t.co/9kpY5ink5c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RahulGandhi: System failed, so its important to do Jan ki baat:  In this crisis, the country needs responsible citizens. I request m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JAIN GAS AGENCY FARIDABAD CONTACT :- 9127823410 10KG AND 30 KG AVAILABLE HOME DELIVERY!! THEY DELIVER IN DELHI AS WELL!!!  #Delhi #CovidHelp #covidresources]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URGENT   Patient name- Meena Devi Age- 50, F Required- 4 dose Remnidesivir, 2 dose of Tocilizumab Hospital - Vishwamitra Hosp, Buxar Doctor- Dr. Rajeev Jha  Attendant detail- Krishna Singh Ph- +91 70520 95257  #CovidHelp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Verified   Oxygen can available  Location - Lucknow  02:40pm , 25/04/21 Whatsapp only :-7999998217  #CovidHelp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[                    Salute to our Covid warriors  https://t.co/vHNzzwv9E8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#urgent Name: sushil srivastava Age: 48 Need: oxygen cylinder and ventilator  Location: vardan Hospital, varanasi.  Contact :7992468076 @dmvaranasi2016]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #InternationalWomensDay is an opportunity to:   challenge gender norms  empower each other  celebrate diversity  break stereotypes  take action  Happy women's Day to all the beautiful ladies out there. https://t.co/ScJFGc5pmM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_jawab_do  We are done with 2 M + tweets but mainstream media are still licking Government's boots. https://t.co/oAPerocnWC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear Government,   Don't make student's life more problematic. Conduct exams on time, Declare results on time. #modi_jawab_do https://t.co/8vzWfMw5n2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_jawab_do   we are about to hit 2 M tweets. Meanwhile modi ji and ssc official   https://t.co/j4ZhkGkqdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how modi working for creating employement in the country.   #modi_jawab_do https://t.co/ALf0PUTHDi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JobKiBaat https://t.co/Sj2EiufKMc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JobKiBaat  Dear, Prime Minister @narendramodi ji,   India is asking.. Where are 2 crore jobs you promised?   India don't want your #MannKiBakwaas- Talk about the jobs you promised   #JobKiBaat https://t.co/rgSg6XaC84]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is pathetic. Students are future of our country. It's awful to see them in this condition.   @narendramodi sir, please look into it on urgent basis. https://t.co/otsJeTUiAb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ab to test match ke results bhi 2/3 din mein aa ja raha, bas government recruitment result aane mein 3-4 years lag ja rahe.   #modi_job_do #INDvENG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ab to test match ke results bhi 2/3 din mein aa ja raha, bas government recruitment result aane mein 3-4 years lag ja rahe.   #modi_job_do #modi_job_do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5     ?       #modi_job_do #Modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/sk9DICGBJv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let them delete the tweets.  you carry out your floods of Tweets.  We are ruling over Twitter.   #modi_job_do  #Modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/Jz703qKQBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Decreasing vacancies continuously every year.   Please do not play with student's future. They are the future of our country.  #modi_job_do https://t.co/VISYvlwyQy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We were told that 2 crores jobs will be given every year.   Kya hua tera wada?   #modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/1UJkDXXPZB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are Trending at no. 1 worldwide.   People from every corner of word are asking #modi_job_do  When will they come forward to address our problem?   #modi_job_do https://t.co/4gjXKEusHP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Bahut hua rojgar ka intjaar  Ab aur nahi chahiye modi sarkar. https://t.co/uA5TjWUN7S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[     10 million tweets  ..   Keep tweeting. Mission 1 crore tweets.   #modi_job_do #modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/mTKog3ncKA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  We are Trending globally since yesterday over Twitter.   Meanwhile godi media : https://t.co/RkdWMnbg7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do After scoring 200/200marks and still not able to get a job.   Condition of students : https://t.co/LpfpnsAyHB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Employment crisis is more important than Political rallies.  Stop focusing on political campaigns. Start focusing on real issues.  #modi_job_do https://t.co/KRX3hAsHxc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Tb to some old tweets of Mr. Primeminister. https://t.co/HUIVOMJ8dJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @dhruv_rathee for standing in solidarity with the students. Please, make a video by raising our issues.   #modi_job_do https://t.co/RwvOCLffJ8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do Dear Govt,   Millions of families depend upon govt jobs to raise their living standard. Don't play with their emotions. https://t.co/zgoAaqu8Hd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Keep tweeting our revolutionary heroes.  We are about to reach at no.1 trending  world wide. https://t.co/LtIIHvwDMf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Keep tweeting. Take a pledge to create history together. Target 10 M tweets.   Get ready to rule the Twitter. 1 crore tweets. https://t.co/PhjU30JKXL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Just look at the timing.   6 million + tweets at 11:50 and 5 million tweets at 12:05.  IT cells can't stop us from reaching 10 M tweets. https://t.co/AiX3LAlTTT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[STUDENT DEMANDS -   1. Timely Exam 2. Timely Results 3. Increase Vacancies 4. Reform in EXAM 5. Waiting list   #modi_job_do https://t.co/cc2kLTo1g7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Tweets have being deleted with the given hashtags. IT cells are applying their cheap tricks to deviate us.   Keep tweeting. Target 1 crore tweets. https://t.co/cr2Y5D2OY0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do   This government is incapable of controlling price hikes in petrol, diesel, gas etc and unemployement. https://t.co/NsImTcQrDB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear students,   This is a fake account with my name.  Please report this ID.   https://t.co/JB1XXE2c2x  #modi_job_do https://t.co/vkrmjwbxCj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  We don't want "achhe din".  Please return our 'bure din'. https://t.co/wcNX2z2EVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Conditions of Students now a days : https://t.co/ayosCWOQzC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Sona nahi hai. Rukna nahi hai. Thakna nahi hai. Tweet karte rahna hai.   Target 1 crore tweets. https://t.co/PFF9CzF9NG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  How's the Josh?   Keep your spirit high, until we get 1 crore tweets. Keep tweeting. https://t.co/2oEdSWs5PH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Dear PM,   Stop focusing on growing beard. Start focusing on creating job opportunities and vacancy. https://t.co/PXHUBEwol7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  We are Trending globally over Twitter since 12 hours. Yet no government officials came to address our problem.   Students to government : https://t.co/3H4JnwE9Jg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Where are 2 crores jobs per year?   Don't play with student's future. They will throw out your government. https://t.co/oCxCe7e9cC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do   Apni hi surat jara tum nigaaro. https://t.co/y7DxYFFsJf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Keep tweeting. Take a pledge to create history together. Target 10 M tweets. https://t.co/odRaJKODOz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Conditions of students now a days: https://t.co/GM3JnQXLZj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Best thing about time is it changes.   Dear PM,   Look at your own tweet. Shame on you. https://t.co/v0DzErteuB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Sold Airport.  Sold Railway.  Sold banks.   Where the hell studens will get employed? https://t.co/VdzFaAbtu2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Dear PM,   Take some time to read your own tweets. And take immediate actions on our problem. https://t.co/G68u0FUbPY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  We're trending over Twitter since last 11  hours. But.. No media channels or govt officials came forward to address our problem. https://t.co/acwL3yH7sw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Our 18 hashtags are Trending in top 30 Trending list.   Meanwhile govt. After seeing all these trends... https://t.co/w1NICZFJ6M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Let's raise our voice for the unemployed youth of our country. Let's stand in solidarity with students. Let's create history together.   #modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/tmK3UYDAu8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[   30     18                  |  Where are all those godi media?   #modi_job_do  #modi_rojgar_do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trending at #2 worldwide. Keep tweeting. Lets rule the Twitter by getting 10+ million tweets.   Few steps away from history.   #modi_job_do  #modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/LMTRvcGw5L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top trends right now. Students are ruling over Twitter. Modi government just cannot afford to ignore the youth of our country anymore. #modi_job_do https://t.co/CM5zHPqGMG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Jab desh Ka PM behra ho to students ko awaaz uthani hi padti hai.  Target 1 crore tweets. https://t.co/lZKUEY2xfl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Let's make 10M tweets in this trend  #modi_job_do https://t.co/RtQkaj6QOc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  #GoBackModi   Stop branding yourself and give some attention on student's demand. https://t.co/8A6KSosJLJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GoBackModi #modi_job_do   Keep tweeting. We are trending at no.1 in the country. Let's make it no.1 worldwide. https://t.co/YfhFC9LVEQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Let's make history together by reaching 10 M tweets. https://t.co/0Y0OWdIsBA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Our legitimate Demands:   1Fair exam process 2Timely examination 3Timely results 4Timely postings 5Transparency  #modi_job_do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  Kudos to our revolutionary heroes. We are ruling over Twitter. It's Time to create history. https://t.co/1Ir2SOMdmc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_job_do  India has highest number of unemployed people in the world. #modi_job_do https://t.co/smjOC8YByh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NarendraModiStadium               ..                 |  #motera  #NarendraMod https://t.co/195jHezicE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NarendraModiStadium                 ..                   !  #motera  #NarendraModiCricketStadium https://t.co/rj2kkXCVDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep tweeting and  Use below hashtags in all your tweets. #cgl19marks #modi_rojgaar_ https://t.co/RPwpM1JPqF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SSC Head Office :   3 millions tweets ho gaye   Meanwhile SSC Chairman :   Normalised tweet count batao. #cgl19marks #modi_rojgaar_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#modi_rojgaar_ #cgl19marks  Youths have power to to bring any change in country. Don't force them to change your government. https://t.co/ykLKUlJjbu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[      l #cgl19marks Seedhi baat. No bakwaas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks Kudos to our revolutionary heroes. We are trending  at no.1 with 3 M tweets. https://t.co/1d6Hg9u8yq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks Kudos to our revolutionary heroes. We are trending  at no.1 with 2 M tweets. https://t.co/RxInxTZKu6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks  #modirojgardo https://t.co/xhtr01Pso2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks  Our Demands:  1Timely examination 2Timely results 3Timely postings 4 Recruit new vacancies 5Reforms in recruitment process 6Increasing vacancy 7Waiting list in ssc 8Sscgd joining   #modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/vEEkzaX27D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks   2018 - 850 Days CHSL 2018 - 546 Days MTS 2019 - 498 Days CGL 2019 - more than 400 Days CGL 2017 - 1,203 Days (Joining pending for many aspirants) What is common b/w these exams?  NONE OF THEM HAS BEEN COMPLETED. Who is RESPONSIBLE? #modi_rojgar_do   #cgl19mark]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks  Dear Honble PM @narendramodi ji, Listen to the voice of the students and youths of the country.  #cgl19marks #Modi_rojgar_do https://t.co/KixG1uWKpj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks  Neta ji : " Give me Blood, I shall Give you Freedom. "   Jumla Maharaj : "Give me Vote, I shall give you Unemployment" . https://t.co/QzErarAZYU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cgl19marks  Our legitimate demands : https://t.co/offTCky3UK]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>