<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/c1Q2wHtQcJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona Because I thought I wouldn't need to provide them all  you'd look up the rest yourself. https://t.co/Nu6INO5TvX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/WKOyqj1TEz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/c6yVLun8uB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona How many people actually know that as of 1986 not 1 vaccine manufacturer is liable for vaccine injury or death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona By believing everything and not researching on his own.  As everyone should when it comes to any medical procedure including shots.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @Buscusriot @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona All of them.  Testing Trials don't end until 2023.   https://t.co/kN4OB328f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@woahhsantiago @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/4tB2dDW4XP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot Caused by the shot.  It's listed as a possible adverse reaction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot @Bitflight_ @JayLite9 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona You truly are an indoctrinated sheep.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AiringGrievence @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona Bye bot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AiringGrievence @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/tSl0rw6Ij0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AiringGrievence @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/8dm0HsXCKe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot https://t.co/twPDudbD8y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @JayLite9 @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona Pfizer testing ends in 2023 https://t.co/kN4OB328f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot Because I'm not.  I don't know anyone who had it or died from it.  So if I'm not around sick people how would I get it?  Magic??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot FDA  CDC websites aren't reliable sources??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot https://t.co/eZ2wpvTbh7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot So if you have a heart attack  tested positive for covid 35 days prior it's a covid death?  But it's an underlying medical condition if dying 48hrs of receiving a covid shot?  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TP4myBunghol @OrionWinning @justinbaragona @Acyn Cases don't equal deaths. https://t.co/gH1cOqe9pQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot Tell her kid she didn't die from an adverse reaction to the covid shots.   https://t.co/F1tZXK0zBR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot Is that all you can say??  Obviously you're the broken one.  No, I just don't trust Bill Gates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AiringGrievence @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona https://t.co/5SJ3rr7hFq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AiringGrievence @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona None.  Because ultimately it's still a personal choice.  I'm just providing information from the CDC and FDA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot So someone can die of a heart attack and be listed as a covid death because 45 days prior he tested "positive" for CoVid. But die with 15 minutes to 48hrs of getting a covid jab  it's not the shot??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot Read the cases.  It's right there on the link.  VAERS reports are  used by the CDC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GrumpyMoe @legalmindedpunk If you left elementary school prior to 1998 it wasn't mandatory.  I didn't need any vaccines to attend elementary, high school or college.   https://t.co/bIYaLksr9o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot Believe flip flop Fauci  Mr depopulation agenda Bill Gates.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot @woahhsantiago @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona Do the reading  research then as I did.  Read the healthcare providers section. https://t.co/aoEvD8u1wR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot https://t.co/5SJ3rr7hFq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona The MMR shots are live vaccines which after getting them you can spread the diseases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona So developing siezures or having a stroke that are completely debilitating so you can't work  need to be unable to care for yourself alone is better?  Ok go for it.  Try reading FDA info on each shot. https://t.co/Y3em7W7i8R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona The testing trials are over.  Vaccines take 5 to 10 years for development  testing.  These have had about 1 year.   https://t.co/kN4OB328f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@woahhsantiago @Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona Obviously you not read anything about these shots  believe everything Fauci, Bill Gates, CDC  WHO tell you. https://t.co/VHaEIjCoNl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OrionWinning @justinbaragona @Acyn Herd immunity is not achieved by vaccinations alone. Natural immunity also plays a pert in it too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1tweet4mamkind @AbeSleeps @OrionWinning @justinbaragona @Acyn They only have emergency use approval from the FDA this still experimental.  mRNA shots have never been used on humans before.  Testing trials don't end until 2023.    https://t.co/rZsfV7dr7V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CathyHeinz1 @mike574 @justinbaragona @Acyn Kids are getting sick from covid.  They don't need the shots.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CathyHeinz1 @mike574 @justinbaragona @Acyn It did happen.   https://t.co/jOobl15xlC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Averre13 @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona Testing trials don't end until 2023.  Since all manufacturers only have EUA from the FDA they're still experimental.  mRNA had never been used on humans before.  It's not conspiracy or propaganda.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buscusriot @mysteriouxTruth @justinbaragona It's considered experimental because all shots available only have EUA from the FDA.  Testing trials don't end until 2023.  Long term side effects aren't known.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanDicksPFT @surveyorX It will hurt football, baseball  hockey for sure between NY  Toronto]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@weathersite @DanDicksPFT They do it now.  They drive from the Toronto area and fly out of Buffalo, NY.   Right now they do it to avoid the mandatory quarantine upon arrival from an intl destination.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VeryBoredMan19 @LisaRago2 @Leonidjrbugriye @littlejackie66 @kayleighmcenany Deaf drivers have special equipment in their vehicles to alert them for different things.  Just like in their homes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Leonidjrbugriye @littlejackie66 @kayleighmcenany I had neighbors who were deaf and drove without any issues.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcdoctorus @littlejackie66 @kayleighmcenany That's discrimination.  Why on earth can't someone be 73 and drive themselves around?  My grandmother drove until she was 90  never had an accident or problem.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShahzadFaisalMD @ppglane I take B12.  I'm a type 2 diabetic  need to take daily.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ppglane @ShahzadFaisalMD Been n it since it came on the market.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VoltarenGel I have RA, a trigger finger and it doesn't help at all.  2x a day  at bedtime for a month.  No relief whatsoever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slimmer79 @catturd2 @tatereeves Mine isn't much better @NYGovCuomo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYSLabor I need my money!! https://t.co/k1Ghj51jae]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYSLabor I've not had a pymt since 3/21.  I completed my DocuSign on 3/18.  I was told my funds should be released by 4/19.  What is going on???  I can't get through by calling. I need to pay bills!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ashrendar82 @joebud123 @catturd2 Doesn't matter, he's not funny.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joebud123 @Ashrendar82 @catturd2 I don't like him either.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@islandjake5 @citizen_working @catturd2 I never liked him either.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AprilWaltons @naomirwolf She needs to report it. Doctors wont do it.  Here is information about reporting an adverse reaction (link to VAERS is in the CHD article):  ICAN reporting system:  https://t.co/RK3aIgi0rx  CHD article on how to report a vaccine reaction:  https://t.co/7ctSFLo2zo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulS62727027 @LoveyPuffyPants @nypost My grandmother had dementia  lived in a facility.  Never had codes to go in or out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AstroPhoenix9 @jackmurphylive @Cernovich It's odd how I'm blocked by people I may have followed but after the big twitter purge I'm blocked by so many I never followed or interacted with.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jackmurphylive Hmmm, don't know why all the sudden I'm blocked by @cernovich.  Don't even remember ever interacting with him. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoveyPuffyPants @PaulS62727027 @nypost I wasn't talking about the article.  The reply was about the person working in a assisted living facility.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulS62727027 @nypost Why are they being held against their will?? Forced incarceration?  If they are of sound mind  body they should be able to come  go as they please.  Not locked in the building.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CelesteZona @Angelaisawake Because they don't believe they're part of the testing trials.  They believe 3 clinical trials is what was needed  nothing more.  They also believe EUA is full official FDA approval.  They look at any other information as false  conspiracy theory.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @Danny_Funaro @GoWokeGoBroke4 @apoorva_nyc https://t.co/HesCZt3xgC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @Danny_Funaro @GoWokeGoBroke4 @apoorva_nyc He used faulty models to predict cases/deaths.  He's been wrong about everything.  Even The WHO stated if you aren't sick or taking care of a sick person masks aren't needed.  He advised 2 masks based on what science?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshMandelOhio @Dannoacton I'd rather go to a bathroom without vaccinated people.  There's so many  unvaccinated people having reactions being around vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @GoWokeGoBroke4 @Danny_Funaro @apoorva_nyc https://t.co/WIVQH2GgDW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @GoWokeGoBroke4 @Danny_Funaro @apoorva_nyc https://t.co/e5JTCpMrX4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @GoWokeGoBroke4 @Danny_Funaro @apoorva_nyc Flip flop Fauci https://t.co/bpFxdpuEcV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @GoWokeGoBroke4 @Danny_Funaro @apoorva_nyc I don't remember him ever stating anything about the faulty models used to predict cases/deaths a year ago.  He can't even make up his mind about masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@az_michelle_w @apoorva_nyc @Danny_Funaro Fauci changed his mind on a whim.  No masks, masks.  He  Birx based what they told us on faulty models.  They still don't know what's going on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The case numbers have been fraudulent since the very beginning.  We've been lied to for over a year!!  Wake up people!!! https://t.co/iF8jypxF0M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BioWhiteFemale @MarkJam92731126 @DailyCaller Though we typically think of dandelions as flowers, the plant is a perennial herb and is one of the oldest herbs used for food and healing  since before Roman times! Every part of a dandelion is edible, from root to flower.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dotsandloops21 @keltnerny @WGRZ What's he have to do with pandemics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dotsandloops21 @TylerPopiela @WGRZ Herd immunity is not achieved by vaccinations alone.  There's people who medically can't get these shots. https://t.co/KJYe4cSCeL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dotsandloops21 @keltnerny @WGRZ Did you forget the H1N1 pandemic in 2009??  HIV/AIDS PANDEMIC (AT ITS PEAK, 2005-2012) Death Toll: 36 million Cause: HIV/AIDS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notliamnorman @DankDllngr @lemon_swizzle @benshapiro 1 billion have gotten the jab??? If you honestly think there's not been deadly reactions you're living in a dream world. https://t.co/tsnSuoFIZP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notliamnorman @2OurHealth @lemon_swizzle @benshapiro Obviously you haven't read the adverse reactions people are having.  https://t.co/5SJ3rr7hFq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notliamnorman @lemon_swizzle @benshapiro They're experimental until officially approved by the FDA.  All 4 manufacturers have emergency use approval from the FDA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianBnew @ZoePrecious2020 Just because you won't get an experimental shot that only has EUA, you're still considered anti vaxx by those who can't wait to get it.  Doesn't matter to them that you've gotten every other vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KOMBUCHABABY @MarcDClair Perfect response!! https://t.co/WoKcsQbvOO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShirlAAdams @BeauJeffrey @ZeroWarningShot @Jrobskc @adamsbeerblog @SKYRIDER4538 @DrDenaGrayson @realDonaldTrump @RudyGiuliani The people who died from taking Chloroquine took a fish tank cleaner not the malaria/rheumatoid arthritis drug.  #FactsMatter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thedreadedaw @kathies01 @HHSGov https://t.co/kN4OB328f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GM_1966 @MinistryBackup8 My friend who is 28yrs old told me the only reason he got the Moderna jab is so he can go to concerts, car races  travel freely this summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WKBW Pricing is way to high to go to local bar band concerts in an empty field.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WKBW You better reread your article. https://t.co/2PWOFGAv4t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@feduplesbian To me it's the same darn thing.  Shedding is just used more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@barkeaterchief @news4buffalo #1same couple as previous pic.  #2 is another I saw posted on IG. https://t.co/CXwbM7Ok8J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@barkeaterchief @news4buffalo No, California.  Hiking while wearing a mask, gloves  a plastic hamper. It's sad but this is how crazy the covid brain washed think.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@feduplesbian It the covid shots shedding.  mRNA shots have never been used on humans  animals died in past testing when they tried mRNA for H1N1.  There's lots of stories of women who are having menstrual cycle problems because coworkers got the jab when they didn't.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPoertsch @Alec_Zeck Hopefully she'll get medical help and report to VAERS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@news4buffalo If you're alone or with just family outside why are they wearing a mask.   Too look like these fools??? https://t.co/hWmvJKboVT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pierrelemoine88 https://t.co/WgR2sKmpT3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brookspw @mercola @advisorrob To protect the unvaccinated from those shedding the covid vaxx.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@news4buffalo https://t.co/cbijNF7HoL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aware_the: #MissingPerson #JoshuaGibson #Towson #Maryland @WMAR2News @wbaltv11 @FOXBaltimore @wusa9 @nbcwashington @WTOP @AngelineDC @M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DarlaShine They must have gone to Inverness to go through the stones from Outlander.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@je_corey @ACTforAmerica @PressSec Let me circle back to you on that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeorgeRichert4 @news4buffalo And??? If there's a loophole  they found it good for them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SilenceNotGold: Corona Scandal - The Biggest Crime Against Humanity Ever Committed...https://t.co/HyRYyLOhFU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EKatholik:  Truck driver believes mysterious event being planned for NYC - video https://t.co/d2dYE9AsCR ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>