<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pickover: This is a form of mathematics humor. https://t.co/14RGUslgeb https://t.co/o3OwFrNC4u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TitanTOC Remember when CIA was essentially Ivy League (frat) guys? Is it less effective now because of the presence of women, immigrants, and people with a wider range of backgrounds? Would we have gotten UBL without Alec Stationwhich was almost entirely staffed by women?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ManilanH Wowza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@page88 And the leaves, flowers and roots are all edible and generally healthy. Jacques Pepin says that he makes dandelion salads at least 2-3 per year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeamusHughes: With no caveats to their assessment, the U.S. Intelligence Community says al-Zawahiri is alive.  During the past year, c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HowardMortman: No WHCA Dinner this year.  Instead: #THISDATE in WHCA Dinner History.  Today's installment: April 30, 2011.  Barack Obam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexplitsas AAW!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GPatrick Sounds as though you, like I, married up quite a bit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheDailyShow: "America can't be racist because it elected two Black people who half the country hates for reasons they can't quite put]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hockeyaunt5: This should of never happened, you should be here right now, my heart is forever broken! I Love  Miss You soooo much Dad!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Systemic racism is totally not a thing.  https://t.co/wuUb9Gh0SI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @7thForces: Today we remember, SFC Allen C. Johnson, 31, was a Special Forces medical sergeant assigned to 1st Battalion, 7th Special Fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RubenGallego: My god this man used to be an elected official...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pickover: Mathematics and mystery.   Shiver in ecstasy. A triangle with sides pi (3.14), e (2.71), and the Golden Ratio (1.61) is almos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: They warned me, if I voted for Biden, wed all be drinking plant-based beer. https://t.co/mC4A0oNgXX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AccountableGOP: The inside story of Trumps bleach injection press conference! https://t.co/T1Dg09Jn97]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MikeMooreDO: Burn it down Harold. Burn it all down. https://t.co/PWJWx8j4I3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NWHL: The NWHL Awards presented by @Discover are next Wednesday the 28th on https://t.co/EHkD9gflXv  Here are your MVP finalists  http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBostonPride: Our thoughts and prayers are with the family and friends of William Hickey and Joe Birolini, and the entire Pembroke co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CSenco The end of that sentence should read, ensuring 100% blue on blue engagement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eric_clapp Yes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkHertling: No US politician would dare openly counter the actions of soldiers in combat. Thats unpatriotic.  Yet several are acti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@ole_b_peters #ergodicity has implications for organizational decision-making as well. https://t.co/neAWwOMxsu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@agileschools @MarkGraban This is a great example of deeper problems in microeconomics. The ergodicity revolution in econ is long overdue. #ergodicity #ergodicityeconomics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikejason73: We have a moral obligation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkGraban: Dueling predictions from one year ago today https://t.co/9zSubIml9o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EfosaOjomo: Its really going to be difficult for low- and middle-income economies to prosper without innovators like @Rockson2 at @mPh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soonergrunt: I don't think I've ever seen a more beautiful confederate memorial in my life. @pptsapper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanPriceSeattle: If you're upset that someone might make $15 an hour, wait til you hear that the median CEO makes $10,240 an hour even]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These people have no shame. https://t.co/OsLjkfhNLL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRickyDavila: Where was the outrage when MAGA lawyer Lin Wood called out for the murder by hanging of Cyber Security Chief in 2020 fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I mean, they totally signed his yearbook and everything. https://t.co/WIBw9Suswj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ambermruffin: After a heartbreaking week in America, we have a new segment of How Did We Get Here on The #AmberRuffinShow tonight. http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: For the 3 phases of a country's pandemic performance, containment (eradication), vaccination, and helping other countries, n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AriBerman: 147 mass shootings in US already this year: let's make it easier to buy guns  2 cases of voter fraud in 2020: let's make it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PR_NHL: Tuukka Rask made 22 saves to record his 300th win in his 552nd career game and became the first goaltender in @NHLBruins histor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karlyparcell Didnt Jesus say, When I was homeless, you knocked down my shelter and built a huge-ass apartment complex?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boo! https://t.co/moOXXPeYMK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PanelSgm1 Im all in on Bragg -&gt; Benavides]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@garlic_gorl you have some work to do. https://t.co/dBCHJwTl3w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Arkansas Gov. Asa Hutchinson: "Are we going to be a narrow party that expresses ourselves in intolerant ways, or are we going]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zellieimani: And there it is.. https://t.co/ZHeiNskq0n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atrupar Also, voting is not a privilege; its a right.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MikePerryavatar Well, Im seeing red. wtaf.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DxMba: Anomalies drive scientific progress. https://t.co/rvoBXPHPbY https://t.co/j4HyIXW2TN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gee. Who couldve predicted this?  Oh. Yeah. Every last one of us. https://t.co/CE4N92tZo1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My son just asked: if horcruxes are parts of souls and dementors eat souls, wouldnt horcruxes be just like Scooby snacks?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In fact, just the opposite: high unemployment benefits led to slightly higher employment levels. https://t.co/5x9aWUskx1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NPR: A new working paper suggests that higher unemployment benefits in the pandemic do not seem to affect employment levels the way man]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HopeSeck: Meet Captain StarEagle: Space Force Swears In 1st Female Native American Intel Officer https://t.co/SnIrTN3HQO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These people have no sense of irony. https://t.co/75sue6Rd1O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BriannaWu: Thread: The story of how @mattgaetz became a target of the Trump justice department is even crazier and weirder than you can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KayeSteinsapir Sending love.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theserfstv: On Sarah Palin advocating for mask use https://t.co/wuaZYExS8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Acyn Its unreal to me that a governor doesnt know the meaning of the word infrastructure. https://t.co/jKYKHGIvGE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CallsignBarbie Prayings not my thing. And Im a dude. But I want you to know that youre in my thoughts. You deserve better than the position youve been repeatedly put in by the far-too-common a-holes of my gender.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Acyn: Apparently Mitch McConnell told President Biden that his package is too big https://t.co/eNIBIcTrRH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JFC. Why are people still doing this? https://t.co/oanGAoWxc3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarasidnerCNN As the adoptive father of a Haitian-American son, when he cried out for his mother, it broke me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LethalityJane: All it took was the NYS legislature making marijuana legal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MonicaLewinsky Not a dumb tweet. You deserve better.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CutlerRidgeLAZ Youre in our thoughts. We have had a few miscarriages and even late-stage fetal demises. Its such a difficult thing. And its often an incredibly lonely experience. Youre not alone. We are with you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WarInstitute: "The Chinese employ operators to attack us each and every day, both cognitively and technically. I think to get more offe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tell me that policing isnt structurally more damaging to Black people again. Try me.  https://t.co/ETyuChBtLC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Angry_Staffer: GOP: I will control the uterus of every female   GOP: voter ID is not only constitutional, it should be a requirement in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NWHL: "Dont cry its just a movie"  The movie: https://t.co/ruD6XveYJV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WalshFreedom: I don't care what was in his system. I don't care if he was drunk. I don't care if he was high. I don't care if he was an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More good news. https://t.co/XH7SJTL26p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cmclymer In our house there is the US National Team and the Mens Team.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Well_Regulated_: A member of our well regulated militia gets out of his vehicle in a movie theater parking lot with a loaded gun in his]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danielmkim: Please be kind, remember to spay  neuter your Confederates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NWHL: As we reflect on this weekend, we want to extend a heartfelt thank you to @Discover. The moment we suspended the season, they wer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthyWomen: COVID-19 left 38-year-old Delia Ramos a young #widow. Now shes on a quest to honor her husband by sharing his story and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaskiaPopescu: *pre-print*  Wastewater monitoring outperforms case numbers as a tool to track COVID-19 incidence dynamics when test pos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sapinker: Unlike many media-ginned crises, the death toll from opioid overdoses is high. But demonizing docs  pharma gets the causatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is (unsurprisingly) despicable. https://t.co/q0CKoGAC8S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@FarshadNayeri  https://t.co/MoaQzmTwQW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A few bad apples, you say? https://t.co/wz8FESHw2j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @D0MXNXQUE: I asked my child if he saw the Lil Nas X video. He said "Yeah. Man. He ain't shy at all" LMAO. I said "They gonna be saying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NolanDMcCaskill: Sign of the day: https://t.co/cErs5TCJya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NWHL: SAY CHEESE  https://t.co/AEOJGP49Pb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffMarek: Congrats to Isobel Cup champions @TheBostonPride. Great win against @WhitecapsHockey.   And congrats to the @NWHL for comple]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Sen. Bernie Sanders: "If we collected just a third, one-third of the unpaid taxes of the very rich we could... make public col]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndyKimNJ: My 5 yr old boy came home and asked me why bigger kid kept calling him Chinese Boy. My son, confused, told the boy Im a New]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarlyPildis Wowza! Im a one-trick pony with my briskets. Any chance youll share the recipe?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@starkvillain Moderate headache, felt sort of run down for ~36 hrs. Then ready to go.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASlavitt: If you cant beat a virus, just stop testing.  If you cant win an election, just stop people from voting.  THAT is cancel cu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RookieCityCop: Every time a politician talks gun control, a whole bunch of cops and Sheriffs get up in arms and say they won't enforce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look, I get that this is kookoo bananas. But Sen. Hyde-Smith and her ilk are not talking to *us*though its a bonus when their nonsense irks us. Shes speaking to the people who already agree with her to reassure them shell uphold bigoted policies c.  https://t.co/LEO8XUjohf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: New York City council ends qualified immunity for NYPD officers https://t.co/iNK73QCqq9 https://t.co/Oo5VOGAmQc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thienan496: Moire pattern generated by an eigenfunction of the Laplacian on the unit-square #laplacian #math #Python https://t.co/H6hDS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FordJohnathan5 @LouiseMensch A stumble doesnt make your story less inspirational. Get after it tomorrow. And the next day and the next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#accidentallyLeftWing https://t.co/n6YCbSXBnj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@garlic_gorl Peggy https://t.co/lJXiTJrDSs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LethalityJane If everyone gets to have their hands in their pockets, how would someone know who the cool kids are?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danacan254: @ThomasRogers77 @ProjectLincoln I need this one! https://t.co/X9wjMDiTzM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mpolymer Hes one of those politicians who would kit up to visit a conflict zone.   And blouse his pants.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: Here's the very good news for the day: "A single immunization boosted neutralizing titers against all variants and SARS-CoV-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atrupar: Hannity on Wednesday: Biden is lost, dazed, and confused  Hannity on Thursday: Biden is overprepared https://t.co/5UucFxwZrm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Well_Regulated_: A member of our well regulated militia shoots himself in the head while playing with a loaded handgun. https://t.co/r2]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>