<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: The more important question for worker safety is Where is #OSHA?  The OSHA Emergency Temporary Standard is now 7 weeks overdue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GWpublichealth: Enrollment for the 2021 GWSPH Summer Institute is now open! The Summer Institute offers one-credit graduate public heal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DerrickZJackson: Derrick Z. Jackson: Bidens new moonshot -- An offshore wind industry to rival Europes https://t.co/jmyZRnzsX2 via @V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordan Barab has been an incomparable, invaluable leader in the fight for safe workplaces.   There are undoubtedly many workers who have not suffered a work injury or illness because of @jbarab's relentless advocacy.   A huge round of thanks to Jordan Barab! https://t.co/11gWSrZgD7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @profsheena: Read this insightful and cogent discussion by the wise @drdavidmichaels who-as the longest serving @osha leader in history-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@covid19_alex @OSHA_DOL I am so sorry to hear that. It must have been very painful for your whole family.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a significant victory for public health - particularly for the health of the children of farmworkers, exposed because they live near fields where #chlorpyrifos is used.    Thank you @NRDC! https://t.co/w1gBE2w5pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3M-5M workers seriously injured  1000s sickened yearly. Much needs to be done to stop jobs from hurting or killing workers.   Read the more in-depth exploration on restructuring  re-imagining @OSHA_DOL by @jbarab and me, published in @AMJPublicHealth.  https://t.co/o3FIt5dFZ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nmeyersohn: Long history of OSHA violations at Dollar Tree stores. Former OSHA director @drdavidmichaels has said many of the company's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is no one more capable of restoring and strengthening @USDOL's Wage  Hour Division than @profsheena - the nation's expert on how fissuring has hurt the wages, job security, pensions  safety of US workers. https://t.co/tkv1x1cDW0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OSHA is 50 years old today. The agency has prevented countless deaths and injuries, but too many workers are being hurt everyday.   The COVID crisis demonstrates that @OSHA_DOL badly needs to be updated and strengthened.  Here's a start: https://t.co/55qdSXeHxX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic is the most pressing worker safety crisis OSHA has ever faced.    There has never been a hazard more deserving than of an emergency standard. @JimGMorris @publicintegrity  https://t.co/0t5ZVERMwq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is Workers Memorial Day.    Take a few minutes to read this powerful inquiry by @amymaxmen into how social determinants -race, poverty, job, immigration status - are driving COVID transmission and great hardship among California farmworkers.      https://t.co/lByZwBZoCS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kathleen_rest: Today is #WorkerMemorialDay. Take a moment to reflect on the sacrifices of our nations fallen workers. Commit to stand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rweingarten: Tomorrow is the 50th anniversary of OSHA. Our goal is the same, people deserve safe workplaces. https://t.co/Iu99CipDLd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The nation is fortunate that @ChrisLu44 is joining our delegation to the United Nations. Chris is a dedicated, principled civil servant, committed to improving the lives of all people, here and abroad. https://t.co/sjz3WwXQX9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Latest from our Lancet Task Force.  Pandemic relief for schools must be applied to enhancements that are evidence-based, pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Orla_Hegarty: *NEW* #COVID19 #Schools Designing infectious disease resilience into school buildings through improvements to ventilation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimothyNoah1: Todays lead story in the NYT about out-of-control Covid spread among working-age folk in Michigan demonstrates why OSHA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: https://t.co/sAG7xZy51v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DebbieBerkowitz: Black and brown workers are at greatest risk. There is a step Biden Can Taken to Help Workers, and He Hasnt Done it @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Workplaces remain a center of COVID transmission: majority of new outbreaks in Michigan are in workplaces.   Vaccinations are helping, but dangerous exposures are nowhere near under control.  Badly needed now: an #OSHA Emergency COVID Standard @EyalPress  https://t.co/93FxIfIdtm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: One notable change that Biden has not made from Trump's anti-worker policies: issuing an #OSHA COVID-19 standard to protect wor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: The hearing that shouldn't have to happen.   House Democrats summon Department of Labor to explain why they haven't issued an #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I could not agree more! @rdnayak is absolutely a great choice to head policy @USDOL. https://t.co/am5tWaIdvo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very good news! https://t.co/wP5cgASLzr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toddntucker: Another amazing pick!!  SEC Chief Gary Gensler Picks Top Labor Union Official for Policy Role: Heather Slavkin Corzos app]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hazardseditor: Work-related deaths and diseases should not be the acceptable cost of production. Infections should not come with the jo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thackerpd: Great fun interviewing @ElleEnvy for @DisInfoChron on #EDCs  #disinformation   A candid conversation with environmental hea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Don_Milton: @drdavidmichaels @jbarab @CathNoakes That study (https://t.co/egrGqktKPW) has not gotten the attention it deserves -- burie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Proud to have testified at the @EdLaborCmte in support of this bill, requiring OSHA to issue a workplace violence standard protecting healthcare workers. Here's my statement: https://t.co/oCWMUP4BVV https://t.co/arS4W3X9zI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One reason to thank Donald Trump:  He so damaged our weak system of public health protections that it needs to be rebuilt.  This is our opportunity to learn from past mistakes and not just rebuild it but re-imagine  restructure it, stronger than before. https://t.co/fjA6KhHGxa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JudahWorldChamp @UMDPublicHealth @GWpublichealth @Don_Milton My keynote "Rebuilding and Reimagining Our Public Health Infrastructure" has now been posted.  My premise: We shouldn't return to the weak pre-Trump pre-COVID regulatory system.    Let's learn from our mistakes and Build Back Better. https://t.co/fjA6KhHGxa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marionnestle: Weekend reading: Safety First forRestaurants https://t.co/xUsMBZcX2Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks, @Don_Milton. Your long efforts are bearing fruit.  In the 2009-10 H1N1 pandemic, OSHA tried to use your evidence that influenza virus was airborne to increase protections for healthcare workers.  CDC and the infectious disease professional societies pushed back very hard. https://t.co/FyPXELWmhw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow! Looking forward to @NaomiOreskes' new book The Cost of Scientific Patronage which, according @DrSerpentine's rave @ScienceMagazine review "should give pause to all scientists who consider themselves immune to the potential influence of their funders"  https://t.co/v1gITE97hO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nathan McCray is a public health star! https://t.co/s5wh8G7i4k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimothyNoah1: Even as Biden lectures governors that vaccinations alone wont end the Covid crisiscases have gone up 4 straight weeksh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NELPaction: Is Biden Ditching His Promise to Protect Workers From Covid-19?  "In Michigan, according to Debbie Berkowitz, worker safety]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see #OSHA being allowed to protect workers. A $136K fine to an employer who prohibited masks sends a strong message to all employers that workers must be safe at work.  But where is the Emergency Temporary Standard? @jamieson @HuffPost  https://t.co/Jd3Ik5XA0Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are whisperings the White House may ditch #OSHA's Emergency COVID Standard.  The OSHA law is clear: workers have the right to be safe at work.  To protect them and slow the surging pandemic, the nation needs the OSHA ETS. @TimothyNoah1 @newrepublic  https://t.co/VtxDcOLt9m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please share. https://t.co/jB9U9AGuaj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jamieson: OSHA just issued a $136K fine against a Massachusetts tax preparer for requiring employees to work without masks. This is jus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Post Trump, just rebuilding our damaged regulatory system is inadequate to address the many public health crises we face.   We need to learn from our past mistakes to reimagine  restructure our systems of public health protection.  @UofMaryland @UMBaltimore https://t.co/YTc5nxt4V4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Don_Milton: Dont miss this talk by former and longest serving Dir OSHA and author of Triumph of Doubt on what we need to do fix how]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kprather88: More impacts due to HCW exposure to SARS-CoV-2 (due to inadequate PPE to protect against airborne tranmission)-higher fract]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are now 4 weeks past Pres. Biden's deadline for @OSHA_DOL  to issue an Emergency Temporary Standard.   An #OSHA ETS is badly needed to help ensure cases in the rest of the country don't follow Michigan's dangerous surge. https://t.co/qw69iBm1BT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UMDPublicHealth: Join us to reimagine our public health system on Tuesday, 4/13! Keynote by @drdavidmichaels will discuss how our count]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jstakala: Health workers' Corona risk is equal to other workers in Finland...the  workplace was the source of infection in 30 % of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaskiaPopescu @CalHospitals Or last month, @ahahospitals minimizing aerosol transmission in response to testimony at a @EdLaborCmte hearing where @linseymarr, a nurse from @NationalNurses and me called for an #OSHA standard to protect virus-exposed workers.  https://t.co/t9E06ISV8X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaskiaPopescu Since the pandemic start, hospitals have been fighting or minimizing aerosol transmission.  From @CalHospitals last March: "We need the CDC to clearly, not conditionally, move from airborne to droplet precautions for patients and health care workers." 1/ https://t.co/LEOI3nD2gp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At some point, we'll look back on this period and wonder how any reputable scientist could reject the idea of aerosol transmission of SARS-Cov-2.    In fact, that moment is now. https://t.co/JyQWFTLySx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont miss this thread. https://t.co/8V8Gw9SllP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Thanks, Hector! https://t.co/PHej8fwMmN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5ZSjR7BilW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: Lesson Learned from the last year:  Today would be a good day to issue #OSHA's COVID-19 Emergency Temporary Standard.  https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CDC has also updated it's guidance, noting that the supply and availability of NIOSH-approved respirators have increased significantly over the last several months. 2/ https://t.co/6cang3Bw0z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doug Parker is a terrific choice to head @OSHA_DOL. He understands workplace safety, cares deeply about the health of the nation's workers  knows how to run an agency-he directs Cal/OSHA, the largest state OSHA plan.     Let's get him confirmed quickly. https://t.co/VPRvwwF3fc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No more excuses and no more decontamination-new respirators for health care workers!  #FDA asserts there is NO respirator shortage.  Hospitals and nursing homes should provide all potentially exposed workers with new respirators. @NationalNurses @AFTunion  https://t.co/LcEArbZR2g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RichardDenison: 6/ Workers got hit particularly hard by Trump EPA policy: Of 425 approved new chemicals, EPA found worker risks for nea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: The CDC director is pleading with the country to take precautions, but workers can't take those precautions without an [#OSHA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZekeEmanuel: With infections  hospitalizations on the rise, COVID-19 deaths will again increase if we do not act quickly. Delaying the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As former head of @OSHA_DOL, it is VERY clear:  &gt;70K new cases every day rates rising among working age people no mask mandates in many states poor ventilation in many workplaces  This pandemic is far from over.  Workers desperately need an OSHA Emergency Standard. #WhereisOSHA? https://t.co/0DRYv4CqHK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abwhite7: NEWS: @UFCW in new federal @OSHA_DOL complaint highlights 1,000 #COVID worker infections as safety failures at #Oklahoma meat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UMDPublicHealth: Were honored to have @drdavidmichaels deliver the keynote address for our eighth annual Public Health Research at Mar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RebeccaARainey: After spending the last 48 hours digging into the status of OSHAs emergency coronavirus rules, the Biden administratio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We learned early in the pandemic-delay is the coronavirus' best friend. The longer we wait to implement precautions, the more people will get sick and the harder it will be to stop this pandemic  and get back to normal. @SecMartyWalsh #WhereisOsha? https://t.co/OWu8LRtGoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PHScientist: #COVID19 continue to highlight contemporary western colonial mores. We must move past dehistoricized  depoliticized view]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: A new wave of Covid cases has hit the United States. Workers will be most at risk. So where is #OSHAs COVID-19 Emergency Tempo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: The #OSHA COVID-19 Emergency Temporary Standard is now 3 weeks late. How many workers have contracted preventable infections ov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: Hey, maybe an #OSHA COVID-19 Emergency Temporary Standard would be a good idea. (Like the one that was supposed to be issued 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AEAPresident: TYSM. I bet youre aware that we also have a specific industry ask for additional reopening funding. HVAC upgrades, testi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @akapczynski: Essential reading. https://t.co/gpXNpBxdPP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["With present and future threats to workplace safety looming, the Biden administration cannot afford to ignore OSHAs lack of resources for even a moment longer." -Henry Burke @revolvingdoorDC @jeffhauser  https://t.co/dMAyjQKuHD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HospitalNurses: @LVHN Union busting proposals:  - Forced Overtime. - No Safe Staffing   - Move nurses from unit to unit for any reaso]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Keith_Smith: "As Chair of the National Association of Manufacturers, I ask my fellow manufacturing and other business leaders to take a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SusanAnenberg: My 1st paper in @EHPonline estimated air pollution disease burdens globally at ~200km resolution. Our paper yesterday di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, prioritize college students but only after states make extra efforts to vaccinate older people, essential workers  others at increased risk of death.  Students are able to mask, distance  wait-and that's what they should do. @franciediep @chronicle https://t.co/VD1QDdkRWp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonahFurman @theintercept The policy of federal OSHA  many state plans under Trump was to respond to worker complaints with phone calls  no follow-up or verification. There are 100s of cases where there were COVID outbreaks following worker complaints to OSHA.   Federal OSHA is changing this now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Without an #OSHA Emergency Standard, CDC COVID guidelines are not enforceable.    This incident at a vaccine production facility represents a second failure: Indiana OSHA not even launching an inspecting following a valid worker complaint. @JonahFurman @theintercept https://t.co/zw6qTTOCb3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do we need to slow the 4th wave, save lives  safely reopen the economy while we try to vaccinate the country?  An #OSHA Emergency Temporary Standard, requiring employers to prevent virus exposure in all workplaces.   This will include the badly needed national mask mandate. https://t.co/yjiqtJvsOV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good to see the discussion shift from "if aerosols transmit COVID" to "how to control indoor aerosol  exposures"  Now if @CDCgov  @WHO move into the modern era  join the discussion, we'd have a better shot at slowing this thing down. @dyanilewis @nature https://t.co/0w3dfsDNYz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Masks in retail establishments stop COVID transmission. And safer shopping will help the economy.  An #OSHA Emergency Temporary Standard would mandate masks for everyone in the store: workers  customers.   But we are &gt;2 weeks behind schedule. https://t.co/EGHjroAenQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RLReindelHi: An OSHA emergency temporary standard (ETS) would require critical protections that are effective at preventing virus trans]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Requiring masks in all workplaces would save many lives.  The single most effective action the Biden Administration could take to advance the mask mandate is to issue an @OSHA_DOL Emergency Temporary Standard. But we are already 2 weeks behind schedule. https://t.co/bYytNXNSc4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfBlackistone: Me @postsports on how sport rewarded Georgia in the '60s, making Atlanta a sports mecca, for standing up for voting ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomPerez: I brought Seema on board to handle some of the most complex issues at @TheJusticeDept, @USDOL and as we rebuilt @TheDemocrats]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hamiltonnolan: One of our country's biggest workplace failures of the pandemic is the fact that front line workers were expected to act]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The hits just keep on coming.  @jocelynsamuels is absolutely the right choice to advance the vital mission of the @USEEOC. https://t.co/49tDA1o7Ya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctoral students -- and everyone else -- do not miss this contest. The winning entries are fabulous.    Now is the time to start planning your PhD Dance.  @Sofialmdo  @ScienceMagazine  https://t.co/5LmJTlVcVv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tryptique: Hey @AdvocacySBA do you plan on including any small businesses that are in communities harmed by the highly toxic PFAS forev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeemaNanda is a fabulous choice to be @USDOLs top lawyer! https://t.co/M3mqarnUzQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fastlerner: I learned so many upsetting things when reporting this piece with @stephanehorel I don't know where to begin. but maybe wit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LorenaSGonzalez: Heartbreaking but true. The family of instacart worker who was murdered on the job will not get the workers comp death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbarab: A correctional officer  nurse, both #AFSCME members, were killed yesterday in attack by inmate at Iowa's Anamosa State Peniten]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RWDSU: 'You dont get treated like a person. They work you like a robot' As Amazons profits climb and its market dominance continues]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrPeterLurie: More than a year into the pandemic it's still clear COVID-19 is an occupational illness. New, on my Beyond the Curve blog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @celinegounder: 12/ In the meantime, @NYCHealthSystem and many other health facilities are following the science, and are now REQUIRING]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GWpublichealth colleague Sara Rosenbaum  Daniel Hawkins have written a lovely tribute to Jack Geiger, my mentor.    Among Jack's many legacies is the Community Health Center, which has become the cornerstone of the nation's primary care system.   https://t.co/LHsDQeaP4y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaadOmer3 @HelenBranswell @abuttenheim +1]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>