<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bradytoday: Peer-reviewed  published today in Environmental Research Letters. Huge  to authors J. Buonocore @Parichehr_S @DrewMichano]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bradytoday:  Launch day! New study from @HarvardCCHANGE: burning gas, biomass,  wood now has MORE negative health impacts than coal i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A decade of the U.S. energy mix transitioning away from coal: historical reconstruction of the reductions in the public health burden of energy  Jonathan J Buonocore, @Parichehr_S , @DrewMichanowicz, @j_g_allen  https://t.co/KMZBXxHCY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3. The share of health impacts of energy use in the U.S. from buildings has increased during the last decade. https://t.co/r8nscAMa86]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2. Natural gas and biomass now have higher health impacts than coal in many states https://t.co/YHap4E33Es]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1. massive reduction in health impacts due to retirement of coal-power plants https://t.co/sNNrv8wSWz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A decade of the U.S. energy mix transitioning away from coal  Important new paper from our #HealthyBuildings team in collaboration with our colleagues at @HarvardCCHANGE   3 key takeaways in this short summary  THREAD https://t.co/pRQm3zOwmD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important step for addressing climate. We advocated strongly for this in 2018, but prior admin wasn't much interested in addressing climate change...  https://t.co/RZO4NMejRO https://t.co/fkoEXpkgFw https://t.co/yDvHthtVsT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Time to make the donuts...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jmartNYT: After a Brown prof said families can take kids on trips and see friends and relatives this summer, a reader sent an email to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're teaming up with Harvard India Research Center (@HarvardChanIRC) to support their efforts on providing guidance for how to stay safe.  Proud of my #HealthyBuildings colleagues for all saying 'count me in', even though they are all extraordinarily busy.  More (very) soon...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apoorva_nyc: Awesome explainer on vaccine efficacy -- ostensibly for kids, but efficacy is a tough concept for a lot of people to under]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Study of children (&lt;20) and transmission, using data from Israel. All members of house tested (PCR).  --&gt; susceptibility of children is 43% relative to adults (95% CI: [31%, 55%]) --&gt; infectivity of children 63% relative to adults (95% CI: [37%, 88%])   https://t.co/11LPhGnRLK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: 1. Current ventilation standards are not set for infection control (outside of hospitals) 2. Many orgs have said "bring in m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashishkjha: Another lesson from Israel  As vaccinations went up in adults, infections went down in kids  Because kids are part of socie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apsmunro: Three great new studies of COVID in children this week!  First, household transmission in Germany   Contacts of PCR pos cas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SchoolSMART  S--&gt; Stay home when sick M--&gt; Mask up A--&gt; Air cleaner in classrooms R--&gt; Refersh indoor air T--&gt; Time outdoors https://t.co/V52i39HSCe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The good people at Harvard's Center for Communicable Disease Dynamics @CCDD_HSPH @HarvardChanSPH. Appreciative of their work this year.  @mlipsitch Caroline Buckee @BillHanage @michaelmina_lab @yhgrad @megan_b_murray @MauSantillana + post-docs, doc/masters students, staff https://t.co/rQV6FQmmoj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brownecfm: This is a great piece on basic personal biosecurity on returning to the office. Question your employer on:   1. Ventilation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The kids will be alright.   LANCET --&gt; risk of death for those under 19 is ~1 in a million  Similar conclusion as the JAMA study from December, but this new study also includes data from US, UK, Italy, Germany, Spain, France, S Korea  https://t.co/T8GwEtNcub https://t.co/JIIBnAb2tf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...we need...a natl and global conversation about ethics of our vaccinating kids, who are low risk for serious complications from the virus, when there arent enough vaccines in the world to protect high-risk adults from dying @JenniferNuzzo https://t.co/sf0TxW8BNx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The India Task Force of the Lancet COVID-19 Commission has published a checklist of necessary strategies to deal with the current second wave of the pandemic  https://t.co/ltQnVHbbMT https://t.co/PQALQvx2AD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @syramadad: India's COVID-19 Crisis Is Spiraling Out of Control. It Didn't Have to Be This Way https://t.co/8nkrzlSri5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nataliexdean: The imminent FDA authorization of a vaccine for 12-15 year olds is great news, and adolescents should be able to access v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @By_CJewett: Newark, N.J. schools bought 3,200+ air purifying devices that can emit 10X more ozone than the industrys self-imposed limi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LaurenWeberHP:  Is your child in a classroom with unproven air cleaner technology?   Our investigation found over 2,000 schools acro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important comment here from Dr @SaskiaPopescu for those who have only had to wear a mask for short durations.   Its very different wearing your mask when you go run errands, and then wearing it all day and working in it,  Build in breaks + hydrate  https://t.co/684M2HxcrI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CathNoakes: @j_g_allen @rachgutman @SaskiaPopescu And this doesnt necessarily mean expensive surveys. Even just reviewing how air gets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Question for your boss: "What have you done to review and improve airflow in the office space?"  If the answer is Nothing, or Were meeting code, thats not enough.  Grateful to be in this piece by @rachgutman, w/ Lidia Morawska and @SaskiaPopescu    https://t.co/amYO78iCaE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I can't stop thinking about this. https://t.co/LBo7o09W54]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: Last July, I wrote about airborne transmission. "...on July 9, the W.H.O. changed its position  going from denial to grudg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres what weve been recommending.  &gt; target 4-6 ACH thru any combo of:  1. Outdoor air (as simple as opening windows sometimes...) 2. Better filters on recirc 3. Portable air cleaners w HEPA https://t.co/8HN1Ovo9xX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/LBo7o09W54]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[me, June 2020: "3rd, a disproportionate burden...is falling on women...This widens another gap in our society, as working women risk either dropping out of the workplace or face career advancement challenges that many men, and those without children, wont have."  NYT May 2021: https://t.co/qhLTxngcgQ https://t.co/LpbE6ofeyE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How is the fall even a question at this point? And, if your school is closed NOW you are failing - the guidance is there, the $ is there, the science is there, the vaccines for teachers are there, the damages to kids continue to accrue. https://t.co/37p97PE9Dw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[--&gt; https://t.co/4QuCvFsApI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[--&gt; https://t.co/YCgVMzxgJn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DhruvRaina: @j_g_allen Also, agree 100% that message on airborne transmission is only reaching the middle class now. folks were doing e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DhruvRaina: @j_g_allen In Delhi, people are very scared. Every household seems to have a positive case and folks are seeing their frien]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Situation in India may feel hopeless, but there are things we can do quickly AND cheaply.  &gt; better masks &gt; rapid tests  @AbraarKaran @RanuDhillon @sri_srikrishna lay out how it can work https://t.co/BMnEIg8awF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: Everyone wants this to be done and we all would prefer to pretend its over in vaccinated nations. But not dealing with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VincentRK: The other factor playing a role in India is is viral dose. With crowding and high prevalence, people are at risk of multiple]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talk to any of your friends with family in India and you will hear just how bad it is there. Horrifying.  Also clear the message on airborne spread has not spread widely, even in US.  Why havent we made better masks a priority? 14 months in, still shortages, still no innovation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlecMacGillis My town...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I agree with Dr. @ShellyMBoulders take here. Its a tragedy.  We knew enough to act early. What was the downside to acknowledging airborne transmission?? More air in buildings? Better filters? People wear a mask? https://t.co/CFxehPKAko]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShellyMBoulder: @trahana @linseymarr @jljcolorado @kprather88 @CorsIAQ @j_g_allen @VirusesImmunity just about a year ago a group of int]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see WHO clarify their position on aerosols. Never thought it would take 16 months to get here (by the time I wrote this one at the end of May last year, had already been harping on airborne/ventilation for 4 full months already...) https://t.co/UMkcYtVuYD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CathNoakes: Today seems a good day to highlight the @WHO ventilation roadmap for COVID19. Some good practical info in here for differen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: SO glad to see @WHO update on transmission!  short-range: aerosols containing the virus are inhaled or droplets contact eye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Important study that will very likely show that a frequent testing approach can dramatically shorten the quarantine period for close contacts.  Schools - pay attention to this one. Important today, yes, but will also be hotly debated come September. https://t.co/we9hCUHsYP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: In the tweet I am referring to nations, particularly high income nations just now starting to say oh, we should do so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TX does not require carbon monoxide detectors. Every home should have them. Avoidable tragedies:  -At least 11 deaths have been confirmed -&gt;1,400 people sought care at ERs and urgent care clinics for CO poisoning -children made up 42% of the cases  https://t.co/RumZU8oSHl https://t.co/jvNgZYuV3G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At our recent faculty retreat when asked about investments we should make going forward, I used the work of @johnbrownstein to argue for a digital innovation hub for public health. For things like this  https://t.co/54b1HKwV7I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnbrownstein @VaccineFinder @CDCgov @HHSGov @WhiteHouse @CastlightHealth @Mapbox @twilio Thank you to you and entire team for excellent work on this. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jenkinshelen Or write it together...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jenkinshelen Been organizing my thoughts on this. Plan to write them up soon. Would love to hear what youre thinking and compare notes...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This was always going to happen, even if you didnt like it, and even if they werent called passports https://t.co/PaltonOtpe https://t.co/QlR2xZf3u3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: The covid-19 crisis in India is a massive setback for the entire world.   India needs the global communitys support to survi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashishkjha: Today, India became the only nation to pass 400K cases in one day: 402K  21% test +  3500 deaths  True infections, deaths l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In car with others who are not yet vaccinated?  -wear masks -open windows -make sure AC is not on recirc mode  One year ago, with @CorsIAQ and J. Spengler  https://t.co/TszgpJd09X https://t.co/osfR8EeQUw https://t.co/mNDHLLD0NU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Windows closed!? https://t.co/rmG9dbs9Gf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Celia_LJ: The nation's experts are in agreement: Your school board should spend stimulus funds on good air filters -- not on things tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Introducing Dr. Emily Jones! Extraordinary talent. It's been such a privilege to a serve as her advisor.  These are the days I just absolutely love my job. Front row seat to the brightest minds who want to - and will - solve the world's greatest challenges.  https://t.co/B5a8D2PX0S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/3WHISbhPsQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[h/t @drdavidmichaels]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The prior administration was hell bent on dismantling our environmental health protections. Big win today.  https://t.co/ePyEpV9P7X https://t.co/DvRNyGgfS2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @murtazaakhter: @j_g_allen The resolution of this story is phenomenal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @murtazaakhter: This whole thread is amazing, for you academics out there https://t.co/JnhKaZ6uzb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you liked my impromptu thread on how these bad risk metrics get 'accidentally' codified, wait til I post one about radon...  (entire Healthy Buildings team collectively rolls their eyes...) https://t.co/d3PluwgnxZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great report on schools and uptake of different ventilation/filtration strategies, by current @HarvardChanSPH MPH student @iamanniehoang (also MD student at UCSF) for @mygreenschools.  Lots of useful insights. https://t.co/aCzGhNgEYp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smart take by @juliettekayyem. Public health guidance has to quickly adjust to changing dynamics in US or becomes irrelevant/ignored.  https://t.co/4WdhYWWeLS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Side note: this is why I also think things like H-Index are nonsense. There are ways to have impact that go behind citations of your work in peer-reviewed journals.  -end-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And then...the VA revised its guidance and DROPPED THE 30% RULE!  Same with Allegheny County! https://t.co/Z8ltJx3ihU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There were hearings on this...where they discussed the false sense of security from this "30%" metric https://t.co/8qLU8HrylJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The VA Inspector General investigated. And, for the first time I'm aware, flagged that this 30% rule may not be all it was cracked up to be, citing our work (!) https://t.co/aKtRELkRBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our paper got attention after there was an outbreak in a VA hospital in ....ALLEGHENY COUNTY (!) https://t.co/BCZd0O1fXc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And we published a paper showing this, which I'm pretty sure has 0 citations, but I still think it's one of my most important papers. Because it did have one key, non-academic citation... https://t.co/pXQzN1MUDM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We did a literature review of all outbreaks we could find to formally test this 30% metric. Guess what? it doesn't work. https://t.co/9Ka1ONtWJv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(we cleaned up the handwritten notes for the paper...but notice how much ties into Best et al. and Allegheny) https://t.co/wU2qYRd7Pm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When we dug deeper it just became a web of self-citations, with all of the studies actually only relying on Best et al.   (here's us trying to untangle the web!) https://t.co/NcQk2qZhIC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From there it got strange. A few agencies, like the Allegheny County Health Dept, started using this metric, citing Best et al.   Then others started to use it, too, citing Allegheny... https://t.co/T3sGJX7SPR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So I started tracing the history of this 30% metric. Turns out it came from a paper in 1983 (Best et al.), where they did an oversimplified analysis and merely *suggested* a 30% cutoff made sense. https://t.co/HHUREQfNQF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Never made sense to me, for obvious reasons (um, what if you took 100 samples and 99 were negative, but there was one positive sample with high levels of L. pneumophila in a bone marrow transplant unit?)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I led the Legionnaires' disease outbreak investigations for my prior firm. And everywhere I went hospitals would cite this '30% cutoff' for determining risk.   If &lt;30% of water samples tested positive, ok. If &gt;30%, higher risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Incredible paper and team tracing the history of the 6' rule and droplet/aerosol issues. Amazing how thin the basis for some of these things are, yet get codified into our guidance.   (I have one non-covid example that is my least-cited, but maybe most important, paper)  THREAD https://t.co/tLWXgQNOnU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[--&gt; https://t.co/bBwtMpbbsX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media attention on India right now, and rightly so. But there are crises playing out all over the world. Including Brazil. Hear from one of the best at @HarvardChanSPH, colleague and collaborator @marciacastrorj    https://t.co/HkQWiDfLUs via @Harvard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are no excuses if your school did not open this year.  Guidance on how to protect kids+adults was there since early summer, stimulus money was there (2x), study after study confirmed it could be done.  Epic failure with consequences that will play out for years. https://t.co/co0atAFDPr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schools closed is a national emergency. Acute crisis - still. https://t.co/nKq4cxfbWw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1. Current ventilation standards are not set for infection control (outside of hospitals) 2. Many orgs have said "bring in more air", but haven't given targets  --&gt; Target 4-6 ACHe ("effective" air changes achieved thru any combo of ventilation+filtration) https://t.co/bvdZkyy03j https://t.co/xIYVqtysPX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashishkjha: Today's India numbers so awful  Record 380,000 new infections   22% test positivity (yikes)  And 3600 deaths, likely a wild]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[&gt; https://t.co/A5V9YwciVd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aimeerawlins: Covid has understandably made us all hyper-aware of air quality, but we should be taking a much closer look at the air in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FRIDAY, 1PM ET. Critical updates on India, presented by @HarvardChanSPH @GHP_HarvardChan. Open to the public. https://t.co/Mp58K1YqiT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VickyNguyenTV @michaelmina_lab @LaurNBC Great additional layer of defense. Using them now. Wish we had these last year. Now need to drive down costs so available to all. https://t.co/kKRceUQ57r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love that dirty water! https://t.co/PlRPwjCAbo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@celinegounder @JenniferNuzzo @Nakhasi_MD @SunnyJhaMD Important work. Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This study - which, again, has actually been out in preprint for a long time - continues to be misinterpreted by reporters. https://t.co/p6Ht1wjgxa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BaccarelliAA Thanks, Andrea.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Commissioncovid: New publication on #school #infrastructure; better ventilation  air cycling reduces risk of #COVID19 transmission tod]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>