<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepAndyBiggsAZ: Im thankful for President @realDonaldTrump and his exceptional leadership at the helm of our nation. He has fought eve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[reinstate 45]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: John Kerry needs to be investigated for violations of the Logan Act right now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday True First Lady https://t.co/aoOexOTpXZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DGwX0FM9TI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hold on to your belief in God! Praise Jesus Christ he died for our sins   Glory be his name]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksorbs And her arm pits are hairy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jewelingbee: @AlanDukeNews Alan Duke - discredited.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlanDukeNews Mike has exposed the truth and you all will go down]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Erin03truth: @AlanDukeNews This is new evidence. Everyone needs to see. Instead of listening to Alan Duke false fact checking reports.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Abeaches1: @AlanDukeNews Mike Lindell is destroying and exposing this Communist so called Fact Checker!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @obiwancannobbio: @AlanDukeNews Mike Lindell is shredding your reputation right now.  Why are you censoring the American people?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cookpartyof6: @AlanDukeNews We stand with Mike Lindell!!!! You, and all associated with you, Mr. Duke are in bed with the CCP and selli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think Mike Lindell should be Attorney General he is doing a great job exposing the coverup and people that are covering them up @AlanDukeNews    I smell prison for a lot of people #FrankSpeech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS I understand why you don't have any followers on Twitter   Must see Absolute proof!!!!!   https://t.co/y29tvVXhPi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VP Must see https://t.co/y29tvVXhPi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS Must see  https://t.co/y29tvVXhPi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great found guilty no reason to riot!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#verdict  Go live on https://t.co/hAzdZZcSqw now!!!  Learn the truth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[watch the science   Go live on https://t.co/hAzdZZcSqw now!!!  Learn the truth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#verdict  check it out  Go live on https://t.co/hAzdZZcSqw now!!!  Learn the truth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Go live on https://t.co/hAzdZZcSqw now!!!  Learn the truth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Egreeno: #mybodymychoice  The only shot I am going to get is from the bar!  @NoCovidVaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#mybodymychoice  The only shot I am going to get is from the bar!  @NoCovidVaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: Its just as easy to buy a scientist as it it to buy a politician.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikepompeo Mike's website is up  https://t.co/mJ2Jvrk5TP ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mJ2Jvrk5TP check it out #FreeSpeech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RandyRRQuaid: BIDEN MAKES ME SICK!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ashli Babbit Had no gun! unarmed white woman and her life matters]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kjw2001 @TheGhostImpala https://t.co/zztxo642GE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matt I smell lawsuit #CNNDone #CNNExposed https://t.co/mc1fJHoptk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: CNN is propaganda. Pass it on.   #ExposeCNN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is criminal!!!!!! PERIOD https://t.co/q2nfoVYtjx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: CNN doesn't care about "news."   The only two things they care about are electing Democrats and increasing their rating]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@phlep_lit2 https://t.co/zztxo642GE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CNNExposed  https://t.co/zztxo642GE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Madam Speaker, tear down this wall!  Thanks for the kind words, @BennyJohnson! https://t.co/gdlR2dT2St]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: #LaurenBoebert4Prison?   Lets raise $30k TODAY to show the Left I have the backing of WE THE PEOPLE  that their botted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennaEllisEsq: We should fear government control more than a virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: I remember the press bashing Trump for touching the rail once. Biden falls repeatedly but Im sure hes the picture of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikepompeo: Strength deters bad guys. Weakness begets war.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattgaetz: I stand with Marjorie Taylor Greene!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepMattGaetz: Joe Biden exudes weakness.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Bidenfall #bidenfalling #bidenSucks https://t.co/baHixEKK9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @w_terrence: JOE BIDEN IS WEAK! #Bidenfall   If #Biden cant stand on his own two feet then how can he stand up for America ?  I miss Pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@QasimRashid No you are so dumb https://t.co/baHixEKK9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Bidenfall He won the most popular President in the World... What a morrroon https://t.co/baHixEKK9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hmmm I wonder what the gas prices will be these summer   #BidenSucks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You are an idiot if you voted for Biden #FACT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennaEllisEsq: FOUR states now fully open and maskless.  It always just takes ONE person to stand up and do the right thing and others]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennaEllisEsq: TRUMP!!!!!!!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTrump: Gas prices are going through the roof - thanks #JoeBiden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan https://t.co/go6dZZuSXR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Need  #proof this says it all  volume needs to be up https://t.co/8UGgkWfy27]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MedinaParsa @BeachCity55 80% of the people are working from home.  not many people commuting the price should adjust for demand! biden establishment corrupt politician = high prices more corruption more corruption]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeachCity55 @motmemes Yea and we are in a pandemic and people are working from home....  #BULLSHITBiden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dictators have to lock down there Country from there people if Biden won by so many votes more then the big O   Maybe he didn't win after all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Egreeno: devils tool twitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Egreeno: f345r3245rwdf2345r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[devils tool twitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[f345r3245rwdf2345r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fa43qrf3q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[erlkfjerlfjrelfkjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[days are numbered]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[roiuewroiweu24398rewfd2w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fsadfwa43fregv3r5gt democrats are demons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fwqerf3rewqfrewfrewf #democratscheat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fqewrf432qf342qf342f4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[f4rf3qfe243f432f432gf4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[frewqf432qrf324rf432rff43]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fewqrf243rf243r342r243r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ref34qrt342qrt342rt432]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[qrf34qr243r43r324]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fq34rdfsrr234qr23r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[faw4rfq34rfr34qfw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fasgf43waf34afwerf34wq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[gv3q5ytdfgvdf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wj78lCTUeD new video most see tv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Make America Warm Again https://t.co/Z8xkz4LO2I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles At least we don't have to see there faces   #NotMyPresident]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@babsmarshall1 @w_terrence 61% my ass poll taken on a dominion machine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TrumpBestPresidentEver https://t.co/zlYSOnpDx1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @w_terrence: HELP ME WITH MY MATH!! Im lost   If 80 + people million voted for Joe Biden then why was Donald J Trump trending on #Presi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Parler is where its at... by twitter you suck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Has Pedophilia Joe sniffed anyone today?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey Joe I would like to say Happy PedoDay  #PedoDay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Day President Trump"   This day was made for President Trump  #BestPresidentEver45]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: Happy Presidents Day, President Trump!! https://t.co/TmNWu3b3ix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepAndyBiggsAZ took the words out of my mouth   #NOTMYPRESIDENTBIDEN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @w_terrence: In honor of Presidents Day I would like to  say Joseph R Biden is not my President   Happy Presidents Day to the greatest P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DiamondandSilk: Donald J. Trump will always be our President!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattgaetz: I love @Publix.   Its where shopping is a pleasure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Real President is in Florida   LIVE: Pro Trump Celebration in West Palm Beach, FL on Presidents Day ... https://t.co/ykSHwUd1Eu via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you notice how the gas prices are going up fast in a pandemic that 80% of the people are working from home and not driving... #ThankaDemocrat   Next year price will be much higher and jobs will be just as stagnate as it was during the BS Obuma years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Freezing Trending because global warming is bull shit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobertWCoon1 They will all be re-elected in a landslide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GOPBetrayedAmerica recall GOP Sens. Mitt Romney of Utah, Lisa Murkowski of Alaska, Susan Collins of Maine, Ben Sasse of Nebraska and Pat Toomey of Pennsylvania]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love #Publix shop shop shop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ LIVE: Pro Trump Celebration in West Palm Beach, FL on Presidents Day ... https://t.co/ykSHwUd1Eu via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Trump Day!!!! #TRUMP2024ToSaveAmerica]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>