<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[How many nurses, doctors, pharmacists are going to experience to mental breakdown when they find out theyre responsible for killing people w these #vaccines...aka #lethalinjections]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor So, when will those of us who are exposed to these lethal injections via guinea pigs be able to sue for involuntary vaccination?? https://t.co/0L468L42gx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe my common sense and ability to read is getting in the way here, but this reads to me that NonVx person is exposed to Vx person, NonVx person can now expose others  https://t.co/dQFfPcxylo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine Shedding  https://t.co/AUf5jpXPIY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Self-Spreading Vaccines  #NoVaccine #NoMasks #FuckGates #FuckBiden #FuckHarris #FuckTheAgenda  https://t.co/wYQAUHxbvA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#LaborUnions No business or company can enforce lethal injection or smothering if the workers collectively refuse! #NoMasks #NoVaccine #NoCommunistGovernment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor Sure, never mind the 3k + who have died from that experiment yall falsely call a vaccine; Im sure that mother of the 5 month old baby that died as a result of her breast feeding after receiving that lethal injection is thankful for such a vaccine-sarcasm heavily implied!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @occultb0t: 17 Genuinely Creepy Photos From A 1972 Rothschild Dinner Party: https://t.co/jS9FRGZ0ix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/qktBEXxvHM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MediaSmarts @kieraevebutler @MotherJones You mean like the ones reported to vaers?? You can download the reports and read it for yourself and yes, it does specifically state reports of miscarriages and irregular bleeding.   https://t.co/0bDjdIBXzl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The next simulation. Of course we all know how their simulations go. #Tyranny    https://t.co/zaR2VSX7HU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SikhForTruth: How Vaccine Passports Will Actually Work.  #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere   https://t.co/Ryk42f13W2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny how politicians and the msm can suddenly do math when it comes down to race baiting but couldnt count their fingers or toes when it came to a 99% survival rate virus.   #Bullshit #Tyranny #FuckTheAgenda #FuckTheVaccine #CovidScam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernardKerik: Anyone that treats black Americans differently does so because @BarackObama has been saying that they are different for t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Democratic Party Now Selling Official Riot Supplies https://t.co/tVBxzXo0RP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 Must be the first glimpse of the notorious laptop to human virus..if McAfee comes out w a vaccine Im calling conspiracy! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read the Vaers reports at  https://t.co/0bDjdIBXzl  #NoVaccine #FuckTheAgenda #uniteandconquer https://t.co/3Lw3OeiJ7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor Each shot brings you closer to death, sterilization, and disabilities. You can read the reports at https://t.co/0bDjdIBXzl  Deaths reported as of 2nd week in April. https://t.co/ZkApFqG4Vt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor @VP https://t.co/d7O05vRJEb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/EZA9QBm2Ot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @clif_high: https://t.co/gafClo34nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 From Clif High - Shedding Woo bitchute  You cant directly post the link bcz of #TwitterCensorship]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: They hate our guts. https://t.co/2xBNPH6GOj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 @mikehalp99 These were taken in December. There was definitely something mixed in w the typical chemtrails. https://t.co/DcjYJ292s9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not wearing as mask will not hurt you #Nomasks , Not getting a vaccine, that isnt a vaccine at all, will not hurt you; its your own ignorance that will hurt you. #NoVaccine #NeverTrustTheirAgenda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zgMbtfnUHc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 Satan, minions of Satan, almost the same thing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: A move by lawyers to consolidate at least 14 lawsuits filed by 8 different law firms in 6 different federal courts is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: The Japanese government has once again failed the people of Fukushima. The government has taken the wholly unjustifie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 God forbid you just stop chemtrailing, GMOing,  creating bioweapons so pharma looks relevant. But no, youd rather turn grocery into pharmacy.   https://t.co/1EPzRV3nfr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: This thing is a cult and I'm going to keep saying it. https://t.co/4uw1RW7Pns]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CollectiveEvol: https://t.co/VSF1JK88sE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ayecee17 @ki4bgf @NC_Governor Yes its the damn time! Hes a damn PedoJoe stroker! You support a Pedo and his crimes then you are just as guilty.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor Cooper vs McCrory The last 1.5yrs, 330+ illegal aliens have been charged with 1,200 child sex crimes in NC. The last 4.5 yrs the NCFIREs states an avg of 34 illegal aliens in NC are charged every month with child sex crimes. https://t.co/5wvJ2MauuR   https://t.co/EcGYJSTste]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Need to know where these alien take over cities are so we can all follow the hot spots from their #bioweapon breakout??  https://t.co/tunblx7YqW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And this was 2019...now we got #PedoJoe and his left hand jerker #RoyCooper bending over  https://t.co/5wvJ2MauuR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBigK47998548: @shortman5427 https://t.co/a8YlHmCyxr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FedEx my package has been sitting in Charlotte since 4/6 w ZERO updates. Charlotte is 45 mins from me; where is my package and why havent I gotten it already?? I want a physical location. Ill go pick it up since yall are acting like USPS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 The only reason they would be scratching their heads is due to lice! Meanwhile, those of us who know this is complete  utter bullshit are left scratching our heads as to how the hell weve gone so long without realizing 9.5 out of every 10 people we came in contact w are sheep!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tracymariedavi @Ssamas34 @HealthInsider Its just another level of discrimination. HIV/AIDS positive persons were refused entrance to damn near everything; they also fought  won that battle and are a protected group within the ADA. Replace the phrase HIV w Covid in the link, discrimination https://t.co/mMn1ypusfm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USNavy sending aircraft carriers.. change the considering to on their way  https://t.co/X4XWruFdxC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Russia hints at #USA  #Bioweapon  https://t.co/az0yKFhtTn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NewsBecker: Caution: Graphic. https://t.co/T2v2NSsxSu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darkjournalist guess they know Fridays are dark journalist night  https://t.co/hxSkGzOhO3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@payneinthekass @helmet_crash @NC_Governor Take the info  link w a grain of salt as weve seen varied interpretations on what they consider true.  This is what makes vaccines such powerful medicine. Unlike most medicines, which treat or cure diseases, vaccines prevent them. https://t.co/thLUSC7kjz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@payneinthekass @helmet_crash @NC_Governor Google? Google?  Theres all the intelligence you need right there ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tvonisakovics @nhc_libertarian @NC_Governor No it does not! You are free to protect your own health as you see fit, gmo foods, fluoridated water, chemtrails, etc. and everyone else has the same rights. My body, my choice...your body, your choice. Or maybe we could just get to the point of who creates bioweapons...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MomJezebel @makeamarkin2020 @DVJakeL @NC_Governor It doesnt prevent the vaccinated person from getting Covid; its only to lessen symptoms of Covid; death, blood clots, and other side effects are just the perks. FYI, side effects can result in the offspring of those given any type of vaccination so dont get fooled by timing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Except that youre not; youre now able to be remotely influenced, hacked like a laptop, and shut down if necessary. Consciousness trap.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: The family feels strongly about a different version of what happened. Maybe not drugs after all?     https://t.co/gUaQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: Sounds reasonable (sarcasm font). https://t.co/kkW8AfxTc6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassports #Tyranny  Its legalization of discrimination;it further creates a split/tiered society, it creates a have/have not society with justified hatred. Communities that form out of the fuck no will be ruthlessly targeted; its star bellied sneetch syndrome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@royale_high Playing on mobile sucks!! You cant pick up the eggs so your beating your phone until it finally picks it up! You zoom out and in and flying is a wreck!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GMOFreeUSA: Manmade disasters do not happen overnight, that's why the release of #GMmosquitoes must be nipped in the bud now! What happ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Usi7sdKD2L  #Border  cams]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CassyWearsHeels @shortman5427 That woman is 100% evil. They know what theyre doing and have been doing it for way too long. https://t.co/mRt7CQellP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor @ncdhhs That one that doesnt prevent people from getting it just like the flu vaccine didnt either?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor Where are the buses going?Those from Nicaragua and other Central American nations have been delivered to Tennessee, Massachusetts, Indiana, Michigan, North Carolina, Georgia, Kentucky, and to large cities in Texas such as Dallas and Houston. https://t.co/mRt7CQellP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mRt7CQellP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats not to trust? #BigPharma will grow the food for you  #NoGMO #NoMonsanto #FuckBillGates #FuckTheVaccine #FuckMasks #FuckTheAgenda  https://t.co/nrZdWSpuIE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GMOFreeUSA: What's the definition of insanity?   Bayer-Monsanto's suite of toxic products that they plan to unleash onto humanity and n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy pre-birthday to me! #1776 https://t.co/cIWmTzi1Mw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PatriotMomma83 @NC_Governor https://t.co/PMGo34OVz6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndyHagens2: @NC_Governor Hay Coop, This you. Raising money for Child Predators? https://t.co/zZUnMy8Kn3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PatriotMomma83 @NC_Governor 100% w you all the way! He can go stay w his pedo buddy Biden and their mentor in China and get the hell out of our state and US. Im sure some of your campaign contributors can support you! https://t.co/QGlTw0VE5g https://t.co/jypBTye45N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LieselGreer @NC_Governor @TheDemocrats Exactly!! THIS is what inciting violence looks like! This is what encouragement of discrimination looks like! Ask all the HIV and AIDS victims how hard it was for them to be treated like equal humans...THIS ISNT HIV OR AIDS! THIS IS TYRANNY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 Im hoping this doesnt represent the collective mind of the 20  under population, but according to at least this one.....the constitution is paper, lives arent.  These sick people have definitely found their audience. https://t.co/wVTpbwjQBx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PFeCgPD3TL  WHO has no enforcement powers; this tells you exactly what theyre aiming for. #FightBack #Freedom #ProtectYourRights]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: Medical Disinformation Alert https://t.co/lIcvwljARA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor https://t.co/YnyOmfOC5c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: stop buying fucking toothpaste with fluoride!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: Calling his shot more than a decade in advance. Almost like magic when you watch this.  You can find my show Macroaggr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: If you cant figure out from these stats whats happening here then the propaganda is working. https://t.co/wJ7pFL2Zsa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sallyKP: https://t.co/Wtw0IwGKEO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: The last part is super important. https://t.co/ctBbrejgCq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rustyrockets: This video on the Great Reset and Eric Schmidt...what do you think?    Watch the full video here: https://t.co/Nu27E0zj6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please tell me how the hell my TV is connected to the internet but my phone and laptop wont?? #Spectrum and their bullshit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McFadden1932: Yes, especially if it was one of those faked mass shootings. https://t.co/0SnKOUZMUG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheBabylonBee Jk....take your shot as soon as you find youre open ;) https://t.co/gBZ4XdYEYb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroaggressio3 I only have one thought that comes to mind for these folks... https://t.co/9oWCQGmvXM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MMALTH9 @cropah @ZubyMusic @PeterJungX @jeremyphoward They also seem the exclude the main element in these studies; the overall health of the person. What is the age of the persons? What are the comorbidities of each person? What is the health history of each person? Blood test for nutritional deficiencies? Etc.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kitty62862 @eastcountytoday @krispykreme We are easily identified, were the healthy ones who enjoy smiling to those we see, breath air free from the ball gag, and not dying from guinea pig injections. Exercising a right is a 2 way street, if you have that right, then its a right to be exercised by all. Enjoy your OS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic They go the extra mile to keep the micro-focus on an individual so that the masses dont look behind them to see that the hand that feeds them is killing us all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SallyMayweather: https://t.co/uxZLgotYk4 https://t.co/4ebjpYGU8f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NC_Governor But hes just helping the state, just like he said he was helping with the states opioid problem  https://t.co/rO6ZYpKFwR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WillieJonesssss @NC_Governor Funny how its actually the reversed who are dying ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bitzymeow4 @NC_Governor Hell no, and wont!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@funnyordie How about go die! I mean, go get vaccinated! Blocking this propaganda bullshit right now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/k8SHbUaO6d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If its unlawful for one state, its unlawful for all AS WEVE KNOWN!!! If you want to wear a mask and take a vaccine, then by all means, you have a right to commit suicide, but do not restrict the right to live freely to others! #FuckYourMask #FuckYourVaccine #NoMask #sc https://t.co/awurwofiSK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get #Cooper the fuck out of NC!! If its not evident that him, or 90% of any government, arent for the people, but instead for their people, then youre just ignorant and blind by choice! https://t.co/LEbQbM5Yq7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hodgetwins If thats the case, then someone is an alien or other type of humanoid with eyes in the back of their head as well ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7kS4m4vUzx  #LoveYourself #NoVaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darkjournalist Im not even going to try and be polite for these bunch of idiots. These people are fucking stupid! They want to be enslaved in hell, so by all damnation, burn for eternity. However, dont grab my spirit by the foot during my ascension, you had your chance!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are not an organic, divine being, then you are not a spirit that returns to source...or, the kingdom of heaven. This vaccine will ensure you remain in eternal damnation. YES! IT CHANGES YOUR DNA! #novaccine #FuckYourAgenda #FuckYourVaccine  https://t.co/GvY9ZkPLZ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hodgetwins: Just another reminder why we dont watch NBA or college basketball anymore. https://t.co/OvfVRljV6S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/sRv4UKRLfB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJBowden1 Only thing thats been obviously ruled out,  for a long time now, is the link between these peoples morals  ethics; assuming they had any at all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: So the six-foot rule for kids in school has now been changed to three-feet by the CDC? So is the "virus" only half bad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroaggressio3: It's almost impossible to be this stupid, but here we are... https://t.co/hM3EdPGIJ2]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>