<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Many of the groups across the country are working to support people who are affected by the new Christmas restrictions, with everything to food hampers to checking in on people experiencing isolation.   Find your group here: https://t.co/LSPWBe7ttH  #lockdown #Christmas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrRosena: This announcement today will have created anxiety and stress for many. Don't be afraid to reach out for help if you are worri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've been quiet as groups have been getting on with supporting their communities  Anyone feeling nervous about lockdown, or who has capacity to support their area, find your nearest group https://t.co/LSPWBe7ttH  Remember - the best organising happens on small and local scales]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Took them 1 hour to find and question us. Took them 1 month to find and question Dominic Cummings. #peoplevspoliticians #themvsus #bodiesdontlie https://t.co/czvhJrxMng]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RETWEET AND SHARE w/ hashtag #BodiesDontLie @jeremycorbyn @OwenJones84 @afuahirsch @GeorgeThePoet @Lowkey0nline @JohnBoyega @AyoCaesar @felixwhite @DawnHFoster @DawnButlerBrent @HackneyAbbott @DavidLammy @BellRibeiroAddy @jonsnowC4 https://t.co/vviBVYSFzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidUK: Outside Dominic Cummings House now. #NoJusticeNoPeace #BlackLivesMatter https://t.co/qn9WPBm72z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid 19 BAME report late and incomplete. @PHE_uk publish full findings NOW! #bodiesdontlie https://t.co/vc17Pak7F7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's coming up to 7pm. Please take your support to your doorsteps and blast out Jimmy Cliff's 'The Harder They Come' in solidarity with #BlackLivesMatter #SolidarityForever https://t.co/ZOCbZT0uaj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amged el-Hawrani, Adel el-Tayr and Habib Zaidi were the first three doctors to die of Covid-19. The govt have repeatedly put BAME lives in danger #justiceforBellyMujinga  #WontWorkToDeath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mutual Aid activists stage die-in outside Cummings house, after govt failure to protect BME lives. #CovidDOESdiscriminate  RETWEET ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Racism is the riskiest pre-existing condition. BAME people UP TO 50% MORE LIKELY TO DIE FROM COVID-19 #BODIESDONTLIE https://t.co/DzNHFy7xz2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hancock says 'black lives matter' whilst risking the lives of BAME key workers and NHS staff #justiceforBellyMujinga #NoJusticeNoPeace #BlackLivesMatter https://t.co/fsopeXqAEq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Outside Dominic Cummings House now. #NoJusticeNoPeace #BlackLivesMatter https://t.co/qn9WPBm72z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ACTIVISTS STAGE DIE IN OUTSIDE CUMMINGS HOUSE AS UK RACISM LEADS TO THOUSANDS OF COVID DEATHS. #BODIESDONTLIE BUT THE GOVT DOES #BlackLivesMatter https://t.co/Zdm04u43dQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you can't/don't want to go out on the streets in a pandemic, here are other ways you can support the #BlackLivesMatter movement from your home.  Written by @MelzDot for @galdemzine   https://t.co/VDcAPaZUDW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've seen some discussion in mutual aid groups about whether to attend #BlackLivesMatter protests in the UK.  If you decide to show your support in that way, check out this thread first. https://t.co/l2N3xooVfB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Local solidarity is great - it's even better when it's paired with global solidarity!   Sign this if you can https://t.co/Ns7vjDoUkw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Practical advise for socialising under new gov guidance.   We recommend still avoiding non essential contact to save as many lives as possible. https://t.co/48MO94l1xR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NEON_UK: These Mutual Aid groups exemplify some of the best ways that communities have been facing the pandemic and Cummings represents]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DocsNotCops: The governments decision to scrap the immigration health surcharge for NHS  care workers must be extended to EVERYONE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/2 Gvmnt response to the pandemic has never been good enough and it is ordinary people who have stepped up to do the work they have failed to.   We must continue to do so now, by staying home and saving lives. No matter how desperately unfair that feels  #covid19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/2 Despite what gvmnt said yesterday, unnecessary travel could still be deadly  Many of us are feelings frustrated, we have lost or are losing loved ones and might feel that if the rules no longer apply to one person, why should  they continue to apply to us?   BUT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And a reminder that the wonderful @Fran_Face developed this list of resources for #disabled people navigating #covid  https://t.co/DSEMSkB0jC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lockdown and social distancing have disrupted all of our lives but people will disabilities are bearing more of the weight.   Please read this article to better understand how to support people with disabilities in our communities.  #Covid19  https://t.co/RcxuBXx24q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Short term support for communities during a pandemic means nothing without fighting for their rights and protection in the long run.  Read this blog by @minnierahman at @JCWI_UK  to see how the #ImmigrationBill would affect key workers currently saving our lives.  #Covid19 https://t.co/g62fU5K9cN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone has the right to safe warm accommodation - especially during a pandemic  Gvmt are starting to cut funding to shelter homeless people. Please push back against this by speaking to your MPs and councils  give extra support to services in your area  https://t.co/osrGDZevnA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ben_rog Hi Ben, there are currently 4253 groups, though often these groups have split down into additional smaller groups to best serve smaller pockets of their neighbourhood. For example, Lewisham is one of the 4253 groups but has split down into 20+ more groups of more local organising]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For anyone else who is a victim or survivor of domestic abuse, support is available in many places including from https://t.co/60a8ercyIY  More details of services can be found here https://t.co/xOOHKrrAEi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Incidents of domestic abuse, including deaths, have been rising under lockdown.  Yesterday was #IDAHOBIT2020 for anyone currently experiencing domestic abuse relating to their sexuality or gender, reach out to @GalopUK   https://t.co/ufl5ZfNQ7U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NCLMutualAid: The community larders set up by #elswick  #arthurshill #MutualAid groups have had a makeover! Thanks to @bt_uk for letti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today there are planned mass gatherings to protest the lockdown. Organisers have direct links to far right groups  We recommend avoiding these spaces  continuing with lockdown but also take care of those in your community who might be targeted by these groups  #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stressed about rent but also wondering whether a rent suspension is feasible, check this from @joebeswick1 at @NEF  then sign up with @LDNRentersUnion   For those of you outside of London you can check the #CantPayWontPay campaign for advice and sign up with @ACORN_tweets https://t.co/XcIkHjccsU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great article on some of the radical history of Mutual Aid.  Mutual Aid in the Time of Coronavirus: Southern Solidarity  More https://t.co/BJwugX3iHv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goosefat101: #ff some orgs doing important activism/education: @EDeportations @ukdecrimnow @BARACUK @lgsmigrants @TransActualUK @Gender]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you, or people in your community, are having to chose between buying food and basic essentials or paying your rent, check out this new campaign from @LDNRentersUnion   #Covid19 #cantpaywontpay https://t.co/k0QWI9XF2Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CheerfulPodcast: "Tens of thousands of people have joined community efforts to look after the most vulnerable in society." @guardian]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi everyone, one last day to fill in this survey so we can start implementing support.  Please take a moment to note down your thoughts if you haven't already: https://t.co/GncIuIOjgB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidUK: Dear local volunteers,  We'd like to know more about the issues you're facing in supporting different members of your commu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For some workers, legal restrictions might make joining a union or quoting section 44 impossible  Long term we need decriminalisation - short term we want to share ways to support with the Mutual Aid network  Pls link to advice below  @UVWunion @lawrsuk @UVWunion  etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidUK: For those of you expected to return to work this morning :  - Section 44 of the Employment Rights Act gives you the right t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Those who are salaried - if you have some spare income, share this on social, by text and over the phone with workers who might be expected to return to work to unsafe conditions.  #JoinAUnion #MutualAid #Covid19UK https://t.co/wWmQIuRBSt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For those of you expected to return to work this morning :  - Section 44 of the Employment Rights Act gives you the right to walk away from any unsafe work  - Join a union  #JoinAUnion #COVID19 #Lockdown]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Government advice is confusing at best, deadly at worst.  We encourage you to listen to doctors and carry on as usual with your mutual aid projects, social distancing and lockdown.   #lockdownuk #COVID19 https://t.co/Z4QWzd7nyr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @seanbaillie9: 3 steps of your asked to return to work: - Join a Union - Dont work without an updated risk assessment  - collectively s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @exiledwolf: For my UK-based followers worried they might be forced back to work, as a health and safety worker, let me present to you w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder to fill this in with your morning cuppa!   https://t.co/HBTBiU1q1E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear local volunteers,  We'd like to know more about the issues you're facing in supporting different members of your communities.   If you've got a moment to fill out this short survey, it won't take longer than a quick brew.  Please share: https://t.co/3YCirJpAm0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LDNRentersUnion: Solidarity to our members at @court_union who are featured in this powerful 12 min video.   Our housing system was al]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NadiaWhittomeMP: If you're a care worker who has faced pressure, threats or disciplinary action for speaking out about PPE, contact my]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SloughMutualAid: A HUGE thanks to all involved in making these banners for English, Punjabi, Polish  Urdu speaking folks in #Slough ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrayInGlasgow: After this all ends. Edinburgh window sign. https://t.co/JHsud1S4P6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can you help support mutual aid for 50 Palestinian families (400 people) on lockdown in the Jordan Valley? https://t.co/PYHFS7eO1r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lgsmigrants: SLRA and organisations like them are continuing to help those in need during the CoVid crisis. But they need your support,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please share: The Effect of COVID-19 on the LGBTQ+ Asylum Seekers.  Help service providers  Govt to understand the impact of Pandemic on LGBTIQ+ Asylum Seekers in the UK.  STRICTLY anonymous, confidential and voluntary.  https://t.co/TQhJmgwlJf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lgsmigrants: 'It was bad, but now its been unbearable': The children going hungry during the pandemic   Children are being excluded fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SistersUncut: We must ensure no one is left behind; and this is only possible through accessibility, interdependence, collective action]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conniebliff: Yesterday an elderly woman in my block taped the first note to the lobby door, so my neighbours and I dropped off some boo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NLSistersUncut: Weve created infographics to share about mutual aid, the consequences of the COVID-19 bill  how we can support each o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NEON_UK: We're very lucky to have @saiogradin guiding us through a 'history of mutual' aid right now as part of our webinar series.   S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lawrsuk: Very pleased to have collaborated on this piece highlighting the unequal impact of COVID-19  the lack of access to support th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@virginmedia Alternatively can you confirm if you did indeed block it at your end?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@virginmedia Lots of us can use it fine, but also lots of people reporting trouble. It looks like at some point you blocked it - are you able to reverse that please? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCWI_UK: Coronavirus is a threat to all of us. In the fight against it, no-one should be left behind.  Check out our guide to supportin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have had complaints from some users who cannot access our groups map page. It looks like it has been flagged as a false positive here https://t.co/ORa1vSmOTR - we are *trying* to contact @virginmedia to try and get this fixed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/3 Mutual Aid groups are continuing to provide a lifeline for their local communities and stepping in to provide the support where the government has failed.   Our full statement here: https://t.co/xiHlSHTX5C  #Coronavirus #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/3 This unlawful arrest adds to a growing concern that police do not fully understand their new powers and are repeatedly misusing or abusing them, and growing concern that the police are utilising their increased powers to disproportionately harass Black and Brown people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/3 We are deeply disappointed to hear about an incident in Fallowfield, Manchester, in which a black man was arrested and threatened with pepper spray whilst running errands for his loved ones.   https://t.co/gT3jTs3uwD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidSlough: What is mutual aid?  Last week we saw a homeless man across the street  crossed over to ask if he needed anything. He]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dis_PPL_Protest: Opportunities 2 tell MP committees how the coronavirus pandemic is affecting disabled people - few different parliamen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our heath is only as safe as our communitys  #LeaveNoOneBehind https://t.co/qWFXXjxfQm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who better than neighbours to do the job quickly? @KelseyMxMo   https://t.co/bq13smOGD5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zarahsultana: Black and Asian people are being disproportionately hit by Coronavirus, reflecting wider economic and social inequalities]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCWI_UK: Coronavirus is a threat to us all. In the fight against it, no one can be left behind.  Check out our guide to supporting migr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some really exciting webinars coming up from @NEON_UK and members of the mutual aid network.  Learn about how to reach and protect more people with your organising, the history of mutual aid and experiences on the ground.  #coronavirusuk #CovidSolidarity https://t.co/rkDaooPwaC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AmeenKam: @kevinjgsmith @CovidAidUK Called an 80 year old patient yesterday. He's unable to successfully do shopping online, and fearfu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NCLMutualAid: County Durham Mutual aid group are on the lookout for people who are able to offer support in some of the smaller towns i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidSlough: 28/28  No-one will be left behind. https://t.co/aGeE9G22gQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidSlough: 19/28  Mutual aid affirms that we're all we've got, we're all we need. https://t.co/lWUvqs45hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidSlough: An Introduction to Mutual Aid - (1/28)  We hope this can be of use   Special thanks to @deanspade  Ciro Carrillo. Che]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out our new look website! It's packed full of resources and support for local mutual aid groups. The site also features a map and searchable directory of the thousands of groups that have sprung up across the UK.  https://t.co/gFwt0wlEcz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @artofactivism: Through the #covidmutualaid whatsapp group set up at the start of the lockdown, children on my parents' street have star]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HandleBards Well share with the London groups! Thank you for doing this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CovidAidSlough: We've made a visual introduction to the mutual aid model.   We hope it can be of use   With special thanks to @deanspa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more resources on supporting migrants during #Covid_19 you can check out this doc from @migrantsorg and others  #LeaveNoOneBehind  https://t.co/2NxZfCaFz7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People around the UK are showing solidarity with those in detention. During a pandemic were only as safe as everyone else.   #LeaveNoOneBehind https://t.co/NevoncAuia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeeWiiii There are links on each group - usually to a FB group or a WhatsApp. If you cant use those platforms get in touch with us and well try and connect you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mulberrybush Hi Diana, you should be able to search the website by postcode. Groups listed are often covering larger regions but if you join your nearest one they can connect you to your subgroup!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@addmy2cents Hi Trevor, can you email us using the contact on https://t.co/AxbcItALyU please? Or we recommend trying the next nearest group as a back up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@walltowallart Theres a registration form on https://t.co/AxbcItALyU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wake up. Feel terrified. See more groups on this. Feel better.  #CovidSolidarity #CoronaLockdown https://t.co/PEGZoyrE4Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DebWhatford Hey there. Sorry to hear youre struggling. You can try and get in touch with your local mutual aid group here: https://t.co/OWpZyfFCQV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnitaBellows12 @Dis_PPL_Protest @Heretoanywhere Have you tried this group? https://t.co/9Y08nrkL3J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SumRogM8: So so happy I managed to get this on video, so unbelievable  The sound of people across Portsmouth cheering for our amazing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEnglandLDN: Thank you London  #ClapForCarers #ClapForNHS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Domestic violence is likely to spike during the #lockdown   If youre concerned about yourself or someone else, weve listed resources here from @NHSuk  @womensaid and @ChaynHQ   #DomesticAbuse #Coronavirus   https://t.co/UtcfOyCFW2 https://t.co/9EHpfpFjf2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People don't need saving, they need community    @Aviah_Sarah_Day and @AnnaVickerstaff spoke to @VICEChangeInc on the principles of mutual aid, local organising in the face of coronavirus, and the importance of #covidsolidarity  https://t.co/Ab7MVu1ZdW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mickhumph Sorry wrong link: https://t.co/LSPWBe7ttH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mickhumph Hi Mick - where are you based? If you look up your local mutual aid group at https://t.co/gyDms3FsnZ someone should be able to help you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @streetskitchen: we need twitter magic!  NEED to magically find lots of #environmentfriendly bento boxes  cutlery URGENTLY so we can c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Millions of you created 3400 mutual aid groups across the UK  thousands more have signed up as #NHSResponders   We think independent community support is still a vital lifeline for people in the face of coronavirus. Our thoughts here: https://t.co/gWX9QyIOJY  #CovidSolidarity]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>