<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[1,927,484 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 139 to 226,644  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,660  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/6z6XTxW99v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As restrictions ease, more workplaces and sectors are able to reopen.  However we must all continue to work together to stop the spread of coronavirus and minimise new outbreaks.  Employers, find guidance and download the FACTS toolkit on our website.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,924,997 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 132 to 226,505  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,660  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/tSpk1BoSy6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To stop the spread, we all need to stick to the guidelines.  So we can keep moving forward and get back together again.  Weve come too far. Were not giving in.  Know the rules  https://t.co/kZjGNz2EDe https://t.co/TS5Z8l4d7n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,922,604  people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus   The total confirmed as positive has risen by 146 to 226,373  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,660  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux  Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/LDjx1m8GOa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,920,170 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 175 to 226,227  Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,660 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/GpU4rmCsc7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,917,236 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 191 to 226,052  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,659  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/WowlerD7E2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Check In Scotland app allows Test and Protect contact tracers to get in touch if there are cases linked to a venue you have visited.   Download the app today to help break chains of transmission and stop the spread of #coronavirus.   Find out more  https://t.co/IJdJeEnGR3 https://t.co/P95Rh8E2sA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,914,123 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 178 to 225,861  Sadly 5 more patients who tested positive have died (7,659 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/SijUuHjdwE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Know how to socialise safely.   6 people from 2 households can meet in certain indoor public places, like cafs or restaurants.   6 people from 6 households can meet outdoors.   Do not meet people from other households inside their home or yours.  Remember to follow FACTS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,910,765 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 204 to 225,683   Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,654 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/qzrLAeIV2h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're aged 18 to 49, get ready to roll up your sleeve.  Vaccination invitations are being rolled out by age. All adults are due to get their first vaccine by the end of July.  Find out more  https://t.co/1MvrM0nOJX https://t.co/ifVfxfGs1x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,906,612 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 133 to 225,479  Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,653 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/a2dhd7eRBF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone can now get two free coronavirus tests every week, to stop the spread and keep us moving forward.  We particularly recommend regular testing for people living with those who are on the shielding list as extra protection.  Find out more  https://t.co/dXmlcO8E2x https://t.co/FcTt4hQzYN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shops, cafes, bars, restaurants, holiday accommodation and visitor attractions are opening up again.  Please stick to the guidance to keep us moving forward.   Weve come too far. Were not giving in.  Know the rules  https://t.co/XZ3ANuKumj https://t.co/7NXPORDl2s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,903,840 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 142 to 225,346   The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,652   Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/juw4Xr1peJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,901,560 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 176 to 225,204  Sadly, one more patient who tested positive has died (7,652 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/dGu07PIXP7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,898,666 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 177 to  225,028   Sadly 4 more patients who tested positive have died (7,651 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/qZzyp29iHZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Further easing of the coronavirus restrictions depends on our actions now.  Sticking to the guidance as we move through the levels will help us to carefully and safely return to a more normal life.  We've come too far. We're not giving in.  Read more  https://t.co/TIe3CyvNqa https://t.co/5R4StXTdMK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,895,925 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 255 to 224,851   Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,647 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/ykpLwAL69h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wherever you have travelled from, you must complete a Passenger Locator Form before you arrive.   If you fail to complete the form, you are risking public health and could be fined.  Read more  https://t.co/jV0fDdzHFR https://t.co/EnZthmkHN3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Remember, it's illegal to travel overseas from Scotland unless it's for an essential reason.  The situation in many countries can change suddenly, so you should only book international travel if its absolutely essential. https://t.co/7wakx4S9Ue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From 4am, Friday 23 April, travellers coming into Scotland from India will face additional restrictions.  Learn more  https://t.co/5LxKrpaFQp  More information on travel  https://t.co/E9MjxMRbbq https://t.co/wXOntj0WuH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,892,819 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 231 to 224,596   Sadly 3 more patients who tested positive have died (7,646 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice   https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/yl1EZDWErH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On 21 April 2021, two previously reported, confirmed #coronavirus deaths have been de-notified following further investigation into the date when the case was first notified to Public Health Scotland.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,889,442 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 273 to 224,365  Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,643 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/rJOQ9FVueG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #coronavirus restrictions in Scotland are easing from Monday 26 April.  This includes the reopening of:  cafs, pubs and restaurants  tourist accommodation   gyms, non-essential retail and close contact services like beauty salons  Learn more  https://t.co/kZjGNyL3eE https://t.co/dCDFS11YXi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Monday 26 April, people travelling to Scottish islands are encouraged to take 2 #coronavirus tests before they travel.   This helps stop the spread of the virus to our island communities.   More information  https://t.co/gESu0F5w0J https://t.co/2obi3HSqwj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Monday 26 April, everyone in Scotland will be able to access rapid #coronavirus testing.   Free lateral flow home test kits will be available for people without symptoms to test themselves twice a week.  Read more about testing  https://t.co/gESu0F5w0J https://t.co/oibzvFDq9Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,885,607 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 178 to 224,092   Sadly 2 more patients who tested positive have died (7,644 in total)   Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrC7f5X Health advice https://t.co/l7rqArSHI2 https://t.co/BrQtc45QuU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Watch live: First Minister Nicola Sturgeon gives an update on #coronavirus (#COVID19) restrictions.   Joining the First Minister is Chief Medical Office Dr Gregor Smith and National Clinical Director Jason Leitch. https://t.co/n1D8sOhVT2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today First Minister Nicola Sturgeon will give an update on planned changes to #coronavirus restrictions.   Watch live here @scotgov from 12pm. https://t.co/tNExMDfLDs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secondary schools across Scotland are beginning to return full time.  All pupils are being offered at-home asymptomatic self-testing for coronavirus twice a week.    For more information about the test, visit https://t.co/3eNQVe3P3p https://t.co/dENg9CBd9Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,882,908 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 232 to 223,914   The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,642   Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrC7f5X Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArSHI2 https://t.co/5OwLol2mD7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,880,598 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus   The total confirmed as positive has risen by 211 to 223,682  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,642   Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrC7f5X  Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArSHI2 https://t.co/oB2ZeU4XJz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,878,146 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus   The total confirmed as positive has risen by 210 to 223,471  Sadly 2 more patients who tested positive have died (7,642 in total)   Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrC7f5X   Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArSHI2 https://t.co/qJ842wEs1T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There will be a one minute silence at 3pm today to mark the death of His Royal Highness, The Duke of Edinburgh.  Please do not travel to, or gather at, Royal Residences. https://t.co/DxG3lxnD2C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We all need to play our part to stop the spread.   Outdoors, a maximum of 6 people from up to 6 households can socialise. Stay 2 metres apart.   Do not meet people from other households inside their home or yours.  Coronavirus hasn't gone away.   Know how to stay safe ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the travel restrictions in Scotland are eased, we all need to remember to enjoy our countryside responsibly.    Respect your surroundings and #StaySafe to protect yourself and others from #coronavirus.  Make sure you know the rules  https://t.co/kZjGNz2EDe https://t.co/XAtwB76lAs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can now travel within Scotland for outdoor socialising, recreation and exercise.   But remember:   no overnight stays outside your local area for this  you must #StayLocal for other reasons like non-essential shopping  public transport capacity is still limited https://t.co/3Z4NgLEXrr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,875,410 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 204 to 223,261   Sadly 3 more patients who tested positive have died (7,640 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/MVmCldSkqL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You shouldn't meet people from other households inside their home or yours.   That's because #coronavirus can spread easily in enclosed spaces.  Stay safe by only socialising outdoors, staying 2 metres apart at all times.  Know the rules  https://t.co/kZjGNyL3eE https://t.co/pFoRT1zYVQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,872,312 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 237 to 222,897   Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,637 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/FvFUQVKGQw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There will be a one minute silence at 3pm on Saturday 17 April to mark the death of His Royal Highness, The Duke of Edinburgh. https://t.co/K6iRYaSQ7P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The coronavirus vaccine is our best protection against serious illness.  But, even after vaccination, we may still be able to pass on the virus.  Weve come too far. Were not giving in.  Find out more about the vaccine at https://t.co/R1BAI0NwM9 https://t.co/NUGpuumuhG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,868,938 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 278 to 222,660   Sadly 3 more patients who tested positive have died (7,636 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/cdAPeMs04Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Scottish Governments Coronavirus Scottish Parliament 2021 election guidance has been updated.  Doorstep canvassing is now permitted in all 32 local authorities.    Read the guidance here  https://t.co/JBnY5qBUMz https://t.co/rOjgUunFzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ We've published updates to the coronavirus protection levels.  Sticking to the guidance as we move through the levels will help us to carefully and safely return to a more normal life.  Find out more  https://t.co/XZ3ANuKumj https://t.co/DXXM4BN7nG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've announced updates to the #coronavirus restrictions in Scotland   From Friday 16 April:  Up to 6 people from up to 6 households can meet outdoors  You can travel within Scotland for outdoor socialising, recreation and exercise   Learn more at https://t.co/kZjGNyL3eE https://t.co/e1rYpP37Lq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,864,747 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 221 to 222,382  Sadly 3 more patients who tested positive have died (7,633 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/JwAboB8YHU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Watch live: First Minister Nicola Sturgeon gives an update on #coronavirus (#COVID19) restrictions.  Joining the First Minister is Chief Medical Officer Dr Gregor Smith. https://t.co/gRLUBmLc78]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today First Minister Nicola Sturgeon will give an update on planned changes to #coronavirus restrictions.   Watch live here @scotgov from 12pm. https://t.co/4H7ictlGfX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Living with FACTS helps keep us safe.  We all need to play our part to stop the spread.  Make sure you know the latest guidance  https://t.co/kZjGNz2EDe https://t.co/Mlg6eiJhje]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,861,999 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 199 to 222,161   The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,630  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/sOigs7ia0e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,869,387 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 250 to 221,962   The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,630  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/d4MnuxR5z7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember to stay local.   Travel within your local authority area is allowed.  But, to stop the spread, we all need to stay close to home wherever we can.  Make sure you understand the rules  https://t.co/kZjGNz2EDe https://t.co/QuAof7yC9V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,853,471 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 281 to 221,712   Sadly 4 more patients who tested positive have died (7,630 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/G8jGpllr6s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,853,471 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 285 to 221,431   Sadly 6 more patients who tested positive have died (7,626 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/yjV8caRmCG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Minister Nicola Sturgeon has shared her condolences with Her Majesty the Queen and the Royal Family, following the death of His Royal Highness, Prince Philip, the Duke of Edinburgh.  Read more  https://t.co/EN6zICp6XO https://t.co/tiSDrFH6I7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Scottish Governments Coronavirus Scottish Parliament 2021 election guidance has been updated with further details on when face-to-face doorstep canvassing can begin.  Read the guidance here  https://t.co/JBnY5qBUMz https://t.co/6bMWJcQeTt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember, if you have any of the below #coronavirus symptoms, self-isolate and book a test straight away:   A new, persistent cough  High temperature  Loss or change in taste or smell  Get tested at https://t.co/NC77zVgzUK https://t.co/2ovNpZYqPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,849,993 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 364 to 221,146  Sadly 1 more patient who tested positive has died (7,620 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/4qO7Kyx1NK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The guidance in Scotland is to stay local. Travel within your local authority is allowed.  But, to stop the spread, we all need to stick to the guidelines.  Read the latest guidance  https://t.co/UKw3KzGdrH https://t.co/wJh79LLlma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,846,486 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 289 to 220,782   Sadly 5 more patients who tested positive have died (7,619 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/GGW1QNAeko]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Minister Nicola Sturgeon has confirmed that almost all pupils in Scotland will return to school full-time after the Easter holidays.    Children who are on the shielding list will continue to learn from home until 26th April.  Read more  https://t.co/7WMwSYqIiD https://t.co/5tfFrTFdZy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,843,048 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 259 to 220,493   The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,614  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/cACLTN0XGZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Watch live: First Minister Nicola Sturgeon gives an update on plans to return to full-time education after the Easter holidays.  Joining the First Minister is Chief Nursing Officer Amanda Croft and National Clinical Director Jason Leitch. https://t.co/4LBVe5UtRv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today First Minister Nicola Sturgeon will give an update on plans to return to full-time education after the Easter holidays.   Watch live here @scotgov from 12pm. https://t.co/3VWev5EoNZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[248 new cases of #coronavirus have been confirmed in Scotland. This brings the total number to 220,234.  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,614.  Latest update   https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/8J0IfJbXCy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From today in Scotland:   More retail services, hairdressers and barbers can open  12-17 year olds can resume outdoor contact sports  More college students can return to campus  #StayLocal unless your journey is essential.  Full details  https://t.co/apvBgDYEd2 https://t.co/icYXZQkOJa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The total number of people in Scotland who have tested positive #coronavirus has risen by 343 to 219,986.  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,614.  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux  Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/HtJMim8QvY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The total number of people in Scotland who have tested positive for #coronavirus has risen 397 to 219,643  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,614  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/eXajPUHAf2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new walk-through testing centre has opened at Edinburgh Clermiston.  There are now 39 walk-through sites across Scotland.   Find the site closest to you at https://t.co/O8R0JjiWBi.  If you have symptoms, book a test immediately  https://t.co/LjnG8pD8me https://t.co/4hNNChfJnw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The total number of people in Scotland who have tested positive for #coronavirus has risen 414 to 219,246  Sadly 4 more patients who tested positive have died (7,614 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/cUl2tVmWev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Scottish Governments Coronavirus Scottish Parliament 2021 election guidance has been updated with further details on when face-to-face doorstep canvassing can begin.  Read the guidance here   https://t.co/I29hZubCPj https://t.co/stfZWJ665q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Know the rules ahead of Easter weekend   Up to 4 adults from 2 households can meet outdoors, including in private gardens.   Dont meet people from other households inside their home or yours.  Travel restrictions remain in place.  #StayLocal rules  https://t.co/apvBgDYEd2 https://t.co/yZMrZHyuX2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If we all play our part we can stop the spread of new infectious coronavirus strains, so we can keep moving forward and get back together again.  Weve come too far. Were not giving in. https://t.co/uX2aRagOAN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,826,274 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 400 to 218,832  Sadly 8 more patients who tested positive have died (7,610 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/16cJEC3KcO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting the vaccine reduces your risk of becoming seriously ill from coronavirus.   When you're invited forward, please roll up your sleeve.  Find out more about the vaccine  https://t.co/p5uea5bHbk https://t.co/mrHF9d4g46]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,821,122 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 542 to 218,432  Sadly 6 more patients who tested positive have died (7,602 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/ACdsbJwIrZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A further cautious easing of lockdown has been confirmed in the latest review of measures.   'Stay Local' will replace the 'Stay at Home' rule from Friday 2 April, and more retail services will be able to open from Monday 5 April.  Read full details  https://t.co/apvBgDYEd2 https://t.co/GX2QqYNYLn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,814,740 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 411 to 217,890  Sadly 12 more patients who tested positive have died (7,596 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/rVRLZ07EES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Watch live: First Minister Nicola Sturgeon gives an update on #coronavirus (#COVID19) restrictions.   Joining the First Minister is Scotlands Chief Medical Officer Dr Gregor Smith and National Clinical Director, Professor Jason Leitch. https://t.co/ea6R96GEgC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today First Minister Nicola Sturgeon will give an update on planned changes to #coronavirus restrictions.   Watch live here @scotgov from 12pm https://t.co/IR0KSipAqM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you wearing your face covering correctly?  Follow these 5 tips to protect yourself and others from #coronavirus   Full guidance at https://t.co/cJp9lTscbY https://t.co/zHNaf1oGKA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,810,709 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 352 to 217,479  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,584  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/CPsaeycqtT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,807,527 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 422 to 217,127  The number of deaths of patients who tested positive remains at 7,584   Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/5K0AW0TMh7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two walk-through testing centres have opened in Dumbarton and Edinburgh Oxgangs.  There are now 38 walk-through sites across Scotland.   Find the site closest to you at https://t.co/O8R0JjiWBi.  If you have symptoms, book a test immediately  https://t.co/Tj1JiBpxnt. https://t.co/LtHmJkynJ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,803,285 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 563 to 216,705  Sadly 6 more patients who tested positive have died (7,584 in total) Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux  Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/r4wdmneivJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The law around organ and tissue donation in Scotland changes to an opt out system from today.  This means that people 16+ who have not recorded a decision about donation will be considered a possible donor when they die.   Record your decision at https://t.co/JBSepoDSXT https://t.co/zDpDjhlFav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,798,430 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 543 to 216,142   Sadly 6 more patients who tested positive have died (7,578 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/DNKFrg4qa0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*Todays positive cumulative cases are not an addition of yesterdays cumulative cases and todays new cases.  177 historical cases were sent in duplicate from the NHS Lothian laboratory and have been excluded from today's cases.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,793,097 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 701 to 215,599*   Sadly 10 more patients who tested positive have died (7,572 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/zhUbkCs5po]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were now in the pre-election period. Our social media activity is restricted until after the @ScotParl election on 6 May.   We will continue to post coronavirus public health information.  Read more information  https://t.co/sa7elHTXdB https://t.co/lnZ5qPoXPU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Social Security Scotland has five family payments for families who get tax credits or certain benefits.  The payments are to help balance your budget and manage family costs, so you can focus on the things that matter to you.  Find out more  https://t.co/lCWWbPi7N8 https://t.co/s0g5T4GkRP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScotGovInter: Today @scotgov publishes Scotland: A Good Global Citizen - our views on defence, security, climate, development  externa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,786,561 people in Scotland have been tested for #coronavirus  The total confirmed as positive has risen by 692 to 215,075   Sadly 3 more patients who tested positive have died (7,562 in total)  Latest update  https://t.co/bZPbrCoQux Health advice  https://t.co/l7rqArB6Qu https://t.co/PHR8ox6oyO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We want to support EU citizens to #StayinScotland.   You can apply even if you don't have a National Insurance Number  Adults and children should apply  Help to apply for the EU Settlement Scheme is available at:  https://t.co/8xKJEJRRx5  0800 916 9847 (free helpline) https://t.co/lXl1EoXpOx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight, Scottish Government buildings will glow yellow.  This marks a National #DayOfReflection to show support for those who have lost loved ones.  Join us by shining a light at 8pm. https://t.co/zkRb5TNYW8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The way in which people have responded to the pandemic has been defined by solidarity, compassion, love and sacrifice."  Watch First Minister @NicolaSturgeon reflect on the last year and thank everyone who has kept Scotland going   #WeAreScotland https://t.co/PEcMOuglDI]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>