<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow. Scandalous!! Well, it DOES always pay to #FollowTheMoney https://t.co/A8GYO7hQwO  https://t.co/JQPKzIbrXW  https://t.co/PzI36z5kQU  https://t.co/W8j5GwRbTH https://t.co/NzGzE8pGG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another great group  newsletter to subscribe to! https://t.co/xplZ4K9605]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure wish people would pay attention! (I recommend everyone subscribe to The Defender newsletter to get up-to-the-minute info on all things Covid. https://t.co/UDMCzJtGBt ++ info on environmental issues as well!) @MikeSchreiner https://t.co/x55lBQ9jKB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#vaccinedeaths @MikeSchreiner @CanadianGreens @OntarioNDP @NDP @OshawaNDP  #waketheheckuplefties!!! @petertabuns @jennkfrench  (subscribe to The Defender at https://t.co/UDMCzJtGBt for more news on vaccine deaths  the REAL Covid-19 agenda) https://t.co/n70SsQ5YuQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any person (or political party) ignoring what's REALLY going on with Covid-1984 is completely irrelevant imo (no; I'm not feeling humble). Subscribe to The Defender newsletter at https://t.co/UDMCzJtGBt to learn about the REAL Covid agenda. The deaths!? Omg.#vaccinedeaths https://t.co/AH9UzbmU8o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't disagree! Human hubris knows no bounds whatsoever. https://t.co/8jJi9tggQz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Credentials?? Geez, humans. #WakeUpAlready https://t.co/nvMRSuOn8p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the friend who tweeted this said, this man is one of our new heroes. He risks much by simply telling the truth. Bless him! https://t.co/svaqyLzsQi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Complicated stuff going on,  I am not keeping up. I suggest folks check out Ms. Frei. I'm including a link to her March 16th piece. A lot has happened since! Please check out her tweets  interviews. https://t.co/ruc1ywcGzj https://t.co/0NjshTyZUj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @canmericanized: @CBCNews @CBCToronto - why am I I doing your job?  Its up to us to decide if we want to give that kind of platform to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oops. I had missed this one too (the NVIC item below). Again, better late than never! (Adding in a graphic from an FDA powerpoint presentation with some inconvenient truths about the vaccine's "possible adverse event outcomes." Found it here: https://t.co/u2PLjF9Yr2) https://t.co/ai6BQH0EH8 https://t.co/UbPgoWyA9t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm a bit behind with this one - but better late than never!? https://t.co/a67J2Qs7ES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChildrensHD: STAY UP-TO-DATE on the latest COVID vaccine headlines from #TheDefender! Sign up TODAY --&gt; https://t.co/cRxbYVSDUq https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Reclaim your voice. Reclaim your health. Reclaim your dignity. Reclaim your autonomy. Reclaim your rights. Reclaim your liber]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking  appalling. https://t.co/xZZkx0XARC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I learned this on the nuclear file. Politicians totally kowtow to Medical Officers of "Health." The MOHs are GODS to the pols. It's a thing. (Is it 'cos the MOHs pull in 3x the salary the politicians do??) https://t.co/Cm522TzdZC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Sotiredofcensorship https://t.co/C4aRCVkeDs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NVICLoeDown: CENSORED: National Vaccine Information Center - The Vaccine Reaction - https://t.co/8dAW6E8C5P   Read Barbara Loe Fishers']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[, since last week's Highwire episode, this: doctors/health experts from around the world explain why these new vaccines are NOT safe. Must-see! https://t.co/BLRgc5yCQK https://t.co/6hgZcnLYWE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let's be more careful here, please - like the Swiss authorities. These vaccines have NOT been proven safe; quite the opposite in fact. Plenty of recent articles attest to this! https://t.co/xyT699qEFu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ so much new science is helping us learn we decidedly do NOT need to inject toxins into our bodies to make our innate (that is; we were BORN with it) immune system work just fine, thanks! #noCovidvaccine for an illness with a 99%+ recovery rate. #LetsGetReal!  #stopthelies https://t.co/OcDhyXWTEw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impt. news from courts re: closure of small businesses. VCC is posting a ton of impt. stuff!! https://t.co/pdZbR0vxDZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One sign also at Queen's Park (Ontario provincial legislature building) today in Toronto! (don't have a photo yet; sorry :( ). FABULOUS activism at work here!! #v4vGlobalDemo https://t.co/vdonR4YwxL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank goodness for all the smart folks rising up! #RiseUp  btw also, thanks to this MD!!! https://t.co/EluOv9Sh0B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Must Read by Harvard Prof @MartinKulldorff  Oxford Prof @SunetraGuptaGreat Barrington Declaration co-authors: "Canadian Cov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well put! Commonsensical! Shouldn't even need to be said, but glad she said it. Sheesh. https://t.co/3ChhAUxtcc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NoLockdowns1: Watch  Retweet: #AdamsonBBQ Skelly is precluded from using social media! This is an egregious Bail Condition since it's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me too! (He sd this months ago. Then changed his tune.) Can't keep up with all the "leaders" who say one thing one minute, then contradict themselves the next. Or, for that matter, all the hypocrisy. "Do as I say, not as I do." Very tired of it. #TurnOffTheLieMachine already. https://t.co/3RJc79a0Wk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: ACTUAL SCIENCE BREAKS OUT !  Real scientist organize and fight back.  Open/public peer review demolishes the PCR test as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Christi45657364: "Top German lawyer, Reiner Fuellmich files lawsuit against Drosten, lead author of the fatality flawed PCR testing pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffereyJaxen: Who knew there were so many #antivaxxers out there? Now doctors and nurses question experimental products w/o liability]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: WATCH + RT my latest "Truth" episode with #Holocaust survivor Vera Sharav on how medical systems can be led astray fro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#onpoli https://t.co/8mk3z6Y8VG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are also excerpts! The Top 5 here: https://t.co/FlWJtvQvku Great reset here: https://t.co/UxqJWLtcaw Mask efficacy study: https://t.co/xYxntYrx45 Whole show = dynamite! #YayHighwire https://t.co/arvgYsRoDG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: An all star line up of speakers attending our https://t.co/s8FjqISR3d  pots  pans  rally tomorrow. Join us and get you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If only more people understood the fraud of this "casedemic" that is not a real pandemic at all. The real pandemic is fear - media-induced. #turnoffmainstreammedia https://t.co/A4bH3n4G7I https://t.co/WMczjMDUzn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If only our "leaders" would listen! https://t.co/HBusodXyWQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The PCR test, eh? Not merely flawed; entirely, utterly, completely fraudulent. (But we know science does not matter to our "leaders." Science  truth have been murdered. Deliberately.) https://t.co/MPXtIG6TUw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kids are the innocent civilians in this war on humans. Imagine keeping our innocent children from being able to BREATHE properly! This is what is being done! But #WeAreWakingUp ( squawking. More of that is needed! Loud squawking  protests. Lots of both!) https://t.co/k0qWbXhLw5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yup. Compliance. Masks are about compliance, though it seems most humans don't "get" this yet. #screwthenewworldorder https://t.co/Q5wd0uAPBr https://t.co/XD1eB3NkHc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good to have him on record with this. #CovidBS (the BS part is the whole use of PCR testing.  the false positives.  the media hype. The fear. The masks. There is a LOT of BS we are talking about here!?) https://t.co/ndBdLHNgmD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The resistance grows  grows! #WeAreWakingUp https://t.co/R6JJM6SFMF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We all need to study up on how to live with the amount of cognitive dissonance with which we are daily assaulted.  most are so unaware, it's scary. https://t.co/9pJCvAAl6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wonder how many adverse reactions here in Ontario?? Been wondering about this after the debacle/deaths in South Korea. https://t.co/CqPZ914uAc https://t.co/G13Y0yKFaW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: An opinion piece today in the Vancouver Sun reveals that as of September 1st, 276 people have died of COVID-19 in B.C.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So good to hear some good news! https://t.co/1LlQgDsVje]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Agreed! https://t.co/wUOkM6LUcf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure do!! https://t.co/jC92D7UK7j https://t.co/ywUtndUj9d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Agreed; we've been dead wrong about autism. What causes it. What's really going on inside the autistic person. Holy, we've been wrong about so many things, haven't we?? But #wearewakingup https://t.co/8Q1RV4D0DK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Thats the CDCs way of saying: these policies are killing people." https://t.co/2L9GbgMMuX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOBS of great links in this! #reportinginconvenienttruths https://t.co/3b6YTCgyYe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrChrisNorthrup: Truth bomb. https://t.co/QMU1CRj8iZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: Yep! The #GreatReset is about multinational corporate stakeholders at the @WEF controlling as many elements of planet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How well put! Indeed! Where ARE those "coincidental" deaths?? https://t.co/hKZ8bIHJQA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elevator etiquette! Guidance for the sheepish, who apparently must be taught how to ride elevators "properly." #elevatoretiquette (Wish I was making it up!? Face the wall, no less!? I would not have believed it if I had not seen it for myself.) https://t.co/sLOnEurdFt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...but we are not surprised, are we? There's a stampede on for this vaccine, apparently. As always, people need to be sure  read the small print. ( also #FTM, as in, #FollowTheMoney) https://t.co/AzF5vVj3gl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So happy to see this item. Somebody who's not been bought by Big Pharma! https://t.co/z8FLBEXNMN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChildrensHD: We want to know whether the US or Chinese governments, or scientists affiliated with them, are concealing data about the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can you say "Follow the money?" Lotsa folks just don't "get" who really stands to gain here. It sure ain't us! #BigPharmaCleansUp https://t.co/WGRwaNEmr5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lots of great quotations about science here: https://t.co/wWQ75HwpvH Many of them will surprise you! #QuestionEverything https://t.co/MlRb8fmW6R https://t.co/0Mh4sXkCw2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I can't keep up to the death count on this. Holeeee. #flushotdeaths? https://t.co/iBLfuKzmW6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TheDefender https://t.co/HmuR07t9Ft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VaccineChoiceCA: Just posted a photo https://t.co/Zl6vlzHAn4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow. The total just keeps rising! Can't keep up with this death toll. #justacoincidence eh? https://t.co/w6vfN2CcUS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All true, sadly. #topsyturvyworld Tired of the ad hominem stuff, that's for sure. VERY tired of all the censorship, too. https://t.co/SMZxpLZFkw https://t.co/g5icDZB3QG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eileeniorio: Project Coincidence has begun.   "Five people have died... raising concerns over the vaccine's safety just as the winter j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow. They admit right up front (well, technically, at the end of the report), how compromised their work is. Whoa. #conflictofinterest https://t.co/Czir5MuOxo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: Ford gets pushback on lockdowns from his own MPPs.  https://t.co/zXdPMdhhwF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't keep up with all the contradictory messages  directives from the so-called "health" "authorities." The reversals. The lies. Just exhausted by it all. Not to mention #disgusted https://t.co/BBEvGXi42Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: Join me, @roccogalatilaw, @MaximeBernier, @Bbawa, in Queens Park, north of the ON Legislature tomorrow at 10 AM. Leave y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More good info in the responses to the tweet. #JohnsonandJohnsonSucksREALBad https://t.co/SQ0QsqhJRB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doozy of a video! Of interest to all with curiosity and concerns about the science behind Covid testing, those with German connections (why did it play out the way it did in Germany??),  any who expect the Green Party to "save" us. #CrimesAgainstHumanity https://t.co/HqDrjt9qAG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yup. Our rational mind just plain checks out when we're living in fear. #wakeuphumans https://t.co/4OB6MuICl0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I guess some of us are just a bit silly! #noflushotformethanks https://t.co/652O4AF4ex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yum. #Not. https://t.co/kdgbyZ1aft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Using "wipes" eh? Most of these things are toxic. But never mind, I am quibbling. Let's just say "Woo-hoo," shall we?? https://t.co/5gfSWoNb8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media lie like mad. They push an AGENDA. YOU know this. I know this. Trudeau knows it too. #TurnOffTheLieMachine already. Here are some musings (along with some good quotes  graphics) about gurus  media, in the context of Covid-1984. https://t.co/42dvSBMS6k https://t.co/GSCNEJdkPo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fabulous, informative conversation! Those who consider themselves "good scientists" really ought to listen to this. #areflushotssafe #areflushotseffective #areflushotsdangerous #flushotinjury #vaccineinjury https://t.co/oqoEjj392k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was slow to get to this. Looks like a must-read! Colour me #NotSurprised if health "authorities" are concealing data. I have many years of experience under my belt as an activist learning NOT to trust "health" "authorities." On nukes. On vaccines. On incineration. Etc. etc. etc https://t.co/h8uvhwlGgm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FABULOUS article,  super-timely!!! #areflushotssafe #areflushotseffective #areflushotsdangerous #DoYourResearch (here's my flu shots posting from last year; clearly needs updating! https://t.co/yOeOfV3IKR) https://t.co/iMZZRK2rBn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Were it not for the test data that you get from the TV all the time, you would rightly conclude that the pandemic was over, as nothing much has happened.Of course people go 2 hospital, moving in2 the autumn flu season...but there is no science to suggest a 2nd wave shld happen." https://t.co/th6nlQ9XgT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank goddess for brave, smart, integrity-filled individuals! https://t.co/mlCgLIgUhB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: 2/ I have signed their Great Barrington Declaration calling on govts globally for a humane, scientific approach to #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Wonderful news! Oxford Prof @SunetraGupta, Harvard Prof @MartinKulldorff  Stanford Prof Jay Bhattacharya met in the US over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['cos almost everyone is bought. Sold their souls for  a paycheque  pension. Upton Sinclair said It is difficult to get a man to understand something when his salary depends upon his not understanding it. Good item about the "casedemic" phenomenon here: https://t.co/B0CNQM4D0i https://t.co/A4sYetVqhy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just don't see how the word murder can be avoided. I really can't. https://t.co/KvciPOeSFy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The always-articulate, frequently-irreverent (but truth-telling) Rocco Galati. #YayRocco https://t.co/bWpCLrqK8y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure lotsa folks awake there!! #wakeuphumans https://t.co/ESktAj2dtf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most humans have no idea vaccines are not properly tested for safety. Or about $4B paid out to vaccine-injured families. Or the babies who die after DTaP shots. Or flu shots. Or MMR shots. I could go on. #WakeUpHumans #WeAreWakingUp Read vaccine inserts!! https://t.co/QOoAQxVBzb https://t.co/aZXqRJZTmC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure hope the answer to this question is a resounding Yes! #questionvaccines #whatsinvaccines #vaccinesnotproperlytestedforsafety #QuestionEverything https://t.co/xYrtDJXBuj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good item to share widely  talk with your peeps about! #handsanitizersaredangerous https://t.co/XZoLHkDIli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta has quietly dropped distancing. https://t.co/oJ72LzVjdR Does anyone "in charge" in Ontario have a shred of common sense left? The ability to think critically? The ability to connect dots? Or read?? Listen to the experts at Sick Kids hospital! https://t.co/i9yPqhlwyb https://t.co/itplIMuyW5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some common sense in the world of U.S. politics! https://t.co/nfYvJ5nmIm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS guy is a breath of fresh air! Has a brain. Can talk. Reason. Use common sense. Wow! I'd sure rather have him as premier of Ontario than Mr. Buck-a-beer Ford. Sheesh. https://t.co/tVRN92bFyO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HighWireTalk: Heart attack deaths up 50% during lockdown, high blood pressure deaths rose by 1/3, diabetes by 1/4 among under 65s, same]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I found this item super-helpful, super-worth sharing with friends/colleagues. I include it in my little collection of Covid "humdingers." https://t.co/kG7kUh6k9m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So go on ahead  trust the testing, if you like. I sure don't. Not even slightly! Spread the word.... (See this 9-minute video on testing: https://t.co/MrcPqKcUYX )  to repeat: #AWomanDeadFor7MonthsGotLetterSayingSheTestedPositiveforCovid!!! https://t.co/pxNjepa1n0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting... I wonder if they will become truth-tellers?? Sure hope so. #TurnOffTheLieMachine (lots of great quotations about truth here https://t.co/DhoxoHmmSM ) https://t.co/FTehFkVJz4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Article is not new (it's from June 23rd). But I can testify that I see around me (here in Toronto) wildly out-of-proportion fear about this illness. Facts don't seem to persuade most. It's ... weird. (I have a button that says #KillYourTelevision. Sure wish people would do it!?) https://t.co/E1hsIqzRuy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GraalTruth: Print It!  @zorogat @matteo_rivi @AntonioSocci1 @CristinaDragani @a_meluzzi @alexkx3 @HaraldofW @princesseffel @FatEmperor]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>