<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Two new publications our from our #indiacovid Task Force, Country-wide Containment Strategies Report at https://t.co/u6GJ5YxLga and a Containment Checklist at https://t.co/Tg0ihalR3B. @Chandrika0501 @epigiri @ChinmayTumbe @CPR_India @oommen  @gargsuneela @_KavitaNarayan @thePHFI https://t.co/nxofQOGIR9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thePHFI: Country-wide Containment Strategies for Reducing #COVID-19 Cases in India: @Commissioncovid India Task Force Lancet Commission]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfespinosaEC: The impacts of the #COVID19 pandemic and #ClimateChange are making the levels of public debt of Small Island Developing S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New publication on #school #infrastructure; better ventilation  air cycling reduces risk of #COVID19 transmission today, makes for healthier kids tomorrow. At https://t.co/ZTevcH2ClW. @j_g_allen @CorsIAQ @ShellyMBoulder @linseymarr @meiralevinson @MarissaVanry @drdavidmichaels https://t.co/818gVkPk6M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfespinosaEC: Comparto mi artculo en el @Planeta_Futuro @el_pais sobre la recuperacin post-#COVID19 con IGUALDAD y desde la accin co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McMasterU: "No one is truly safe from COVID-19 until everyone is safe." John Lavis and fellow members of @TheLancet @Commissioncovid ta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNSDSN: Join our team! SDSN is hiring a Communications Consultant who will help support communication and social media efforts for SDS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Global Health #Diplomacy Task Force Member Ok Pannenborg is speaking April 20 in a @ForeignPolicy dialogue! Hope to see you there! https://t.co/YrwUWNe5VE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLancet: On the coverIt's almost a year since the formation of the Access to #COVID19 Tools Accelerator (ACT-A) partnership. The pan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India Task Force's new publication calls for vaccinations  renewed focus on NPIs, no blanket lockdowns, only localized restrictions. Read at https://t.co/OpTmczPRMW #COVIDSecondWave @thePHFI @MoHFW_India @ICMR @TheLancet @epigiri @ChinmayTumbe @CPR_India @oommen @Chandrika0501 https://t.co/kbnf1bzzDq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNSDSN:  Do you have real-world examples of actions that mitigate greenhouse gases and benefit health? The @LSHTM_Planet Pathfinder In]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfespinosaEC: Today for #WorldHealthDay I share  this message, especially dedicated to health and care workers.  Health is not a commo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New article from @SusanMichie @DrChrisBullen @JVLazarus @lavisjn @jwthwaites on #COVID19 #variants warns #vaccine will not be enough. https://t.co/3Mz3v2WBwe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New piece in @TheLancet from our #Vaccines  Therapeutics Task Force examines key questions relevant to global vaccine #security, #justice, #equity, and #diplomacy. Read at https://t.co/HSEb7VNqFV https://t.co/aBLF46qj5e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new tool in the fight against #COVID19, @sdgstoday's new dashboard, updated weekly, is full of interesting data like #COVAX Facility committments and purchase agreements. Our #FridayMotivation to end this #pandemic! https://t.co/tUglKVodMp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sdgstoday: Want to follow #COVID19Vaccine purchases across the globe with us?  Our dashboard ft. @DukeGhic data displays maps of purch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sdsn_TReNDS: How can #data be leveraged to support #LMICs vaccine prioritization? Register for this event on April 15 to learn more  h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We spend most of our time inside. But how do building conditions affect the spread of COVID-19? The Task Force on Safe Work, Safe School, and Safe Travel examines the role of building ventilation systems in their statement: https://t.co/Spawhk4uqC @UNSDSN @ShellyMBoulder https://t.co/SFczhp3hA8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lbaknin: The World Happiness Report is out now and takes a close look at how mental health, life evaluations, and social connections ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ITUSecGen: No issue is more important to @ITU than ensuring everyone can benefit from the digital technologies+services that have prove]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one is safe until everyone is safe says the Task Force on #PublicHealth Measures to control #COVID19, new report available at https://t.co/jWNc0Amrx8 @DrChrisBullen @agaviriau @UNSDSN @jwthwaites https://t.co/0AX4bdrHN2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does global recovery present an opportunity for #sustainable, #inclusive, and #resilient development? The #Green Recovery Task Force published its first statement to answer that very question. Available at https://t.co/72nqiuY7Mp. @pkoundouri @I_Serageldin @UNSDSN https://t.co/foCWMI1V2I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GabyCuevas: Una reunin productiva en la @Commissioncovid hoy. Como Copresidenta, compart los planes del grupo de trabajo sobre Ayuda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfespinosaEC: Today we presented the progress of the Task Force on Global Health Diplomacy and Cooperation before the @TheLancet COVID-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mebottazzi: Latest from the #Vaccine and #Therapeutics Task Force of the @TheLancet Commission on #COVID19. Read our primer for healthc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfespinosaEC: #Covid19Vaccine roll out and distribution should guarantee equity, fairness, transparency, and be well funded. Cooperati]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An analysis of #COVID19 task forces from 87 countries found only 3.5% had gender parity. For a more inclusive future, women must be involved in the #COVID19 response  recovery. On #IWD2021, join us and @UN_Women to demand more women in decision-making! https://t.co/CJ7AQQyxq3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No matter which way you slice the data  it seems the mental health in many nations around the world has declined, which is not particularly surprising, - #COVID19 Commissioner @lbaknin. She talks #mentalhealth  more in this interview w/ @VancouverSun  https://t.co/4evkdAJqxz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HappinessRpt: .@lbaknin Associate Editor of the @HappinessRpt shares the research done with The Lancet @Commissioncovid with The @Vanco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ISGLOBALorg: The Lancet @Commissioncovid in which #ISGlobal is a participant- has published a statement outlining the priorities that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The #COVID19 pandemic is unlikely to end until there is global roll-out of vaccines that protect against severe disease and drive herd immunity."   Read this article published by the  @TheLancet to understand the challenges receiving the vaccine-&gt; https://t.co/YitHA1Kjqr https://t.co/eAcVeA36Fd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @womeninGH: Women's unpaid and underpaid care work must be recognized. At the #GenderEqualHCW initiative launch, @mfespinosaEC discusses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This article from @NatGeo identifies the link between human-led deforestation and disease transmission: increased human-forest interactions are causing the weakening of disease containment as an ecosystem service.  Read more about deforestation here: https://t.co/JUBjzhINiL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow our Facebook and Linkedin Pages to stay more connected and updated to the Covid Commission!   https://t.co/ACls9wzwUR https://t.co/MDI6EnpWPw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tracking R offers, in real-time, estimates of the Effective Reproduction Rate of #COVID19.   For further information on their methodology, see Tracking R of COVID-19: A New Real-Time Estimation  -&gt;   https://t.co/fEEwLWE6XC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ISGLOBALorg: How many years of life have been lost to #COVID19 globally? Any novelty regarding possible treatments? Are approved vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Covid Commissioner Miriam Khamadi Were. Dr. Were  became Head of the Department of Community Health at the University of Nairobi in 1982.   In 1985, she was appointed Head of Health and Nutrition at UNICEF Ethiopia.   Read more about Dr. Ware here https://t.co/OromOMcJvC https://t.co/mbGFRikBc4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNSDSN: The Lancet COVID-19 Commission recently released, Enhancing Global Cooperation to End the COVID-19 Pandemic: Statement of the L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Checkout the Covid Commission Media Archives of all relevant articles, interviews, and press release about the work and information concerning the pandemic. https://t.co/ckJHYTRd8B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This FAO report from July 2020 shows the public on food system disruptions from #COVID19 in Africa by country level. The report details a variety of updates, ranging from violence towards farming groups, to advancements in relief efforts. Read more here-&gt; https://t.co/0dAz7VvjLQ https://t.co/PAiVP3sNE4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read a new op-ed on the Demand Side of the Pandemic: How it is vital to get people on board beforehand and ready to take preventive measures, including vaccinations  Read here: https://t.co/YkX0KJvoUt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 Commission is proud to share, "Enhancing Global Cooperation to End the COVID-19 Pandemic: Statement of the Lancet COVID-19 Commission."  The statement details the top three priorities to suppress the pandemic in 2021. Read here:  https://t.co/mDSDbFFtJB https://t.co/7SGIAfgtwi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a recently published comment in @TheLancet, the #COVID19 Commission calls for three urgent actions in the COVID-19 response.  Read the full comment here: https://t.co/oXbHGOFoSc https://t.co/0tCiYnx3Xl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OKaradagCaman: Honored to be one of the contributors!  Enhancing Global Cooperation to End the COVID-19 Pandemic: Statement of the Lanc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is an urgent need for #COVID19 vaccines and therapeutics in low-income and middle-income countries . Read more in this piece from #COVID19 task force members, No Nation can Stand Alone in this Pandemic -&gt; https://t.co/1qGPCcdaXq https://t.co/AQR20e8Kwa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women scientists and medical staff are on the frontlines to combat #COVID19 . On International Day of Women and Girls in science, meet and read about some of the #WomenInScience who are putting their lives on the line! https://t.co/tURNMI7OsF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Rates of #COVID19 cases remain high. In the last 7 days, the United States has averaged more than 107,000 new cases of COVID-19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Economic recovery plans to #COVID19 should support the transition towards sustainable and inclusive societies based on the #SDGs and the #ParisClimateAgreement. Public investment should be oriented towards sustainable industries and the digital economy,-&gt; https://t.co/IG8TnR7U1k https://t.co/C9UswHc4tp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Covid Commissioner Dr. Peter Hotez.@PeterHotez is an internationally-recognized physician-scientist. As head of Texas Childrens CVD, he leads a product development partnership for developing new vaccines for #COVID19 Read more about Dr. Hotez here -&gt; https://t.co/5qeyNOSg98 https://t.co/JFmC2mZVJ1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There must be a considerable global effort by the international financing institutions to restructure debt and provide development aid. https://t.co/FQ0Tf6bRol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There has been a sharp drop in public revenues at all government levels, and the situation for developing countries is particularly dire as countries are unable to finance social services and protection programs. https://t.co/kcK9VeAUfe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: 3 factors that can help you make safe choices when you're in an area of widespread #COVID19 transmission: (1) Location (2) Proxi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: The illusion that things have gotten much better when they're still worse than the first 9 months of the pandemic. Not a tim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: As we mark a year of the ongoing #COVID19 pandemic, WHO thanks donors  partners for their support  contribution in boosting coun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since underlying health conditions increase the risk of #COVID19 , understanding the number of people at risk  and how this varies between countries should inform the design of strategies to shield those at high risk. Read more about it @TheLancet here-&gt; https://t.co/8v1UHrWI5F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medical populism in which leaders spread false information about medical knowledge to downplay the virus or spectacularize the crisis, has contributed  to this failure. Learn more about the failure of the suppression of the pandemic from our task force-&gt; https://t.co/luYf2hHQpP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Several countries have failed to suppress the pandemic. This is often due to a failure to implement the full package of NPIs, as well as high inequality, low social trust, and political polarization. https://t.co/9JXq6cb9Ed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This article from @Nature reflects on historical insights gained about pandemic prevention and suggests the importance of the behavioral and social sciences, as well as the prioritization of health communication. https://t.co/KMuhSOVuIK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfespinosaEC: It is critical to multiply the manufacturing capacity for the #COVID19 #vaccines and guarantee provision, access and depl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UNICEF reported in August 2020 how school closures worens inequalities in access to education. This report shows inequalities across the world and promotes its Framework for Reopening Schools as a tool for policy reform, Click here to learn more-&gt; @UNICEF https://t.co/tiZOMA4awL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Covid Commissioner Mara Fernanda Espinosa. Maria is a diplomat with more than 30 years of experience in non-governmental and international organizations. She's an expert in foreign policy within the United Nations. Full bio here: https://t.co/lZBuAGaLqH  @mfespinosaEC @UN https://t.co/4jtPt1Gdcx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 Data Repository by the Center for Systems Science and Engineering (CSSE) at Johns Hopkins University tracks the number of confirmed COVID-19 cases, deaths and recoveries for all affected countries. https://t.co/xE4upwoiNV @JohnsHopkins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See how your community is moving around differently due to #COVID19. The reports chart movement trends over time by geography, across different categories of places such as retail and recreation, groceries, parks, workplaces, and residential -&gt; https://t.co/yUzk17ypen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Share your #COVID19 experience and improve public health insights! @YouGovUS COVID-19 Public Monitor gather[s] information about COVID-19, asking people to share their experiences of the global pandemic.  Access here -&gt; https://t.co/uLMNXjtzRc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLancet: Pregnant women were excluded from early #COVID19 vaccine research and are not a high-priority group for vaccination. With ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Covid Commissioner Muhammad Ali Pate. He is the Global Director, Health, Nutrition and Population Dr. Pate, a U.S. and Nigerian national, was until recently the Chief Executive Officer of Big Win Philanthropy, based in the UK.-&gt; https://t.co/YYj5FQEkf5 @muhammadpate https://t.co/IRxvteLIDN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The death rate for Nipah virus is up to 75% and it has no vaccine. While the world focuses on Covid-19, scientists are working hard to ensure it doesn't cause the next pandemic." Read more on ways scientist are being proactive in preventing pandemics -&gt;https://t.co/2bxDQIqpcG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Coronavirusgoo1: Massive news coming out of Israel:  60% reduction in infections among 60+ years old 13-23 days after first dose https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @moderna_tx: We just announced that the Moderna COVID-19 Vaccine retains neutralizing activity against emerging variants first identifie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HoustonHealth: #COVID19 vaccines currently in development in the US do not use the live virus that causes COVID-19. Symptoms like fever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNSDSN: Stay up to date on The Lancet #COVID19 Commission by following @Commissioncovid ! https://t.co/3wBBagmd0T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This article highlights how #COVID19 is a syndemic pandemic, as the inequalities are directly related to the social determinants of health, and result in an unequal economic impact. The authors show similar results of the 1918 Spanish influenza pandemic. https://t.co/zzK8p7Ba7o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: As of January 18, national forecasts predict that 17,000 to 29,300 new #COVID19 deaths will be reported during the week ending]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AFP: #UPDATE In a dramatic about-turn, the new US administration on Thursday thanked the World Health Organization (#WHO) for leading t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This article describes the next steps planned in China that follow the containment effort, and encourages global cooperation to manage the COVID-19 pandemic Read more China's prevention strategies for #COVID19 @TheLancet   https://t.co/r3fqn6lsvr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: Should people who have had #COVID19 still get vaccinated? https://t.co/ROBtyg0SzY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: WHO's Healthy Cities @Viber sticker pack!   Show your friends  family how you are staying healthy  happy in your city during #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LancetGH: The February issue is now live! #visionloss #blindness #diabetes #COVID19 #NCDs #GBD #cervicalcancer #anaemia #malaria #South]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This @WHO  report highlights the disruption of immunizations due to #COVID19, as well as previous concerns over the virus transmission when attempting to receive vaccinations. The authors stress the importance of the delivery of routine vaccinations.  https://t.co/LICaUJqrGJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@UNICEF published in May 2020 that #COVID19  will significantly impact maternal and infant mortality. It provides models from the Lancet Global Health journal, and incorporates how access to food and missed immunizations add to high rates of mortality https://t.co/DGn7Dd6w6Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How has #COVID19 impacted teenage girls in #Kenya? Pregnancies in young girls have risen due to the increase of transactional sex to help support their families financially. School closures have increased sexual violence and healthcare systems are strained https://t.co/NHuay2H7dR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time Magazine reports how #COVID19 has disproportionately affected women in major industries of the U.S. economy, accounting for more job losses than men in every sector. Experts report that this is due to women having to balance employment and family care.https://t.co/CHNqPcnVV1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This UN report lays out a socioeconomic response plan to compliment existing health #COVID19 response plans. The framework consists of: 1. Health  2. Social  3. Environment  4. Economic Protections for vulnerable populations  https://t.co/pB7XtaB1Ky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The @IMFNews is providing financial assistance and debt service relief to member countries facing the economic impact of the #COVID19 pandemic. This page provides an overview of assistance approved by the IMFs Executive Board since March 2020." https://t.co/W1kjRapceA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Lancet #COVID19 Commissioner Gabriela Cuevas Barron @Medios_GCB She was elected Federal Member of Parliament for the first time when she was 21 years old. Since then, she has been three times Federal Member of Parliament. -&gt; https://t.co/udHz2dSqd4 https://t.co/q7BcgjrtXu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Research shows that the #COVID19 pandemic has the potential to push 100 million people into poverty on a global scale. Read more on this impact from @WEF -&gt; https://t.co/sPZZjNXMZL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 has major economics impacts: the article reveals old and underlying deep racial and socioeconomic divides, and the recent protests of demanding reform of systems of policing that have harmed black people for centuries -&gt;  https://t.co/pxKypB541P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out the Oxford #COVID19 Government Response Tracker which systematically collects information on policy responses that governments have taken, looking at 17 indicators such as travel restrictions, and has data from more than 180 countries.  https://t.co/0irdA0nqrn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Kirsten Brosbl, a member of the Covid Commission and founder of Parliamentarians for the Global Goals: a  global initiative for parliamentarians who work on the 2030 agenda. She founded and chaired the Danish Parliaments All-Party Group on the #SDGs https://t.co/vl8gfSxpzk https://t.co/ZHj0TUOMFJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy New Year from the #Covid Commission! Thank you to everyone from the Commission for their hard work in promoting solutions to improve public health and support economic recovery from #COVID19 Please continue to follow us for more updates pertaining to #COVID19 this year. https://t.co/UvqjHGjs8M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sdsn_TReNDS: As African countries continue to confront the challenges posed by #COVID19, a recent @nytimes underscores the importance o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How has #COVID19 impacted #SDG1? The @WorldBank reports that due to COVID-19, extreme poverty is likely to increase ~.5-1%, representing 71 million more people. The extreme poor will be concentrated mostly in South Asia (~50%) and Sub-Saharan Africa (~33%) https://t.co/6iWYtIeE3o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Commissioner Laurence Boone. Boone is the OECD Chief Economist and Head of the Economics Department. In her role on the Lancet Commission, Ms. Boone will be supported by Ms. Francesca Colombo, Head of the Health Division at the OECD. @LauBooneEco https://t.co/UFKUVluH04 https://t.co/NIElcFw8GJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Commissioner Dr. Joseph Allen. Allen is an associate professor of exposure science at the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health and has been involved with infectious disease research and control strategies for over 12 years.  https://t.co/k2ftWIFRUc https://t.co/53aVju82V0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOWPRO: @takeshi_kasai @Commissioncovid @JeffDSachs @Nadokoulu @aumeah @minhealthnz @minhealthci @DrLiAilan @healthgovau @MOFAkr_eng @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lbaknin: @Commissioncovid And beyond honoured to have the input of these exceptional scholars: @DunnHappyLab @Daisy_Fancourt @jedeneve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Commissioner Dr. Lara Aknin. Dr. Aknin is an Associate Professor of Psychology at Simon Fraser University, former Fellow with the Canadian Institute for Advanced Research. Read more about Dr. Atkin. @lbaknin https://t.co/QiIzHMGhPc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOWPRO: Dont miss the @WHOWPRO x @TheLancet @commissionCOVID forum where countries across Asia and the Pacific will share lessons on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Commissioner Dr. Salim Abdool Karim, a South African clinical infectious diseases epidemiologist. He is the Chair of the South African Ministerial Advisory Committee on COVID-19. Read more about Dr. Salim's work on our website https://t.co/suBGOAfBQY https://t.co/tALZkSJ9we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid-19 has had a devastating effect on the elderly populations. Read the details in the article from this UNA-UK. https://t.co/MNIObaqJce  #COVID19 #CovidVaccine]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>