<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to advertise on behalf of the Government that there is a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Can you help us to knock the lying mainstream media off their perch? We cant do it without your support... https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Weve started a Summer Fundraising Campaign which will allow us to finally knock the mainstream media off their perch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report propaganda on behalf of the Government.  Meanw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING - We can't ignore the link between the C0V1D Jab roll-out and sudden rising "C0V1D" Deaths any longer, India is one coincidence too far... https://t.co/tJklyI8w77]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: @BBCNews take millions of s of your money by law to report propaganda and lies on behalf of the U.K. Government.  Me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report lies and propaganda on behalf of the Governmen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews:    ... We rely solely on your support, can you help us to knock the lying Mainstream Media off their Per]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Summer Fundraising Campaign  Help us to knock the Mainstream Media off theirperch https://t.co/s7H2RNXhlc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews:  During the year of the "Deadly" Pandemic the NHS had its quietest year in decades . Occupied NHS beds were 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - Dr Mike Yeadon has revealed to us in an exclusive interview that There is no logic to the statement that w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - A whistle-blowing Senior NHS Board Member has come forward to say the UK Government has taken full control]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - You are being lied to and manipulated by the mainstream media inluding @BBCNews about the Covid Crisis in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: We need your help to fight back against the censorship and compete with the mainstream media... https://t.co/spReSP5Upa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Love what we do? Then please help us to keep doing it.. https://t.co/spReSOOj0A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Google, Social Media  Fact Checkers are doing their best to discredit us. You will by know that all our investigations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Pfizer document confirms 'C0V1D Vaccine Shedding' leading to 'Menstrual Cycle Disruption' and 'Miscarriage' is possible]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - A whistle-blowing Senior NHS Board Member has exposed that the UK Government has taken full control of the NH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING- The C0V -1D jabs are so safe that just 722,732 adverse reactions have been reported to the MHRA including se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - Pfizer document confirms 'C0V1D Vaccine Shedding' leading to 'Menstrual Cycle Disruption' and 'Miscarriage']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Its time to knock the mainstream media off their perch... Please Support us today in our mission to bring you more of t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Mainstream media are paid millions of s of your money to report propaganda for the Government.  @BBCNews take millio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Every time we follow the money it leads us to Bill Gates... https://t.co/kS2mciBc1N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DisparatePost: Know this -  https://t.co/mwUcFZTatX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING- A tragic milestone has been surpassed. Over 1000 deaths have now been reported to the MHRA as adverse reacti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Whistle-blowing NHS Board Member says The Government are committing Genocide, and your children are next https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: First they came for the elderly, and I did not speak out because I was not old. Then they came for the disabled, and I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Silverf34781188: Young good looking lady, life ruined https://t.co/lZziqlwKuf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - Adverse Reactions to the C0V* -1D jabs now include 9,723 blood disorders, 10,633 eye disorders including blin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sapiofoxxxxxxxy: A freedom of information request made to Public Health Scotland has revealed that 2,207 people died within twenty-eigh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - Woman left paralysed from the neck down after having Pfizer C0V1D jab... https://t.co/2FR7ZEgZAG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: A huge group of Doctors from around the world have united to tell the public that the C0V1D jabs are Unnecessary, ine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Matt Hancock has blood on his hands https://t.co/ypFNmvup8n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - Two teenage girls suffer cardiac arrest and sadly lose their lives after having the Pfizer C0V1D jab... htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Injecting a child with an experimental Covid-19 vaccine would be madness, they dont need it https://t.co/wTwnGhaJb8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BoylieBoyle: Really have a look at this one. Warning: Dark https://t.co/bY1F0XbJxk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1keydonkey: This article explores some notable distortions in the way MSM is covering Covid in India. Everything is not as it seems! ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: You are being manipulated and coerced into taking an experimental jab.  How do we know this? Because the tactics are all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - Adverse Reactions to the C0V* -ID jabs now include 9723 blood disorders, 10,633 eye disorders including blind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Think how much has been sacrificed by the British people to 'protect the NHS'.  People have lost everything - jobs, busin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmandaF48429802 Have a link?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heachy_1979 @JS49 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@David28787016 @magicbu92001094 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WeWillBeFree82 @Ben78__ https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveG06322664 @GillianMcKeith https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GillianMcKeith https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wetbadgers @perfectpolly20 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anthea06274890 @IMchaffie https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlackersNot @SteveG06322664 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickAdamsinUSA https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Telegraph https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EndUKLockdown1 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KathyConWom: I am appealing to every Conservative and every Londoner who values truth and honesty to vote for @LozzaFox as the capita]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KathyConWom @SimonPearson961 @LozzaFox https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: NOT ON BBC 'NEWS': BELGIAN POLICE TRAMPLE PROTESTORS (It's for your safety!) https://t.co/wVM8pT04fg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Demo2020cracy @SteveG06322664 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 @Rainbowandsteel https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoodyBluesv2 @PoliticsForAlI @ChathamHouse https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @ChathamHouse https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JJacqs59 https://t.co/FXLmp3AEHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING - You are being lied to and manipulated by the mainstream media inluding @BBCNews about the Covid Crisis in India, in order to maintain the level of fear which has been induced in the population since March 2020... https://t.co/m74P22WlAE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CollinsMikeyc: Fear-mongering, Lies and Propaganda - Uncovering the Truth about India's alleged "Covid Crisis" https://t.co/1Q5qIEDgxX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Climber551970: Whistle-blowing NHS Board Member says The Government are committing Genocide, and your children are next  Daily Expos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReformUK_EA: When are people going to stop, think, research this experimental biologic  what it does when it enters the body.   Just l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Andrew41544161: Heartbreaking  Two year old dies after having the Pfizer Covid Vaccine  Daily Expose https://t.co/1GqOwC1vWq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Meggone2: SHOCKING!  U.K. Government release 13th report on Adverse Reactions to the Covid Vaccines  Daily Expose https://t.co/b5vP1F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews:     A Daily Expose Investigation...  Untangling the web of Fear-mongering, lies, and propaganda b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Summer Fundraising Campaign  Help us to knock the Mainstream Media off their perch https://t.co/qvrzQuorpS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Part 2 of our investigation into the Covid Crisis in India untangles a web of deceit, lies, and propaganda thats been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @In_Hope_: @DDurwent They must have vheard about the genocide.  Whistle-blowing NHS Board Member says The Government are committing Gen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING - The mainstream medias narrative on the Covid Crisis in India is nothing more than Fear-mongering, lies and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Whistle-blowing NHS Board Member says The Government are committing Genocide, and your children arenext https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: UK Gov. awards 320 million tax-payer funded contract for Covid-19 Media Propaganda Campaign which runs until April 20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LynnBrittney2: NHS Board Member whistleblower says they had great doubts about the 'vaccines', "but in a nutshell, what we were told in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report lies propaganda on behalf of the Government.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews take millions of s of your money by law to report propaganda and lies on behalf of the U.K. Government.  Meanwhile we report the facts that they refuse to and rely solely on your support.  Please support us today... https://t.co/eqjlBqHnYv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report propaganda on behalf of the Government.  Meanwhile we report the truth and rely solely on your support.  Please support us today... https://t.co/eqjlBqpN6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report lies propaganda on behalf of the Government.  Meanwhile we report the facts the mainstream refuse to and rely solely on your support.  Help us to become the new mainstream media.  Support us today... https://t.co/eqjlBqpN6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report lies propaganda on behalf of the Government.  Meanwhile we report the facts the mainstream refuse to and rely solely on your support.  Help us to become the new mainstream media.  Please support us today... https://t.co/eqjlBqpN6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews take millions of s of your money by law to report propaganda and lies on behalf of the U.K. Government  Meanwhile we report the truth and rely solely on your support.  Please support us today...  Lets knock them off their perch... https://t.co/eqjlBqHnYv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mainstream media are paid millions of s of your money to report propaganda for the Government.  @BBCNews take millions of s of your money by law to report lies on behalf of the Government.  We report the truth and rely solely on your support.  Please support us today... https://t.co/eqjlBqpN6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING - Dr Mike Yeadon has revealed to us in an exclusive interview that There is no logic to the statement that we need to vaccinate everybody in order to stop this, its just nonsense. https://t.co/U9iCARCype]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Doctors from around the world say the C0V 1D jabs are "ineffective and dangerous"  (Video by @DentyAndShaz) https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@naomirwolf @AlexBerenson https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lyndonx: If you do not believe a few people can control 7bln then think again  https://t.co/s2WosWiCcJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: This post is being hidden by Twitter. Please re-tweet the original post if you can see it... https://t.co/2ZxrFDnnsH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This post is being hidden by Twitter. Please re-tweet the original post if you can see it... https://t.co/2ZxrFDnnsH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreeFromTyranny: This is a scandalous crime against humanity. This obscene experiment must be stopped! https://t.co/ECyBS9g8v3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mainstream media are being paid millions of s of your money to report lies and propaganda on behalf of the Government.  Meanwhile we rely solely on your support to report the facts the mainstream refuse.  Help us to become the new mainstream media.  Support us today... https://t.co/eqjlBqpN6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theblogmire: @DailyExposeNews are doing some great "Investigative Journalism" on Covid and vaccines - something the Mainstream Media ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve started a Summer Fundraising Campaign which will allow us to finally knock the mainstream media off their perch with your support!  We rely solely on your support whereas they are making millions of s of your money by advertising propaganda for the Government. https://t.co/eqjlBqpN6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AutumnPhoenix4: Do read this.. We MUST act to STOP this Government damaging the children https://t.co/HBHQBpNl36]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SmallHotChilli: Apparently, so many don't think this is a problem  https://t.co/jCRPe12N2k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MinistryBackup9: The Public Speak - "ToffeePud" - we talk being autistic with autistic kids. https://t.co/Y5N0S7o2US]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson @JNJNews @Amy_Siskind https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson @naomirwolf @CDCgov @AlexBerenson  https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roadtoserfdom3 @bilks https://t.co/okucV9JUdu]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>