<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's all the reasons not to take the jabs  https://t.co/M1Gb3mA7kY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simsy1977 @DailyMailUK Professor Bhakdi suggests making a Will after 3 https://t.co/q3BrOJ4f20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sapiofoxxxxxxxy Aren't the pictures  footage of people being ill  dying being recyled from a dangerous gas leak last year?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cindersCA It's just when people claim things like this that perhaps aren't true it tends to throw everything else they say into question ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Censorship continues https://t.co/eRXItKxn5A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TerryTyler4 Apparently, so she claims in the video but I can't find any reference to it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulafr68963440 Does it make sense alongside plans to depopulate?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrsSMHI: You call me a conspiracy theorist. If I'm wrong, what's the worst that can happen to me? I end up with egg on my face and have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anybody know if she is right about the UN here in UK? https://t.co/6YuuBBR8w3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Paired with the rollout of related surveillance technologies  digital tracking devices, vaccine passports, brain-machine interfaces and planet-wide 5G  COVID vaccines are a critical component of central bankers plan to establish a global control grid." https://t.co/isReqzuUQI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The waxxed can transmit spike proteins... https://t.co/NN7Eq7bRZt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warning from NHS whistleblower https://t.co/PaWe097hVR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jenny6015: Just back from another late night drive over the forest to take supplies to a sick relative.  Managed to dodge two foxes, ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toadmeister: Stephen Reicher, a Professor of Social Psychology at the University of St Andrews and member of SAGE, has warned that the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GarySidley: Dominic Raab's recent comment that restrictions such as #masks may be with us beyond June 21st clearly shows: If we don't l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GarryRyanUK: @NEUnion @GavinWilliamson As a teacher and a member of the NEU, this is pathetic.  You are issuing unevidenced assertions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidjthunder: This tweet is deemed misleading by Twitter. Hmm... A vaccine pass - imposing significant costs  inconvenience upon th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hilltopgina: Carling: Stop using plastic rings that kill animals! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/usKZ50IErP via @UKChange]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RJellicoe: How many birds must be chopped up by these monsters before they realize Green isn't working? We will be told they do if that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hemsedalgirl: @conspiracyguy10 https://t.co/RVBHRbhHZ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pfizer donates $70 mn medical supplies to India, seeks quick vaccine approval No pressure then https://t.co/vEzmoo9sF3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ ...ensuring that nobody would believe her warnings. Cassandra was left with the knowledge of future events, but could neither alter these events nor convince others of the validity of her predictions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cassandra Syndrome. How many of us are experiencing this? (From Wiki) 1/ Cassandra was a daughter of Priam, the King of Troy. Struck by her beauty, Apollo provided her with the gift of prophecy, but when Cassandra refused Apollo's romantic advances, he placed a curse...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonnyhodl Or Sweden?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Article...Raab talking about safeguards after June 21st: "'I think it will be around distancing  maybe there will be something around masks.' Such hysteria, not backed up by any scientific evidence, must be instantly questioned and challenged." YES! https://t.co/Poi31k86TU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Julia Hartley-Brewer @JuliaHB1 grouts her @talkRADIO studio floor with Liz Truss when discussing the illiberal and autho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Julia clashes with International Trade Secretary Liz Truss: You have battled for freedom and liberal values all your politi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CrimsonCode1: CV19 Conspiracy Theorists - Are the people who have taken the time and effort to research official and clinical trials do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AI_Clayton That is dreadful  so underhand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pass this on to all parents who still want to have a say in how their children are treated at school https://t.co/qqHYIGE608]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elizabe14729684: Once upon a time, the thought of living in New Zealand  was a dream. Now sold out to communism  Investigation concl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danielkotzin: For 30 years, I have been donating my blood and blood products to anonymous strangers. I have donated plasma, platelets,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danielkotzin Well said]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good point https://t.co/YA8jOw2bJv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kaimjansen: @smile28554950 Don't ask for permission. Send your kid in with an exempt badge ( they can get stuffed!). Simple, effective]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The FDA have not approved ANY of these so-called [waxines]" and other news https://t.co/FmAWVWqcdj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good for this lady https://t.co/HUvUXmwfwH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Telegram: "India this morning filmed by a resident, no lockdown, no panic, if it was left to the mainstream media, everyone would think the world was ending because of Coronavirus." https://t.co/sc19c8vaoY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @smile28554950: Just to mention again. Davina McCall posts this heartfelt tweet and its deleted less than 10 minutes later. By whom and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaneDryden4 Isn't there a saying that if you divide up the workload you get twice as much done?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A longer 2 minute clip about google's biases and perceived "jobs" https://t.co/okL5kKwfww]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrDPoole @socialHATchat @offshorebella Thank you :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllenLandau2 @brandiwill001 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2kRYUGxYnC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nurse in Halifax, Canada talking about waxines etc. 10 mins 20-ish in, she says that UK is going to have the UN deployed on our streets until 2023. I can't find anything on this - is it accurate? https://t.co/qcEwEYJ5dK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Arwenstar Their transmitted spike proteins?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CrumblingN: @Reuters I wonder if those Epstein Island visits finally wore them down? Do people realize he was flying on Epstein's plane]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dunardtrek @let35828674  I think it might be because they believe that it's not as bad as having convid BUT one at least (age 50 no co-morbidities) had already had it in December - no consideration for natural immunity. I really don't get it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahFBPE The point is that others are going without more and more. No need to be patronising.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I will add because we are both exempt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@firefly1379 I've noticed it before. E.g. Two members of the extended family have high blood pressure etc and said they would rather take a pill and continue eating/drinking what they like than to make any changes. Passive as .... and irresponsible IMO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Went into two small shops this weekend, no masks in one, only one young couple and cashier in the other with. Then accompanied someone to AE - neither of us wore masks although I wasn't allowed to stay in after they'd done the convid checklist #TakeOffYourMask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StrumpetsV: So they have now told us there is a variant that 'evades the test' they want you to know that you may be sick with an illne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Protestlockdown: Please go out and protest on May 15th   No social distancing  No masks  Hug people if you can   I will be in London th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mmjblair: Dreams of Freedom https://t.co/zvaAQEm63d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllenLandau2 @brandiwill001 I think I have managed to persuade my 30 y/o daughter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wjjaap @mmjblair (Take out spaces to view the previous one) Or this one: Professor Bhakdi M D explains mR N A waxxines, spike proteins, clotting, Immune Dependant Enhancement ...suggests if people have a third shot of any make, they make a Will! https://t.co/q3BrOJ4f20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wjjaap @mmjblair Might be this video which explains the AZ one https:// healthimpactnews. com/2021/urgent-5-doctors-agree-that-covid-19-injections-are-bioweapons-and-discuss-what-to-do-about-it/?fbclid=IwAR2OpwT3MRM64CVmGPW397_L-t8Kc9bATEXaqdKk_tlLJzsfFWSUENc4YdQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cindersCA Not sure they've developed these yet but there is some expert concern about transmission of spike proteins.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllenLandau2 @brandiwill001 So am I but not happy he's had it. It's not like I didn't try. It all fell on deaf ears and blind eyes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jenny6015 That's the length of the clip ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@socialHATchat @offshorebella Sorry I don't know. I just saw that on a Telegram channel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllenLandau2 @brandiwill001 I spent several hours around some waxxed yesterday but it was mostly outdoors. I sleep next to one every night but he has had no side-effects whatsoever after the 1st one, not even a sore bit on his arm, didn't even feel it go in apparently ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Self-spreading waxxines - you can get one even if you don't want one https://t.co/ejH01IWiIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leaked docs suggest google want to programme people https://t.co/2MjayF7Jca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@smallangryboy @SharpieDj That's a no. Get chucked out for that sort of thing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jenny6015 I know that's tough, but we need to make peace with that somehow. At least they cannot say that we didn't say anything / try ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jenny6015 I'm sorry to hear that. It is very difficult for us but it is their choice. It is even their choice to make an uninformed decision on it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[O dear https://t.co/Z4kx5Zw7VW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - A group of Doctors from around the world have United to inform the public that the C0V*ID jabs are unnecessa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GillianBateman5 Good answer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllenLandau2 @brandiwill001 That's concerning. I hope you feel better soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very concerning https://t.co/LxdJNyTicj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could of bin worse, could of bin spelt defiantly  https://t.co/gRRtvbp3U1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simsy1977 Prof Bhakdi suggests making a Will after 3 https://t.co/q3BrOJ4f20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @debrose1921: @moolie61 @TheHayride Id say so he prewarned us but no one listened well some did Event 201 is all i needed to know https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HilaryWallace1 Exactly. I mentioned this to another lady who asked if my OH has had it  I said she needs to ask him. She got quite flustered but I said I don't understand why ppl think it's ok to ask about medical details, she said it's bc this is unprecedented but it's still not ok IMO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - Adverse Reactions to the C0V* -ID jabs now include 9723 blood disorders, 7699 cardiac disorders, 10,633 eye d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraWeeden Went into two small shops this weekend, nobody masked in one and just the cashier and one couple in another]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@orange44black Good players are thin on the ground at our club]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterStefanovi2: Now on 14.4 million views!  irrefutable evidence of PM breaking ministerial code   questions in Parliament  cross part]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@let35828674 Two of them have had really bad side effects and still going for the 2nd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: 1/: Dear #ZeroCovid fanatics, I sometimes wonder whether you are aware of what you are causing with your attitude. You mock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shortstufftuck @scottyy147 @JohnnieSammons1 @goddeketal @RobPadoa Flu vaxxes and the like do that, these experimental ones don't https://t.co/q3BrOJ4f20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jenny6015 No like-minded others there, not much laughing... matches are serious business ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RupertaMargate @WinterOakPress Isn't there also a connection/correlation with meningitis?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Frm Robin Monotti: 'PROJECT FEAR INCREASES INFECTIONS, CASES, DEATHS' "In sum, the association between stress and disease occurs because chronic stress interferes with the bodys ability to turn off the immune systems production of inflammatory chemicals" https://t.co/2aopMAn9Yd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Andrew_its_lies Yes I watched the more recent remake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I don't understand all of it but... https://t.co/b1ZqpFr13A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PinkIris13 @SteveG06322664 It's all perpetuating what they are doing to us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DR ZEV ZELENKO "Do you understand what this meanswe are are injecting viral genetic code for the spike protein into innocent people and it gets into almost every cell In the body."  https://t.co/DMcKIhJHVs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Professor Bhakdi M D explains mR N A waxxines, spike proteins, clotting, Immune Dependant Enhancement ...suggests if people have a third shot of any make, they make a Will! https://t.co/q3BrOJ4f20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marthaburneston @cindersCA I have lost so much faith in people this last year. This is one of the few places I feel some support  encouragement...with people I have never met!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marthaburneston @cindersCA It may have been because I was physically tired after the match but I did think 'o ffs, they are going to drag the rest of us down with all this unquestioning compliance']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@k_jaydi I have put the question (to covhysterics) as to why, if it's that deadly, there has never been any hazardous waste bins out in public, with ad campaigns  fines for those who don't dispose of them properly. I don't get a reply  I can see it's not even going in. So in denial]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I'm retired, I am free to speak out as I see fit".  These are the experts we can trust IMO https://t.co/VVXWmk1nC4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MyNamesGuy @Crystalangeles2 @MoriartyProfJ3 Agreed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Found out today that workers in our local hospital have been told that, whereas they used to have to dispose of their masks in 'offensive waste' bins, the ordinary waste bins are now ok. Wait a minute? I thought there were all these waxxine resistant scariants about ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Crystalangeles2: @MoriartyProfJ3 BOMBSHELL... UK Government just signed a 320 million ad contract for Covid 19 related ads till March]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Captain44618202 @BeddoeRoger Yes, I spoke to another lady (in her 60s) afterwards who has not been jabbed and says she won't...unless she finds herself too restricted e.g. no theatre, restaurant etc. I told her that the trials don't end for 2 to 4 years yet but don't know if that made any difference]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>