<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[We are investing nearly 30 million to test vaccines against COVID-19 variants, helping protect the UK from future outbreaks.   https://t.co/XfLTzBEyUp https://t.co/NXVKAvl2fZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Work in lockstep to tackle threats to our shared security. The UKs Carrier Strike Group will visit India later this year and our navies will undertake joint training exercises to enable future cooperation on operations in the Western Indian Ocean.  [6/6] https://t.co/w9NYWxQwvO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Increase cooperation between British and Indian universities in areas like health, emerging technologies and climate science.  A new Migration and Mobility partnership will also make it easier for Indian students and skilled professionals to study, work and live in the UK.  [5/6] https://t.co/cTQkRp74fJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Agreeing an Enhanced Trade Partnership that deepens the UK-India economic relationship and beginning negotiations on a Free Trade Agreement that will double trade between our two countries over the next decade.  [4/6] https://t.co/1vzBJQQ0V1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Working together to accelerate the development of clean energy and transport, protect biodiversity and help developing countries adapt to the impact of climate change.  [3/6] https://t.co/V7DzAorCOB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Expanding the UK-India health partnership and improving international supply chains to ensure critical medicines, vaccines and other medical products reach those who need them most.  [2/6] https://t.co/BIYJlQBksY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today Prime Ministers @BorisJohnson and @NarendraModi agreed a 2030 Roadmap for UK-India relations.  Here are some of the things it commits us to   [THREAD 1/6]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Today @NarendraModi and I spoke about how we can overcome the pandemic and strengthen the ties between our two countries.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 6,500 new jobs will be created around the UK thanks to 1 billion of new UK-India trade and investment.   https://t.co/r60dmQu4U6 https://t.co/BXZJQwC5DG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FCDOGovUK: G7 foreign ministers meet today in London for the first face-to-face #G7 Foreign Ministers Meeting in more than two years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The legal limit on the number of mourners at funerals will be lifted in England at Step 3 of the Roadmap, so family and friends can pay their respects in greater numbers. https://t.co/r4Y80NYbG5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Prime Ministers message on Northern Irelands centenary year. https://t.co/g8CgvNeehL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are playing our part in the fight against the coronavirus surge in India:   Sending 1,000 more ventilators to help the most severely affected  @CMO_England providing advice and expertise to his Indian counterpart  Find out more  https://t.co/vYj3Dp8CSU https://t.co/gmaktUGmnj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy #OrthodoxEaster to those celebrating today. https://t.co/LrGKNAg9cn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're aged 40 or over, or if you turn 40 before 1 July 2021, you can now book your COVID-19 vaccine.   https://t.co/PtTfjuUfkn https://t.co/frvrvjDl3S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over this Parliamentary session, we have passed laws to protect our NHS, drive jobs and investment, and regain control over our trade and borders.   Here are some of the 44 Bills passed that deliver on the peoples priorities     https://t.co/J8saYIVJHd https://t.co/L25A6q8qXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prime Minister @BorisJohnson and Chancellor @RishiSunak met students and teachers at King Solomon Academy in Marylebone, London to hear about what its been like getting back to the classroom. https://t.co/ux8bae17r0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have recruited , new police officers, beating our target of putting , more officers on our streets in the first year of our recruitment drive.   Over  years, we'll recruit , police officers to cut crime and keep our communities safe. https://t.co/KDBTRRxMRR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: I want to thank Arlene Foster @DUPleader for her dedication to the people of Northern Ireland over many years. She will c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Vaccines Taskforce has secured an extra 60 million doses of the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine.   The extra doses will help support preparations for the  COVID-19 vaccine booster programme from the autumn.   https://t.co/RCju7Kc4Wn https://t.co/Ely1sXabXZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: COVID-19 press conference (28 April 2021)   Speakers:    @MattHancock, Secretary of State @DHSCgovuk  Prof Jonathan Van-Tam, Deputy Chief Medical Officer for England  Dr @NikkiKF, @NHSEngland https://t.co/uPgdCzerU2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch today's coronavirus press conference live on our channels at 5pm. https://t.co/3AhHqU95pK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: A quarter of UK adults have received 2 doses of a COVID vaccine, giving them maximum protection against the virus.   This]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dwppressoffice: 16,500 young people have already started a 6 month paid job through the #Kickstart Scheme and more are starting every d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Queen Elizabeth Carrier will sail to the Indo-Pacific region on her first deployment this summer.    @HMSQNLZ is the most advanced vessel ever built by Britains shipyards  a physical manifestation of the UKs strengths and values     https://t.co/RUSavcox7V https://t.co/sgSIeFISXY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSuk: Every vaccination gives us hope.  Join the millions already vaccinated, to protect yourself and others.  Find out more about the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: We stand side by side with India in the shared fight against COVID-19. Vital medical equipment is on its way from the UK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Today we pay our respects to the ANZACs who fought at Gallipoli, and remember all those who have fought with courage so t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Beacon of Hope: The UK Vaccine Story.     Watch below or on Youtube: https://t.co/C0ETBduoTN https://t.co/ELY77ZESbb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @G7: Calling young Cornish artists  @CornwallCouncil and @G7 have launched a poetry  art competition ahead of #G7Cornwall, to be judg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: I welcome the Court of Appeal's decision to overturn the convictions of 39 former sub-postmasters in the Horizon dispute,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A very happy St. Georges Day from Downing Street!  https://t.co/tzG1a4MuMu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Football is for the fans.  That's why we are asking what you think needs to change, so fans' interests and experiences are put first.   We must always protect our national game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy St. George's Day!  https://t.co/57GnYgXLXj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK is proud to join our partners in the new $1bn #LEAFCoalition to stop deforestation, cut global emissions and put nature on the path of recovery.   https://t.co/XEWAyBuvWK   #LeadersClimateSummit #EarthDay https://t.co/2JqNlkajxQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine update: Doses administered across age groups (England).   https://t.co/NwGZJTXLht https://t.co/BrnuoeUAsJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets make this decade the moment of decisive change in the fight against climate change.   The Prime Minister's statement at the #LeadersClimateSummit convened by @POTUS: https://t.co/no9N04AcXU  #BuildBackGreener | @COP26 | #EarthDay https://t.co/afAShf5buw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: The commitment from @POTUS today to cut US emissions by 50-52% by 2030 is a game-changer. It will have a transformative i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Prime Minister @BorisJohnsons statement at the #LeadersClimateSummit convened by @POTUS https://t.co/dMmm1CPX5U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COP26: The wait is over...   The #LeadersClimateSummit  22-23 April, 1pm BST  A global virtual event  Watch live as leaders from a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: We've reached a significant milestone with 1 in 5 adults now having had two COVID-19 vaccine doses. This is a huge UK-wid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: I would like to send my warm wishes to Her Majesty The Queen on her 95th birthday.  I have always had the highest admirat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DHSCgovuk: We are launching an Antivirals Taskforce to identify treatments for UK patients who have been exposed to #Covid19  The taskf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK's new Antivirals Taskforce will identify innovative COVID-19 treatments to reduce transmission and speed up recovery.   We aim to have at least 2 effective take-home treatments by the end of the year.   https://t.co/H8PYvPEXoj https://t.co/zqsB9qpTqP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD 2/2: COVID-19 press conference slides (20 April 2021)  2 The number of people who have received a vaccination for COVID-19 in the UK   https://t.co/5193faPqyg https://t.co/A3nYvlZCrb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD 1/2: COVID-19 press conference slides (20 April 2021)  1 The number of people in hospital with COVID-19 in the UK   https://t.co/5193faPqyg https://t.co/0X0Pi765iQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: COVID-19 press conference (20 April 2021)   Speakers:    @BorisJohnson, Prime Minister   Dr @NikkiKF, @NHSEngland https://t.co/1pRc2Njqro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GPforEducation: Educating our children is the smartest investment the world can make  W/100 days until the Global Education Summit #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Earlier @OliverDowden and I met with representatives from the @FA, @PremierLeague and football fan groups to discuss acti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch today's coronavirus press conference live on our channels at 5pm. https://t.co/GUPLTKOPkO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Its fantastic that weve been able to enjoy some more freedoms with family and friends since 12 April.  As we continue w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 10 million people in the UK have now received their second coronavirus vaccine dose.  Thank you to everyone involved in this extraordinary effort.   Please book your vaccine appointment if you are eligible. https://t.co/CBmlp8USKS https://t.co/MtwpyFMFcA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Memoriam HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, 1921-2021. https://t.co/nnP3It3Huk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A one minute silence will be observed at 3pm today in memory of HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh. https://t.co/EETAAxb5jI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Prime Minister paid tribute to His Royal Highness The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh yesterday at Britannia Royal Naval College, Dartmouth. https://t.co/uCYKArIgm0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today the Prime Minister visited Britannia Royal Naval College, Dartmouth to pay his respects to HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh.  He saw a naval officer passing out parade and observed a minute's silence in memory of The Duke of Edinburgh. https://t.co/VAXdxtRPL3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy New Year to those celebrating #Puthandu.   Britains Tamil community makes an enormous, positive contribution to our society.   Once again, it remains important to celebrate safely and remember hands, face, space and fresh air. https://t.co/AAe9RNAzm2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prime Minister @BorisJohnson wishing Sikhs in the UK and around the world all the joy and happiness of #Vaisakhi. https://t.co/nabWH6Ab5s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: We have hit a hugely significant milestone by offering jabs to everyone in the nine highest risk groups, giving them the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prime Minister @BorisJohnsons tribute to His Royal Highness The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh in the @HouseOfCommons. https://t.co/MLP7VWaRkl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some coronavirus restrictions are being cautiously lifted across England today, as we move to Step 2 of our Roadmap.  Heres what you need to know [tap to expand]   https://t.co/u7IORZiwMn https://t.co/9iq0yGI4Qn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prime Minister @BorisJohnson's full statement on the death of HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh.  https://t.co/rihbsnhUsy https://t.co/SPuFCzi0zV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prime Minister @BorisJohnson on the death of HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh. https://t.co/MeYm9vxwxg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @transportgovuk: The Global Travel Taskforce report has set out the approach to safely restart international travel. This will ensure bu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NHSEngland: Having the vaccine does not break your fast, its not considered nutrition.  GP Dr @fhussain73 reassures all those observ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: 6 million people have now had their second jab.  Yesterday over 400,000 second doses were given.  A huge thank you to eve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prime Minister @BorisJohnson visited Cornwall to meet some of the businesses and retailers preparing to safely reopen on April 12th. https://t.co/Kaeshsj08P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: I am deeply concerned by the scenes of violence in Northern Ireland, especially attacks on PSNI who are protecting the pu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today the Prime Minister is in Cornwall seeing the preparations being made by businesses and retailers in the county ahead of the easing of some restrictions on Monday in England. https://t.co/wuo6wKIsIp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Thank you @MHRAgovuk and JCVI for your important work looking at the AstraZeneca vaccine, which has updated on the potent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MHRAgovuk: MHRA issues new advice concluding a possible link between #COVID19 Vaccine #AstraZeneca  extremely rare, unlikely-to-occur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today Prime Minister @BorisJohnson was in Macclesfield to welcome @AstraZenecas new investment in helping provide cancer treatment to those that need it around the world.   #BuildBackBetter https://t.co/mrnORNuiXK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BorisJohnson: Very promising news that the @ValnevaSE vaccine shows a strong immune response and will progress to Phase 3 trials.  If i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Get your vaccine or your second dose when your turn comes.   Use the free NHS tests, even if you dont feel ill. You can order on https://t.co/6hgrnGrAd1 here: https://t.co/OuSHJr4n29 https://t.co/GOWd9HGEuW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD 4/4: COVID-19 press conference slides (5 April 2021)  Test 4: Our assessment of the risks is not fundamentally changed by new Variants of Concern   https://t.co/8mksGcs4zx https://t.co/mxNin3YhBV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD 3/4: COVID-19 press conference slides (5 April 2021)  Test 3: Infection rates do not risk a surge in hospitalisations which would put unsustainable pressure on the NHS   https://t.co/8mksGcs4zx https://t.co/f8pjzWaU7E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD 2/4: COVID-19 press conference slides (5 April 2021)  Test 2: Evidence shows vaccines are sufficiently effective in reducing hospitalisations and deaths in those vaccinated   https://t.co/8mksGcs4zx https://t.co/qzucHnK6vN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THREAD 1/4: COVID-19 press conference slides (5 April 2021)  Test 1: The vaccine deployment programme continues successfully   https://t.co/8mksGcs4zx https://t.co/iHowE0IZ7v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: COVID-19 press conference (5 April 2021)  Speakers:  @BorisJohnson, Prime Minister  Prof Chris Whitty, @CMO_England  Sir Patrick Vallance, @UKScienceChief https://t.co/tZ4tNuHkHz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch today's coronavirus press conference live on our channels at 5pm. https://t.co/8mbVLQ8Sfq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay safe, keep following the rules, and have a very happy Easter. https://t.co/cX8YJrZ0e2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay safe this Easter weekend. Wash your hands and keep your distance. https://t.co/spsSxMSw54]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On this day 300 years ago, Sir Robert Walpole (1676-1745) became the First Lord of the Treasury and, in effect, Britains first Prime Minister. He remains the longest holder of this office, serving 21 years.   Read more about Britains first PM here: https://t.co/1eWZs9hycY https://t.co/eziJB0TXjr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were launching a competition with @RoyalMail for children to design a stamp collection featuring their COVID Heroes  to honour their tremendous work.   PM @BorisJohnson and Royal Mail CEO Simon Thompson on how to get involved   Enter here: https://t.co/xEcqU9xEcm  #HeroStamps https://t.co/TJx40U17q8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celebrate Easter outdoors.  In England, you can meet in groups of up to six people or two households. https://t.co/1AXNL3ruSJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today National Living and Minimum Wage rates go up  benefitting around 2 million people.  Make sure youre being paid the right amount: https://t.co/uoeFUZFceE https://t.co/3ELqLpSauq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Lifetime Skills Guarantee will give adults free courses to get the expertise they need to find new, better jobs.   #BuildBackBetter   https://t.co/1aQiNnM2Bn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @beisgovuk: Hello pay rise.  National Living and Minimum Wage rates increase from today.  The rise means someone working full-time on th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@KirenCollison and @ShamezLadhani are now answering questions about Covid-19 vaccines in an AMA on Reddit.  LIVE NOW. Join here to ask a question: https://t.co/PbhzkJbnse https://t.co/LrMUqiNHqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomorrow @KirenCollison and @ShamezLadhani will be answering questions about Covid-19 vaccines in an AMA on @Reddit.   Go to r/Coronavirus at 2pm to ask your question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some coronavirus restrictions have been cautiously lifted across England.    https://t.co/geLJVUK9lR https://t.co/SIE7KeKiow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember: outdoors is generally much safer than indoors.  The way to continue on our cautious but irreversible roadmap to freedom is to follow the rules. https://t.co/HUtMbWbUsp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: COVID-19 press conference (29 March 2021)  Speakers:  @BorisJohnson, Prime Minister  Prof Chris Whitty, @CMO_England  Sir Patrick Vallance, @UKScienceChief https://t.co/hUs8E6wN4A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch today's coronavirus press conference live on our channels at 5pm. https://t.co/4nDCahyono]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As we cautiously exit lockdown in England, we should continue to observe the restrictions on social contact to keep people safe.   https://t.co/wYsooCbPKP https://t.co/Nny3GQWsca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some coronavirus restrictions are being cautiously lifted across England today.   Heres what you need to know [tap to expand]    https://t.co/wYsooCbPKP https://t.co/DkSr5qjSjR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From tomorrow, some restrictions in England are being eased.   Here is what you need to know  https://t.co/sSpWCZu0Na]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[30 million people have now received their first dose of the vaccine.   Thank you to everyone who has helped make this possible.  Find the latest UK data on vaccinations here: https://t.co/UV6XO3ziu1 https://t.co/apQuxsRaR4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight we joined millions across the globe in switching off our lights for #EarthHour2021. We're committed to protecting the environment as we build back greener.  https://t.co/GzbSnVuIee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were investing 500m in mental health services, which will expand NHS talking therapies to an additional 1.6 million people.     https://t.co/w8hbJnLdlk https://t.co/2YqHA0b7Gd]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>