<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@realSaraBeck Wonderful!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: My favorite take-away from @TheLancet report is this page of co-benefits from improving indoor air quality in schools  b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What you should know about air cleaners  https://t.co/6qHhO1Ib04]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JimRosenthal4 That is so brilliant! https://t.co/JBmoa4De9E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CathNoakes: I keep seeing statements sceptical of airborne that state its not known if the smallest aerosols contain infectious virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: 1/ UPDATES TO COVID-19 AEROSOL TRANSMISSION ESTIMATOR  We have just implemented several updates:  - added increased risk o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: 1/ TEN SCIENTIFIC REASONS IN SUPPORT OF AIRBORNE TRANSMISSION OF SARS-CoV-2  Peer-reviewed publication in @TheLancet   An]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: How is the fall even a question at this point? And, if your school is closed NOW you are failing - the guidance is there, th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KHNews: Academic air-quality experts agree on whats best for schools: More outside air pumped into classes, MERV 13 filters in heating]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Wymelenberg @meganmorrone I really honestly didnt feel a thing. Was it the arnica or the Tylenol I took??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BEonthetoilet: Whoop whoop !! Shout out to @CathNoakes @ShellyMBoulder. And all the other amazing scientists who have fought this battl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes!!! My 14 y old will get vaccinated soon! Then my family will all be vaccinated. I cant wait. https://t.co/wyoAKE5ebZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marwa_zaatari I am a precautionary principle kind of scientist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: An important piece on the dubious "air cleaning" products being sold to school districts  businesses. Via investigations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And @marwa_zaatari has my support, that's why I provided a peer review of the letter and signed on. NOTE We are doing research at University of Colorado Boulder ~ our preliminary study shows the tested ionizer really doesn't do anything...kind of like a nice vase, room decor... https://t.co/TxfD85EDXi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not only is Pat incredibly hard working and brilliant the BioSpot-GEM Sampler is an amazing aerosol sampling instrument perfect for collecting virus and other microorganisms @AerosolDevices https://t.co/NBgwridnnU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: Congratulations to Pat Keady of @AerosolDevices for being recognized by @ceotodaymag in the select group: 'Business Women]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Based on Boeings technical assessment, further study/development of air ionization by the industry is required before the technology can be incorporated for effective disinfection of airplanes in response to global pandemics caused by respiratory viruses such as SARS-CoV-2." https://t.co/yzoWVuLIJ1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcelHarmon1: School districts that installed electronic air cleaning technology are not devoid of responsibility. But it's also impor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BilboBa14980115 @LaurenWeberHP @By_CJewett @KHNews here ya go: * A hopefully helpful short report on air cleaners (https://t.co/k3YO2nCqWc)  * Portable air cleaner tool: https://t.co/dWi0MNMVuy * YouTube Video on how to use the Air Cleaner Tool: https://t.co/sMfurhDNha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LaurenWeberHP:  Is your child in a classroom with unproven air cleaner technology?   Our investigation found over 2,000 schools acro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LaurenWeberHP: We talked to facility managers in Kansas whose phones hadn't stopped ringing with pitches and parents in Montclair, N.J.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spend your $$$$ on proven approaches and technology such as HEPA filtration and HEPA air cleaners, natural ventilation and even germicidal UV light https://t.co/Yg4hBvInDk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @First10EM: After fighting all year to get people to accept the science on airborne spread, only to be denied because of @WHO recommenda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: SO glad to see @WHO update on transmission!  short-range: aerosols containing the virus are inhaled or droplets contact eye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShellyMBoulder: "Routinely I recommend technology that has been proven time and time again to work effectively for the application.  I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kircher_mike @trahana @linseymarr @jljcolorado @kprather88 @CorsIAQ @j_g_allen @VirusesImmunity @WHO stuck in their old mental model of how infectious diseases are spread...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@trahana @linseymarr @jljcolorado @kprather88 @CorsIAQ @j_g_allen @VirusesImmunity @WHO when we realized they were blowing us off, we published our letter on airborne transmission with an additional 200+ scientists signing on.  They said to us thanks but no thanks we are not rewriting our guidance our our position that it is not airborne.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder... This happened @WHO https://t.co/t4ohUsT1cO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShellyMBoulder: @trahana @linseymarr @jljcolorado @kprather88 @CorsIAQ @j_g_allen @VirusesImmunity just about a year ago a group of int]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ReginaRyerson your gonna want to read our next paper coming out in a couple of weeks....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Routinely I recommend technology that has been proven time and time again to work effectively for the application.  I stick with what the research shows as effective.  Which gets to a main point of this blog..."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I also get asked by friends and colleagues (and people who just find me via the internet) to recommend a technology that they could use in their home to improve their indoor air quality."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This blog I wrote in 2013 seems rather timely: "In-House Reports vs. Peer-Reviewed Publications for Air Pollution Control Technology" https://t.co/40QHkXXihh via @ShellyMBoulder]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: 29/ The paper on the Skagit Choir outbreak, led by @ShellyMBoulder.   The clearest airborne transmission case of the early]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@trahana @linseymarr @jljcolorado @kprather88 @CorsIAQ @j_g_allen @VirusesImmunity just about a year ago a group of international scientists coordinated a meeting with @WHO to explain that this pandemic is airborne. We were flabbergasted that they shunned/ignored us...the rest is a tragedy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sri_srikrishna: Public health poster in SF: Covid-19 virus travels in the air and collects indoors @AbraarKaran @RanuDhillon @jljcolo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: 1/ A SIMPLE WAY TO ESTIMATE THE RISK OF INDOOR SUPERSPREADING  Our preprint using the airborne transmission model  Capture]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: 16/ We also show the effect of different mitigations of common activities (school, restaurant, choir)...  We see that the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jmcrookston I totally ignore it (?)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kevinrigbyjr Oh ya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marinavance: Recommendations for band class/practice/rehearsal to minimize the risk of COVID transmission.  (cc @ShellyMBoulder)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sjbeckerphd Glad you spoke up. The NYT doesnt not correct its self very often.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lstops I can imagine you are not going to be making donations to the MIT alumni association any time soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidElfstrom: U of T is making all classrooms achieve 6 ACH with #ventilation and #filtration, the same as for health care patient exa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidElfstrom Nice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Embarrassing, just embarrassing that this happened: "BVSD board member asks to rescind mask policy and make wearing one a choice." Huge kudos to @BVSDcolorado board prez and others for standing up for science and declining this ridiculous request. https://t.co/WKA3oGv1UB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nockingpoint do you ever respond to emails from your customers requesting help with their memberships?  I first asked to switch memberships to a different club, and then I got frustrated because of no response and decided to just cancel, but I still can't get a response...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@juliagelke @j_g_allen @CorsIAQ @linsey They haven't responded with loads of data showing how effective the devices are?? you don't say...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrNickClements https://t.co/3QtK5aOsd6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Colorado, COVID Case Rates Are The Lowest Where Vaccination Rates Are The Highest (And Vice Versa) https://t.co/3ettnBLT1I https://t.co/enUTTAg8YD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YES! @CUBoulder steps up and requires vaccines, as well as the CU Sytem https://t.co/tk1VtpZlsy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Commissioncovid: New publication on #school #infrastructure; better ventilation  air cycling reduces risk of #COVID19 transmission tod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UniversalMaski2 @Iamgoingtosleep @danaparish @DrKatrin_Rabiei @akm5376 @SherriDouville @jessica_bassett @GosiaGasperoPhD @SprkJoy4BtrDays @ProfCharlesHaas @jljcolorado @meganranney @kprather88 @Poppendieck @HuffmanLabDU @mdholte @BarryHunt008 @citlanx @NjbBari3 @CDCgov @Surgeon_General @DvsBlack @RWalensky @nynursesunited @Cleavon_MD @APIC @DRTomlinsonEP @microlabdoc @sri_srikrishna @CDC_Firstline @noellejt @yaneerbaryam @DrEricDing @mvankerkhove @linseymarr @Don_Milton @CDCDirector @NuritBaytch @DrEricLevi @realsmartchange @AnuAnandaraja @ErinSandersNP @j_g_allen @DrNancyM_CDC @celinegounder @AmyTanMD @WHO @TheNETEC @myrabatchelder I worked with a school district in Quebec to ensure good design of their air cleaners. They did an impressive job of assessing, installing, operating  the air cleaners to reduce risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrGarthK @CorsIAQ @j_g_allen @linseymarr Homes are ventilated very differently and really not at all. Definitely need to improve home ventilation to reduce transmission!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: Excellent new guide on healthy #school buildings. Should be mandatory reading  discussion by all #K12 school boards, dis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CorsIAQ: Honored to have worked on this w/ @j_g_allen, @ShellyMBoulder, @linseymarr, and several other key contributors.  "Designing in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Latest from our Lancet Task Force.  Pandemic relief for schools must be applied to enhancements that are evidence-based, pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[on designing infectious disease school resilience into school buildings: Im betting your gonna want to read this new report we @j_g_allen @CorsIAQ @linsey and others just authored, and then send it to your local school https://t.co/1a454e20wp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kprather88 @trahana @jljcolorado @linseymarr @CorsIAQ its painful to watch @WHO twist and turn themselves into pretzels to get the physics to resonate with the story that they have made up about how this infection is spread]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kprather88: This is GREAT explanation of what air is and why plexi barriers dont work for aerosols. Next time u see barriers inside,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BobTeskey @Poppendieck ...yes...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HaywardScoreCEO @HernandezLabCU Awesome. Thanks Bill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@epibuff @sailorrooscout Wow ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wexlerwriting @JimRosenthal4 @EnergyVanguard The blog says portable air cleaners have to be plugged in. The electricity goes to power the fan that is needed to pull air through the filter media. Also there have been air cleaners with no fans in them. And guess what! These dont really work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a really great blog and quick intro to indoor air quality and air cleaning  https://t.co/KQxoJRACtC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marinavance @NSF You worked so hard for this! Excited for the great aerosol science coming from my your lab ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulatwal @Tolling_Bell @DFisman @CBCQuirks @SonyaBuyting @trishgreenhalgh @jljcolorado @zeynep @kprather88 @linseymarr @chipatucsd Yes this stack effect has transmitted a number of infections ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DFisman @CBCQuirks @SonyaBuyting @trishgreenhalgh @jljcolorado @zeynep @kprather88 @linseymarr @chipatucsd Thank you for listening deeply, and learning! And likewise we have learned so much from you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeborahSills: My students @pcupay and #LauraLe are amazing.  They created this fantastic video about Covid transmission and ventilation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Corsi filter box reduced PM2.5 by 92% on average! yep. It works: https://t.co/AUmkeEuKk5 My student is testing a filter she made in her small apartment, challenged the air cleaner with cooking emissions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a great way to start a Friday, great lecture packed full of @IndoorChem research in my air pollution control class by @CorsIAQ! Learned carpets promote tons of chemical reactions and so do people. https://t.co/6okBel8YeL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: "We urgently need safer air in schools"  Last month Profs. @ChemDelphine at CU, @marinavance at CSU,  I wrote an #OpEd p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marwa_zaatari Marketing material does not constitute scientific evidence. But it is often enough to convince individuals that the product has been tested and does what it claims to do. Plus price also seems to help. The more $$$ the better since you get what you pay for in many minds]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UniversalMaski2 @BrendanCarmich7 @Iamgoingtosleep @danaparish @DrKatrin_Rabiei @akm5376 @SherriDouville @jessica_bassett @GosiaGasperoPhD @SprkJoy4BtrDays @ProfCharlesHaas @jljcolorado @meganranney @kprather88 @Poppendieck @HuffmanLabDU @mdholte @BarryHunt008 @citlanx @NjbBari3 @CDCgov @Surgeon_General @DvsBlack @RWalensky @nynursesunited @Cleavon_MD @APIC @DRTomlinsonEP @microlabdoc @sri_srikrishna @CDC_Firstline @noellejt @yaneerbaryam @DrEricDing @mvankerkhove @linseymarr @Don_Milton @CDCDirector @NuritBaytch @DrEricLevi @realsmartchange @AnuAnandaraja @ErinSandersNP @briancolder @j_g_allen @DrNancyM_CDC @celinegounder @US_FDA @AmyTanMD @WHO well now that is a helluva good question]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@allisonbailes and how about aerosols for aerosol?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ARISense_AQ we want these for our NSF study @DrNickClements]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical points from this article: 1. there is no safe level of  PM2.5; 2. exposure to air pollution kills people; 3. traffic related air pollution is toxic. Government urged to set tougher UK air pollution limits after death of girl, 9, from asthma https://t.co/1BlCMd50uG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mdc_martinus: Unbelievable! Until TODAY, against all evidence, the @WHO keeps denying the truth about SARS-CoV-2 being an airborne viru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PassiveHouseBB @dilemmanorton @shawnahenders19 @therilesyouknow @natalie_j_irwin @EfficiencyCAN @LizGosselin @erin_burbidge @jessehitchcock @CanaryScience @DianaUrge @EmmaOsmun @AnnMarieFallon_ @Kara_Rosemeier @ClareEParry oh thanks Bronwyn!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you haven't read this paper yet by the awesome CSU team including @ChemDelphine you are missing out! Quantifying Proximity, Confinement, and Interventions in Disease Outbreaks: A Decision Support Framework for Air-Transported Pathogens https://t.co/dlsf5u9yaC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so glad my email, letter, and conversation with Supervisor Chavez helped it get this unique beneficial program implemented to provide funding for HEPA air cleaners https://t.co/skLYyHkuDd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeromeusa Funnily enough since there was minimal transmission at institutes of higher Ed, Colorado placed university/college faculty after K-12 faculty. I think we did too good of a job keeping down the transmission on CU campus!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I got my 2nd vaccine! https://t.co/jZdSdMb389]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you freaking kidding me??!! Scientist Linked to Great Barrington Declaration Embroiled in World Health Organization Conflict of Interest, Paid to Refute #COVIDisAirborne https://t.co/3g7NRluV09]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@reoxoo @linseymarr Hi not doing interviews at this time!  School is almost out gotta get those students over the finish line]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Frankly, I think he just can't admit he's wrong," said @linseymarr...Top Canadian WHO adviser (Jon Conly) under fire after downplaying airborne threat of COVID-19 (finally) https://t.co/CvR5zTJI5J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrPieterPeach: Short range aerosol concentration gradients has been one of the most blindingly obvious concepts facing the most amount]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SERIOUSLY one of the best tweet threads this whole year, and thanks for @jljcolorado + colleagues for this brilliant piece of work putting together all the puzzle pieces showing SARS-CoV-2 transmission happens by inhaling virus containing aerosol. period. end of story. https://t.co/Gyicu1ZOEM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please be next to announce mandatory vaccines @CUBoulder it is the smart way (and really only way) to safely open our campus in the fall. https://t.co/c4k0JVEmSf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An evaluation of portable high-efficiency particulate air filtration for expedient patient isolation in epidemic and emergency response. Interesting 2004 paper from the excellent CDC/NIOSH engineering branch https://t.co/bi4tBfNbJP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: I also want to thank @ShellyMBoulder and @cedenolaurent for early convos on ACH for schools. We built a simple tool over wee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@j_g_allen @cedenolaurent Not only was it done over a weekend but I was on a road trip across the Western US talking to Joe on my phone from our VW Eurovan ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zeynep: "Ten scientific reasons in support of airborne transmission of SARS-CoV-2." New paper in @TheLancet by @trishgreenhalgh, @kprat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quantification of Shared Air: A Social and Environmental Determinant of Airborne Disease Transmission with @CDCDirector as one of the authors @jljcolorado #COVIDCO2 #PLOSONE https://t.co/tqmGtdXIqa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamLichtenstein @marwa_zaatari @MarcelHarmon1 @linseymarr @jljcolorado @WBahnfleth @CorsIAQ @stephensbrent @kprather88 @IAQinGWN ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drmansfeldt Do you find that the ww shows the virus shedding sooner than the saliva tests or vice versa?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FaiolaLabUCI ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eatplaylove They make terrible fries. I beg to differ. Enjoy SB!!!  Did you find Spudnuts?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI - COVID-19 Outbreak and Hospital Air Quality: A Systematic Review of Evidence on Air Filtration and Recirculation  https://t.co/FRFDTBsEXW]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>