<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@drkatmclean @sophiescott2 @MelissaSweetDr Thanks - but can I respectfully say that I think dropping a male name here kinda makes ruins the focus. I don't have the right words. However good my intentions, keep the focus on the excellent women communicators for a message like this IMO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelissaSweetDr: Male voices dominate the news. Heres how journalists and female experts can turn this around https://t.co/nBWxaRsqQo #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sophiescott2: @MelissaSweetDr And use Twitter to seek out female experts! They are there and amazing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LukeDashjr That's your response? Dude.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New COVID-19 case identified in NSW, venue alerts in Sydney's eastern suburbs https://t.co/Q2k3Dub4Qm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pardonedostrich @Alice_Porter I was right. Have patience was the msg back then. And that's what I'd say now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the misinformation age, the @ConversationEDU is an essential island of hope providing context for current events and writing with more facts than feelz. https://t.co/c9BCdVKEOR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey rainy Wednesday Brisbane https://t.co/8FuHScNQdt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billnyc @Leugar24 Money is found for all manner of things. When there's a desire to find it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StillDelvingH @CT_Bergstrom @DrEricDing @GuptaR_lab @Le___Doc @dgurdasani1 Ask ~220 human respiratory viruses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarvelStudios: The world may change and evolve. But the one thing that will never change, were all part of one big family. https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why don't we have dashboards of domestic violence attacks  murders? This is a chronic disease of society. If this was notifiable we'd publicly track it with weekly reports  spend lots to identify  protect against it. Why don't we care enough? #domesticviolence #DomesticAbuse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GregDore2 Where were the fines for Italy, the UK and the US by the way? Why now? How many have travelled to and from Australia in the past 16mths?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GladysB: NSW is home to some of the leading experts in mRNA technology which includes manufacturing the COVID-19 vaccine. Exploring opp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marvel, that trailer brings me such joy. But it still doesn't distract me from @TheBadBatch ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Glamam28: @schwarmerei1 @MackayIM Oh yeah. It's tomorrow down there. May the 4th be with you. https://t.co/peAxAgMp3y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Stephen_Stanton: Less than 6 hours to go until the premiere of #StarWars #TheBadBatch on #DisneyPlus! Have you got your watch-along bin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @greggrunberg: Happy #MayThe4th #StarWarsDay  https://t.co/ztFKMi9K8m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@schwarmerei1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @schwarmerei1: @MackayIM I saw this and thought of you https://t.co/me8Atgz4SR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tmprowell: What causes blood clots? Many things: cancer, surgery, being sedentary (really, go for a walk). You know what else? #SARSCoV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeffBullard16 You can leave me out of these theories going forward. Thx.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LaurenWeberHP:  Is your child in a classroom with unproven air cleaner technology?   Our investigation found over 2,000 schools acro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReusVisser: Prof. Andreas Beyer has offered a devastating critique of both the Review Report and the Addendum of the @BorgerPieter-Kmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aishamae: How coronavirus spreads.. Advice from @WHO versus the Australian Department of Heath (@healthgovau version doesnt mention ae]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gorskon: The latest antivax disinformation about #CovidVaccine is that its recipients shed spike protein, which sickens people and ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: SO glad to see @WHO update on transmission!  short-range: aerosols containing the virus are inhaled or droplets contact eye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RichardfromSyd1 @mvankerkhove Nothing if I understand your question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But July2020 (Oct2020 update) version leaned specifically on the larger respiratory droplets. Not wanting to trigger anyone here - just noting. https://t.co/tBBRuZuwbs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichaelYartys @throse_gd D'Oh. My bad. Time for bed!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As @mvankerkhove notes https://t.co/9Qzli0RVBw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mvankerkhove: @SaskiaPopescu @BogochIsaac This language is not new. The updated QA reflects updates from guidance from last year   if]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@throse_gd Where is the text - do you know?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VirusesImmunity: After many months of planning and hard work by so many (incl. @hmkyale @Dianaberrent @wade_schulz @CharleszYaleMed @Aa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenBranswell: .@WHO Director-General @DrTedros is seeking a second term. Remains to be seen if he will be challenged. https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plea for national guidance on hotel quarantine, after W.H.O. accepts speaking and breathing is spreading coronavirus https://t.co/LYPZDZBMM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jennamclarke: COVID may be insidious but there is a more imminent threat terrorising and threatening the people of Perth https://t.co/I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaMottram: After W.H.O. issues new advice that coronavirus is airborne, @rajah_mich says it is "seismic". She explains why it matter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CathNoakes @PrasadKasibhat1 @microlabdoc Yes that was a popular adaptation of Prof Reason's model.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@judysimpson222 @Brian_Orak @a_chtung @CDCgov It can indeed. And it can persist for quite a time in some cases. Perhaps there's a role for reinvigorating the immune response, among those cases at least?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CathNoakes @PrasadKasibhat1 @microlabdoc I absolutely didn't. I came far too late to this. I think because I was simply getting my info from the wrong sources. And this wasn't my area of expertise so I missed that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@throse_gd @Warish73 @DrPieterPeach Warish/Ivy - is this something we can all try to setup?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@richardajabu @Warish73 @CDCofBC Extremely unlikely as cells outside the body are on a path to death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Warish73 @throse_gd @DrPieterPeach But access can be applied for. Collaborations can be formed. Things can be achieved, despite the extra work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drvyom: Similar results for both AZ and Pfizer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aperfectstrange @richardajabu @CDCofBC Vital antigens I think. Suggested persistent gut infection.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeffBullard16 Where is this difference?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeffBullard16 No.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Warish73 @liammannix https://t.co/J3c1xR20Ms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Warish73 @DrPieterPeach Any ideas why Warish doesnt have access to epi data @throse_gd?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good piece. But no clear answer (spoiler alert). Pop-up local sample collection for the win? https://t.co/YvqvSqUuVB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroliter: I disagree with this take. The virus remains SARS-CoV-2, and the disease, COVID-19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RidleyDM @kindenough2018 @notdred @Brian_Orak @macroliter But the possibility exists and shouldn't be entirely discounted without more data... "There is a realistic possibility that VOC B.1.1.7 is associated with an increased risk of death compared to non-VOC viruses" https://t.co/1WgdQ8evaN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RidleyDM @kindenough2018 @notdred @Brian_Orak @macroliter "..nd thus compromised timely access to hospital care" https://t.co/HJfCqtvz7P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RidleyDM @kindenough2018 @notdred @Brian_Orak @macroliter And it's complex "501Y.V2 variant was associated with in-hospital mortality that was 20% higher in the second wave in South Africa than in the first wave..//..due mainly to the greater transmissibility of this variant, which rapidly overburdened health services.."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RidleyDM @kindenough2018 @notdred @Brian_Orak @macroliter Not quite that absolute. "We show an increased risk for hospitalisations and ICU admission associated with the SARS-CoV-2 variants" https://t.co/ZkyuhZ8rSf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WryWryWry3 And if you're a scientist who isn't here to help others learn or to learn yourself, maybe you're actually contributing to the problem, or just have no plan to help the public understand what they *already* find scary  overwhelming.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WryWryWry3 I absolutely have no problem with pointing out  suggesting a correction for something that is flat out wrong/wobbly/unclear. My point was we can do that without aggression (esp when an error isn't intentional misinformation). I don't think that way of communicating helps anyone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @macroliter And mine.  I have some other deleting to do now.  Thx.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroliter @Brian_Orak Thx. Sorry for sticking my nose in. Can't help myself sometimes-am trying to work on that. I was just trying to say keep the grumpiest responses (which I'm all for btw!) for the true f!$%heads.  But I've learned something from this, so all good! /out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MauritzPreller @TheEliKlein @macroliter I admit I've struggled with what has largely been good content framed in a way that the public will understand (I've overlooked mistakes), versus past deeds I find atrocious - the person vs their expertise. This was a kick in the butt that has helped me coalesce that thinking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @macroliter I'm across that and agree about the person and his actions and his arrest. Should we discard his experienced opinion though?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheEliKlein @macroliter Okay. I hear that. I'll withdraw my comments in this thread and give it all some more thought.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @macroliter Huh? You're not being called a denier by me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @macroliter Ah, so it's more than some tweets that you're addressing here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @macroliter You're definitely a hero]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brian_Orak @macroliter Yep. Definitely the way to address these life-threatening concerns. Pull down a useful messenger, in public because of some imperfect tweets. I hope you spend same % of  time on those wilfully lying  spreading disinformation. Guess not, else you'd have no time for this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DRTomlinsonEP @DrPieterPeach Jimenez, Marr, Milton and others didn't kill it despite a truckload of engagement in recent months. IMO, it now really needs WHO and each country's major public health institutions to campaign about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DRTomlinsonEP @DrPieterPeach Suppressed or poorly communicated across disciplines or not acted on because too much effort and work...etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KurtadikarKetan @macroliter Too much performance pressure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'd rather call it a taxi than change the syndrome name because of mutations to the causative agent and a fractional change in established patterns of transmission and outcome. We could be calling "flu", influenza 2021.4.x.1 if we adopt this approach https://t.co/PExZiC7pfm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @buitengebieden_: Silverback gorilla stops traffic to cross the road..    YT: BBC Earth https://t.co/NPF1bV97nx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jljcolorado: La Plaza de @LasVentas tirando el dinero y contaminando con teatro de higiene. El sol ya desinfecta rpido, y este virus s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GYamey: Blimey. Sweden is not, um, doing well in controlling viral transmission. https://t.co/IulRJinOeo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's still a thing of the present??? https://t.co/WHuALQ9pyx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JVLazarus: 1/ SARS-CoV-2 elimination, not mitigation, creates best outcomes for health, the economy, and civil liberties  In @TheLancet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KurtadikarKetan @Crof Bloody hell.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YouAreLobbyLud So the "fishy" part was that it spread in a way different from what Hospital IPC had prepared staff for?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mvankerkhove: Important paper on the duration of antibody response for #MERS-CoV.   Although this is still not fully understood, this s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InCytometry @UK_Centrist @mvankerkhove @CDCgov Yes that is the point here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KurtadikarKetan @Crof Hulk smash. Wolverine mutant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Crof *into]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SixandLaura @YouAreLobbyLud Could you have a guess?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Longevity of Middle East Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus Antibody Responses in Humans, Saudi Arabia. "MERS-CoVspecific neutralizing antibodies were detected for 6 years postinfection" -so, ya know, patience people. #MERS https://t.co/IBKYMdkLfk via @CDCgov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JAI_SHRI_BHARAT @UQ_News @abcnews Not sure anyone is fighting with the original variant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianAdams66 @Crof That second paragraph is precisely why that headline shouldn't exist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YouAreLobbyLud Why? Didn't you get samples tested?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcGozlan: Une seule dose de vaccin stimule limmunit contre certains variants du SARS-CoV-2 chez des personnes ayant dj t infect]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Crof Talk about a headline that doesn't need to exist. They could mutate onto cabbages. But *have they*?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rosewind2007 Same. Really disappointed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kprather88: https://t.co/nEMWJ6CVC9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kprather88: India is now spraying disinfectant from drones. They are in desperate need of clear recommendations from @WHO on how to pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolutely. The absence of these conversations is astonishing. RSV and MPV and flu each kill. Can we only hold one thought in our heads at a time? https://t.co/5flEEHSsQ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanSuan2 @GregDore2 (people watch TV?)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@velevetmaggot (Then it will be aptly named ) https://t.co/88SLqEOCaE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PerpetualWinger @StephenKing Or GONE WITH THE WIND, a story of SARS-CoV-2 transmission]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: A very good US Saturday reporting for new vaccinations. 3.3 million. Brings the total given to ~244 million doses and well o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey @MicrosoftTeams - a proper black and a proper white would be awesome for the excellent Shifts App.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thinkofthehuma1 Nuh. That's the swarm of midges in my backyard.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites Really? Where is this??]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>