<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCEnvironment: Today is #AsthmaAwarenessDay. If you have #asthma, talk with your doctor about your asthma treatment goals and how to a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DiseaseDetectives in CDCs Laboratory Leadership Service lead cutting-edge #PublicHealth projects inside and outside of the lab. Applications are open through June 4. Attend a webinar to learn how to make your mark as a #LaboratoryLeader: https://t.co/JUzElI3iK5. https://t.co/KpnxBaIbhT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay on top of global #COVID19 vaccination progress using CDCs COVID Data Tracker. The new Global Vaccinations tab allows you to monitor vaccinations by country, including the number of doses administered and the brand(s) of vaccine. More: https://t.co/mOHHidneO1. https://t.co/YCds5JEExc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCEnvironment: This Air Quality Awareness Week be air aware! Check the Air Quality Index (AQI) at https://t.co/VpVsYMchgZ and adjust y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Almost everyone in the U.S. now lives within 5 miles of a #COVID19 vaccination site.   Now that it's easier than ever to get a COVID-19 vaccine,  #SleeveUp so we can start to do some things that we stopped doing because of the pandemic. Find a provider: https://t.co/6RIBRCJpZu. https://t.co/uHnJ8tWWMM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HCPs: In this #HowIRecommend video, pediatrician Dr. Tolu Adebanjo explains how to improve childhood vaccine recommendations through using a presumptive approach, sharing personal stories, and attentively listening to parents: https://t.co/P1LicbmdZq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDCs Peggy Honein was on the front line with state health departments to slow the spread of #COVID19  made sure they knew about new discoveries from their data. Even with COVID-19 vaccines widely available, she says we cant let our guard down. More: https://t.co/w4w4w4bZYT. https://t.co/HdW7ahGSO4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When talking with friends and family about #COVID19 vaccines, it can be helpful to ask open-ended questions to explore concerns. For example, ask, What are your thoughts about the vaccine? More conversation tips: https://t.co/tGGql5cDOC. https://t.co/SuVMIdoxCe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDC_NCEZID: World #HandHygiene Day is May 5. Cleaning your hands with alcohol-based hand sanitizer or soap and water is a simple yet ef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCEnvironment: May is #AsthmaAwarenessMonth! If you have #asthma, know your triggers and learn how to avoid them. Find #asthma facts h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @USAGov: You don't have to struggle with your mental health alone. Follow @USAGov this #MentalHealthAwarenessMonth for practical tools t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 vaccines can help us get back to doing the things we love.  As of May 3, more than 147 million people in the United States had received at least one dose of COVID-19 vaccine. Of those, more than 105 million are fully vaccinated.   More: https://t.co/zYLe3H12re https://t.co/jc3TEpNnic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations to CDCs Principal Deputy Director Anne Schuchat, MD (RADM, USPHS, RET) on being named a finalist in The Partnership for Public Services 2021 Service to America Medals, known as the Sammies. https://t.co/KLQcLDnt7Y https://t.co/z1NykNQkjf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[School Administrators: Employees can reduce the risk of getting #COVID19 while preparing or serving meals. Clean frequently touched surfaces. Prioritize outdoor serving and seating. #WearAMask and stay at least 6 ft from others. Learn more: https://t.co/vsF3eau1ky. https://t.co/YZ0WVxFNJA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New @JAMA_current study reviews US cases of CVST with thrombocytopenia after JJ #COVID19 vaccination. CDC recommends clinicians check patients presenting with symptoms for CVST or other thrombotic events, and for thrombocytopenia. https://t.co/ul4Wrwiqfy. https://t.co/nhC4Vo5p2P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HCPs: Are your patients asking about the Johnson  Johnson #COVID19 vaccine?  New tools are available to help you answer your patients questions. Your strong recommendation can help patients make an informed decision about getting vaccinated.  More: https://t.co/pB3ONoRJZ1.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@ONDCP  @CDCInjury #DrugFreeCommunity coalitions helpprevent youth substance useby implementing evidence-based strategies and activities at the community level. Learn more: https://t.co/iDf7H6DY43. https://t.co/drvWlEK9EP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since life has been anything but routine lately, heres a friendly reminder to make sure that routinely recommended childhood vaccinations are  part of your child's safe return to school. #VaccinesWork  https://t.co/N4EvHmcubn https://t.co/D1ziVDVH4C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its #NationalPetWeek!  During the pandemic, pets have given us comfort and companionship. Take steps to keep your pet healthy  itll keep you healthy too!   Learn how: https://t.co/8V3c09WDrI. #OneHealth https://t.co/hj0okPRdnY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today @MinSanteRDC and @WHO announced the end of the #Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of the Congo. CDC will continue supporting @MinSanteRDC to prevent, detect, and respond to #Ebola outbreaks. https://t.co/D3u2HcmP7r https://t.co/nIbMgTCMlH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccines are here! For help spreading the word about the safe and effective vaccines with older adults, get the Older Adults Toolkit at https://t.co/R7b3W4rNlD. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/Tw0Dq2hKFQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you a recent recipient of a doctoral degree? CDC is recruiting global health experts for its new postdoctoral fellowship in global HIV and TB. Click the link to apply: https://t.co/o4kDKy0543. https://t.co/7R9Jhl1AlG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May is Hepatitis Awareness Month! A month to raise awareness, learn the ABCs of viral #hepatitis and talk with your healthcare provider about hepatitis testing and #vaccination. Learn more: https://t.co/Jz524sqdOQ. https://t.co/IAEA2Z8x5R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To encourage the nurses you know to get vaccinated against COVID-19, get the Nurses Toolkit at https://t.co/R7b3W4rNlD for resources to help you have these important conversations. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/wEuIWCUz9X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May is Lyme Disease Awareness Month. #DYK Lyme disease is the most common tickborne disease in the United States? Learn more about preventing tick bites: https://t.co/Mml5OpL47L. #GetTipsStopTicks @CDC_NCEZID https://t.co/W3JvGYtA2T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following health and safety measures that protect against #COVID19 helped reduce severe illness from March-October 2020, but cases rose during the winter. We cant give up now. Keep doing your part to stop the spread. Get vaccinated. Wear a Mask. More: https://t.co/2D2kWEJgoS https://t.co/lK4TBZA37G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Subscribe to get CDCs COVID Data Tracker Weekly Review sent to your inbox every Friday: https://t.co/m5w5IKMJIv.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC monitors #COVID19 cases, deaths, variants,  vaccinations worldwide. If youre traveling, make sure you understand the situation with COVID-19 where youre going so you can travel as safely as possible. Learn more: https://t.co/F4bAyObDp1. https://t.co/smaoZ7rZoz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 vaccines are an important tool to stop this pandemic. Millions of people in the U.S. have been safely vaccinated and are starting to return to activities they missed.   What are you looking forward to doing once youre fully vaccinated?   More: https://t.co/FJMon7WlFO. https://t.co/voh5UiScew]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Parents: Youth and summer camp enrollment is near. To slow the spread of #COVID19, encourage kids to #WearAMask that fits snugly over their nose  mouth, tell an adult if they feel sick, and stay 6 feet away from others. More: https://t.co/BSgsPiqW0q. https://t.co/Wtxgmtd8Lx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new @CDCMMWR details a safety review of Johnson and Johnsons Janssen #COVID19 Vaccine. The review shows many people report not feeling well the day or so after vaccination, but these effects are non-serious and temporary. Learn more:  https://t.co/7JWA8N9mL2. https://t.co/gojCU1yCRL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Recipients should be observed on site for at least 15 minutes after any vaccination, including #COVID19 vaccination. Learn more: https://t.co/QcfPCviXPH.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Findings in the new CDC MMWR show that #COVID19 vaccine safety monitoring systems are working as intended to detect adverse events, including those that do not generally meet criteria for being serious. Learn more: https://t.co/QcfPCviXPH.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fainting  other anxiety-related events can occur after administration of any vaccine. A new @CDCMMWR shows that fainting was more common after Johnson  Johnsons Janssen #COVID19 Vaccine than after flu vaccination. Learn more: https://t.co/QcfPCviXPH. https://t.co/y7ru4nSOCi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDC_NCEZID: Stay healthy by making handwashing a regular part of your cooking routine. #Washyourhands to prevent spreading germs to you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 26, national forecasts predict 2,1008,700 new #COVID19 hospitalizations will likely be reported on May 24. More: https://t.co/Xys80ZGlxV. https://t.co/f5ZPyzd3zp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 26, national forecasts predict 1,9006,600 new #COVID19 deaths will be reported during the week ending May 22. That would bring the projected total number of U.S. deaths to 583,000595,000. More: https://t.co/rcqjOX3Ypl. https://t.co/TQ1OySkex9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 26, national forecasts predict 158,000601,000 new #COVID19 cases will likely be reported during the week ending May 22. More: https://t.co/7AP4I3S9PU https://t.co/ufGPInakr1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you thinking about getting pregnant or are already pregnant and have sickle cell disease (SCD)? Learn how #SCD is passed in families and how to have a safe and healthy pregnancy with this shareable fact sheet: https://t.co/oUlAVBfxaL. https://t.co/oXFudA7G3T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New @CDCMMWR finds Alaska #COVID19 prevention measures for the seafood processing industry, where workers often live together while also working in crowded plants, might have reduced the spread. More measures could further reduce COVID-19 cases. More: https://t.co/F8fxGc9UBh. https://t.co/BF5gseN3Jd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you have questions about Johnson  Johnsons Janssen #COVID19 Vaccine?  You can learn more by talking with your healthcare provider or visiting: https://t.co/SVTRkBgIET. https://t.co/QJqE5lUNxz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New @CDCMMWR finds risk of #COVID19 was higher among farmworkers who worked mostly indoors in large groups than among those working alone, in smaller groups, or partially outdoors. Physical distancing, testing,  vaccination can help slow COVID-19 spread. https://t.co/PzGgQ82L5F https://t.co/z74X0DU4i6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New @CDCMMWR describes first linked U.S. clusters of people infected with the B.1.351 variant of virus that causes #COVID19 with no known link to travel. Prevention strategies like masks, physical distancing,  vaccination are critical to slow the spread. https://t.co/83tDeBej5B https://t.co/zC5efEGMLn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrJudyMonroe: I had the pleasure of talking with @CDCDirector Dr. Rochelle Walensky for #AspenIdeasHealth. Check out my blog where I hi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This National Infant Immunization Week, make sure your little patients are on track with routinely recommended vaccinations. Get resources for talking with parents about vaccinations. https://t.co/ijoBmfX0L2 #ivax2protect #NIIW https://t.co/bohmJxOSnj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join millions of others in the U.S. and  #SleeveUp for your #COVID19 vaccine, so we can all get back to seeing our loved ones and doing the things we love!   Everyone in the U.S. age 16 and older is now eligible to receive a COVID-19 vaccine.  More: https://t.co/FJMon7WlFO. https://t.co/nGph58jChA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHNSC: The United States is delivering emergency COVID-19 supplies worth more than $100 million in the coming days to support our partn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 rates are falling. The current 7-day average of new daily cases is 53,934, a 16% decrease from the previous week. If youre not fully vaccinated, practice healthy habits to slow the spread.  Get vaccinated. Wear a mask.  Stay 6 feet apart.  More: https://t.co/gp6X4zTnBT. https://t.co/NkS5LQCtxq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A CDC study found mRNA #COVID19 vaccines help keep you from getting COVID-19 under real-world conditions. Health care and essential workers who were fully vaccinated with an mRNA vaccine were 90% less likely to get COVID-19. Learn more: https://t.co/ikY41QTKP5. https://t.co/iehp80mBE1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[School systems  local governments: Help families prepare for their childs return to school. Remind them that children may have missed routine vaccinations during the pandemic. Children should be up to date on all recommended vaccinations. Learn more: https://t.co/mdgcsGmYHW. https://t.co/549T6UqsTb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that, by the age of 2, routine vaccines help protect your child against 14 serious diseases? Check with your doctor to ensure your child is up to date on vaccinations. #ivax2protect #NIIW https://t.co/e2Hce30pQg https://t.co/vvLtr81SSn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Camp Staff: Slow the spread of #COVID19. Keep healthy camp environments  operations. Get vaccinated as soon as you can, stay 6ft from others, #WearAMask that fits snugly over your nose  mouth. Encourage sick staff  campers to stay home. More: https://t.co/BSgsPiqW0q. https://t.co/reuGVVxZbV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New @CDCMMWR has good news: mRNA COVID-19 vaccines (Pfizer-BioNTech, Moderna) reduced the risk of #COVID19-related hospitalization by 94% among fully vaccinated people 65+. CDC recommends getting a COVID-19 vaccine to prevent severe COVID-19 illness: https://t.co/W4SFuV6wQp. https://t.co/Jf4ph2rl4s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HCPs: Are your patients asking about the Johnson  Johnson #COVID19 vaccine?  New tools are available to help you answer your patients questions. Your strong recommendation can help patients make an informed decision about getting vaccinated.  More: https://t.co/pB3ONoRJZ1. https://t.co/RMtrenzQhE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DYK? CDCs COVID Data Tracker allows you to compare trends in #COVID19 cases and deaths for up to 6 US states, territories, or regions. Learn more about how the pandemic is affecting your state or region through this interactive dashboard: https://t.co/Scwfd7l3S6. https://t.co/3prgfwzUwA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCEnvironment: Join us in celebrating 20 years of restaurant food safety research by CDCs Environmental Health Specialists Network! L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 vaccines play a key role in ending the pandemic and helping us get back to normalcy.   Millions of people in the U.S. who are fully vaccinated can safely enjoy time together indoors without wearing masks. Learn more: https://t.co/FJMon7WlFO. https://t.co/okW9MuFUhP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This National Infant Immunization Week, help us spread the word that this year its more important than ever for children to stay on track with routinely recommended vaccinations. https://t.co/yb1JfK2snJ  #ivax2protect #NIIW https://t.co/7bd0JGgzKc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People fully vaccinated against #COVID19 can participate in some indoor events safely, without much risk. Outdoor visits and activities are safer than indoor activities. https://t.co/s5kXwg65fB https://t.co/ZVDpCaQAIO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When choosing safer activities, consider how #COVID19 is spreading in your community, the number of people participating in the activity, and the location of the activity. https://t.co/s5kXwg65fB https://t.co/TZhssyVGKB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are fully vaccinated against #COVID19, you can start doing many things that you had stopped doing because of the pandemic. If you havent been vaccinated yet, get a vaccine as soon as you can. See full details: https://t.co/s5kXwg65fB https://t.co/fvhehUiiCi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new @CDCMMWR reaffirms the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) recommended use of the Johnson  Johnson #COVID19 Vaccine. ACIP determined that the vaccines known and potential benefits outweigh its known and potential risks. More:  https://t.co/JNOVWW1T4b. https://t.co/SpLpQXTh78]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have recently traveled, attended a large social gathering, or been in a crowded indoor setting, consider getting tested for #COVID19.   Learn more about testing: https://t.co/Bhk0Y8ctB8. https://t.co/6J4ig1yh1i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HCPs: Attend todays COCA Call at 2pm EDT: Johnson  Johnson/Janssen #COVID19 Vaccine and Thrombosis with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome: Update for Clinicians. Learn more:   https://t.co/nXVim8dUTr. https://t.co/98lXPK2Zxu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many families routines were disrupted this year because of #COVID19 including having regular checkups and receiving recommended vaccinations. National Infant Immunization Week is a great time to ensure your child is up to date. #ivax2protect #NIIW https://t.co/N4EvHmcubn https://t.co/tpDOI8fJ4Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 vaccines are now more widely accessible.  As of April 26, more than 140 million people in the United States had received at least one dose of COVID-19 vaccine. Of those, more than 95 million are fully vaccinated.   More: https://t.co/zYLe3H12re. https://t.co/aM4RxhKlLz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to healthcare providers and frontline workers across the country for taking extra steps to care for children safely during the #COVID19 pandemic and helping to protect the health of our families and communities.  #VaccinesWork #NIIW #ivax2protect https://t.co/WMcJec2H5L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turning 16 means you can get your license AND your #COVID19 vaccination. Everyone 16 years and older is now eligible to get a COVID19 vaccine.  More: https://t.co/yJFqxDIlhb. https://t.co/m76VEbBfSV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CDCTips is looking for stories about the health effects of smoking on former smokers and their loved ones who take care of them. Have a story to tell? https://t.co/Sj5PMwvM93 https://t.co/WsNEnxyYZd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HCPs: Want to know more about Johnson  Johnson/Janssen #COVID19 Vaccine and Thrombosis with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome? Attend the COCA Call, Tuesday, April 27, at 2pm EDT. Learn more: https://t.co/nXVim8dUTr. https://t.co/RIrSun3Qwb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCGlobal: The #polio program delivers more than just the polio vaccine. Polio health workers also respond to #malaria, #Ebola, #measle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[April 28 is International Noise Awareness Day. Loud noise can be the volume of noise coming through your earbuds or headphones. Learn more about how to protect your hearing. https://t.co/eLQAFTBAVV. https://t.co/lCtWdb5Lug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DYK? If you have symptoms or have been exposed to someone with #COVID19, you can get tested for free.   To find a free testing site, visit your health department website or the HHS Community-Based Testing Sites webpage: https://t.co/8Yx3XcHCLM. https://t.co/IYeA7LgmzE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join todays CDC #COVID19 Partner Update Call at 3:00 pm EDT, Keeping up With Critical Diabetes Care and Prevention During COVID-19.   Retweet and Register: https://t.co/DgcvyJs75q.    #Diabetes #COVID19 https://t.co/7SpOYfEfk9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This National Infant Immunization Week, its more important than ever to help protect children from vaccine-preventable diseases. Talk to your childs doctor to make sure they are on track with routinely recommended vaccinations. #ivax2protect #NIIW https://t.co/N4EvHmcubn. https://t.co/0YY7DwwJFc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know 1 in 6 children has a developmental delay or disability?   If you are concerned about your childs development, there are steps you can take to help, see them here: https://t.co/BjZXrLImoA. #ActEarly #AutismAwarenessMonth https://t.co/vf7fvqiX4g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cancer doesnt wait, and neither should you. Take care of your health with routine cancer screenings. Talk to your doctor about what screening tests are right for you. https://t.co/FhgqnP6wMB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctoral-level healthcare professionals, scientists, and nurses: Put your knowledge to work as a CDC #DiseaseDetective for a lifechanging experience in #PublicHealth! Apply now to the Epidemic Intelligence Service: https://t.co/keaIG3Vbz9. https://t.co/GcAMh8Pqii]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do your part. #WearAMask   #SlowTheSpread of #COVID19. Make sure your mask fits snugly against the sides of your face w/ no gaps along the sides or top of the mask. More: https://t.co/rjQXPVBQHe. https://t.co/25B5VlFhE2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disruptions from #COVID19 mean too many children have fallen behind on routine vaccinations. Join us for National Infant Immunization Week to help ensure children get caught upand are protected for in-person learning and play. #IVax2Protect #NIIW https://t.co/yb1JfK2snJ https://t.co/7u8yrxSRJJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meningitis is a diagnosis no parent ever wants to hear. Thankfully, vaccines can prevent infections from some types of germs that cause meningitis. Learn more about meningitis this World Meningitis Day on April 24: https://t.co/MZaumel4ON. #DefeatMeningitis https://t.co/sQHQcGGMMq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC and @US_FDA lift recommended pause on Johnson  Johnson (Janssen) #COVID19 vaccine use following thorough safety review. See full statement: https://t.co/yTTGfGsgSH https://t.co/1kYETjWUgJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Subscribe to get CDCs COVID Data Tracker Weekly Review sent to your inbox every Friday: https://t.co/m5w5IKMJIv.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 22, 2021, more than one-third of people in the U.S. 18+ are fully vaccinated. Now, all people 16+ are eligible for a #COVID19 vaccine. Getting a vaccine will help protect you, help protect others, and help end the pandemic. Read more: https://t.co/F4bAyObDp1. https://t.co/xIcdFBok3i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As more people get #COVID19 vaccinations, recent COVID-NET data show adults over 65 years now make up less than a third of all COVID-19-associated hospitalizations - down from more than half at the beginning of the year. Get vaccinated when you can. More: https://t.co/dTvhftTxuV https://t.co/3y1t2YXI8m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WeCanDoThis! By getting vaccinated against #COVID19 as soon as we can, we bring our nation one step closer to stopping the COVID-19 pandemic. Lets #SleeveUp and do our part. Find a COVID-19 vaccine provider near you: https://t.co/6RIBRCJpZu. https://t.co/lR7YJWKpZi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC has classified SARS-CoV-2 variant B.1.526.1 as a variant of interest. Some treatments for #COVID19 have shown to be less effective for this variant, but current vaccines are still anticipated to reduce the risk of severe illness.  Learn more: https://t.co/yl5AuKBhdt. https://t.co/zMVdI5EIxy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SALMONELLA OUTBREAK: Do not eat, sell, or serve recalled Jules Foods products with any expiration date: cashew brie (classic, truffle,  black garlic), artichoke spinach dip, and vegan ranch dressing. https://t.co/ynuIbW5djG https://t.co/9eh9BFIrX6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a new @CDCMMWR, possible COVID-19-related symptom visits were common 1-6 months after diagnosis among adults with #COVID19 who didnt require a hospital stay. Patients  clinicians should be aware of the potential for post-COVID conditions. More: https://t.co/Z1jBzuGrFg. https://t.co/YM5pEPamJG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDCs Laboratory Leadership Service trains PhD scientists to serve as #DiseaseDetectives in the field and in #PublicHealth labs across the country. Attend webinars to hear fellows experiences and get tips for applying by June 4: https://t.co/JUzElI3iK5. https://t.co/sXK2NSHcm9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 19, national forecasts predict 2,2008,200 new #COVID19 hospitalizations will likely be reported on May 17. More: https://t.co/Xys80ZGlxV. https://t.co/c4YaucwaNd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 19, national forecasts predict 2,1008,800 new #COVID19 deaths will be reported during the week ending May 15. That would bring the projected total number of U.S. deaths to 579,000596,000. More: https://t.co/rcqjOX3Ypl. https://t.co/NrtmJkcjfy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of April 19, national forecasts predict 249,000724,000 new #COVID19 cases will likely be reported during the week ending May 15. More: https://t.co/7AP4I3S9PU. https://t.co/zRJcE5mjDq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) plays a role in vaccine safety monitoring, including #COVID19 vaccines. ACIPs 15 members review many aspects of vaccines, like safety  effectiveness. Learn more about ACIP: https://t.co/bHCGKohsRS. https://t.co/jS4fiGuwBW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[School administrators: CDC has released updated guidance that can help in planning for and implementing #COVID19 case investigation and contact tracing in K-12 schools and institutions of higher education. Learn more: https://t.co/1v22PrPeYj. https://t.co/CGs7zP8rPa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you have symptoms of COVID-19 or if you could have been exposed to someone with #COVID19, consider getting tested.   For testing locations near you, visit your health department website or the HHS Community-Based Testing webpage: https://t.co/8Yx3XcHCLM. https://t.co/G3iM19WWor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new @CDCMMWR finds nearly 400 #COVID19 cases occurred among incarcerated people at Idaho correctional facilities with work-release programs. Correctional facilities with work release programs should consider steps to reduce COVID-19 spread. More: https://t.co/glFkrxAS5M. https://t.co/1fitN0u5BN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alaskas testing and quarantine requirements for air travelers, started in June 2020, may have limited #COVID19 brought into the state and contributed to the states low case numbers last summer. Learn more: https://t.co/Sl5vW94N6E. https://t.co/8JfeC2e6QX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCMMWR: New, free CE from MMWR  Medscape. Adults with disabilities reported frequent #mentaldistress almost 5 times as often as adult]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nearly 60% of U.S. states and territories are reporting high rates of #COVID19. Help slow the spread in your community:  Wear a mask.   Stay 6 feet apart.  Get vaccinated when its available to you.  Avoid crowds. More: https://t.co/gp6X4zTnBT. https://t.co/9CqJ1R1Xig]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>