<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@northerness Would you expect anything else from those that shop at Primark]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sign this  https://t.co/CHuWLVqU6b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RailwayMobb Fantastic   the people who will flock to your boozer will be go-getters who live their life, the type of people you want to surround yourself with    @RailwayMobb   #NOMASK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @LozzaFox It ends Nige when the dullards amongst us wake the fuck up. Ive been hugging, snogging  had a few #Tinder experiences all year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you could live anywhere in the world which part of #Texas would you choose? https://t.co/N6PEK4DE38]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ @davidkurten https://t.co/mwmzFB9mp9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillyPi85064558 @northerness @DominicRaab Shithouse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmyTanMD Crank]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@offshorebella Ive been saying this for a year - in the immortal words of a very fine wise man give violence a chance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord It has but then you get #Hospitality venues like @MoxyHotels who deserve to be run over twice by a bus https://t.co/Kxsh9KvtUT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DickPower369 Her labia claps when she walks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your going out of business @MoxyHotels  you deserve it   #Hospitality #Brainwashing https://t.co/8WEwDnZsXZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any person capable of angering you becomes your master....  Ive never worn a mask, never been asked to wear a mask never will wear a mask  I control my rhetoric   #mask #BorisJohnsonOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreddiePye_ Not stopped delayed what a shit show of a club #mufc are   #Glazersin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GlazersIn #GlazersIn #GlazersIn  Fantastic comedy at a shit show of a football club - #mufc https://t.co/DotUpjo7fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top man @NoelGallagher  https://t.co/ewQFPzM6w5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock @Conservatives Please knock on my door please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[. A society incapable of affirming life and accepting death will be populated by the walking dead, adherents of a cult of the demi-life who clamour for ever more guidance from experts.  How science has been corrupted@UnHerd https://t.co/5bpHCV2ApB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They report the pts admitted to hospital post jab were frail and elderly. This is the same for all hospital admissions for the Rona but they dont report frail  elderly in the daily fear propaganda    https://t.co/Imeiz4XFOD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This man.....!!! Kneel Starmer is going to save the U.K.     https://t.co/anm32nuoJf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Australia is a fallen country RIP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miss_anthrop75 12 of us watching the football today followed by a full blown orgy - done this every week for a year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To all scientists that have never had a night out - Go Fuck Yourselfs - why?  Read this   Sports fans face told to stamp their feet instead of shouting  singing  https://t.co/mIkaez7CmH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FlowerP79667758 How do you explain Florida, Sweden  Texas and why are they not all over the media.....?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@confidencenac Hes an odious little twat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katie Hopkins is a joy to listen to, today she talks about the potato in a wig @BorisJohnson his latest shag  @JohnLewisRetail   Outstanding Katie   https://t.co/psyNxosbt6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would you leave your kids alone with this one? https://t.co/CrobZiZ5Oa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone need inspiring this morning....?  Do not stress,  @graemeling  is where to go to get it. Not sure what pronoun one uses to identify oneself but it will blow you away]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The nanny state will Ban female football - please  Girl footballers suffer more concussions . . . but play on  https://t.co/hQTW4ws0eG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@graemeling @TiceRichard Keep in touch inspiration the country needs you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@graemeling @TiceRichard Well thats put me in my place hasnt it sugar tits. Please enlighten me with more words of wisdom as I feel Ive much to learn from such an open mind as yours . I truly feel inspired, huge thanks in anticipation of your next pioneering thought provoking master piece]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AgreeT0D1sagree Try our game Natalie- weve banned words bubble, allowed  masks - we shake hands, kiss  laugh at the melts who are scared of taking responsibility for themselves  are in a rush to be a victim.  You offer more to society than the fearful ever will]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@graemeling @TiceRichard Highly diligent of you - quick question you double mask, dont you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TiceRichard Not listened to them since day 1 - dont even no what regulations are in place]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Complete lie, 4 out of 10 people would not trust this turd   #JohnsonMustGo https://t.co/0PyUIJDSME]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I eat steaks  for breakfast you crank - deal with it   #vegan #veganbollocks https://t.co/h4UpqqVxCa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a fucking bell end  https://t.co/8MT14x08zU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not worn a mask once and never will https://t.co/G5ULe70qDF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fucking melt  https://t.co/Hi4tPLWwqD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The demise of the US  How the #USA lost its place globally. The most PC Woke country on the planet with people in the thousands fleeing #California    https://t.co/rw1AxllUAg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The worst player @benmendy23 ever to play for #Mancity comical watching him]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This guy  what a scum bag https://t.co/w1pPrp5N7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britain  USA accuse #Russia of an assault on democracies - the hypocrisy of #Britain  #US  to even utter the word #democracy   Putin must find these 2 countries  their people nothing other than a stain on the planet   Russia will rule the weak spineless woke agenda west]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The champions league of #Woke countries  Can you put these countries in order of #wokeness heres my top 4   #Canada #US #GB #NewZealand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[you lot in the #US voted for this, for Christ sake take him back to his care home  elect @joerogan youve become a parody of yourselves    https://t.co/Sa0Zn6WNeH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@uandmeeverlong @JackPosobiec Thats the death toll of 6% of reported deaths died of covid as reported by the CDC - 6% now the U.K. saying a 1/4 of reported deaths died of covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Admittance on lies and driving fear   Secrets are always exposed   https://t.co/azGl7ILEmV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmma85 Went to local, asked to wear mask outside we all told them to fuck off they said ok we just have to tell you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller Big TIT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YardleyShooting But not due to his Stella performance simple because the opposition parties are TITs  Vote #Reform]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please dont the masses in the U.K. will go into meltdown.....  Actually thinking about this please do, anything to lock the masses away for another year I welcome https://t.co/aEzGpsiPgi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You the people of Britain have allowed yourselves to be lied to by the fear porn. You the people of Britain have destroyed yourselves  your country. Dont simply blame your odious government - you are the guilty ones   #Britain #Sheep #Gutless   https://t.co/SbFfX4cpCI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just been to gym  Amazing this Rona virus, Its in the gym reception picking on people, masks needed but it wont  go upstairs into the gym as no masks needed, clever twat isnt it  #NoVaccinePassport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well done #London when they lock you down again in a few months remember this - this time do not fucking allow it  https://t.co/Bce3gOPMtD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow, Ill bet this Doris has never been back scuttled in her life   https://t.co/T03L62n6Jg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looks like the aliens have had enough of the shit show called planet earth .   Please abduct the whole of Westminster to include every minister of every political party.  Video of UFOs buzzing Navy warship is leaked  https://t.co/XNMHHNfbhv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But this is the variant our lying bastard PM  so called world leading scientists told us was more deadly leading to the #sheep double masking   #fearporn   Kent Covid variant does not increase risk of death  https://t.co/uB0GqXvc0o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Off to boozer to discuss medical fascism - 12 of us on it today, not 1 of us having the magic potion.  We all run our own businesses, understand risk  take responsibility for ourselves  This is my world  the masses arent welcome  #BorisJohnsonOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@northerness I can do what ever the fuck I like as I dont comply]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5rkApO8GmZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny thing about getting older, your eyesight gets weaker but your ability to see through people gets better   #BorisJohnsonOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Election Address by Boris Johns-On   Heres what Johnson has achieved as #PM of the U.K.   Keep this in mind for the local elections in May  https://t.co/hznkZf6mNB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its time the propaganda changed from fear to health education- this will encourage  inspire people to strive for positive  impactful change both personally  for the greater good of the country]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Memorable morning   Out for 15k run - ran past 2 slobs, female touching 200lbs at least wearing masks eating @McDonalds they shouted  I should be wearing a mask I wiped the floor with these pedestrian minds -  I can look in mirror  feel proud   #Brainwashing #fearporn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look up the meaning of #Facisum   Forceable suppression of oppression  These 3  plus the    Prove me wrong   #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/S1nQ9wNnwo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MyBodyMyChoice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Josef Mengele part 2   New Zealand if you allow this you deserve whats coming your way    #NoVaccinePassports #Nocovidvaccine https://t.co/z5HW4vCSbv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The difference between humans and animals.   Animals would never allow the dumbest of the heard to lead them  #BorisJohnsonOut #BorisTheLiar #EndTheLockdown https://t.co/xerz5RQpoY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is @Edwina_Currie the Doris the knobbed Major...? https://t.co/fM3vwNnyNO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On average the left is power hungry the right are paranoid   But.....we are all on a spectrum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@orpheuseurydice @naomirwolf Wait for evidence whilst conducting a live trial - Id suggest you, you little twerp touch your toes  take all the magic potions at the same time then lock yourself away as clearly you offer fuck all to society]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why would we expect anything other than another shit show  These vaccines are approved for emergency use only - an experiment   Under-40s could be asked to take an alternative to AZ Covid vaccine  https://t.co/LIILovOx4T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The once mighty Great Britain now a terrified little island   #BorisTheLiar https://t.co/kewLP6cEDI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a time of deceit telling the truth is a revolutionary act. ~ George Orwell  #BorisJohnsonOut #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now the Johnson  Johnson experiment is paused in the US  #lies #NoVaccinePassport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ah, the trust worthy YouGov pol - well then, book me in for a blood clot   #lies #borisout   https://t.co/glnDWlgbSI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A pint of @SamuelAdamsBeer tastes like Ass https://t.co/DvvXeKtzaN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Correct,  the fans are acting like cunts accepting this https://t.co/umf2846d1e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The British public https://t.co/npcmNUALX0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If contraception pill has a risk of blood clotting rate of 1 in 1000 AZ vaccine has a risk rate of blood clotting of 1 in 10000, then why the fuck does it need to be restricted by multiple countries and medical advisory bodies...?  Its all looking very fishy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is a village somewhere that has lost its idiot  https://t.co/26EappOooS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britain will reach heard immunity come Monday  The next logical steps therefore should be isolate the sheep for life. They become our labours, they do as told without question. They dont build they dont create.  The rest of us, well carry on as we always have done]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its now time hospitality came together as one  took personal responsibility @Sacha_Lord disobey, collectively open or go under.  The public will support this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Genius #government toilets are inside, assume youll only allow a quick shit in the streets then....?  This  https://t.co/RdssqQgdre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPJHodges Youve had more than a dose of AZ vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A tiger doesnt loose sleep over the opinion of sheep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: The White House rules out federal vaccine passports. Apparently Joe Biden cares more about his people's right to privacy and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the Land of the Free? #Freedom  #USA #USA #USA  https://t.co/0iNFioyj5M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beefqueen @mattletiss7 Morning sugar tits, your running pal has just informed the world you sleep in a mask as well. Youve been rumbled you crank]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beefqueen @mattletiss7 Correct james, start with cunt then go from there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beefqueen @mattletiss7 You a double masker James....?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lies lies  more lies from @BorisJohnson  the dick head general public keep touching their toes https://t.co/e2F5joqb7B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[and this sums up this age group https://t.co/00GdTXh5O7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickBoles Heres Nick everyone - can you imagine the stimulating action packed rich  eclectic life this odious fart has lived]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres @DPJHodges bitch slapped once again https://t.co/soBJvrRi78]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont get battle weakened I get battle hardened  #BorisJohnsonOut #BorisTheLiar https://t.co/cALOGWQGS7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#wanker #BellEnd #Tyrant  #Killer  #lier  The list is never ending https://t.co/obBfq70Vn5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBGRichie: Boris Johnson is a wife-beating scumbag who used to burn 50 notes in front of homeless people for shits and giggles. That's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But lets not support this, that would mean that #Trump was correct about this also  https://t.co/wapZ07EMcH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emmaverde9 @Mario_Falcone @MattHancock You seriously believe this after all there lies...? When the country is riddled with odious little twerps like you they can and are doing as they like]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>