<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IUIDfellowship: #idboardreview 30 M from Haiti routine blood draw post-hospitalization for complications w/ congenital disorder. Giemsa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: The number of new daily #COVID19 cases has been increasing for 3 weeks.  As of April 5, over half of U.S. states and territorie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDdocAdi: When the status changes to under review https://t.co/9HwUZ8z89h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SuperBugDoc: Hot off the press #AACJournal. Real world assesment of ceftolozane/tazobactam resistance in P. aeruginosa during therapy a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoF_MDPI: "Associations between #Cryptococcus #Genotypes, Phenotypes, and #Clinical Parameters of Human Disease: A Review " from Dr. Jo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @f2harrell: @AmstatNews The statistical method is more than an array of techniques. The statistical method is a mode of thought; it is s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO: No one should be left on the sidelines in the race against the #COVID19 pandemic.  On International #SportDay, were calling on ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AkiyoshiKitaoka: Disks appear to rotate. https://t.co/cYlBK9QwU4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JClinMicro: Evaluating the Rapid Emergence of Daptomycin Resistance in Corynebacterium: a Multicenter Study  "Daptomycin nonsusceptibil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AaronGoodman33: ABCDEFGHs of Thrombotic Microagiopathies  A = Antibody to ADAMT13 (TTP) , Atypical HUS B = Bone marrow transplant (post]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PatoCulto: Quin hizo esto? https://t.co/3rB4Y0O8p6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AaronGoodman33: Crystals of Death  Happy Monday!  Amorphous blue green crystals  In cytoplasm Neutrophils + monocytes Acute liver fail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InfectiousDz: This is COVID in Chile. It's current COVID peak is the higher than it has ever been. https://t.co/5Sujc7MJ9T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @surgeonshall: The father of modern surgery, Joseph Lister was born #OTD in 1827. Lister transformed the surgical world when he introduc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArgaizR: Another cheap strategy for SIADH  6 scoops / day  250 mosm / day  15 grams of Urea  15 USD  / month  Thanks to @NephroGuy a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IdVilchez: @FranciscoMarty_ https://t.co/yzHreE0hke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IdVilchez Welcome to the team!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SurgeryLegends: The ligament of Treitz (suspensory muscle of duodenum) marks the division between the duodenum and jejunem, and between]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainmaker1973: This scanning electron microscope picture shows a nerve ending. It has been broken open to reveal vesicles (orange and b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CaracasChron: The Pandemics Brutal Toll on Venezuelan Doctors and Nurses; by @osiocabrices https://t.co/rQf6gMAT7F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IUIDfellowship: #idboardreview 50 M immigrant from Mexico presents w/headaches, fever, pleuritic chest pain  adenopathy. +eosinophilia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainmaker1973: There's a place in Morocco where you can find goats perching on these trees' branches. Yes, goats on trees [read more: h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: Weve learned now with COVID that by the time you start to see increased activity through your symptomatic [only] tes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OdedRechavi: Combining research with teaching  https://t.co/ssP9AGJXqD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_FranciscoMarty: "sunrise's blast!" by @_FranciscoMarty #500px https://t.co/agguvIQwSY  #sunrise #ballooning #mushroom #amanecer #blast]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScienceMagazine: A new #SciencePerspective reviews what is known about the emerging plasticity of #SARSCoV2 as well as how best to trac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @f2harrell: Excellent summary of many types of endpoints.  Need to add longitudinal ordinal outcomes to the chart.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarvardBiz: Ideal mentees are enthusiastic, energetic, organized, and focused. They embrace feedback while remaining honest and respons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JClinMicro: Latest episode! Gaps in Laboratory Diagnosis of Fungal Diseases with Dr. Esther Babady (@EBabady), Dr. Sean Zhang  Dr. Sha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @romeerizwan: Spread the wings! Bald Eagle in flight (Near Medford Boathouse, MA).  #loveweekendbirding #lovebirding #birdsofprey https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StoriaMedicina: #OTD of 1933, Yurii Voronoy made the first organ transplant attempt in #history, by grafting the #kidney of a 6-hour de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: Real email today from a student:  Prof, what is your secret for success?  Not sure how to respond, but might share this graph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: .@DrLeanaWen had an idea: Instead of closing.. they could rapidly test every child.. immediately... to tell you if yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarvardBiz: Successful teams reward continuous learning. https://t.co/GyohUq4cdL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MayoClinicINFD: Weekend Digest  An Korean immigrant presented with early stage cholangiocarcinoma.    H  E stained tissue biopsy shown]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @transplantID: To much ?! LOL  #IDtwitter #MedTwitter https://t.co/ZcM2nTrROC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: CDC issues updated guidance on travel for people fully vaccinated against #COVID19. See full statement: https://t.co/lT4XvQVp5D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AllisonRBond: Starting a night             Leaving a night  shift                                shift https://t.co/KFGCpgTeDG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@transplantID @FungalDoc @DrLuisO @DrNeilStone Here is a case and review from a few year ago. The isolate in this case was also echinocandin   https://t.co/D3LV734hEz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@transplantID @FungalDoc @DrLuisO @DrNeilStone For Geotricum voriconazole works well. I dont think adding other stuff helps. Get it tested for other azoles in case you run into toxicity. I think it is frequently echinocandin resistant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarlosdelRio7: Fully vaccinated people may travel, CDC says https://t.co/bd7rYYJVE5 Great news!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PergamIC: After lots of advocacy from the @ASTCT @BTMPublicPolicy and others - @CDCgov recognizing that Bone Marrow Transplant patients]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JakeJohnsonMD: Pt admitted w AMS.   Pt: I'm feeling cold, but I think it's b/c I'm near the window.  Intern: Well, spring is on the way]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamRodmanMD: For all those who wanted a recording of my grand rounds on diagnosis, here it is! https://t.co/GsX40N8BnO https://t.co/9I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SmithsonianMag: Presenting the winners of our 18th annual photo contest! https://t.co/dloVQYbnTa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidSteensma: #ClonalHematopoiesis is just one example of a general process of pre-malignant somatic mosaicism  clonal expansion. (CH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AaronGoodman33: Monoclonal Gammopathies of Clinical Significance!  Divide by organ!  Skin: POEMS NXG Scleromyxedema Cryoglob Schnitzler]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GermHunterMD: Deep cutaneous fungal infections in solid-organ transplant recipients   This 20 yr study from 8 derm centres in France fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeremyFarrar: Best so far https://t.co/hACZWYbVBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoF_MDPI: "#Fungal-Induced Programmed #Cell #Death" https://t.co/oCgU5UnLYF How programmed cell death is induced by fungi that commonly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @onisillos: Ultimate proof that microbiology is the greatest science&gt; Chocolate's secret ingredient is the fermenting microbes that make]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KellyABridges: I believe that for our pharmaceutical interventions to be meaningful, we must have sufficient WASH facilities in place.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ml_barnett: I've been a lot thinking about this paper ... barely made a stir on Twitter  It's a national update on racial disparities i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: @nickshort3000 @RapidTests @US_FDA @AbbottNews @QuidelDX The change that made this possible was a terrific decision by]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: BIG NEWS!!  Rapid Antigen "Paper Strip" Tests get over-the-counter use from @US_FDA!  NO prescription or doctor need]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StoriaMedicina: The great cardiologist Samuel A. Levine died #OTD in 1966 at the age of 75. He was a pioneer in the treatment of corona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MSG_ERC: Images in Clinical Medicine: #Talaromycosis https://t.co/JOsl20gxTO https://t.co/hHf8QLBJ0g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelGIsonMD: Calling all #TxID clinicians - @ttsorg needs your help in understanding what specific topics need to be covered to best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Yale gets a #face lift, a new face!  Bo has been an awesome multidisciplinary leader, congratulations! https://t.co/QaTg8yVgLM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pomahacMD: Im excited to share that I accepted an offer to lead the Plastic Surgery at Yale. It is a distinguished group of faculty an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDSAInfo: IDSA Board member @CarlosdelRio7 administered Atlanta Mayor @KeishaBottomss first dose of the COVID-19 vaccine. https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NobelPrize: The youngest person awarded a Nobel Prize in the sciences (so far) - Lawrence Bragg was born #OnThisDay in 1890. Together w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megtirrell: A potential #covid19 vaccine in time for back-to-school. Pfizer shows 100% efficacy in kids ages 12-15 (18 cases on placebo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IDSAInfo: IDSA member Angelica Kottkamp, MD (@angelickott) shares her experience as an Hispanic physician seeing first-hand the disprop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: Very good piece by @zeynep making the case for ring vaccination in areas experiencing surges. + many other smart observati]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @k_stephensonMD: Join this @MassCPR Anniversary symposium tomorrow on #COVID19 #vaccines and pathogenesis (3/31 4pm EST). Im honored to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DGlaucomflecken: Teamwork https://t.co/2Kf1ipdMAr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kakape: To give the numbers a bit of context: Earlier this month, after about 1.6 million AZ vaccinations and 7 reported cases of CVT,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kakape: According to @PEI_Germany about 2,7 million people have now been vaccinated with AstraZenaca vaccine in Germany. Amongst these:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: The Louvre has released an online platform featuring all of the museum's artworks, consisting of more than 480,000 pieces https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainmaker1973: Bats and dolphins evolved echolocation in the same way (down to the molecular level). An analysis revealed that 200 gene]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MJAckermanMDPhD: Im very very excited about this collaborative effort from @MayoClinic @MayoClinicCV  @AliveCor. This @CircAHA paper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ParasiteGal: The Parasite Case of the Week 632 is up: a fun histopath case with a twist: https://t.co/vVixVWuo8q   #asmclinmicro #MayoC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GermHunterMD: Congratulations @camwolfe! Your #IDTwitter fam are delighted that your tireless work during the pandemic is being recogni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tony_breu: 1/11 Why is alkaline phosphatase elevated in biliary obstruction?  This question was debated for decades. The current explan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StoriaMedicina: The british pharmacologist JR Vane was born #OTD of 1927.   He was awarded the #Medicine @NobelPrize in 1982 along with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenBranswell: A @CDCgov led study suggests the mRNA vaccines are 90% effective in a real world setting  and a setting where people a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @f2harrell: New edition of Statistical Thinking News available w/new recommended #Statistics articles by @Marc_Buyse @MaartenvSmeden @Ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NarjustDumaMD: The #DumaLab is moving up North!   I'm excited to announce I will be joining the team @DanaFarber as the Associate Direc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IUIDfellowship: #idboardreview 50 F presents with enlarging painful breast mass. Biopsy: cystic spaces lined by cuff of neutrophils, GP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hboucher3: Congratulations @EmilyBlumbergMD   #WeAreID #transplantID @IDSAInfo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @monterogabriela: A bombshell article. Reading Epic corruption in a 22 yr Socialist rule, and Maduros stepsons being the true benefi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting analysis by .@safimichael .@guardian: stranding of #Megaship in #Suez #canal was foreseen by many  https://t.co/5OlXfYc1BU  #Evergreen #EVERGIVEN #egypt #trade #containers #balooning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SamuelDM18: Pearl of the weekend ID call : Pulmonary lesions described as "ping pong balls" over the phone. Turned out to be pulmonary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Even as some restrictions ease, lets keep protecting ourselves and others. #WearAMask. Stay 6 ft apart. Avoid crowds  poorly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thomasngmorris: Believe it or not, this bulky bit of kit from the early 1960s is... a defibrillator! https://t.co/yG69wMOWxB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarvardBiz: Working more isn't the same thing as getting more done. https://t.co/IJdBiteqRi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RAEinforma: #Actualidad | huso horario  Un huso (con h) horario es cada una de las partes en que queda dividida la superficie terrest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalVectorHub: Some wonderful news: #CotedIvoire  has eliminated #SleepingSickness  as a public health problem! Congratulations @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lucasmorin_eolc: Always disappointing to see reputable medical journals publish rubbish nutritional epi studies with no regard whatsoev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainmaker1973: The falling green characters at the beginning of all of the Matrix films have become perhaps the most recognisable visua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @profvrr: Alessandro Sette joins #TWiV to discuss role of T cells in COVID-19,  that amino acid changes in #SARSCoV2 variants of concern]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shell_ki: Ad hominem attacks seem to now be the standard fallacious argument style on #science twitter  How about we move on from that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_FranciscoMarty: "Rothkodian dawn!" by @_FranciscoMarty  #500px https://t.co/Zt7RCR9Rlp   #dawn #sunrise #ogunquit #maine #newengland #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #WearAMask when you are taking care of someone who may have #COVID19. Put your mask on before you go into the room with that pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AaronGoodman33: Saturday Night Blood  55 yo male presents to ER with SOB and chest pain. Troponin and BNP elevated.  WBC 39,000, Hgb 11]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IHC_guy: @Chucktowndoc @JLHornick How often do I order a KIT in giardiasis??? . . . only EVERY time!!!  #EverydayAndTwiceOnSunday #Dont]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarvardBiz: When your space is a mess, you are too. https://t.co/cj1bMMfDu2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainmaker1973: How do emperor penguins stay warm enough to survive in -40C or colder? This group of penguins demonstrates the dynamics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @phagedirectory: .@drdaphnemiller describes how most viruses around us are benign, while some are lifesaving. She interviews @DocSaimaAs]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>