<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Have you heard about CQUIPS+? The virtual learning platform connects #qualityimprovement and #patientsafety professionals, researchers and learners to share their work and learn with and from one another. Learn more: https://t.co/FW6iJwGFCE https://t.co/9nAYQiBu7n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ONNEIHR_2020: Register today for the @imn_ontario and ON-NEIHR Spring Gathering (Part Two) featuring IMN-ON faculty panelists!   Visit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteiniBrown: @UofT_dlsph's Institute for Pandemics (IfP) has established an Advisory Table to help inform the Institutes impact on our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Obesity greater risk factor for severe COVID-19 in young people, study shows" PhD student @Bexit90 shared her thoughts. https://t.co/Hnf7g3fEUy https://t.co/4LHqjz2T2p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TorontoStar: "It's not vaccine hesitancy, it's inequity."  Organizers take us inside Toronto's northwest vaccine pop-up clinics where l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KateMMulligan: #PublicHealth leaders need to know how to build strong  savvy relationships between experts, decision makers, service p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ELESHCanada:  @UofT students   is now accepting nominations for their 2021/22 executive team! Nominations are open until ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteiniBrown: Another excellent and timely front-page @TorontoStar story by @UofT_dlsph's @UofT_ijb. https://t.co/8tELvBBvXQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Census 2021: Canadians are talking about race. But the census hasnt caught up," writes @dlsphjournalism Fellow Bryony Lau https://t.co/xhGV1yvV9i via @ConversationCA https://t.co/qTzfsL1LTZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @workingatuoft: Celebrating  Recognizing Asian Heritage Month  The University of Toronto proudly celebrates the contributions that Asia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UTM: 100,000! Since the THP UTM RAWC Clinic launched with @THP_Hospital and @RegionofPeel 2 months ago, more than 100K #COVID19 vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TODAY - Join the next CVPD Seminar Series  @deshaynef of @uOttawa_SEPH  @CHEO presents on Immunization during pregnancy with discussant @Segun_JKO  https://t.co/YVTkXXvSj4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to our partners and panellists for a great week!   - Institute for Pandemics, @UNICEFCanada, @DrJeffKwong, @IDEpiPhD, Dr. Melissa Andrew, @upshur_ross, @DMorleyUNICEF,  @onomeako of @AmrefCanada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Centre for Vaccine Preventable Diseases (CVPD) hosted two webinars last week for World Immunization Week.   You can find the recordings here: https://t.co/VdeQxBhYga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As India continues to break COVID-19 records, Prof. Prabhat Jha ( @countthedead ) says Canada could have done more to strengthen the global distribution of vaccines. https://t.co/NAnwdtE7gN https://t.co/ZiEIHMgWtW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TDRnews: Introducing our new podcast #GlobalHealthMatters! What has #COVID-19 meant for the world of health research? Join @GarryAslany]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnTory: May is South Asian Heritage Month, in which we celebrate the history of Canadians of South Asian descent.  This month serves]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UnityHealthTO: We have a limited number of spots available at St. Joseph's vaccine clinic that we are opening to those 18+ who live in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You're invited!  CVPD's Seminar  Dr. Deshayne Fell (May 3)  ON NEIHR  IMN: Day 2 - Navigating this Time Holistic Wellness for Indigenous Scholars (May 7)  STAGE International Speaker Seminar Series (ISSS) with Clare Turnbull (May 7)  Details: https://t.co/hQ4kuuRRJW https://t.co/mzJbul9jhk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrJaniceDuMont: The #transLINKProject is still seeking diverse voices to shape a research agenda on #SexualAssault and #IPV against tra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CivicActionGTHA: ICYMI: DiverseCity Fellow alum @ImaraAjani is leading a new Climate Resilience Lab at @UofT_dlsph.  This high-impact,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PTP_CPAC: Peter Jni, director of Ontarios COVID-19 scientific advisory table, discusses the measures the Ontario and federal governme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAgenda: "I think it's really important to remember that there are people behind those numbers... they have families, they have peopl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT_TCAIREM:  MAY 11  We're pleased to host @UMich professor Jenna Wiens for a public lecture! She'll discuss how clinicians can use]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is absolutely no evidence whatsoever of shedding of spike protein in vaccinated individuals, nor is it even theoretically possible, says Prof. @PakesGlobal via @AFPFactCheck https://t.co/ggvX3JxZaP https://t.co/1fp97bbmQP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeAreCanPath: CanPath is #hiring a Project Coordinator to join our dynamic team based at @UofT_dlsph! The Project Coordinator will supp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofTNursing: #COVID19 has drawn into sharp focus the impact that #nurses have on community health engagement  and the needs of vulnera]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new @UofT lab led by Prof. @ImaraAjani will bring together lessons from climate change research and the future of community-based resilience work with a racial justice lens. https://t.co/wrPB0hIMto https://t.co/pAgm9BWHuf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Learn how @UofT_dlsph is paving the way for leaders from underrepresented  historically marginalized groups through its hig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UTM @alexgillespie Congratulations to UTM!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT: As India's COVID-19 cases continue to rise, the #UofT communitys thoughts are with our students, staff, faculty and alumni from]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["South Asians are suffering from COVID-19 disproportionately as loved ones in India are dying. Racializing the variant opens up racist scapegoating" write @SaleemRazack and Prof. @ananya_tb https://t.co/bZEZDlCFNq https://t.co/4Nx3DRcxry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CPAC_TV: LIVE: Ontario releases latest COVID-19 modelling data   https://t.co/UOdFnJagn2  EN DIRECT : LOntario dvoile ses nouvelles d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bhmcovid19: Thank you and shot out to @flow935 for this free one month Public Announcement Ad.  https://t.co/fEPuLt0P2T   @UofT_dlsph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TorontoStar: #Breaking: Ontario to open vaccine bookings for anyone over 18 by end of May. https://t.co/NTzgzZIo7p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["How Pfizer Makes Its Covid-19 Vaccine?"   Very cool info videos and images from @nytimes to guide us through this interesting process.   https://t.co/jxkZN5sEeI https://t.co/Gq2t5xklpP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof. Arjumand Siddiqi's work with Tressie McMillan Cottom, sociologist at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, and Sandy Darity was mentioned in a recent @ezraklein podcast episode. Super neat!   Read the transcript here: https://t.co/Nf6ozmXdND https://t.co/VzNE7qo7Y1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof. Quynh Pham suggests that the province may want to look at replicating the work done by Vaccine Hunters Canada on a large scale. https://t.co/sMUAZjaY0z https://t.co/fQW758B2ce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KateMMulligan: This is a positive step, but it is not sufficient to meet the public health needs right now, said Mulligan of @UofT_dl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Congratulations to Dr. Audrey Laporte  Dr. Arjumand Siddiqi of @UofT_dlsph, the new editors of Healthcare Papers by @Longwo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new lab led by Prof. @ImaraAjani brings at U of T will bring together lessons from climate change research and the future of community-based resilience work with a racial justice lens. https://t.co/wrPB0hIMto https://t.co/by7qLOUr66]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteiniBrown: Today at 3 pm I will present the latest modelling from  @COVIDSciOntario. Slides will be posted on https://t.co/oOvVHkUTOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*New panelist*  Don't miss tomorrow's "Ensuring Global Access to COVID-19 Vaccines" event at 1-2 EDT, with @UNICEFCanada, @upshur_ross, @DMorleyUNICEF,  @onomeako of @AmrefCanada   https://t.co/qoXjYkOiTb https://t.co/rVkcZWi5eh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LongwoodsNotes: #Justreleased! Latest issue of Healthcare Papers focuses on the institutional context for #globalhealth in the #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joe_cressy: NEW: we're announcing a partnership between the City of Toronto and Vaccine Hunters Canada.  Starting today @VaxHuntersCan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: Want a behind-the-scenes look at how N95 masks are studied? @jscott_toronto of @uoft_dlsph will tour you around his lab  te]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Indias harrowing coronavirus surge is a global problem: New variants and slow vaccine rollouts are a threat to countries everywhere"  Prof. Prabhat Jha (@countthedead) shared his thoughts with The Business Insider https://t.co/3hFgdxwaHT https://t.co/n2L7VcvWTc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT: #UofT assesses, upgrades classroom ventilation as it plans for in-person learning this fall  https://t.co/ZeI5hUZYZy https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many people in India thought the country had escaped the worst of #COVID19. What happened? Prof Prabhat Jha ( @countthedead ) shared his thoughts with the @nytimes https://t.co/szZzK5ME2V https://t.co/eazXpr0Y7R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthyDebate: We're partnering with @UofT_dlsph  @CTGHealthcare to create Pillars of the Pandemic, a series about those who have cont]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JPSoucy: Leaky lockdowns? Toronto and Peel lockdowns in November increased travel in the week following to shopping malls and restauran]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations Kaley! We will miss you. #weareDLSPH https://t.co/cISSDzjqsb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteiniBrown: I'm very pleased to share that @MerckCanada has given $3 million to @UofT_dlsph's Centre for Vaccine Preventable Diseases]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mariasundaram: Proud to be lead author on this study illustrating health equity problems with COVID-19 response *and* analysis. These p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 infection rate for Indigenous people in Toronto is 23 per cent higher than that of the citys general population, according to data compiled by a coalition of Indigenous health providers and analyzed by Prof. @JanetSmylie https://t.co/4CBra3UefI via Toronto Star https://t.co/UkXf6g9H5B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomorrow, @UofTs Centre for Vaccine-Preventable Diseases will make an announcement on new support for advancements in vaccine science and health innovation. Register to watch: https://t.co/OZDaJTcM3L #UofT https://t.co/D3UIG34UEH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: As  deals with a #COVID19 disaster,  needs to be a good ally  My @Forbes piece with input from @SarooSharda_MD @ananya_tb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovCanHealth: (1/6) Update from Health Canada: new safety information about the #Janssen #vaccine before it is distributed in Canada.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uoftalumni: Did you know that we have special GIPHY stickers to help show your #UofTAlumni pride?   Bring the spirit of #UofTReunion to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UofT: Virtual 'spotting' could help keep drug users safe during #COVID19, according to researchers from @UofT_dlsph  @CAPUDofficial #U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CP24: #BREAKING: U.S. to export 60 million doses of AstraZeneca coronavirus vaccine abroad in coming month: AP sources https://t.co/BOl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Novel tactics are needed as statistics point to an uptick in fatal opioid overdoses in Canada, further worsened by the pandemic.  [FULL STORY: https://t.co/ZvhDJwXSNP]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the spottee overdoses, the spotter will call a neighbour, friend or an ambulance to come and help, says Natalie Kaminski, a research assistant on the project.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Before someone consumes a drug, they call their spotter who will be there with them as they use, says project lead and Prof. Carol Strike. The spotter stays on the line with the spottee for another five to 15 minutes to ensure they are safe or call for help if needed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With spotting, the spottee consumes their drugs in a safe location like their home and a friend, family member or an acquaintance known as a spottermonitors through a digital method.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DLSPH researchers and @CAPUDofficial are studying a remote supervised-consumption model known as spotting to understand its benefits among people who use drugs.  STORY - https://t.co/ZvhDJwXSNP https://t.co/5uVJUrF4Ks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @UofT_ijb just released another story as part of the Generation Distress series.   This story is part of a cross-border investigation into youth mental health with the Toronto Star and IJB.   Read the story and the thread. https://t.co/iMhzNPGm4W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[. @ihpmeuoft Prof. @sriharanabi who studies burnout in the medical field, says Canadas health care workforce is facing a burnout crisis. This, on top of an already strained system pre-pandemic, is resulting in staffing shortages in every profession https://t.co/UsoOvPRc3M https://t.co/bQUGdyIVph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more events, check out our latest event digest  https://t.co/adXEa0DBVs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Then, on April 29, @UofT_dlsph's Institute for Pandemics and @UNICEFCanada co-host the event "Ensuring Global Access to COVID-19 Vaccines" with speakers @upshur_ross, @DMorleyUNICEF,  Dr. Sonali Kochhar of @uwdgh   https://t.co/qoXjYkwHuB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FIRST, on April 26, Prof. @DrJeffKwong, @IDEpiPhD of @MCGillGHP, and Melissa Andrew of @DalMedSchool discuss #COVID19 Vaccine Effectiveness   https://t.co/UXlkTDaXTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coming up next week!  Join the Centre for Vaccine Preventable Diseases @UofT_dlsph @UofT for two webinars during @WHO World Immunization Week 2021 #VaccinesWork]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnTory: Protect yourself. Protect others. Get vaccinated.  Make an appointment as soon as you're eligible: https://t.co/e5JSvWjSxD ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @countthedead: Ebola killed 10K total. No of children dying from malaria per week=10K. A malaria vaccine, if effective, would be a huge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @utjcb: During outbreaks, paid sick leave enables workers to quarantine and isolate without being unduly penalized financially. It's cru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EpiHarris: New #RxEpi study in Drugs  Aging led by Mike Campitelli and @cj20_maxwell shows opposing time trends in the use of warfarin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Experts explain why Canada's third wave is less deadly so far  and why we still need to be concerned. - Prof. Peter Juni shared his thoughts. https://t.co/t79HW3sEPD https://t.co/Ajd4QgZIfW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You're invited to our upcoming webinars!    #COVID19 Vaccine Effectiveness (April 26)  Ensuring Global Access to COVID-19 Vaccines (April 29)  ON NEIHR  IMN: Day 1- Navigating this Time Holistic Wellness for Indigenous Scholars, Part One (April 30)  https://t.co/adXEa0Vdk2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: CDC advisory panel recommends that the use of the JJ COVID-19 vaccine should resume without restrictions https://t.co/HF17MfI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAgenda: "Nobody wants to talk about this publicly because it requires admitting that your ship is going down."  @PandemicEthics (@u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof. @maxwellsmith led a @WHO policy brief titled "COVID-19 and mandatory vaccination: Ethical considerations and caveats" with contributors from Prof. @upshur_ross and Beatriz Thom. https://t.co/lCidQZpxyV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @globalnewsto: Ontario says pregnant women have been moved to the 'highest risk' category of the province's COVID-19 vaccine priority li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome Breanna! https://t.co/5zRbXnw2LG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfessorFeng: The Ontario Health Teams Impact Fellows Program is LIVE!  Check out this video https://t.co/a5Lz2mNtq9 @ihpmeuoft @UofT_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fellow @mariasundaram said if there is any slow uptake among racialized, front-line workers, its because provinces havent done enough in terms of being given paid time-off to get vaccinated, or other workplace protections. https://t.co/angaIWTsAc via CTV News https://t.co/rMrEIyH0au]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeoHlthNetwork: Important new paper from this excellent team! "Neighbourhood characteristics associated with the geographic variation i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The once obscure approach to smell loss has captured the publics attention. Evidence that it works, however, is thin," writes Maeve Gamble, a @dlsphjournalism fellow. https://t.co/xzth9OP59l https://t.co/oe9rxA06uX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We can't blame it on people's individual behaviour or their depth of understanding of the crisis," Prof. @KateMMulligan said. "So we do need better communications. We need the kind of communications that makes us feel that we matter." https://t.co/MM4DDo2Ces via CTV News https://t.co/C8ejnLU2Oi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DjKinitz: Curious about the harms of #conversiontherapy in Canada? Check out our article! Really proud of our team  @NoConversionCA! h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof. @DFisman says #COVID is transmitted through aerosols which makes ventilation and masks the most important factor in avoiding infection -- not cleaning surfaces. https://t.co/jeOI3hZKyV via Metro Morning https://t.co/GT6uOVyjV5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prof. Arjumand Siddiqi speaks on the @COVIDSciOntario table's "The Way Forward" statement on @am640 https://t.co/wbkvVxQL3t https://t.co/tE09WcD7pb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's still time to nominate an exceptional healthcare professional. Submit your nomination by May 3, 2021. https://t.co/JjyekKW8Ua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ihpmeuoft: IHPME alumni @notjustaRN @SeyMD  @DrShawnMondoux say the training they received @IHPMEqips equipped them to lead #QI initia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JaredSHopkins: Breaking: Pfizer identifies first confirmed fake versions of its Covid-19 vaccine, in Mexico and Poland, as high demand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McGillGHP: .@IDEpiPhD will be among the panelists for a special #worldimmunizationweek webinar this coming Monday, April 26, 2021, 12 P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TorontoStar: We cannot police our way out of this pandemic, but we can reallocate resources to forge our way toward a healthier, safer,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A recent study found that microdosing psychedelic drugs had beneficial psychological effects  but so did a placebo. That might seem like a dose of cold water for this promising area of mental health treatment, but Prof. @DrMorisano sees it differently. https://t.co/POCtggblY6 https://t.co/ng4krdYBZx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U of T researchers established @CANUEConsortium comprised of more than 80 environ-health experts who will work together on an urban health research program that will improve understanding of how cities can evolve to optimize health.(Sept 2016) https://t.co/YALjXokd06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do we need sustainable health care?  Launch of Centre for Sustainable Health Systems at U of T aims to tackle climate change through the organization and delivery of care (Nov 2019) https://t.co/1MY53zMGeS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new study led by DLSPH alumnae found that the United States is experiencing a rise in vibriosis, an infectious disease caused by cholera-like bacteria, and rising sea temperatures from climate change are likely to blame. (Oct 2019) https://t.co/NCx89HxHPj]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>