<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[It would be crazy to build a portfolio that didn't consider inflation a major risk, says our columnist  https://t.co/U4zU6iCgfx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebooks oversight board will announce its decision on Donald Trumps Facebook ban today. Heres how it will work. https://t.co/M6s2CZKWvE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres what were watching before Wednesdays trading action kicks off https://t.co/vdPhRMseqP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bitcoin-focused firm Galaxy Digital has agreed to buy BitGo for $1.2 billion in cash and stock, the first $1 billion deal in the cryptocurrency industry https://t.co/ofLSn9W0M5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At The Wall Street Journal's CEO Council Summit, Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen walked back comments she made earlier suggesting that interest rates might rise #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/Zq1zFQzTSz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The route to a listing on Shanghais once-hot STAR Market has become harder, prompting some startups to favor offshore IPOs over Chinas answer to Nasdaq https://t.co/datiPgd0FO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. stock futures edged higher, pointing to a rebound in the major indexes after concerns about inflation and a rise in interest rates eased https://t.co/LEn4JJxUDj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Zealands government blocked a motion to label Chinas treatment of Uyghurs as genocide https://t.co/0DaRttQ8fM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Service sector activity continued to revive during April, even in parts of the world where extensive restrictions remain in place to contain Covid-19 https://t.co/kmAofjDMnb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A spring surge in Covid-19 cases is beginning to recede in Europe as the continents vaccine rollout is finally gathering pace, boosting hopes of a broad reopening of the regions economy before the summer https://t.co/R4R4gUtasA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pandemic and its economic shocks are aggravating a problem European officials have grappled with for years: how to turn the EUs size, wealth and brain power into world-class companies by commercializing its breakthroughs https://t.co/1kCwbHcTKv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/5xQPDPcm8q https://t.co/SW9LP7NtnY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some landlords and startups are looking to profit from the rising popularity of remote work by bringing small co-working spaces to suburbs and apartment buildings https://t.co/ujirCCAfqz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeep maker Stellantis slashed planned production by 11% in the first three months of the year due to the global chip shortage and warned of additional cuts in the weeks ahead https://t.co/CAxxQyRKIa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The EU is looking to pursue big Chinese companies in much the same way its regulators have targeted U.S. multinationals such as Apple and Amazon https://t.co/JBCmego8xc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Should young home buyers take advantage of low rates or wait until housing prices cool down? Two sides debate it https://t.co/UU11L5j95G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patagonias cult-favorite Baggies shorts have been a brand mainstay since 1982and the popular, often sold-out style is becoming increasingly hard to find. Too impatient to wait for the restock? Here are 3 equally appealing options. https://t.co/tKFHBE9STF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hawaiis hospitality industry is slowly returning to life, belatedly joining the mainlands rebound as domestic travelers make their way to the islands https://t.co/GcpKyg0YsS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Israels Benjamin Netanyahu missed a deadline to form a new government, a development that would lead to the end of his 15-year rule if his opponents can patch together their own alternative coalition https://t.co/l5tHtnxZUP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former New York state Assembly Speaker Sheldon Silver was furloughed from federal prison after serving less than a year of a 6-year sentence behind bars https://t.co/6gErvnBq93]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The rise of electronic trading has made floor traders nearly irrelevant in most financial markets, and exchanges have been shutting down trading pits in Chicago and elsewhere during the past two decades https://t.co/39ZiL2SYKQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/5xQPDPcm8q https://t.co/ehcGy1m0Ww]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From @WSJopinion: Chalk one up for Sen. Scott, the first American politician in memory to pull off a response to a presidential address to Congress that upstaged the president himself, writes @wjmcgurn https://t.co/cSWiVxixgU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. births fell 4% in 2020 as the pandemic and lower birth rates among millennials usher in an era of lower fertility https://t.co/1JnJmhMmJo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actress and singer Jane Birkin recalls growing up in London, why boarding school wasnt for her and how she became the inspiration for an iconic Herms handbag https://t.co/ENmgQ4ST37]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Nasdaq temporarily suspended broadcasting prices for Class A shares of Berkshire over several popular data feeds. The price was too much for its computers to handle. https://t.co/0SjiCkVXvn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shes a professional snowboarder making $30,000 a year. Hes a photographer and graphic designer earning about $50,000. They want to save for a house while still paying off their debts. Here's one financial adviser's suggestions on how they can swing it. https://t.co/vKN7K2Jojo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roughly six months after buying a Miami Beach property for $42 million, Shutterstock founder Jonathan Oringer is listing his modern Hamptons home for $52 million https://t.co/enobhheFxb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Slice, a pizza-delivery platform that partners with 16,000 independent pizzerias nationwide, has generated more than $1 billion in sales since it launched in 2010. Heres how its founder built the business. https://t.co/WGI9MHb7k8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Manhattan federal prosecutors have asked a judge to appoint an outside authority to oversee a review of materials seized by FBI agents from Rudy Giuliani in their investigation into his work in Ukraine https://t.co/4crLOxaLGy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trucking company Yellow got a $700 million coronavirus loan last year by being labeled as critical to national security. A congressional panel says maybe it wasnt. https://t.co/ZqHVMI8MWc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People who endure adversity or trauma often feel more confident, resilient and brave afterward. Endurance athletes, who often experience a type of post-traumatic growth, offer their hard-earned advice. https://t.co/pshrJVELNV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From @WSJopinion: Software company Basecamp wants an apolitical workplace. Cue the outrage. https://t.co/FjUuP4LfSN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pandemic and its economic shocks are aggravating a problem European officials have grappled with for years: how to turn the EUs size, wealth and brain power into world-class companies by commercializing its breakthroughs https://t.co/a7sMLTgwOy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At a new Taco Bell outlet in Times Square, customers can order and pick up food without ever interacting with a human https://t.co/E4TZp26XWa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bank of America says it's exploring more ways to innovate and keep up with demand for its technology after the pandemic brought an uptick in customers using its AI-based virtual assistant, Erica, online money-transfer service Zelle and mobile check deposit https://t.co/Xp0THFCVES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why so many in the millennial generation are falling prey to impostor syndrome https://t.co/SJ9CDpOkkG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Gateses have run the foundation as co-chairs since its inception in 2000, equal partners with side-by-side offices on the sixth floor of its headquarters. https://t.co/dFGzUh4Xww]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Users who run afoul of Facebook's hidden guidelines for what people are allowed to say on the platform can end up in Facebook Jail with little chance of appeal https://t.co/zhYZJT2Igg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The price of Berkshire Hathaway's Class A stock has grown so high, it has nearly hit the maximum number that can be distributed on Nasdaq's data feeds https://t.co/N9sHLJzbWo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Listen: In today's episode of The Journal podcast, @newley traces the ongoing conflict between the Indian government and global tech giants over freedom of speech in the worlds largest democracy https://t.co/FO52Qc33Xd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is live music again on the streets of New Orleans, and vaccinated tourists are a hopeful sign for places that rely on visitors and have suffered in the pandemic  https://t.co/Vpu2LemxnC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unraveling of finance firm Greensill could take a heavy toll on steel towns like Georgetown, S.C. without intervention from a metals magnate some blue-collar workers see as a savior https://t.co/aNwglKiwB6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coffee prices are rising and experts are predicting the trend will continue, due to pandemic supply chain woes and climate change #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/M2126YT1gh https://t.co/9t460j3Yvq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From @WSJopinion: On one level the woke CEO debate concerns the balance between voter access and election securitybut on another it concerns deep questions about enforced conformity, American culture and the future of capitalism. https://t.co/Ej1xJpo0PH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking: The lawyer for former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin filed a motion seeking a new trial, alleging prosecutorial and jury misconduct, and saying a change of venue should have been granted https://t.co/LguLAkAO4c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Frances National Assembly approved a bill backed by President Emmanuel Macron to cut greenhouse gas emissions, over objections from environmental groups who said it would leave the country short of meeting Paris climate accord targets  https://t.co/XTdLnfjmHP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fundamental challenge is the complete and total dominance of China in this industry. Watch as we follow the new players in the supply chain for rare earths, which are critical to the tech we use everyday. https://t.co/HPED4PPNzc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy said he had concerns about Rep. Liz Cheneys ability to serve as one of the partys top leaders, signaling ebbing support for the prominent critic of former President Donald Trump to remain in her post https://t.co/WQY9prcNhI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An elevated section of Mexico Citys subway system collapsed on Monday, plunging several cars onto the road below and killing at least 23 people https://t.co/MZNGW12ch7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In his first congressional appearance since his confirmation, Attorney General Merrick Garland requested more money to fight domestic terrorism, bolster enforcement of civil-rights law, combat gun violence and promote other Biden administration priorities https://t.co/VE5Pf7T9Bz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyft reported 13.5 million active riders in the first quarter as demand improves from the pandemic-induced slump https://t.co/n0s2UaEErj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While shares of lenders have soared this year, investors now have a reason to be cautious on the longer-term outlook. @telisdemos explains. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/ADNrK4279q https://t.co/46FuhxR3iH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook has been quietly working to prepare advertisers for the long-anticipated ruling by its oversight board on whether the company should reinstate former President Donald Trumps Facebook and Instagram accounts https://t.co/IWMye7ki81]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Biden said Tuesday he expects to meet with Russian President Vladimir Putin during his trip to Europe in June https://t.co/Tpr7EgGs0W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen speaks with WSJs @GeraldFSeib about rebooting Americas economy #WSJCEOCouncil https://t.co/kvF4AH0pVC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York City schools officially killed snow days for at least the coming academic year, saying that in case of severe weather next year, schooling would go remote https://t.co/qy4PmFtseK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From @WSJopinion: President Biden estimates more funding for IRS audits will generate hundreds of billions in revenue. But a lot less money is likely to be found than he and progressives think. https://t.co/sb4HI46I5u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 42 million people with federal student loans have seen their payments paused during the Covid-19 pandemic. @amberbburton reports on what some borrowers did. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/in9RNWMmk4 https://t.co/zJeCAjTV6Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you invest in women you get a real return. Soccer star Abby Wambach shares her predictions for U.S. womens soccer https://t.co/xMdcxlx9wk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some of Americas top executives, including the CEOs of JPMorgan Chase and Zoom Video Communications, say they are souring on some aspects of remote work and that there are clear signs of burnout in an era of nonstop video calls https://t.co/cC0kAFguaG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theranos founder Elizabeth Holmes made her first court appearance in over a year, after her approaching criminal-fraud trial was delayed by the pandemic as well as her pregnancy https://t.co/nb8CSHCy15]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WSJWhatsNow: Pfizer has boosted full-year guidance on sales of its Covid-19 vaccine, and analysts said Pfizers Covid-19 quarterly vaccine sales exceeded expectations https://t.co/0fLD0HJ57w https://t.co/3WFldVMzW9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A man shot by at least one FBI agent after an hourslong standoff outside the Central Intelligence Agencys headquarters has died, the FBI said Tuesday, a day after the incident https://t.co/1STMjU2LRN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Live chat apps like Discord and Telegram are drawing young investors looking for faster-paced, real-time conversations with other investors as they follow market trends or seek investment advice https://t.co/xp3qh6GoPU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Biden aims to get 70% of adults at least one vaccine dose by July 4 as the administration said it will reallocate some doses to states with higher demand https://t.co/RJVp6BgEuK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Slice, a pizza-delivery platform that partners with 16,000 independent pizzerias nationwide, has generated more than $1 billion in sales since it launched in 2010. Heres how its founder built the business. https://t.co/lm92SOdcrN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shareholders at General Electric and ATT rejected the companies executive compensation plans in nonbinding votes, the latest blue-chip companies to be rebuked by investors over how they paid leaders during the pandemic https://t.co/BFYIkMNx0r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An elevated section of Mexico Citys subway system collapsed on Monday night as a train made its way across, plunging several cars onto the road below and killing at least 23 people. Here's what we know. https://t.co/OD5oxJ2iCB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden administration officials  told states that the U.S. will reallocate Covid-19 vaccine doses that go unordered to states that are in need of additional shots, a person familiar with the matter said https://t.co/ci5BWmZJGR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A spring surge in Covid-19 cases is beginning to recede in Europe as the continents vaccine rollout is finally gathering pace, boosting hopes of a broad reopening of the regions economy before the summer https://t.co/mwcrHJ9R6h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From @WSJopinion: Leaders greatest failure was not focusing on the elderly, who had lower costs and far greater benefits, write Charles L. Hooper and David R. Henderson  https://t.co/mnqvrfSsAR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dozens of major companies, including Microsoft, American Airlines and Unilever, made a joint statement against any changes that would restrict eligible voters access to the ballot in Texas days ahead of a vote in the state legislature on a voting bill https://t.co/rCUJe1KO7q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Businesses will pay more to borrow if they miss green and social targets. The penalties are small and the targets easy to hit, so whats the point? https://t.co/PCOHiRVfsp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The essential tool for enjoying a glass of wine is a good corkscrew, according to wine columnist @LettieTeague1, who shares her favorites https://t.co/s7AKxsexyt https://t.co/UaWlRsMlS8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An 80,000-acre Montana ranch believed to be one of the largest private undeveloped properties in the Rocky Mountain West is hitting the market for $136.25 million, making it one of the most expensive properties ever listed for sale in the state https://t.co/6U3uwb6R7l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unraveling of finance firm Greensill could take a heavy toll on steel towns like Georgetown, S.C. without intervention from a metals magnate some blue-collar workers see as a savior https://t.co/VW7izqgOu4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook users who run afoul of its secret guidelines around what people are allowed to say on the platform can end up in Facebook Jail with little chance of appeal. What Im learning about Facebook is not to talk on Facebook. https://t.co/aZpwSc282t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon believes a boom is coming in the American economy, with growth that could stretch into 2023, but he warned that the government could waste it away if ambitious spending plans arent held accountable https://t.co/7kgc5x6DPo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The surge of coronavirus infections in developing countries such as India amid a relative scarcity of vaccine supply means that the pandemic will keep spreading until mid-2022, according to the inventors of the BioNTech vaccine https://t.co/xmtzW1Ott3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu  appeared set to fail to form a new government, unable to overcome objections from his right-wing and religious partners to forming a government that would require the support of an Islamist party https://t.co/QHd9NrwPdj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dogecoin has surged more than 10,000% in 2021. So, what is the cryptocurrency that started out as a parody less than a decade ago, how did we get here and why are people so excited about it? https://t.co/XQgcRwcqmX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mall owners have hit on a new way to fill gaping holes left by failed department stores and other departing big-box tenants: hosting public schools in need of more space https://t.co/NMKzXChjp9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From @WSJopinion: A dramatic expansion of child care is a bad deal for American parents. More important, its a bad deal for American children, write @JDVance1 and Jenet Erickson. https://t.co/VzUeHReHfw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pandemic and its economic shocks are aggravating a problem European officials have grappled with for years: how to turn the EUs size, wealth and brain power into world-class companies by commercializing its breakthroughs https://t.co/akjVdFQxgu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who pays when corporate taxes go up, workers or shareholders? Four years after the 2017 tax law, Democrats and Republicans are debating anew who shoulders most of the burden https://t.co/68nk3pbexo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lumber prices are breaking new records, leading to huge profits for sawmill owners and rising costs for home buyers and renters. @davidhodari takes a closer look. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/EElaHjQD3a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billionaire Alec Gores has become a serial SPAC backer as the market has heated up for special-purpose acquisition companies. He has methodically created 13 SPACsmore than any other investor. https://t.co/5Gt3nSlnuM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase CEOJamie Dimon speaks with WSJ Editor in Chief Matt Murray about Americas rebound from the pandemic #WSJCEOCouncil https://t.co/49NUXwM0fm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CVSs profit rose for the latest quarter, partly driven by gains from the rollout of Covid-19 vaccines https://t.co/PCcqrsmpEf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A rescue operation was under way after an overpass in Mexico Citys metro system collapsed, sending a train plunging, trapping cars under rubble and killing more than 20 people #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/zaZpoOpS2X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. stocks such as Tesla, Apple and GameStop are attracting German investors, as negative bank rates prompt risk-averse savers to shift their money https://t.co/aRM9JQkgZH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres what were watching ahead of Tuesdays opening bell https://t.co/dykGjwnhWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apollos private-equity portfolio appreciated by 22% during the first quarter, beating out rivals and easily topping the SP 500 https://t.co/P20lxiQZjz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heard on the Street: Lenders awash in cheap funding face no credit issues for now, but that might not last https://t.co/2rOIvP300Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates and his wife, Melinda Gates, co-chair of their philanthropic organization, say they will continue their work at the Bill  Melinda Gates Foundation after they divorce #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/P9HF9YTXKt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Governors across the U.S. are rolling back restrictions, as more than 40% of all U.S. adults are fully vaccinated and daily Covid-19 case numbers decline https://t.co/jY5RjxcqyV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The SP 500 is on course for modest losses ahead of a string of earnings and data that will likely show the trade deficit widened to a fresh record in March https://t.co/YjZxRB3LtS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many adolescent girls arent getting enough nutrition from their diets, worrying doctors who say deficiencies could lead to future health problems https://t.co/XLBGddhsiC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heard on the Street: TSMC has attracted increased attention as the U.S.-China rivalry has intensified. But theres another Taiwanese chipmaker worth looking at: MediaTek. https://t.co/9QIV7RhTFo]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>