<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[And if this was a double header, it would be over in the 7th inningnn https://t.co/sWiDVFeRkH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz @judebirch That will literally ruin this civilized society....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ryanobles OMG...Its like in Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory... https://t.co/3uSq1AYdz3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kilmeade @POTUS Is it really worth inciting the hate and division like this????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnaCabrera And Matt Gaetz stays???? Something is very very very wrong....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BretBaier Compare those three days to three las days of January in Trump presidency.... Jan 5, 6 and 7, 2021....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxReports @RepLizCheney @JeremyAdler They are leaving Matt Gaetz alone but have this problem with Liz Chaney....  Something is very very wrong ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@B1ackSchefter Good lord....what is happening to this country....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillKristol What I want is the percentage of people sho voted against this candidate within the general population of that district. If that number is high, lets face it, were f-cked.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes.  Think about this.. https://t.co/aSCBOB1X12]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We should let #AntiVaccine people fall behind. They made their choice.  Good thing is, once we vaccinate all the rest of the population we will be out of the #pandemic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EVargasTV @BillKristol @Liz_Cheney This will be an epic right vs wrong battle!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We really need to approve energy use of #COVID19 #vaccine for 12-15 age groups as soon as I possible by @US_FDA !!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BretBaier I hope you come to your senses and be on the right side of the history.   Seriously....  either that or you do believe in white race holding on to the power....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its time to fix things before too late... https://t.co/yzcFn2ppHv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d Or crazy F-k nut!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realSLAGLE1 @LocutusOfBill @BretBaier @FoxNews Aye aye!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LocutusOfBill @BretBaier Thanks for calling it out in civilized and  logical manner!   @BretBaier will stay quiet along the @FoxNews trumpian lies and will go his way out to call out shit like Biden picking dandelions...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DWPippy Foreign influence...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EVargasTV Agreed!  Even with masks on!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Thats good. But not sure it will happen....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KimJonesSports Borrowing Connie Corleones line:  Is he as good as he looks, @nyjets fans??????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman Gaetz is just great evil.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeskyReport Yes.  I see him being really good at some point!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeskyReport It wont be too bad for him to spend sometime in AAA and get things regroup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bblock29 Two things:1 theres disgusting, hideously  deeply seeded prejudice against women in the society where criticisms against women are so much harsher and disgusting to endure. 2.Gaetz is just a great evil. Hill is a normal person. 1st has a solution 2nd dont....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Well good for them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BretBaier @inbetweenzine In between Donalds cheeks....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnKingCNN @Jerry_Remy Something special is happening with this years young @RedSox team!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxNews Conversion of oil source to other carbon neutral energy forms require active RD participants from current oil industry.   I dont know WTF Kerry invested in but mere investment to oil industry is not a bad thing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnaCabrera We should be entering the early phase of hurd immunity]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Borrowing Connie Corleones line:  Is he as good as he looks, @nyjets fans?????? https://t.co/0ubBMeZgIR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you dont get thus analogy, youre not American  https://t.co/5vQ7YV9inR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its unbelievable....when @RedSox loses, most of AL East teams lose as well.  Telling you, something special is happening!   And everyone knows and loves you, @Jerry_Remy !!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Patriots One thing for sure, Mac Jones will be much better than Zach Wilson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KimJonesSports @Patriots Slow down Kim Jones, Macs no Tom...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnKingCNN they were talking about you!   @JohnBerman Go @RedSox !!!! https://t.co/XDg2FUoGoh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kellyinvegas Is this for real or your speculation???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrunoAmato_1 Hes simply appealing to his supporters.  Growing gap of education and intellectual level will the biggest divisive reason in this country....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EVargasTV Thats not how it should be described.  Its racist elements in this country or any other country that are needed to be eradicated.  Of course this country is not a racist country. But lets acknowledge there are racist elements in every parts of this country.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanaPerino * eradication]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JacquiHeinrich @BretBaier Basic decency doesnt exist no more...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TaraSetmayer @FLOTUS How come no one says it?!?!  She and the VP are HAF!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanaPerino Your Secretary of Transportation says it all the time.  WTF?  You are mow blatantly bullshitting too???   Seriously, WTF!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ResisterDude Please dont post these types of photos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanaPerino Do you not get it or is it too difficult for you to understand???Vaccine will protect you from severely ill but does not guarantee virus from replicating in your body, which then can be transmitted to others.  Irradiation only happens when virus stops jumping from host to host!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jtomase Telling you.... something amazing is happening this year!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RedSox Something amazing is happening!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last 2 wins @RedSox earned are results of some amazing #BaseBall playing...   something special is happening with our Boston Red Sox!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillKristol For those who value individual freedom, they sure cant honor that on others.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gmatsumura2 What Carson and them want, how can that be implemented??? How?  Remove over 50% of US population??   So for example,what happens to those married to non-whites?  They can stay?  How about their kids?   Whos even white and whos not?  Its a pure crazy evil belief.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KimJonesSports @AndrewSiciliano @NFLMedia @nflnetwork Love kim jones!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I saw few people wearing #mask pulling them down then sneezed and put them back up.  Whats up with that logic???  What am I missing here????  Its like wearing a condom through out then removing it just before....well never mind ....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics No body cares!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuzzJamie @jaketapper @Bakari_Sellers It wont end well.  Because racism is wrong.  Its evil. Its not a right thing.  Therefore good will always triumph over evil.  It just is...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum Probably watched by same f-king idiots shouting 1776.....  atrocious idiocy...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ohdaveMS @jaketapper @Bakari_Sellers She should just let it all hang]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill That much hate, huh?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@spokeumbra @FoxNews @BretBaier I was being sarcastic, referencing Trump believing Putin more than his own intelligence...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @Bakari_Sellers Lets face it. The cats out of the bag. Fox talk show hosts are racists and they (for some reason) feel comfortable now openly admitting it. Big mistake. Trump litmus test exposed closet racists.  Social backlash will be profound and this wont end well for them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @BretBaier Hes strongly denying it.  Why? Dont you believe him?  Hes strongly denying it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What @FoxNews is doing to this country and the rest of the free world is extremely harmful for long time to come.... https://t.co/lzyN3sXEPo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnaCabrera @KamalaHarris @DanaBashCNN Thats exactly what Trump supporters said about him.  I dont like to hear that kind of talk from either side.  Let the results speak for themselves!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good split, @RedSox !!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FeelGoodPage11 Avian UBER!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good lord....@RedSox sucking started again...i am getting miserable....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter @mortreport Oh the jockstrap comment.  What an incapable loser]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeskyReport One of the reasons why Cora is good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Most number of militias?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jtomase Who knew...getting fired unexpectedly, literally few say before the start of a new season turned out to be the best thing happened in his career!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mdnij34 Exactly!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien I wholeheartedly agree with you!!!  Can you imagine of some one like Scott Atlas was advising Trump from the beginning???  She did what she had to do.  Theres no nefarious intention in her part whatsoever!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics I know this sounds awful but sadly agreed by both party bases...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics He will never make out of racist Republican base primary...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Oooooo_Donna @Cdsfrog @AnaCabrera True true !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @BretBaier No no no no NO!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Oooooo_Donna @Cdsfrog @AnaCabrera True, although probability of worldwide COVID-19 irradiation by end of the year is very very unlikely.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ESPNStatsInfo All games should be 7 innings.  So much to gain and nothing to lose.  I bet #MLB will get this done in couple of years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timothy30434590 @FXGuy9 @CNNPolitics *guilty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alefeusch @AnaCabrera If you feel that way, rightfully so you should be able to choose.   I am tremendously thankful we have choices!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cdsfrog @AnaCabrera Thats a fantastic news!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timothy30434590 @FXGuy9 @CNNPolitics Both sides are guilt.  Were not electing prom kings and queens.  Suggestions of Oprah, Ivanka, and even Michelle Obama are not what we need.  We need people who deeply understand how governments work, how to write bills that works properly and capable of getting things done.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnaCabrera So @AnaCabrera obvious question is someone who received different vaccines can receive this booster shot and achieve sufficient protection?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FXGuy9 @CNNPolitics I fully agree.  My point applies to both sides!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics What public service track record does he have??? Any legislative experiences?  We cant send these unqualified people to congress....  nothing against him, but for these positions, we need people with experience and expertise.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickconfessore @jaketapper This wil certainly create more variants....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bradfo @jtkantor I am so sorry for your fathers loss.  But, what a tremendous blessing to have a 80year old friendship!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jtomase Hes never gonna spend that kind of money ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeskyReport: Lineup for tonight Give it a like and make sure to RT https://t.co/qXGjIwJZ6s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jtomase Young teams. Dont count them out.  Especially AL west, grueling travel schedule during the summer always favor young teams.  Now that Texas has indoor park, they will play much better later part of the season.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingJames #Accountability is correct....accountability of parenting, responsible actions, following law, no finger pointing and not stabbing people with knives as well.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And he creates positive environment that doesnt pressure young players and let them swing and pitch to their potential!!   Something special is happening with our @RedSox https://t.co/dq0W2sseuI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny how things have changed... https://t.co/3QtPEaBVZo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Is he related to Tucker????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All but one team failed to gain a game on @RedSox after a loss tonight.  Something special is happening to the Red Sox this season!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson o -&gt; *platform]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Keep serving cheap shit to your poor ass constituents...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Seriously, I dont think hes all there.  Ive seen this type of mental digressions.  Key is we should not allow this type of person to have o like this.  Similar to preventing mentally ill person from buying guns, as his friends would say.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IResister @Carter13Sf Lock them up! Lock them up! Lock them up! Lock them up!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeskyReport Boone is so fired...]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>