<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Duchessjean1 I agree that something needs to be done as it is  all so embarassing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HOW TO STOP COMPARING YOURSELF ON INSTAGRAM - YouTube https://t.co/nfZs2R1e4A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Astrid_Tontson: A still of a still morning https://t.co/AOJgksDLMh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ninjavspirate01: I need help finding the guy who saved my life in Hyde Park today! I was having an asthma attack and he stopped, asked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Angela_Griffin: Mare of Eastwood on @skyatlantic. Brilliant in every way. #katewinslet is divine. Beautiful work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meddiebaddie: #Nowplaying On My Way - dRem TGI /@dremtgi [https://t.co/MZ32w6GaMa] listen now at {https://t.co/5B9EJ3yqSV} #dremstuff #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JonJonesSnr: Perhaps Boris Johnson should display his sponsors on his suits like sports people do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Evening Standard Comment: Khan is failing to protect Londoners https://t.co/xr0dpGcFiT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EveningStandard: "Crime has consistently been cited by Londoners as the most important issue in this election, and it is the Mayors Ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I keep every single one of mines. https://t.co/GcvsNuZNIH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaegawise: It's a hard life sometimes...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A bit mean, dont you think! https://t.co/cXTxLml87h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IS LOVE ALONE ENOUGH TO STAY?? https://t.co/mTcENfIZFZ via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Piers Morgan's launches attack on Meghan Markle for 'exploiting' her royal title https://t.co/r0aRZApRSn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zellweger, DiCaprio, Beyonce among stars given VIP status under new UK points-based immigration system https://t.co/lZ86yU2Sns https://t.co/NnWz5RBzbD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are no words. R.I.P.  British woman Mayra Zulfiqar killed in Pakistan 'after refusing to marry a man' https://t.co/8O5SAk6IYQ https://t.co/W0Cvla3fDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VitIllankovan: Im so terrible at taking compliments! As Ive not been exposed to them growing up, if I receive them now Im incredibly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daughter of murdered PCSO asks well-wishers to light candle for her https://t.co/MIdLouRAjo via @MailOnline]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBCFoodProg: .@jaegawise wants you to raise a glass to your favourite drinks producers (or yourself) by nominating for this years  #bb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PopCrave: Jesy Nelson reveals that being on set of the music video for Sweet Melody after lockdown was her breaking point:   I immed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ohhh Dear! Let me reach for my inhaler  https://t.co/oF5nzdPG5U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@able1954 Bit chilly this end!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @able1954: Took My dogs for a walk. Nice outside!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Used_ToDrum: A 19 year old musician says something whilst wearing underwear and that is a "headline" in the "World News" section of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attempted abduction of boy, 11, on walk home from school in southeast London - Evening Standard https://t.co/rROSgsmhzc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaviesWriter: Sending love and support to all of you fantastic writing and reading friends!  #bookworms #reading https://t.co/uy72JXuG7j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@guardian This is sad and I am sure this must have happened to other people too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They're good! https://t.co/xbDMz1tkGe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michellegayle1: @TheLouisEmerick Yep. History degree ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecrowdview: MRT @Susanjmccann #motivation Stand up for your values... #IQRTG #quote https://t.co/1T7YCI863e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Used_ToDrum: You all listen to @Spotify. So how is it they lost 2.2 milion a day in 2020? I guess this is also a tax ruse as they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chloeeverton: Wifey  https://t.co/OrLOh3Xabs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMailUK: Can you beat Kate's cost-per-year? Duchess is royally frugal when it comes to fashion with outfits starting at just 7.77]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Priceless!  https://t.co/yewWmhzfj3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meddiebaddie: #Nowplaying The Life They Choose - Trevor /@TrevorGear |[https://t.co/cq3YShFXay] listen now at {https://t.co/5B9EJ3yqSV}]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CAA_Official: We have a Spotify playlist of all our singles, we hope you like it (kind of like a Greatest hits, but without the hits) h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KennethHolland: 3 Things You Want to Happen with your Email List https://t.co/jdBmRkkvHj #EmailMarketing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LadyCecilyNevil: HRH Prince William Duke of Cambridge https://t.co/PBZpgl6tgS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VinceMat01: I dont give a damn how much you love a person, Just dont let them treat you like a popeye.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CAA_Official: Please PRESAVE our new single Fifteen Minutes  https://t.co/r0JIti36gY Or FOLLOW us on:- YouTube https://t.co/pkGYF6eV3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiasazand @MartinD35757404 Hmmm..... The state of this country, with leadership like this. We are the 'laughing stock!']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How disgraceful, for anyone to behave like this. If people want money, they need to work for it and if they cannot work, then in the US, there is a support system but you do not steal other people's pets or  anything else, for that matter! https://t.co/7DpF3R6A6g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Susanjmccann: The bad news: nothing is permanent. The good news: nothing is permanent.  Lolly Daskal #quote]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickystevo I am so sorry to hear about your father.   Please accept my condolences.  Much love and support to you from your family.   You have really been through the mill.   Don't forget, just a whisker away.  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WineShowTV: Jaega @jaegawise stealing the show AGAIN. Big up @WildCardBrewery with their sensational IPA that managed to blow Dom + Jim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lol_Vertigo: @wafbinthedark @lee3erry @MPeopleHeatherS https://t.co/TkNehigv08]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lol_Vertigo: https://t.co/FCsgPbSZ9R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MPeopleMusic: Heather Small | M People | Singles @SpotifyUK Playlist: https://t.co/kDkHGNn433  Includes: United Together | Moving On Up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lornypop Oh no, that is not 'a little mucked up at all'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19: Doctors scramble for oxygen supplies as India's coronavirus crisis worsens - Sky News https://t.co/WsMmKhyi2D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WOW!  That is definitely 'not on'. https://t.co/gy8GKbuzV8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASAPMoneyGang: Lil Durk Type Beat https://t.co/iAU7TA1xXA via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meddiebaddie: #Nowplaying why dont you let me hold your hands - dRem tgi /@dremtgi [https://t.co/jCLm55UfRK] listen now at {https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who's let the #SussexSquad out the #bag  on a Bank Holiday.....Sheeze!!! #BankHolidaysnooze]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@acgrayling Really???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArchewellBaby Problematic!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier League clubs to sign up to Owners' Charter in wake of European Super League fiasco https://t.co/o5YJo4Ac4C https://t.co/eWqCO3mMx8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Murky__Meg: Global Citizen Vax Live event isnt being aired globally! Yes its on YT but thats not really the definition of global! Li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMirror: Harry 'realises he's frozen out' and 'isn't so thrilled about new life in US'  https://t.co/nzAoKvcpuq https://t.co/GAPgbm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyMirror I think that this is the reality of it so the PR wheel is churning to hype things up, in order to make  Harry more of a household name, than he already is. Remember, that it is all in the name of charity though!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLouisEmerick: Good morning all happy @Ballstocancer #makeiingmemoriesMonday Its raining so it must be a #Bankholiday never mind,d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelsGotTalent: Wow #melaniegayletalent is #trending on #IMDB #imdbpro  My Company Meter has gone up 554,865 over the last 12 months,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ MDMA cured my alcoholism: The trial offering an escape from trauma by @Telegraph https://t.co/6HmkextLM9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet And who said that they are not concerned about that. No offence but I do not think that you know how other people think or are feeling.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AngelaRayner: Remember the two child limit which pushed children into poverty, the stigmatisation of working class families and Tory MP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Errr.....#ElonMusk needed #AntoniaDale's help! The #comedyqueen and if you have never heard of her YOU WILL!!! https://t.co/iu0LMoPgRl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any rotis is nice yet a 'healthy brown rice roti' even better.... https://t.co/SgG3XpyNLa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMirror: 'Distraught' pals of Brit who vanished in Caribbean still in the dark 8 weeks on  https://t.co/U4WKCBUgMk https://t.co/dVL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMirror: New list of animals at risk of dying out forever - from orangutans to red pandas https://t.co/IPKNtWgvz2 https://t.co/MckP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeedSTUnited Good morning and you have a Happy Bank Holiday too!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeedSTUnited: Good morning and a Happy Bank Holiday Monday to you all, my lovely friends. Have fun, but please stay safe   Here we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Such a good an inspiring article".  Repair Shop star JAY BLADES: My breakdown and a bitter divorce https://t.co/tVff4nYefY via @DailyMailCeleb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Susanjmccann: Houses by Klara Rajnai  https://t.co/tnLMxoiMiU https://t.co/wi4iEnfOGb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giving up some of your own #money and raising money for #charity are entirely 'two different things'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KensingtonRoyal: Thank you to everyone for the kind messages on our wedding anniversary. We are enormously grateful for the 10 years of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @asandamagaqa: Her Majesty. The Queen Royal Highness #AfricanPrincess: #MantfombiDlamini. Daughter of King Sobhuza II of Swaziland. Pri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalFamily: The Queen has sent a message to the people of Northern Ireland on the centenary of the Government of Ireland Act coming in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalFamily: Today The Queen held Audiences via video link from Windsor Castle.   Mr. Sidya Ould Elhadj from Mauritania and Ms. Simona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lol_Vertigo: NEW REMIXES RELEASED TODAY!  Heather Small | United Together | Remixes By Mr. G  Duncan Forbes: Buy or Stream: https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KennethHolland: Stop expecting the same https://t.co/Ns4YcQ7o50 https://t.co/LPPDnGOn4E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Good morning from Cornwall  https://t.co/DYqbgxT5S9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville Good Morning James]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brainstorming03: How could non-autistic people experience how it feels to be on the #autism spectrum? https://t.co/pm46dh6mIP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SheCometh Next thing, he'll be running for 'President!'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArchewellBaby If he's so 'Global', then why doesn't he give up some of his 'Gobal Money!'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChloeBellerbyMH: You CARRY a large burden, but you are NOT the burden ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davemacladd Poor thing, always looks terrified]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @crystalbonnar: I cannot be arsed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crystalbonnar Neither can I ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[William and Charles won't 'open their arms to Harry again as he crossed line' https://t.co/tDoJuYzy8S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 TIMES??? He's been stoop up that many times?  OK! You know I've got sucked into #CatfishUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 @ta_mills Did we really have any democracy under Boris? I wonder!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaegawise: Nominations are now open for all you drinks producers for the #bbcfoodawards!  To enter either a drinks producer you love ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spot on! https://t.co/OFC4KgSXEH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DerekMiller36 Moi and the crew lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations and Well done to these siblings yet personally, I do prefer the educational route once it is applicable. https://t.co/6sUd4o7eZj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wise Words! https://t.co/uHehq9OV3c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Of all the people, she should know!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DerekMiller36 You're missing out!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Sales is one thing but misleading the #customer is another and it could lead to a day in #COURT so companies #BEWARE!!!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>