<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[People in green zones still need a permit, exemption or exception to enter Victoria. Permits can be obtained at https://t.co/v9Ej7FMa8U. Exposure sites can be updated. If you have recently travelled from NSW, continue to check https://t.co/tbusPehW6G [5/5]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Public health officials in Victoria will continue monitoring the situation and will provide updates as needed. All locations in NSW remain green zones under Victorias travel permit system until further information is available, including genomic sequencing results. [4/5]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Using travel permit data, the Department will today message people who have entered VIC from NSW since 30 April. Flight manifests have been requested from the National Incident Room. Authorised Officer presence and spot checking will be increased for flights from Sydney. [3/5]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria is declaring all exposure sites published by NSW Health as Tier 1. If you are currently in VIC and attended any of the following sites on this website (https://t.co/tbusPehW6G) you must contact us at 1300 651 160, isolate and get tested, and quarantine for 14 days. [2/5]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria has launched a number of preliminary and precautionary public health actions in relation to the COVID-19 case in Sydney announced today. [1/5] https://t.co/46sPAapufZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mccloulou Thanks for pointing this out, our phone service options have changed and the correct selection is indeed option 1  option 1  option 1. Hopefully you still managed to book in? Visit: https://t.co/BsYAA2Moq8 or give us a call 1800 675 398]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolynAOBrien Thanks for pointing this out. Our phone service options have changed: option 1  option 1  option 1.  See more: https://t.co/BsYAA2Moq8 or give us a call 1800 675 398]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kylieac1 Thanks for pointing this out, our phone service options have changed and the correct selection is indeed option 1  option 1  option 1. Hopefully you still managed to book in? For more info visit: https://t.co/0pTdfXQgbF or give us a call 1800 675 398]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EnergySafeVic: Today, we mark the beginning of Carbon Monoxide Awareness Week. From 3-9 May we will be sharing information with our aim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSW Health is advising people who have been to the following exposure sites to immediately test and isolate until more information can be provided. This advice also applies to people currently in Victoria who were at these locations during the specified times: https://t.co/FwIcqoSXJ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@NSWHealth has been notified today of a new COVID-19 case in Sydneys eastern suburbs  with urgent investigations and contact tracing underway. Victorian health officials will continue to monitor the situation and will provide updates as soon as more information is available. https://t.co/uzp5ZM2WMF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/4rS4iCZJTK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Belinda is one of ~35k registered practising midwives in Australia's public health system - supporting women through pregnancy, labour, birth  beyond with skill, care  professionalism.  Thank you to Belinda  all our midwives for the work you do  #InternationalDayOfTheMidwife https://t.co/eSbT5bQdqT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new cases reported.  - 8,406 vaccine doses were administered - 19,402 test results were received More later: https://t.co/lIUrl0ZEco  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/lDvvdOCxMc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you from a community that speaks a language other than English?    Translated videos are available in 18 languages on common COVID-19 topics. Share these videos with your loved ones:  https://t.co/9GdvQYN8OV   For more, visit: https://t.co/hOJRjlKm2r      #COVID19Vic https://t.co/F8mNeMGPEc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/7xgOSd4Br8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our thanks to all who attended a vaccination centre yesterday. The number of reported doses is a 105 per cent increase from the same day last week. Over 13,000 Victorians called our booking hotline yesterday - you can too, by calling 1800 675 398.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reported yesterday: No new local cases and 1 new case acquired overseas (currently in HQ). - 6,923 vaccine doses were administered - 14,325 test results were received More later: https://t.co/lIUrl0ZEco  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/Z7OElyNTxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Spritzbottle Hi @Spritzbottle, Thank you in advance if you experience a longer than usual wait time. For more information about your test results please visit - https://t.co/TxPgyeAdWI  Take care, DH Social Media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/dfO2WfGtou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're currently experiencing very high call volumes through our vaccine phone booking service, with over 5,000 calls received before 9:30.  Thank you for your patience on the phone. Reminder for those eligible: to book, call 1800 675 398 (option 3, option 2, option 2).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bondybloke Testing sites are located throughout Victoria. Visit:  https://t.co/WZI0U7BRyW  If you don't have a testing site near your home, you can contact your GP, local community health service or local hospital to discuss options available to you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VictorianCHO: This aint a race or anything, but cmon Victoria - lets get vaccinated. Its our path to safety. https://t.co/iVuvS3pJqz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 1 new case acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported. - 835 vaccine doses were administered - 11,660 test results were received More later: https://t.co/lIUrl0ZEco  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/9kmNvnjEy6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[KEY LINKS ABOUT EXPOSURE SITES: Victorian exposure sites page (including advice for interstate sites): https://t.co/SQ5trZH2NI WA exposure sites: https://t.co/OFwL0rtDD6 QLD exposure sites: https://t.co/1rzWuUcFti Where to get tested in Victoria: https://t.co/WZI0U7Tsqu [4/4]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Using information from orange zone permits, more than 3,800 messages were sent to people who have arrived from Perth since 27 April advising them to check exposure sites and contact the Department if they have visited any. [3/4]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria has declared ALL of these sites as Tier 1 exposure sites. If you are currently in Victoria and have been to one of these sites you must immediately contact the Victorian Department of Health at 1300 651 160 and quarantine for 14 days.  [2/4]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WA EXPOSURE SITES UPDATE:   Western Australia has listed new exposure sites linked to COVID-19 cases announced recently. The full list is available here: https://t.co/OFwL0rtDD6 [1/4]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/e7ZB5ByEMH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria, its up to all of us to keep checking in.  Its the best way to stop the spread of coronavirus, and keep protecting our businesses, communities and each other.   So lets keep it up.  Because checking in keeps us safe and open. https://t.co/T7kWVNQYv3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Orthodox Easter! Celebrate safely with those you love this year. Find out what you need to know about hosting a COVIDSafe gathering: https://t.co/lKaU4CRa7I https://t.co/o37xR4tjZM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 1 new case acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported. - 1,280 vaccine doses were administered - 12,284 test results were received More later: https://t.co/lIUrl0ZEco  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/Nw9irEjJ9s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are in Victoria and you have been to any of the listed exposure sites, immediately contact the Department of Health at 1300 651 160 for advice and action. [7/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Queensland has also published a number of new exposure sites related to a case of COVID-19 in Brisbane Airport. The full list is available here: https://t.co/1rzWuUcFti. [6/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perth and the Peel region remain orange zones under our travel permit system. Authorised Officers will continue to meet all Perth flight arrivals to ensure they understand their obligations. Arrivals to Victoria since 27 April will be messaged about new exposure sites. [5/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are in Victoria and you have been to any other exposure site in WA listed on its website, we still require you to immediately contact the Victorian Department of Health at 1300 651 160 for advice and action  as it may differ from WA advice. [4/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 30 April: Mirrabooka Mosque (Masjid Al-Taqwa) between 1:15pm  2pm  28 April: Agha Juice Caf in Joondanna between 6:50pm  8:00pm  28 April: Spudshed in Stirling between 1:30am  2:30am [3/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria is declaring the following new exposure sites in WA as Tier 1, requiring people currently in Victoria who have been at these locations at these times to immediately quarantine for 14 days and contact the Victorian Department of Health at 1300 651 160: [2/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXPOSURE SITES UPDATE   Western Australia has listed new exposure sites linked to COVID-19 cases announced today. The full list is available here: https://t.co/OFwL0rtDD6 [1/7] https://t.co/xMssGBqbPv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/H6G1BPa4oa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If youre aged 50+, you can receive the COVID-19 vaccine from 3 May at a high-volume vaccination centre.  Walk-ins are allowed, but you're encouraged to book ahead by calling 1800 675 398.   To see locations, details and opening hours, please visit https://t.co/irFcdJbPcf https://t.co/fj4bfycn1W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 3 new cases acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported. - 3,124 vaccine doses were administered - 15,248 test results were received More later: https://t.co/2vKbgKHFvv  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/K64ZGmLr1A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/gmrFJZLJLh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Falls are a major cause of injury for older people. An estimated 1/3 of people aged 65+ fall one or more times a year. Although many of these falls dont result in serious injury, they can cause minor injuries.  Make your home safer: https://t.co/1VSbmjYHvV #FallsAwareness https://t.co/gy3K095yFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elizru @ptv_official @metrotrains @yarratrams @VictorianCHO Hi there, To report a restrictions breach please contact the Police Assistance Line on 131 444 (available 24 hours a day) or online via https://t.co/nT6fLODQFK  Kind regards, DH Social Media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoryBurnside Hi there,       For details on how to contact the Department of Health for general enquires or complaints, please see https://t.co/rE8P3tyfA1       Kind regards,      DH Social media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking for more info? - Information about the COVID-19 vaccine: https://t.co/d8pAvJ7uqP - Information your nearest high-volume vaccination centre: https://t.co/irFcdJtq3N - Information about the flu vaccine: https://t.co/kpN9f7Yn7B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's #WorldImmunisationWeek  as prep for flu season begins, the @healthgovau COVID-19 vaccination program expands. Remember: COVID-19 vaccines don't protect against flu, so you should still have a flu shot - it's recommended that you have both vaccines at least 2 weeks apart. https://t.co/xEjWa3t4Wu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 2 new cases acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported. - 4,123 vaccine doses were administered - 15,656 test results were received More later: https://t.co/2vKbgKHFvv  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/xOUZlUmuJG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Viral fragments have been also detected in other sewer catchments in Melbournes north, west and east, and in Benalla.  Please get tested if you have any symptoms, no matter how mild. Stay home until you have your result. Find a testing site near you: https://t.co/6fxm69jPGP https://t.co/wYppxJMIRN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus fragments have been detected in wastewater from Melbournes western and north-western suburbs. Anyone who lives in or who visited these suburbs between April 18  26 April should be alert for symptoms of COVID-19 and get tested if any develop. #COVID19Vic https://t.co/X8oHKVpfqR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/0QCJEgVUmt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Aimees husband battled with his mental health, sherealisedshe also neededsomeoneto talk to. She found acounsellor who helped her process the experience of supporting someone with mental illness.  Hear her story: https://t.co/KIkWHGyWQi #timetotalkvic https://t.co/DuaSuaMjcu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 1 new case acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported. - 3,662 vaccine doses were administered - 16,891 test results were received More later: https://t.co/lIUrl0ZEco  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/9MvbGgsKfu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/qKObFKrQJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After the disruptions of 2020, the Smile Squad free dental program is now rolling out to more schools around Vic. New locations have been announced with more to follow soon. See https://t.co/5xva4cLnuD for more info or look out for the orange vans coming to a school near you. https://t.co/6lDtJ33rpv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@grantwyeth Hi there, Thank you for your feedback. It has been forwarded to the COVID-19 taskforce for consideration.   For the latest information and updates please continue visit https://t.co/MDEnCPweVk  Kind regards, DH Social Media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dasnagman Hi there,  For more info please see https://t.co/ebyFUQBHjy   If you have further questions please call the hotline on 1800 675 398 to discuss your situation.  Kind regards, DH Social Media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reported yesterday: no new local cases and 2 new cases acquired overseas (currently in HQ).  - 3,839 vaccine doses were administered  - 17,015 test results were received  More later: https://t.co/2vKbgKHFvv  #COVID19Vic#COVID19VicData https://t.co/sM4zoUbrye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Scobbes Hi there,  A condition of entry to Victoria under an orange zone permit is that you agree to get tested within 72 hours of entering Victoria, even if youve had a (COVID-19) test prior to your arrival. Testing location: https://t.co/WZI0U7BRyW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information about Victoria's travel permit system, visit https://t.co/IPsVKkkdqW. To obtain a permit, visit https://t.co/v9Ej7FMa8U. To contact the Department if you have any questions, call 1300 651 160. [7/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The small number of contacts in VIC linked to exposure sites in WA will be reviewed on a case-by-case basis according to risk and must await contact from the Department of Health regarding their conditions and clearance. Some won't be released from 14-day quarantine. [6/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any primary close contact linked to QF778 on 21 April must continue their 14-day quarantine period.    Any casual contact linked to the Tier 2 exposure site Melbourne Airport Terminal One can end their isolation period when they have received a negative test.  [5/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People currently in Victoria with an orange zone permit  having entered Victoria between 17 April until the red zone came into effect  can end their isolation period when they have received a negative test.  [4/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People currently in Victoria with a red zone permit  having entered VIC after 2:01am 24 April  will be able to be released early from their 14-day quarantine period if they have tested negative. They must await formal clearance  release from the Department of Health. [3/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People entering Victoria with an orange zone permit must isolate, get a coronavirus test within 72 hours, and stay isolated until they receive a negative result. [2/7]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victorias Chief Health Officer has declared that the Perth metropolitan area and the Peel region in Western Australia will be designated orange zones under Victorias travel permit system from 12.01am Wednesday 28 April. [1/7] https://t.co/sdeaIbYIto]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/Ztt98h0J6i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marie31252787 There are different high-volume centres open to people who are eligible to receive a COVID-19 vaccine. To check eligibility please visit: https://t.co/BsYAA2Moq8. To book call 1800 675 398 - select option 3  option 2  option 2.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aviationtat Border arrangements are constantly reviewed based on the health situation in each state and territory. Please see:https://t.co/KbEGHUJyJc  If you have further questions please call the hotline on 1800 675 398 to discuss your situation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maxmia Victorians can travel interstate but please be aware of current restrictions. Border arrangements are constantly reviewed based on the health situation in each state. You will need to apply for a permit to re-enter VIC:https://t.co/9kEYrbGGgg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VicGovDFFH: Nominations for the 2021 Victorian Protecting Children Awards are now open.    Do you know someone who demonstrates excelle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 4 new cases acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported. - 3,369 vaccine doses were administered - 16,875 test results were received More later: https://t.co/FrqsjewwxB  #COVID19Vic#COVID19VicData https://t.co/FKocQvLsCX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/GRLisLaCwD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetterHealthGov: Immunisation is important. It's one of the best ways you can protect your family  vulnerable community members from i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catttttti Hi there, When the zone designation for an area changes (re-zoning), requirements on what to do next may change too.  For more information visit https://t.co/IjIwtvuWVc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AuntAdaDoom1 Hi there, There is increased demand for coronavirus (COVID-19) tests right now. Thank you in advance for your patience. For more information about your test results please visit - https://t.co/TxPgyeAdWI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LazaridesM1 @beertaster3 You should get your test results within 2 days of being tested but sometimes there are delays and it can take longer. You can contact the location where you had the test to follow up. Find the details here: https://t.co/vap76nU9uq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can also get a vaccination through a GP  in fact, GPs are the best place to turn if you have any questions about your health. You can book online at https://t.co/d8pAvJ7uqP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From May 3, this centre will also vaccinate people over the age of 50  and you can make a booking now for May 3 and beyond.  You dont need an appointment, but its encouraged  call 1800 675 398 and select option 3, option 2, option 2.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From today, 26 April, our high-volume vaccination centre In Ballarat opens its doors to all members of the public in Phase 1a and Phase 1b  including people aged 70 and over.  The centre is located at 613 Main Rd, Golden Point. https://t.co/pSlnkVv8SZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new cases reported. - 516 vaccine doses were administered - 12,680 test results were received Got symptoms? Get tested. More later: https://t.co/0xmnS4N9DN  #COVID19Vic #COVID19VicData https://t.co/M5riTRN4Qn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/VH0p3RGrVv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paccraig Hi there, For more information please visit https://t.co/QbDYfQ8XaT   Apply for a permit:https://t.co/LtbRNvZtrL    You can call the Victorian Coronavirus Hotline on 1800 675 398 for further advice]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kathryn_ricka Hi there, Your question may already be answered on our FAQ page. View them here:https://t.co/fcDjm6HttM  If you have further questions please call the hotline on 1800 675 398 to discuss your situation.  Kind regards, DH Social Media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scenedeath From Wednesday 21 April 2021, a number of high-volume vaccination centres will open to people who are eligible to receive a COVID-19 vaccine. To check eligibility for you or a family member visit: https://t.co/sGbbidtshO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lovelee02happy @DanielAndrewsMP @VictorianCHO Hi there, Testing sites are located throughout Victoria. To find out where to get tested, visit:  https://t.co/WZI0U7BRyW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As always,if you are feeling unwell, #StayHome More information on staying safe and well:https://t.co/IU4C5Lm81V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To protect those who are vulnerable, remember to be safe today. If you are heading out:   - maintain physical distance, or wear a mask if you cannot keep it - practise good hygiene - ensure that frequently touched surfaces have been cleaned and disinfected if you are hosting https://t.co/zQduorfs4o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yesterday there were no new local cases and 1 new case acquired overseas (currently in HQ) reported.  - 1,464 vaccine doses were administered  - 13,941 test results were received  More later https://t.co/2vKbgKHFvv  #COVID19Vic#COVID19VicData https://t.co/55haKlCyTQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exposure sites in WA: https://t.co/OFwL0rtDD6  Exposure sites in VIC: https://t.co/SQ5trZH2NI  Where to get tested: https://t.co/WZI0U7Tsqu [6/6]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victorias exposure sites are:   QF778 from Perth to Melbourne on 21 April  get tested and self-quarantine for 14 days regardless of result.  Melbourne Airport Terminal One on 21 April between 7pm and 7:30pm  get tested and stay isolated until negative. [5/6]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WA has also published other exposure sites (find list in the links below) requiring people who attended to get tested and stay isolated until negative.   If you have attended these sites, please also contact us ASAP at 1300 651 160. Exposure sites and advice can change. [4/6]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are currently in Victoria and were at these high-risk locations during these times, you must get tested and immediately self-quarantine for 14 days regardless of your test result  and contact the Victorian Department of Health ASAP at 1300 651 160. [3/6]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Fortune Five Chinese Restaurant in Northbridge on 18/04/2021 between 5:30pm  7pm  Kitchen Inn, 19/17-23 South Street in Kardinya on 18/04/2021 between 12pm  2pm  Anything La Corner, U5-6/910 Albany Hwy in East Victoria Park on 17/04/2021 between 5:30pm  8pm [2/6]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Western Australia has updated its COVID-19 exposure sites, determining the following five sites to be high-risk:   City China Garden in Northbridge on 20/04/2021 between 5pm  8pm  Good Fortune Roast Duck House in Northbridge on 19/04/2021 between 5pm  8pm [1/6] https://t.co/MmSHg1174q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For more information on todays #coronavirus (#COVID19) situation in Victoria, see todays media release: https://t.co/2gJVGeoa04]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@spartacusjsmith @spartacusjsmith Hi there, Your question may be answered here https://t.co/IPLCcdK0cw  If you wish to discuss your situation further, please call the coronavirus hotline on 1800 675 398  Kind regards, DH Social media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@heytom Hi there, Testing sites are located throughout Victoria. To find out where to get tested, visit:  https://t.co/WZI0U7BRyW   Kind regards, DH Social Media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@demimakers09 Hi there,   Your question may be answered here: https://t.co/IPLCcdK0cw  Kind regards,  DH Social media]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>