<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BoerboelBritish: Why dont the 99% of us that are not offended by everything, quit pandering to the 1% that are ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charlie_lawson1: Specially for all those of you who are still terrified by Whitty Vallance and the other one..... Handjob....or whateve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pub_politics: Whos got more personality   Like for Starmer   RT for for this rock https://t.co/lI1HYGvKYP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HubNewport: Open at Rodney Parade stadium every Thursday 12:00-18:00.  We offer veterans and their families a place to socialise and ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TiceRichard: Utter rubbish.... no evidence, no data, just lots of upset stressed children being scared rigid totally unnecessarily. If]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RorschachDefile: Any chance people can help me get a few of my old followers back from my suspended 2k account, I miss the interactions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WeWillBeFree82 So it may be, but if so then let them! Won't hurt me and unlike them I won't give them grief for it!  Ok, maybe just a snigger but that's all!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnMappin: Share this. https://t.co/tYgiNYN2l3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: Unlocking society is not enough. We need to unlock people from fear.   People for whom any risk is now too high.   We h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: BBC in 2001   "Children will never see snow in Britain by 2020"  Yorkshire in May 2021 "Yeah, right!" https://t.co/02ak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/ZVCvsOeJNw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep! https://t.co/PLesS4Xprf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lying barsteward! https://t.co/IZPowcQprh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goonbiscuit: Parents, it's time to start acting like it - stop your healthy children from wearing a muzzle (as that's what it is)  sto]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: We will Not be asking for Covid Certification based on Test to Enter or any other health papers. We shall be #openforall ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet  FIND ALFIE A HOME CAMPAIGN 2021  #Edinburgh #Scotland   Alfie has been overlooked for a while, he's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexanderProud: I will not be asking to see any Covid passports or certification at Proud Group. Britain is famous for liberty. This is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS! https://t.co/dI1JAzuT6x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdzGCol @Mariebe10098426 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ella32823623: They know masks are useless, you want to know why are they are continuing with them? They keep you subservient, compliant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Over 650,000 people lost their jobs in hospitality in 2020 despite only 226 outbreaks of covid in pubs and restaurants.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naughtynell101: Children should not be forced to wear masks any longer in classrooms. The Weimar ruling in Germany has found them harmf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKCopHumour: The Police Family remembers you.   R.I.P. Julia.  #WeWillRemember #SayHerName #JusticeForJulia #ThinBlueLine https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/N63EzgQcyF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @statsjamie: Simple message lets move on from this debate and start to get some freedoms back. https://t.co/aw7s3fXdBv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help find the owner of this Lab  FOUND #COVENTRY  Female Labrador found 4 May 2021 With Dog warden Coven]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Toby find a home #DEVON https://t.co/ubgsLJYjzM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Christi75367510: #SackSAGE we never voted for them, or Bill Gates. #ConservativesOut https://t.co/FnZQKzlTvz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Vincent find a home #LINCOLNSHIRE  Aged 1-2 looking for an adult home with large breed experience,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MiriMission: Sadie needs a forever home.  She was attacked by a pack of dogs  beaten by humans so her back legs are paralysed  To adop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GGDollPhotos: Can you help?... https://t.co/WLHw9VK4Tt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HappilyUnwoke: Concern for missing girl, 16, who has links to Blackpool https://t.co/pLeeQsvVTA Anyone seen her? #Blackpool #FyldeCoast]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Rumba find a home #LEEDS   Ex racing Greyhound aged 5-7, loves training and learning, looking for a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyguy10 @MaizyDaizyZzzz I'll volunteer to be the one who doesn't ever have it so she has to stay in forever! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @snowball1926: End our government's control of the people.  TAKE OFF YOUR MASKS! https://t.co/jsIpG6TDtD https://t.co/smvRXmhT2p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BE4RP4UL @Anshul__K Picked yourself up a bot there Anshul! Unfortunately it appears you got a thick one! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Leroy find a home #Bridgend #Wales  Aged 13, Jack Russell Cross, can live with children aged]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Tosca find a home #SOMERSET  #cats #CatsOfTwitter https://t.co/EbTWKgn1Im]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jannermaid1: Senior NHS Board Member Warns: Stop The Genocide Or Our Children Are Next https://t.co/MmAfoCW7I9 via @ukcolumn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WIONews: At least 20 Indian companies, including Serum Institute of India, to invest in the UK, as both countries announce a $1.39billi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WYP_PCSO211: A public message from PCSO Julia James daughter. Tonight at 7pm I will be lighting my candle for Julia James. I think I s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Todd find a home #Taunton   Aged 8, looking for an experienced adult home to go on with socialisi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fact_covid: The @Join_ZOE COVID Symptom Study app is now predicting fewer than 15,000 people have symptomatic COVID-19 in the UK at the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These people deserve to be strung up! They are supposed to care for kids not abuse them! So angry! https://t.co/bN09aw2Jsh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrankSp82601647: Take off your muzzle.  Refuse the injection.  And the lie just crumbles.  It all ends.  #TakeOffYourMask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/xCJJgc0gXj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Loki find a home #Cotswolds #Gloucestershire  Akita aged 10 months, can live with children aged 11+]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/2NQMhMiUR5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bbcpress You lot wouldn't know the truth if you found it in a doorway! #ScumMedia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesCranworth: Covid has gone in the UK The majority of the UK lives in a covid free zone Every mask wearer now is just a brainwashed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Gordon Brown is going full tilt today to get the world vaxxed  to get us to pay for it. As noted, I think the real de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingsleyBates Best of luck Kingsley! xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apsmunro: There was a lot of hoo-ha about too many children attending primary school in the last lockdown  The ONS school infection sur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lyndonx: We will be in a caste system if people allow the #VaccinePassports in. Those who have and can and those who have not and cant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZoePrecious2020: Scared of a virus with a 99% recovery rate?  If so avoid all public places and stop going to work.  Don't make others]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Covid hospital deaths reported today:  East of England: 0 North East  Yorkshire: 0 North West: 0 South East: 0 South We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: Are we "crying freedom" yet, @MattHancock? https://t.co/WjS3JkfGR7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: If you own a pub , restaurant , cafe, Hotel or an events business, please join our movement against Vaccine Passports. BOTH my]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Michael80789776: Are you listening, Hollywood and performing artists?  Spot on... here  https://t.co/Yhft7B3wrK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrislittlewoo8: After only 1 death reported today, ppl need to ask themselves  Why do they want to jab children?  Why is social distan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AJKayWriter: I used to trust in the safety of vaccines and the good faith intentions of people who recommended them.  I no longer do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @martinpmurray: There is a long road ahead to secure our economy this is why We MUST allow ALL #Hospitality sectors to REOPEN NOW 2BILL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrCharlesL: COVID anxiety syndrome is a condition that has been worrying me for some time. Many are suffering.  It's more widespread th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: Governments around the world stole our humans rights  freedoms  now want to implement digital control over every aspect]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: URGENT please retweet to help Kenny find a home #NOTTINGHAMSHIRE   Aged 14 lovely Collie looking for a quiet adult home as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: Please support this. Let's get back to normal. #OpenForAll https://t.co/DwRPIwkjMT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_V5M1000: #TakeOffYourMask https://t.co/xMUHECRpn3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/q7MGfOhes2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DickDelingpole: Ultimately, the restrictions will kill the pubs which gold plate the rules. Regular drinkers are the least bed-wetty an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Slinky find a home #Lincolnshire   Sweet boy, aged 10, would love an adult home with a garden as on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MsJenSurvivor Bright but very blustery here Jen, freezing though!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieEmmaUK: Enoughs enough.  If you cant see through the vile propaganda by now and it scares you rather than making you angry the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UsforThemUK: Thank you @calvinrobinson for speaking out. We agree - shocking and negligent behaviour from @PHE_uk - putting children at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Bruno find a home #MANCHESTER   This lovely Staffie smiler is looking for a home with adults or chi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hughosmond It's such a corrupt world we live in ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We need more like this! https://t.co/vw8ZlVBcfb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hmmm? https://t.co/ODpxkW2QFK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TJ0056: @RealLordBrexit https://t.co/uoXlKh7HQa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@steveluke7 My private one is still only seeing emergencies!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Enough is enough. We've got six weeks to show the government that if they don't give us our lives back we're just going]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @accountingetc: "Three weeks to flatten the curve" to "Let's experiment on children" in just over a year.  The decline of humanity is ra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep! https://t.co/mx82LE7G10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/H1FtGhZVY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Kara find a home #CountyDurham    Lovely Akita aged 8, would like an experienced adult home as only]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Naughtydonna1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stuh40 Such a disappointment..........]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Billwoo43533006 Night Billy xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @calvinrobinson: We should ditch masks in schools with immediate effect.  Leaked Public Health England documents show officials failed t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeesValleyVoice: 5 dogs looking for forever homes from Dogs Trust Darlington https://t.co/csdtgXgC89]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why? Just why? Ah yes, just the latest bandwagon! Best of luck with that one mate! https://t.co/BIBwwF9mbm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: Request:  This is gonna be a big 2 weeks  Its going to be when we get gov to either listen  have our freedom  Normality  O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/RbjIf3289V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Why does everything to do with the return of normal life and fundamental freedoms have to be "probably", "we hope" or "th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Wolf14064576: Help required for a friend  please  looking for the following in South Somerset   A) a piece of land not being used to h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UnityNewsNet: HIGH IMPORTANCE: We can reveal the Global CEO of Omnicom Group who won the 320 Million Covid19 ad contract is a member o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TakeOffYourMask #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/oxYv26HOMB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Urgent retweet please to help Rupert and Bella find a home together #Wales, currently North Wales could re home Nationally]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/kxylh53ZeZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SwanwatchUk: GOOD MORNING THIS IS AN APPEAL TO THR PUBLIC   IF ANYONE KNOWS THESE VILE LITTLE CUNT OF TWO TEENS THEY NEED TO HAND THEM]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>