<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[A very helpful thread outlining how current #covid19 vaccines are effective against circulating variants in real-world scenarios.    We still need to keep a close watch on emerging variants, but to date, mass vaccination seems to do the job.   Vaccines are winning.   https://t.co/lh10qUBLCc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kellygrant1: It's still a bad scene out there in Ontario hospitals, but with cases declining, the province now thinks it can avoid the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GurdeepA Thanks for posting this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MikeMacNcheese @f_l_o_u_r_i_s_h @taimhuynh @GraphicMatt Look at the green dot (40s) when AZ was approved for 40+. Impressive.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBCNews: @jillpromoli @cdavidnaylor https://t.co/Jztd3JAcax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CityMelanie @breakfasttv Great to chat with you. I didnt know this (may the fourth) was a thing. Turns out its a thing.   Also nice to discuss AZ and JJ vaccines today. I hope we cleared up a few issues.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@meg_michael_ Excellent point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honest conversations about the Risks, Benefits, Alternatives  Context enable people to make informed decisions...  ...and after this thought exercise, many have suggested to take (and/or receive) the 1st available #COVID19 vaccine (which is very reasonable).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AZ/J+J vaccines - helpful to explain:  1. Benefits: Protection from dangerous infection, spillover benefit to family, close contacts  2. Risk: Incidence of clotting events  3. Alternatives: Waiting for mRNA vaccines  4. Context: Large 3rd wave in , younger ages in hospital/ICU https://t.co/kEoNAtvfHv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apoorva_nyc: BREAKING: The news I get dozens of emails about: The FDA is planning to authorize use of Pfizer's vaccine in adolescents 1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CP24: Ontario may shorten interval between vax doses as more supply expected: Elliott  https://t.co/JjgeVncOHN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdTubb I agree. They have been consistent. Its also important to contextualize risk. These are potentially life-saving vaccines, but we have to be transparent about the risk  enable informed decision making. Weve never had this much COVID-19, and these vaccines can ( do) save lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JPTasker: "What we're saying  and what we've been saying all along  is that mRNA vaccines are the preferred vaccines," says Dr. Shell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how you bake equity into #covid19 vaccine rollout   (Great thread by Joe Cressy) https://t.co/ADpDUkD2Oz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jayme_poisson Oh yeah. We will when the dust settles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kellygrant1: I wrote today about infections after the 1st dose in Canada. There was plenty of info I didn't have room to include, so if]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We are doing this because we want to help the country."  An inspiring interview with @VaxHuntersCan, a group of volunteers working to get as many Canadians vaccinated as possible.     https://t.co/GsWyLxCDX5 by @jayme_poisson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @taimhuynh: Not all pop ups have hours-long line ups. Maybe 1 or 2 weeks ago w/ vaccine shortage. This one was 15 minutes wait this afte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ Proof of vaccination to cross an international border is a contentious issue for some, but  1. People can choose to be vaccinated (or not) 2. People travel 3. Sovereign countries determine border policy as they see fit  ... circles on that Venn diagram may not always overlap.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/ More details from the European Union regarding #COVID19 vaccinations  travel:  "...anyone who has received the last dose of an EU-approved vaccine at least two weeks beforehand will be permitted to travel."  Details  https://t.co/Z6YJhE2Ey4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattgallowaycbc: "This is the month when Canada breaks the back of the pandemic." https://t.co/cWPFd39PuR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHOAFRO: The latest #Ebola outbreak in #DRC has been declared over after just 3 months. Twelve cases, six deaths  six recoveries wer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PHealthGnome Thank you for this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shawn_Anderson Nothing is really new. Their page has been updated, but they've said this for a while in other communications.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mvankerkhove @SaskiaPopescu @DrMikeRyan @doctorsoumya Remember this well. Your communication (and that of Dr Ryan et al) has been very helpful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lots of discussion about essential workers.   They are prioritized...  Apr 29: Licensed childcare workers May 1: Essential workers group 1 May 10: Essential workers group 2  Source: https://t.co/FWvk1ibqjA https://t.co/4dGoi6VZjz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sherrithinks @shaunpeet @MandelRobin Starts tomorrow at 0800]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: We are fortunate that vaccines induce such a strong immune response and provide protection from all of the virus variants th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottGottliebMD Be right over...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The World Health Organization just updated #COVID19 transmission info, discussing that the infection is mainly transmitted in close proximity (1m), but longer-range transmission is possible in poorly ventilated/crowded spaces. Glad to see this.  Source: https://t.co/TfNEiNOSDE https://t.co/MxCXQVwXsk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonHerriot Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1. Provincial website to book an appointment: https://t.co/So50giA2fj  2. Provincial phone number to book an appointment:  1-833-943-3900]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting tomorrow (May 3), EVERYONE 18 years  older living in 114 Ontario postal codes highly-impacted by #COVID19 will be eligible to book a vaccine appointment on the provincial/public health websites.  Source: https://t.co/ON2oioeR04  114 "hot-spot" postal codes:  https://t.co/ef8hAAtWEl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rubiconcapital_ That's basically it.   I don't see how, as Canadians, we would have influence over another country's health policy. Do you?  If we choose to not be vaccinated, we will be limited.   We may as well have the infrastructure to properly document vaccination for those who choose it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rubiconcapital_ Regardless, people can choose to believe that COVID is serious or not/get vaccinated or not.  But a growing list of countries recognize that COVID is a PH threat  are requiring proof of vaccination.   Those who chose to not be vaccinated will have limited travel options. Simple.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rubiconcapital_ Uuuuhhhh....have you seen whats happening in healthcare systems where the virus transmits unchecked? Tons of examples globally. Im in ON. Its bad. Its a PH threat by any measure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rubiconcapital_ @janephilpott Both c19 and yf are significant public health threats - both can cause large outbreaks, cause significant illness in some of those infected, and overwhelm healthcare system capacity. Both are vaccine preventable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rubiconcapital_ @janephilpott Hi Kelly, the key here is that there is precedent for demonstrating vaccination to a communicable disease (that poses a public health threat) for the purpose of crossing an international border.   Seen with smallpox, meningococcus, yellow fever, COVID etc.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DFisman @AshTuite Thanks for sharing.   Good news - preliminary, but more evidence suggesting current vaccines will have some efficacy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zchagla @TorontoIDDoc @janephilpott Digitize it on the passport or travel document.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@janephilpott Agree 100%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nikikgray @alanmcn1 One deep fried caterpillar cake, please.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @l_stone: The Globe estimates that by the end of July, the country should receive enough doses for all eligible people to be fully vacc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Addendum: Just FYI, there are countries that require Yellow Fever vaccination, regardless (above).   There are *many* other countries that require proof of  vaccination for those travelling from a region where Yellow Fever is endemic.   https://t.co/dM1g00Dw6H https://t.co/noVl7r6Whc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NoahIvers @VaxHuntersCan I tried it this AM and it worked really well.   This is all thanks to @ZainManji and @VaxHuntersCan - dedicated volunteers making useful work-arounds for our convoluted sign-up system.  @KamilKaramali has a great write up of how this came to be here:  https://t.co/J3Ujdq1NXx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5/ So regardless of our opinions on the matter, it appears that proof of #COVID19 vaccination will be required for international travel.   May as well be ahead of the curve  quickly find ways to electronically/securely document vaccination status, that meets global standards.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4/ There is precedent for this.   Many countries require proof of Yellow Fever vaccination to enter.   If you show up without proper documentation you either: 1. get turned around at the border, or  2. get vaccinated at the border (if available).  Source: https://t.co/lRfZilCn53 https://t.co/3WB8RFYtsq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/ #COVID19 vaccine certification for travel will likely be a global norm:  https://t.co/37dLzxJoAx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ There are a growing number of countries requiring proof of #COVID19 vaccination for travel...18 are currently listed here.  Also the EU just announced they would be open to vaccinated travellers from the USA this summer.  https://t.co/9VOeqMpCwe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1. "Health Minister Patty Hajdu says her government embraces the concept of 'vaccine passports'  will come up with a form of certification to allow vaccinated Canadians to travel internationally."  Smart move  good to be proactive.  https://t.co/ulfbPb8bSx by @peterzimonjic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KamilKaramali: 1/7 This https://t.co/kUHjmG8DZz website can occasionally be used to create some wondrous things.  Tonight, it fostered]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: The covid-19 crisis in India is a massive setback for the entire world.   India needs the global communitys support to survi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Effect of 1st dose of #COVID19 vaccine on reducing hospital admissions at day 28-34 (real world data from Scotland):  *Pfizer: 91% *AstraZeneca: 88%  Different study than the one below, but same message:  2 doses better than 1, but 1 dose very helpful.   https://t.co/fm6owfWNGm https://t.co/yMYdcU2QpU https://t.co/9c0VSJOpsl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well hello there, Pfizer...  https://t.co/HVoFDQf5Lz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brittlestar @brittlestar, the master of effective public health comms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brittlestar: UNEXPECTED VACCINE SIDE EFFECT https://t.co/6ToTW6XLw9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 vaccines are for everyone.  Toronto is taking meaningful steps to ensure new immigrants  refugees have equitable access to vaccination.   Program details  https://t.co/YPCLInAXW0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrRossanaRosa We dont know each other but congratulations on 1. Your growing family, and 2. A fantastic tweet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @docschull: Canadian universities: it is time to announce the same requirement. https://t.co/HTdYxzkhDJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mikeggibbs @AntibioticDoc Correct.   In Ontario, those with organ transplants or certain types of cancer are receiving the 2nd dose at the 21/28 day interval:  https://t.co/vUY1aYZnsB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NathanStall Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Dr. Fauci on CNN: "We look at the data and the impact that the vaccine is having, it's even better than what you would ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidWCochrane @VassyKapelos Congratulations!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@parsnipper @DrDavSweet This is very good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @parsnipper: Here's an algorithm we created in BC to help assess COVID patients who are "stalled" or not improving after the initial cou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TaliBogler @OntarioCollege @OCFP_President @tara_kiran @nilikm @NoahIvers Moderna to primary care. Pfizer to pharmacies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nilikm 1. Primary care to have expanded role (can't come soon enough).  2. Primary care to administer AZ, J+J (when we have more),  Moderna.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JKoumaris Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NathanStall @carolemacneil Pfizer is challenging to work with (reconstitution, storage, etc). It's likely going to be used mostly in mass vaccine clinics, pop-ups, pharmacies.  Moderna is easier to work with  will be moved with increasing frequency to primary care clinics - set to expand (not soon enough)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vancouver leading the way by giving people opportunities to safely enjoy a beverage outside in public parks....much better there than in others' homes.   #COVID19 harm reduction at work. https://t.co/4uQqQ5EjUJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryFernando_ @ericbenchimol Many of us agree as well. @cdavidnaylor  I wrote this a few weeks ago.  https://t.co/szItSgllXp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Effectiveness of either Pfizer or Moderna #COVID19 vaccine on hospitalization (for those over 65 years old):  1. ~94% following 2 doses 2. ~64% following 1 dose  1st dose is very helpful, but still need to maintain precautions.   https://t.co/rKnqxg7EnR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bistro_on Essential workers are prioritized in early May:  Cannot Work from Home Group 1: May 3 Cannot Work from Home Group 2: May 10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VaxHuntersCan: [ON] We are optimistic about the new eligibility timeline announced by the province today. We'll continue to be here to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ After the 2 week vaccine push in highly-impacted areas the plan is to continue to vaccinate these areas via a few mechanisms:  *Age cutoff is 18+ in hot-spot mass vaccine sites *Essential workers prioritized]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/ Ontario's #COVID19 vaccine plan:  1. Pour vaccines into hot spots 2. Vaccinate essential workers 3. Lower age cutoffs through May, with 18+ by May 24 4. 18+ in hot-spots mass vaccine sites in early May 5. Move Pfizer to Pharmacies  Very helpful. https://t.co/or3VfvwAtX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cowboyskanuck Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Billius27 @Genia11 I don't either.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NathanStall @PrabSarkaria Stay tuned...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bistro_on Amazing. Will try them next time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bistro_on @ryandoyleshow @_scottreid I've got to try these.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bistro_on @_scottreid Is this a thing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paimadhu @zchagla @redcrosscanada Thank you, Madhu. Great advice for Canadians to support India.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Zadz74 Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: 1st shipment of Johnson  Johnson's COVID-19 vaccine now in Canada. 304,800 doses of the vaccine arrived at Toronto's Pearso]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8. With time, vaccines will help us return to normalcy.  Take home points:  -Vaccines work really really well -2 doses better than 1, but 1 still really good -Maintain precautions after 1 dose, you are not invincible  We'll get through this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7. Also, while these vaccines are really really good, they are not perfect. People can still get sick even after 2 doses.   It's pretty uncommon, but it can happen.   The CDC discusses it here: https://t.co/7bK2rldjwW https://t.co/7sjQuxixaV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6. So what do we do?   The same thing we've been doing all along...mask indoors, avoid close, confined, crowded settings. Ventilate rooms. Spend time outdoors. You know...the usual.   Also, we'll probably get 2nd doses before 4 month due to supply. (Probably).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5/   So can you get #COVID19 even 2 weeks after your 1st dose?  Of course - but your risk is much lower.  Can you get really sick?  Sure - but your risk is also much lower. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4/ But going back to the 1st point, while 1 dose provides pretty decent protection from #COVID19, 2 doses are ideal.   Stretching out the interval between dose 1  2 i(in Canada) provides protection to more people over a shorter period of time.  This will end our pandemic faster.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/ Here is some of the data backing up NACI's statement above, but from a clinical trial.  This graph below is with Pfizer...look at how people start to gain protection ~12-14 days after their 1st dose (red line).   Pretty impressive.  Link: https://t.co/SONs86le1N https://t.co/n5OEyXAuK0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/  NACI outlines protection after 1 dose of a vaccine in their recent document:   "Most importantly, these studies show one dose of the Pfizer-BioNTech  AstraZeneca vaccines are approximately 80% effective against hospitalization..."  Details: https://t.co/jY5TjswFHB https://t.co/js0g7qeGum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/ A few points to clarify a few points...  These vaccines are really really good, but not perfect.  One dose of a vaccine provides excellent protection against #COVID19 infection, but of course 2 doses provide more protection. https://t.co/GkV4kvj0bM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joe_cressy @VaxHuntersCan @VaxHuntersCan on fire!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joe_cressy: NEW: we're announcing a partnership between the City of Toronto and Vaccine Hunters Canada.  Starting today @VaxHuntersCan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@supriyadwivedi @RobSilver You need your own TV show]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vast majority of side effects are mild and self-resolving.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DadEducator "In this prospective observational study, we examined the proportion and probability of self-reported systemic and local side-effects within 8 days of vaccination in individuals using the COVID Symptom Study app..."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best data to date on side-effects following Pfizer (BNT162b2)  AstraZeneca (ChAdOx1 nCoV-19) #COVID19 vaccines.  Systemic side-effects were reported in:  *13.5% after 1st dose Pfizer *22% after 2nd dose Pfizer *37.7% after 1st dose AZ  Link: https://t.co/gvulHDQ3Fm  Details https://t.co/i2oVb5qUNL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelloStephano Not a dumb question at all. Unfortunately no benefit of diet/medications that we know of to proactively reduce rare AZ-related blood clots.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>