<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Increase in daily #COVID cases and #COVID19 deaths seen in Maharashtra, Karnataka, Andhra Pradesh, Delhi and Haryana  12 States/UTs have more than 1 lakh #ActiveCases   :JS @MoHFW_INDIA   #StaySafe #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/V3xXQKeLWX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Active Cases: 34,13,642 Deaths: 2,18,959 Cured: 1,62,93,003  :JS @MoHFW_INDIA   #StaySafe #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/zokS1tXh9p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  LIVE NOW:  Media briefing by @MoHFW_INDIA on the current #COVID19 situation in the country  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe   Watch: https://t.co/OeaScqXbge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  #COVID19Vaccination registrations have begun for those above 18 years of age.   Get yourself registered on https://t.co/aSRAR6Fbhu / @SetuAarogya / @UmangOfficial_  #We4Vaccine  #LargestVaccinationDrive  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/GkSjcoYOl5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Steps taken by Indian Customs for expeditious clearance of #COVID relief related imports:  High priority for clearance by the customs systems for processing, as compared to other goods  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/4zZU2eOXop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Are steroids advisable in mild #COVID19 cases  Taking high dose steroids in mild cases may lead to severe viral pneumonia.  Steroids should be taken in moderate illness.  It may be harmful if taken in initial 5 days of mild illness: Dr. Guleria, AIIMS https://t.co/MbLRSFUIby]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona  Is CT scan required in mild #COVID19 cases  If you are asymptomatic, have mild illness  oxygen saturation is normal, there is no need of a #CTScan   CT scan is required only if you have moderate illness: Dr. Randeep Guleria, Director, AIIMS  #StaySafe https://t.co/J3p9T9pL4B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   Availability of #COVID19Vaccine doses (As on 5th May, 2021 till 08:00 AM)   Follow #COVIDAppropriateBehaviour to #StaySafe  #Unite2FightCorona #We4Vaccine  #LargestVaccinationDrive https://t.co/QmvahgFkw2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Fake news around #COVID19 is as harmful as the virus itself.   Think before believing  Think before sharing  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/GA5iDLnKw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  @IITKanpur decides to produce around 30000 #OxygenConcentrator by June.  It has invited industries to come along  assured all kind of help to achieve this goal.  - Shrikant Shastri, Professor, #IITKanpur  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/X9K3G6FwM3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Key decisions for boosting medical staff availability, as announced by PM @narendramodi:  Medical staff who have completed 100 days in #COVID duties will be given govt job.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/wAT6fHDDS0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  @IITKanpur decides to produce around 30000 oxygen concentrators by June. It has invited industries to come along  assured all kind of help to achieve this goal: Shrikant Shastri, Professor #IITKanpur #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe  @MoHFW_INDIA @drharshvardhan https://t.co/XMHfJODPZg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mayank23Agrawal: "COVID    Oxygen "   -AIIMS   -     3    ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  The States/UTs have also been requested to issue directions to concerned officials at various levels.  MHA has also drawn attention to the recently issued advisory of the Director General (Fire services, Civil Defence  Home Guards). https://t.co/QmLRtroBym]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ministry of Home Affairs draws attention of States/UTs on need to have plan of action to ensure no fire incidents occur in health facilities, particularly #COVID19 facilities.  MHA highlights need for States/UTs to ensure uninterrupted power supply in COVID dedicated facilities. https://t.co/HFTbKXruXz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   What guidelines/precautions should I follow while taking Ayush-64   There are no such special precautions to be followed while using Ayush-64.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/45QmyJzrnl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   Is Ayush-64 safe for pregnant  lactating women   The safety of Ayush-64 in cases of pregnant  lactating women is not established through scientific studies.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/IsrO9bslQV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   Is Ayush-64 safe if taken after vaccination   Yes. If a person gets infected even after vaccination, Ayush-64 can be taken within 7 days of testing RT-PCR positive for SARS CoV-2.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/yb3H2RHOwQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   Can a #COVID19 patient with other co-morbidities take Ayush-64   Patients with co-morbidities like hypertension  diabetes can take Ayush-64 for asymptomatic, mild to moderate disease  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/A5BGcWD10Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   Should Ayush-64 be taken as standalone treatment in mild cases   It can be taken as a standalone treatment in mild cases under supervision of an Ayurvedic physician.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/dQdbI9GPWo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   What is the ideal dose for Ayush-64 in #COVID19 patients   The dose for asymptomatic COVID-19 case is 2 tablets of 500mg, twice daily, one hour after meals with warm water for 14 days.  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/ojRCMd0R53]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   Who can take Ayush-64   Patients of mild to moderate #COVID19 cases showing initial symptoms and asymptomatic cases of COVID-19 can start taking Ayush-64 within 7 days of diagnosis.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/p6QqDh2yL3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Some important FAQs on #AYUSH64   What is Ayush-64   Ayush-64 is an Ayurvedic formulation developed the @CCRAS_MoAYUSH.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/QophAbjJJ1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBHomeAffairs: MINISTRY OF HOME AFFAIRS (MHA) DRAWS ATTENTION OF STATES  UTs ON NEED TO HAVE PLAN OF ACTION TO ENSURE FIRE INCIDENTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoRD_GOI:    18    ,  1           ,         #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   Increasing gap between #COVID19 Recovered  Active cases of India (June 01, 2020 to May 05, 2021)  #StaySafe #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/8ZSCPG3Mke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Resources for creating health infrastructure for #COVIDCare, include establishment of medical oxygen generation  storage plants  manufacturing  supply of Oxygen concentrators, ventilators, cylinders and other medical equipment for countering #COVID19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Ministry of Corporate Affairs clarifies that spending of CSR funds directly or through pooling of resources for creating health infrastructure for #COVID care are eligible CSR activities.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafeStayHealthy https://t.co/2uTkTPWgxM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FinMinIndia: Ministry of Corporate Affairs clarifies that spending of CSR funds directly or through pooling of resources for creating]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Government of India has so far provided more than 17.02 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of Cost (As on 5th May, 2021, 8:00 am)   Over 36 Lakh doses, in addition, will be received by the states/UTs in the next 3 days  #We4Vaccine #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/dO6iROri2n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @airnewsalerts: #IITKanpur decides to produce around 30000 oxygen concentrators by June. It has invited industries to come along and ass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  3,780 deaths were reported in the last 24 hours.  Ten States account for 74.97% of the new deaths. Maharashtra saw the maximum casualties (891). Uttar Pradesh follows with 351 daily deaths.  Details: https://t.co/ATkzL7GVuF  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/M1caaR232A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Twelve states cumulatively account for 81.25% of Indias total Active Cases.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/1UCm8BgBRO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Ten States report 70.91% of the new cases.  Maharashtra has reported the highest daily new cases at 51,880. It is followed by Karnataka with 44,631 while Kerala reported 37,190 new cases.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/YtqyaPpTPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Nineteen States/UTs have a weekly positivity rate higher than the national average.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/G6eMbFZYPI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Seventeen States/UTs have a weekly positivity rate lower than the national average (21.46%).  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/3GVI0tZ4gv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Indias cumulative recoveries stand at 1,69,51,731 today. The National Recovery Rate is 82.03%.  3,38,439 recoveries were registered in the last 24 hours.  Ten states account for 73.4% of the new recoveries.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/smjy2yRd9w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Ten states account for 66.86% of the cumulative doses given so far in the country.  #We4Vaccine  #LargestVaccinationDrive  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/JFT7hjeYGh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  India took only 109 days to achieve this milestone.  In comparison, the US took 111 days while China required 116 days to achieve similar figures.  #We4Vaccine  #LargestVaccinationDrive  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/PEZHgcD16n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  India becomes the fastest country to exceed 16 Crore cumulative vaccinations as the Nationwide Vaccination Drive expands.  More than 6.7 Lakh beneficiaries of age group 18-44 Vaccinated under Phase-3 of Vaccination Drive.  #We4Vaccine #LargestVaccinationDrive https://t.co/W1E9LNc2cR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Installation of 2 high capacity Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) completed at #AIIMS, New Delhi and @RMLDelhi hospitals.   Oxygen supply to #COVID19 patients to begin from today evening.  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/jEJcU5B0LK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   Highest number of #ActiveCases in several states of India (as on 5th May, 2021 till 08:00 AM)   Follow #COVIDAppropriateBehaviour to #StaySafe  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/MeNVauNvOK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBMumbai: 'He got #COVID infected after taking #Vaccine'  many have this notion   Even while in queues at #Vaccination centres, foll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Highest number of daily #NewCases in several states of India (as on 05th May, 2021 till 08:00 AM)   Follow #COVIDAppropriateBehaviour to #StaySafe  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/1D0qzwmcU8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Do's  Don'ts to be safe while in indoor settings  Do's Wear mask Maintain 6 feet distance Wash your hands  Don'ts Do not touch front portion of mask Do not eat with others Avoid centralized air conditioning  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/wZdvz3ILD4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  India registered more than 3 lakh (3,38,439) #COVID19 recoveries in the last 24 hours.   Together, we can win the battle against COVID-19.   #StaySafe and follow #COVIDAppropriateBehaviour   #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/UBwYwcDUm7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Are steroids advisable in mild #COVID19 cases  Taking high dose steroids in mild cases may lead to severe viral pneumonia.  Steroids should be taken in moderate illness.  It may be harmful if taken in initial 5 days of mild illness: Dr. Guleria, AIIMS https://t.co/aFeQHJK65g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Govt. of India has so far provided more than 17.02 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of Cost  More than 94.47 lakh doses are still available with the States/UTs to be administered  Details: https://t.co/PKRn1iH5rV  #We4Vaccine #LargestVaccinationDrive https://t.co/NUUsEHb8P0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CoronaVirusUpdates:   State-wise details of Total Confirmed #COVID19 cases (till 05 May, 2021, 8 AM)   States with 1-60000 confirmed cases  States with 60001-550000 confirmed cases  States with 550000+ confirmed cases  Total no. of confirmed cases so far   #StaySafe https://t.co/CT50iuHBUh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBMumbai: LIVE shortly: Address by #RBI Governor   Watch: https://t.co/RvGPcqtsBr   @RBI @FinMinIndia https://t.co/wA3mVckowh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  These Medical #OxygenPlants are designed for a flow rate of 1000 liters per minute.   These will overcome logistics issues of oxygen transportation and help #COVID19 patients in emergency.  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafeStayHealthy https://t.co/3EYDZPlFQN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Installation of 2 high capacity Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) completed at #AIIMS, New Delhi and @RMLDelhi hospitals.    Oxygen supply to #COVID19 patients to begin from today evening.  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/X0F2Cp4GTL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoHFW_INDIA: #Unite2FightCorona  Installation of 2 high capacity Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) completed at #AIIMS, New De]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CoronaVirusUpdates:  #COVID19 India Tracker (As on 5 May, 2021, 08:00 AM)  Confirmed cases: 2,06,65,148 Recovered: 1,69,51,731 (82.03%) Active cases: 34,87,229 (16.87%) Deaths: 2,26,188 (1.09%)  #IndiaFightsCorona #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe   @MoHFW_INDIA https://t.co/kX7ZeXCoBk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  #COVID19Vaccination Status (As on 5th May, 2021, 7:00 AM)  Total vaccine doses administered (so far): 16,04,94,188  Vaccine doses administered (on 5th May, 2021): 14,84,989  #We4Vaccine #LargestVaccinationDrive  @ICMRDELHI @DBTIndia https://t.co/fGMnMUxeUa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CoronaVirusUpdates:   Total #COVID19 Cases in India (as on May 5, 2021)  82.03% Cured/Discharged/Migrated (1,69,51,731) 16.87% Active cases (34,87,229) 1.09% Deaths (2,26,188)  Total COVID-19 confirmed cases = Cured/Discharged/Migrated+Active cases+Deaths  #StaySafe https://t.co/rUrQfzjnNb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNinIndia: Despite overstretched healthcare systems due to #COVID19, midwives have continued to provide essential medical services to m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  India's Cumulative Vaccination Coverage (As on 05th May, 2021, 08:00 am)   More than 16.04 crore doses administered  More than 6 lakh beneficiaries of age group vaccinated in phase-3 of the world's #LargestVaccinationDrive  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/nV3tjnuOXc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CoronaVirusUpdates:  #COVID19 testing status update:  @ICMRDELHI stated that 29,48,52,078 samples tested upto May 04, 2021  15,41,299 samples tested on May 04, 2021  #StaySafe #Unite2FightCorona   @DBTIndia https://t.co/5q26KLSO6L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   #COVID19Vaccination Status (As on 04th May, 2021, 8:00 PM)  India's Cumulative Vaccination Coverage exceeds 16.04 Crores (16,04,18,105)  1st Dose: 13.00 Crores (13,00,03,225) 2nd Dose: 3.04 Crores (3,04,14,880)  #LargestVaccinationDrive #StaySafe https://t.co/kKPUae6NXR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Know the fundamentals before using a #PulseOximeter    Have a look to this video  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe  @MoHFW_INDIA @drharshvardhan @PrakashJavdekar @PIBHomeAffairs @PIB_India @WHO @ICMRDELHI https://t.co/QGQtQWOC1I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrakashJavdekar:       #LargestVaccinationDrive  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/3S44KiJVIC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   India crosses a Landmark Milestone with more than 16 Cr doses administered.   More than 13 Cr Vaccine doses administered as First Dose.   Over 3 Cr Vaccine doses administered as Second Dose.  #LargestVaccinationDrive   Details: https://t.co/Ve0ZK4FMeJ https://t.co/XZLqXfAQpR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   More than 2.29 lakh (2,29,999) beneficiaries of age group 18-44 vaccinated in last 24 hours.  More than 6 lakh total vaccine doses administered to 18-44 age group till now.  #LargestVaccinationDrive #We4Vaccine https://t.co/WZCXmmLplG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona  Is CT scan required in mild #COVID19 cases  There is no use of a CT scan if you have mild #Covid.   1 #CTScan = 300-400 Chest X-rays!  With frequent CTs, risk of #Cancer in later life increases, for youngsters : Dr. Randeep Guleria, Director, AIIMS https://t.co/moqxBtzJjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrakashJavdekar: DRDO to install five Medical Oxygen Plants in Delhi  Haryana in the first week of May.  The equipment arrived at AIIM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:      #COVID19        .  #Unite2FightCorona #StayHomeStaySafe #StaySafeStayHealthy https://t.co/6e5ZFvSaN4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrakashJavdekar: Some facts related to Doses of #Covishield and #Covaxin ordered by GoI.  #LargestVaccineDrive https://t.co/6eN16ZbMbT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   India's Cumulative Vaccination Coverage: (As on 04th May, 2021, 08:00 am)   More than 15.89 crore doses administered  More than 4 Lakh beneficiaries of age group vaccinated in phase-3 of the world's #LargestVaccinationDrive  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/bvvLqZ3N6i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   Government of India has so far provided more than 16.69 crore vaccine doses to States/UTs Free of Cost (As on 4th May, 2021, 8:00 am)   Over 48 Lakh doses, in addition, will be received by the states/UTs in the next 3 days  #We4Vaccine #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/HNYXmS0r2H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona  #COVID19 Vaccination   I have recovered from #COVID19, when can I get vaccinated  A recovered #COVID19 patient should wait for at least 4 Weeks before getting vaccinated  Watch this video to know more  #LargestVaccinationDrive #We4Vaccine  @PIB_India https://t.co/EGMpDbkfdR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ICMRDELHI:     -        . @MoHFW_INDIA @PIB_India @COVIDNewsByMIB @M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   #COVID19  ,         ,                ()                   #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/szfuy4KASJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   The two leaders discussed the #COVID19 situation and the successful partnership on #Vaccines.  PM @narendramodi thanked for the prompt medical assistance provided by the #UK in the wake of the severe #SecondWave of #COVID19 in India.  https://t.co/rLGdFPeWyQ https://t.co/4u1jHDhFWE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   Installation of 2 Medical Oxygen Plants (funded by #PMCARES) has begun at war-footing at #AIIMS and RML hospital in New Delhi .   Will start supplying oxygen to patients by tomorrow evening.  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/xhwVHKR8Zv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   Prime Minister @narendramodi and the PM of UK @BorisJohnson held a Virtual Summit today.  Leaders discussed #COVID19 situation  ongoing cooperation in fight against the pandemic.  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/8qkcWee2Q3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MEAIndia:  PM @narendramodi and the PM of UK @BorisJohnson held a Virtual Summit today.  Leaders discussed Covid19 situation  ongo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   @DRDO_India to install five medical #oxygen plants in Delhi  Haryana  Equipment arrives at AIIMS  RML Hospitals in New Delhi  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe   Details: https://t.co/TZJn48wKBu https://t.co/cdx2DwAHl4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona  The tankers from #UAE with 140MT #LiquidMedicalOxygen transported from Gujarat via #OxygenExpress will reach Delhi tonight.  #Unite2FightCorona   @MoHFW_INDIA @drharshvardhan @PiyushGoyal @MEAIndia @DDNewslive @CMODelhi @IndembAbuDhabi  https://t.co/ATcyvWTdqK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona   Union Government did not waste time in effective allocation  distribution of #COVID19 relief material  Coordination Cell in @MoHFW_INDIA started working from 26th April 2021  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe   Details: https://t.co/ortT9q0CFq https://t.co/KpCmyzV1VS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   The standard operating procedure for allocations taken out by the @MoHFW_INDIA on 2nd May 2021  Based on the above criteria and principles, 24 categories of items numbering nearly 40 lakhs have been distributed to 86 Institutions in different states. https://t.co/nq7OOyylBJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   The materials are being given by countries due to the immediate and urgent requirements in different parts of the country. This help is over and above what Govt of India is already providing, and is thus an additionality for the states and UTs.  #StaySafe https://t.co/de6KJdHYIG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  The steps taken for expeditious clearance on fast track basis are as follows  A cell was created in the @MoHFW_INDIA to coordinate the receipt and allocation of foreign #COVID relief material as grants, aid donations.  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/s1GszXLdNJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Indian customs is sensitive to the need for availability of #COVID related imports including #Oxygen and related equipment etc.  The steps taken for expeditious clearance on fast track basis are as follows  #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/nMEzfxVGZl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBMumbai: Never do it!  Some #COVID19 patients have a tendency to copy-paste their medical prescription  give it to relatives!  Takin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:                         ,  ,  ,                @COVIDNewsByMIB     #We4Vaccine #StaySafe https://t.co/VUmxh2eXKr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:      !                        ...  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe  #StayHome https://t.co/lnzK3yPj96]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIBFactCheck: A message claims that people can register for #COVID19Vaccination by downloading a mobile application through the given l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CoronaFacts:  Can Thermal Scanners detect #COVID19 infected people   No, thermal scanners don't detect #COVID infected people. They just detect body temperature.  #MythBuster #IndiaFightsCorona #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/6OILV4ndFI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CoronaFacts:  Myth:- It is not safe to take #COVID19Vaccine during menstruation   Fact:- Menstruation has no effect on COVID-19 Vaccine efficacy.  #MythBuster  #IndiaFightsCorona #LargestVaccinationDrive https://t.co/EBylkQiLqA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoHFW_INDIA: ,                       ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Effective Allocation by Govt of India of #COVID19 supplies received from Global Community for fight against Global Pandemic  Medical Infrastructure of 38 Institutions across 31 States/UTs strengthened  Details: https://t.co/ntqtY6mXmp  #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/XUFAxWombl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Threefold increase in production of #Remdesivir in the country  will soon be able to meet growing demand. - Minister of State @mansukhmandviya  Number of plants producing Remdesivir also triples  Details:https://t.co/vhRULHzB4U  #Unite2FightCorona  #StaySafe https://t.co/p6KgciGrWf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Hum paanch bachayen #COVID se   Wearing mask  Physical distance  Staying at home  Washing/ sanitising hands  Getting vaccinated   #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe  #StayHome https://t.co/w2vYRrK5gx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Maintain #COVID Appropriate Behaviour  Do Not lower your guard!  Wear Double Masks Wash Hands with Soap Often Keep Your Home Well Ventilated  Maintain #PhysicalDistancing   #Unite2FightCorona #StaySafe https://t.co/WQBu9vnJv8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoHFW_INDIA: Lets create a safe environment for the people around us by following simple COVID Appropriate Behaviours, everytime. Be c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  Steady Reduction in Daily New Cases (As on 4th May, 2021, till 8:00 AM)  #Unite2FightCorona  #StayHomeStaySafeSaveLives https://t.co/dRfYciiEaP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:   Follow #COVIDAppropriateBehaviour to #StaySafe    Always wear face mask Properly   Maintain 2 Gaz Doori...  Sanitize/Wash hands frequently   Safai Bhi, Dawai Bhi, Kadai Bhi... Jeetenge Corona se Ladai Bhi...  #Unite2FightCorona #We4Vaccine https://t.co/1tLxyDE0YZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PIB_India: 5th series of consignments carrying 545 #OxygenConcentrators from the US arrived in #India today morning  https://t.co/Qzk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#IndiaFightsCorona:  #COVID19 Labs in India (As on May 03, 2021)  #StaySafe #Unite2FightCorona https://t.co/I4lHnouMyU]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>