<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotia is reporting two deaths related to COVID-19. Two people with families, friends and neighbours.   Please protect yourself and the people in your community by doing what you can to limit the spread of COVID-19. https://t.co/apQrFnZNAS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deux dcs, 153 nouveaux cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/OOGuJ40SdY https://t.co/2JLh5Ce23K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two Deaths, 153 New Cases of COVID-19 https://t.co/5dfua0KR41 https://t.co/N0hRSK3Utu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang will provide a #COVID19NS update today at 3 p.m., available on Facebook Live, YouTube and at https://t.co/MsTOQ7V2y5. https://t.co/y5RMfq5ARN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Supports for Business Available Soon https://t.co/VGLZ49KY9Q https://t.co/BUPooocl03]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@NS_InclGrowth Minister Labi Kousoulis will provide an update on government's support for businesses today, May 4, at 11:30 a.m.  Watch on Facebook Live, YouTube or at https://t.co/nEw03nW7Gk. https://t.co/kOXYgammAM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The following people should continue to book COVID-19 tests at https://t.co/dcM8YjDmbB    anyone with symptoms  anyone who has been notified that they are a close contact of a known case  anyone who was at an exposure location  anyone who has travelled outside NS/PEI/NL https://t.co/ICmXaz70oJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: A friendly reminder that if you have an appointment at a vaccine clinic, you must go alone unless you need support due to phy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Following your test, you will receive a text with your negative result. Please do not share the text number you receive upon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La Nouvelle-cosse annonce 146 cas de COVID-19 aujourdhui, 3 mai. Il y a en tout 943 cas actifs dans la province.   Pour plus dinformation, lisez le communiqu : https://t.co/Nqicdgq9Qb https://t.co/3ishURhYEB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotia is announcing 146 cases of COVID-19 today, May 3. There are a total of 943 active cases in the province.  For more, read the news release: https://t.co/LAKmvr0DJD https://t.co/NUtOS4uwba]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rapid testing is encouraged for people who:   are 16+  do not have symptoms  have not travelled  have not visited a potential exposure location  have not been in contact with someone who has tested positive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DYK: Rapid tests are different from the COVID-19 tests you book online? Rapid tests are completed at drop-in pop-up locations and do not add to the @HealthNS laboratory's workload.  For pop-up site locations and dates, click here: https://t.co/pLmJrW5auj https://t.co/E63Ctt7jHs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les gens de 50  54 ans peuvent maintenant recevoir un vaccin contre la COVID-19; une premire clinique de vaccination au volant verra le jour https://t.co/CEM9UnLWas https://t.co/idp17rDBs9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People Aged 50 to 54 Now Eligible for COVID-19 Vaccines; First Drive-Thru Clinic https://t.co/3GJ6wyw7Cr https://t.co/plBAND9mtz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang will provide a #COVID19NS update today at 3 p.m., available on Facebook Live, YouTube and at https://t.co/MsTOQ7V2y5. https://t.co/bKRBAZiPfU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La Nouvelle-cosse annonce 133 cas de COVID-19 aujourdhui, 2 mai. Il y a en tout 822 cas actifs dans la province.  Pour plus dinformation, lisez le communiqu : https://t.co/gPJ54sN1XB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotia is announcing 133 cases of COVID-19 today, May 2. There are a total of 822 active cases in the province.  For more, read the news release: https://t.co/UD37VJbrGt https://t.co/ZugszPnjS7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ToddGillard Hi, Dr. Strang addressed this. He suggested you look for vaccine within your area first, but travelling for vaccine, if necessary, would be considered essential.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: ** NEW: The pop-up testing site at Centre 200, Sydney will also be open Sunday, May 2: 12 p.m. to 4 p.m.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La Nouvelle-cosse annonce 148 cas de COVID-19 aujourdhui, 1er mai 2021. Il y a en tout 713 cas actifs dans la province.  Pour plus dinformation, lisez le communiqu : https://t.co/bKOTGVQOzP https://t.co/p2poAorq7L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotia is announcing 148 cases of COVID-19 today, May 1, 2021. There are a total of 713 active cases in the province.  For more, read the news release: https://t.co/5Acem3napY https://t.co/qXYVtdMRkh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Examples of non-essential travel are shopping for non-essentials, social events, family visits, or going to a beach or park outside of your community.   By staying apart, we can protect each other. Stay close to home. https://t.co/G0skWLZ78B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NS_Museum: Take a deep breath. We can do this.  https://t.co/wG2EilHCeK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: If you do not fall under one of those categories and have an upcoming appointment booked, please cancel it using the link in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Pop-up, rapid #COVID19 testing is available this weekend for people who: -- are over 16 years of age -- do NOT have symptoms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nseducation: Students in grades 7-12 can access free one-on-one online mathematics tutoring sessions at NS Homework Hub. Extended hours]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Due to the increased number of COVID-19 cases in in the province and work associated with the COVID response, Nova Scotia Hea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its critical that we do everything we can now to protect each other, our health-care system and our vaccine rollout program in the days and weeks ahead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotians: if there was ever a time to stand together this is it.    Stay home. Follow the restrictions and make safe choices to limit your contacts and movement. https://t.co/nFXqitkwQp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For people who cant get to a food bank or local food support program, Feed Nova Scotias COVID-19 Food Box program is available. Call 211 weekdays between 8am and 8pm to see if this program is a good fit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Need help? Looking for community resources? Visit https://t.co/bh3wXae5Gq for information on food banks, local food support programs, mental health and addiction services, financial assistance, and more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The following people can and should continue to book COVID-19 tests:  -- anyone with symptoms -- anyone who has been notified that they are a close contact of a known case -- anyone who has been at an exposure location -- anyone who has travelled outside NS, PEI and NL https://t.co/XJtZAFyake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Soixante-sept nouveaux cas de COVID-19, changements relatifs aux tests de dpistage https://t.co/R3mR2WAYAi https://t.co/kTV6rYz34v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plan de vaccination sur la bonne voie, plus de 300 000 doses administres https://t.co/EuW70jgyaQ https://t.co/aenFikhvga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine Plan on Track, Tops 300,000 Doses https://t.co/rowlOP1Dq0 https://t.co/RKPZMpiASS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sixty-seven New Cases of COVID-19, Testing Changes https://t.co/MFyrhZPYgD https://t.co/QIhmUewSDE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Chair Appointed to Forestry Innovation Transition Trust https://t.co/WLIHJfgNCN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Pop-up, rapid #COVID19 testing is offered to people who: - Are over 16 years of age - do NOT have symptoms - have not travell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read this thread from @NSLAE to learn about the restrictions around travel for post-secondary education. https://t.co/1iQ8s0G42p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Highway 104 Twinning Project Update https://t.co/wUVp59bKJg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weekly Traffic Advisories https://t.co/LLaTU6MMaR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Le vaccin dAstraZeneca maintenant offert aux gens de 40  54 ans https://t.co/TomL8Ilt2p https://t.co/ye5GW30fKw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People Aged 40 to 54 Now Eligible to Book AstraZeneca Vaccine https://t.co/IbptPBhc2C https://t.co/LjlpHLVZQK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang will provide a #COVID19NS update today at 2 p.m., available on Facebook Live, YouTube and at https://t.co/MsTOQ7V2y5. https://t.co/s2cA1xGfpO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nseducation: Nova Scotias Child Care Subsidy helps eligible families, with children 12 and under, pay for a portion of child care fees]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nseducation: To support workers who require child care in order to continue working, Nova Scotias regulated child-care centres and lic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For mental health resources, go to https://t.co/bYgWKBvbhj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay in your community, do only what is essential, and take care of the people around you, including yourself.  We will move forward together.  For details on COVID-19 restrictions in your area, visit https://t.co/znaLcqkeyk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The next two weeks are a critical time in Nova Scotia as we fight the third wave of COVID-19.   The decisions you make can have a huge impact, so please make the right ones. https://t.co/mtnNqNKGoY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Visiting a primary assessment centre for a #COVID19 test? Heres a few things to keep in mind. Please make sure you have your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Soixante-dix nouveaux cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/z7mxgyioJK https://t.co/98OBZxXZlg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seventy New Cases of COVID-19 https://t.co/1IXpQ1lDFc https://t.co/6b9HRBkhY4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficeofANSA: A COVID-19 Testing Clinic is open for residents of East Preston on Thursday, April 29  Friday, April 30 at the East Pres]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang will provide daily updates this week.  Briefings will be held: -- today, April 29, at 3 p.m. -- Friday, April 30, at 1 p.m.   You can watch on Facebook Live, YouTube, or at https://t.co/nEw03nW7Gk. https://t.co/jUolV5zDFu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimMacgillivray Hello! It will become available tomorrow (Friday). There will be more information today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ouverture continue des centres de garde denfants et aide financire du gouvernement provincial accorde  ces centres pendant le confinement https://t.co/10ArJVNuvW https://t.co/ZyXudqd40N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Child Care Centres Remain Open, Receive Financial Support from Province During Shutdown https://t.co/FEyHRd7jRn https://t.co/CzsX7pVAMT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Frontline workers can text FRONTLINE to 741741   And all Nova Scotians can call the Mental Health Crisis Line at 1-888-429-8167  For more information and resources, visit https://t.co/bYgWKBvbhj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Young people can text CONNECT to 686868 or call the Kids Help Phone at 1-800-668-6868   Adults can text NSSTRONG to 741741   Post-secondary students can text GOOD2TALKNS to 686868 or call 1-833-292-3698]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this third wave of COVID-19 in Nova Scotia, you might be feeling anxious or uneasy. It is normal to feel that way during uncertain times. As you check on those around you, make sure to check on yourself. Supports are available. https://t.co/TiHhhTk52B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Soixante-quinze nouveaux cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/dDzWvLJAYn https://t.co/MpzCrfUiWF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seventy-five New Cases of COVID-19 https://t.co/ArIDcml8EY https://t.co/umwEFhoJZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NS_TAT: Due to the increasing cases of COVID-19, road tests are suspended for two weeks, starting April 28, 2021. Road tests that were]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nshealth: Choose the right type of test. Only book a symptomatic test if you have symptoms.  If you have no symptoms, you must book an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BCC_NS: COVID-19 Testing In The Preston Township. COVID-19 cases have been increasing in HRM. Public Health is working diligently to ke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Yarmouth--a new COVID primary assessment centre is up and running at Yarmouth Mariner Centre BY APPOINTMENT ONLY. Open to bot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Rapid testing in Sydney moves to a new location for Wednesday, Apr. 28:  Centre 200, 481 George St, from 11 a.m. to 7 p.m.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: In Halifax/Dartmouth rapid testing available Wednesday, Apr. 28 from noon to 7 pm at these sites: -East Dartmouth Community C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang will provide daily updates this week.  Briefings will be held: -- today, April 28, at 3 p.m. -- Thursday, April 29, at 3 p.m. -- Friday, April 30, at 1 p.m.   You can watch on Facebook Live, YouTube, or at https://t.co/nEw03nW7Gk. https://t.co/roJKoOh1O0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nova Scotians Honour Workers and Families on Day of Mourning https://t.co/Al0VhePzja https://t.co/Xd3bAMgY8K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Une nouvelle cole signale un cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/YsF5DhL6ZM https://t.co/GKxK3VmnxL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One New School Reports COVID-19 Case https://t.co/IwcuY7j4n5 https://t.co/YBa9lJ9oQC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nouvelles restrictions pour toute la province https://t.co/Dcq7xgADPL https://t.co/aNQ3nAgseF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Restrictions For Entire Province https://t.co/gjt9ru2lQZ https://t.co/gqvVjylzpw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are experiencing technical difficulties with Facebook Live. You can watch the briefing on YouTube at https://t.co/MEzJULDt2Y.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are experiencing technical difficulties with Facebook Live. You can watch the briefing on YouTube at https://t.co/MEzJULDt2Y. https://t.co/yBJT6sVv5u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PLEASE NOTE: Todays briefing has been rescheduled to 4 p.m. https://t.co/zGj3ggDKsN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quatre-vingt-seize nouveaux cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/NoQmC6l3Og https://t.co/3rxItaKoqM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ninety-six New Cases of COVID-19 https://t.co/GSUTQGOge4 https://t.co/IqiFBtAbyZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang, Nova Scotia's chief medical officer of health, will provide an update today, April 27, at 3:30 p.m. https://t.co/5B1IZpV1gH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NSLAE: To help protect our communities  slow the spread of COVID-19 the NS Chief Medical Officer of Health is encouraging everyone in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trois nouvelles coles signalent des cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/YAqs0WsguW https://t.co/hT38N9DqVy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three New Schools Report COVID-19 Cases https://t.co/e4IZcW7Qc6 https://t.co/x01tT4HHn6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HealthNS: Please do not leave your community to get a COVID test. We recommend people use their judgment about what their community is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nseducation: All public schools in Halifax Regional Municipality (HRM) and surrounding areas will close Tuesday, April 27, and move to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les gens de 55  59 ans peuvent maintenant recevoir les vaccins de Pfizer et de Moderna contre la COVID-19 https://t.co/xbVeqARres https://t.co/DrzoZWjfeJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People 55 to 59 Now Eligible to Book Pfizer and Moderna COVID-19 Vaccines https://t.co/VLHCPsfN1l https://t.co/GFR6EgtkEO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Des restrictions sont ajoutes partout en Nouvelle-cosse https://t.co/ker4ctLG1L https://t.co/n8jc1TIlRq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Restrictions Added Across Nova Scotia https://t.co/3Jp9T9mxAR https://t.co/BMITPXtC01]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Soixante-six nouveaux cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/eRq3gh3ele https://t.co/T5ls15IyVa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sixty-six New Cases of COVID-19 https://t.co/qzVCxIPUXR https://t.co/fc8G6Ye0qV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adoption de lapprentissage en ligne par les coles de la Municipalit rgionale dHalifax https://t.co/sZ0ycWPQ2y https://t.co/AhrX4YeyGK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HRM Schools Move to At-Home Learning https://t.co/a9iRHopT0g https://t.co/nwlZscjqM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nshealth: Another wave is upon us. But waves have crashed on our shores before, and we have always found a way forward. We know what to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Application Dates for Annual Cape Breton Moose Hunt https://t.co/RdtSwxli1y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier Iain Rankin and Dr. Robert Strang will provide a #COVID19NS update today at 3 p.m., available on Facebook Live, YouTube and at https://t.co/MsTOQ7V2y5. https://t.co/RnxzcRISwa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Neuf nouvelles coles signalent des cas de COVID-19 https://t.co/ijnteX6Duw https://t.co/LOqLy4yYqW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nine New Schools Report COVID-19 Cases https://t.co/19KRwu0Zrb https://t.co/3S6xHh31JF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rduction de la taille des rassemblements  lextrieur dHalifax, imposition damendes plus leves https://t.co/JiVxqBHIDL https://t.co/Hy1hWD6A3A]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>