<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@WHO #AskWHO waiting for your response... I was in the session today as well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CareemPAK are you guys in your senses? You always come up with a stupid controversial thing every now and then  please be rational while being innovative  #BreakingNews #Pakistan #careem #marketing https://t.co/4yLjaSaUvU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WHO #AskWHO two basic questions, 1 - How Covid Vaccine exactly works? Please share complete step by step process. 2 - What are the chances in percentage of not having Covid again after getting vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In vogue right now             " " #COVIDEmergency #COVID19 #Pakistan https://t.co/dQeSIOpoSl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[              https://t.co/VyorSM4hGp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yaar Ramiz Bhai total 2 century ki hain ap nay, ap tu rehnay he dain  #achasorry @yousaf1788  https://t.co/pPOWuY3MRK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mailtoali89: @fahadmustafa26 why you, your guests and general public in your show first wear face masks and practice social distancing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bairstoe or Buttler k baad hazir hai Rizwan or Sarfaraz  DFM who took this decision, DURR FITAY MU  https://t.co/ZJAuLvlDYW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the tweet     #pakistanstandwithindia https://t.co/AdiZWtsA8W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[         This is the tweet    #pakistanstandwithindia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are such a nation that if Satan will come to us and say that God did injustice to me, we will create a hashtag #justiceforsatan  https://t.co/Alultn3Mqh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are such a nation that if Satan will come to us and say that God did injustice to me, we will create a hashtag #justiceforsatan #Covid_19 #coronavirus #EndiaSaySorryToKashmir https://t.co/RnzAYXoXpp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With these SOPs, poor are going to die anyways  this isn't practical at all. Poor is only a word for the people brain storming these policies I'm afraid  https://t.co/m2WN0oiutV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heads up @TheRealPCB @babarazam258 It can happen to any team even us  love for you all and 3rd would be intereating ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zzefusion Our laws unfortunately force us to find an illegal way so that the law makers can have their share instead of the Govt. Alas!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive Wasim Bhai that never deserved a response ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalSNI: Every #smartphone must be protected from #cyberattacks. Get 50% additional off this #Ramzan on "#Bitdefender Mobile Security]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If American Shooter / If Muslim Terrorist  #AllLivesMatter #Indianapolis #HumanRightsViolations https://t.co/dQyST7VxNv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@city42 please correct your Ramzan Clock and apologize from the people for false timings.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive Wasim Bhai ye tu genuine lahoriyon wali empathy hai ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive @babarazam258 Wasim Bhai series win abhi confirmed nahi  deleted bhi perh lia tha tweet ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look at #fakharzaman strike rate  what a win #BabarAzam #PAKvSA #SAvPAK #No1ODIBatsman https://t.co/VblTifXnDS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is Babar Azam for you  #Respect #BabarAzam #PAKvSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryamNSharif I can feel you pain ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realshoaibmalik @MirzaSania @wasimakramlive wasim bhai you are such a super leader, Twitter pay bhi team ap k naqs-e-qadam pay hai  @realshoaibmalik Maafi murshad  and happy to you to your Bay-Gham ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Both my parents got vaccinated and Alhamdulillah no side effects observed, please encourage your elders to get it asap and get them registered immediately if not done yet  #COVIDVaccination #COVID19 #COVID19 #coronavirus #Coronaviruspakistan @UsmanAKBuzdar @Dr_YasminRashid https://t.co/CnF5tNX6NB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SyedaNosheenPK @MaryamNSharif Apa he keh dia hai  hun gayi seat ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just for fun  although if it is the actual case, still #IK is better  #fun #PMIK https://t.co/xhozzxFlgQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the change Imran Khan promised. By-election were never meant to be lost by the sitting government. Congratulations #patwario #NA75Daska]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharmilafaruqi @KElectricPk Are you not the part of Sindh government?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No Caption #PAKvSA #SAvsPAK #Pakistan #sarfaraz https://t.co/5IvJApqhWk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back to Back centuries by #fakharzaman  #PAKvsSA #Pakistan #savspak https://t.co/x9QgfIVtlZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In your face  @QuinnyDeKock69 #PAKvsSA #Pakistan #fakharzaman  https://t.co/ToYD1tWi5a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@QuinnyDeKock69 you won't be able to stop @FakharZamanLive today or you want to try any thing MORE UGLY? #moron #cheater #PAKvsSA #savspak #3rdODI #fakharzaman #QuintondeKock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalSNI: #Smartphones without proper #cyber protection are prone to data breach by #cyberattacks. We are offering 50% additional off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamShaniera @wasimakramlive bhai jaan not missing you a bit, this is what I felt at least, keep a check on him ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryamNSharif #achasorry ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryamNSharif Baaji definition tu perh leni thi   Brethren is a fancy plural form of "brother" and is most often used in religious contexts. ... Though it literally means "brothers," brethren frequently refers to members of the same religious community.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharmilafaruqi Ap ki aj kal BAD LUCK he kharab hai ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmbassadorNawaf #skardu  https://t.co/brS6yitCRL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharmilafaruqi She seems to be the physically ZINDA version of bhutto ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The only real run scoring machine #Pakistan ever had. #babar  #PAKvSA https://t.co/FEkgABoE4K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aamir_ibrahim01: We need a smartphone in every hand for a smart nation. Applaud the efforts  of Muzaffar Paracha n @AirlinkALC 2 turn t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cybersecurity is the current and future biggest threat. To avoid it for less than a rupee per day is to be considered as blessing. Go get it guys    #Bitdefender #Pakistan #smartphones #DataProtection #Digital #Jazz #digitalpakistan https://t.co/ffHnizKAtu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryamNSharif https://t.co/Y19sWDFpOQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryamNSharif @SyedaNosheenPK https://t.co/Knkz3qE4PQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive Or un world's best bowler main ap BEST that  magician you were, magician you are on #Twitter  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive Wasim Bhai ap bhi na  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillGates @gatesfoundation It's time to pay back to the world Sir. You have been blessed with trillions, you can easily get the whole world vaccinated on your own. Do it and get much needed prayers this time around, got so much money already. #COVID19 #coronavirus #BillGates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get it, its not even a rupee per day and worth buying because One #cyberattack and all you private data can be compromised. #cybersecurity #Pakistan #Coronaviruspakistan #cybercrime #PAKvSA #DataProtection #BreakingNews #smartphones #android https://t.co/a5qHIqH9dx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@falamb3 @cricket_wallah That level of acquaintance ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SHABAZGIL Dr. sb yeh tu ap NS ko bhi kaha kertay thay ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamshafaatali Baba Gee jugtain kerna or nakal utarna ap ka kaam hai wohi kerain...oh Acha ap bhi paisay bananay walon main a he gaye hain na morning time main ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@manahil__saeed @SAfridiOfficial You must be in the air and will stay there for a very long time for sure ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SAfridiOfficial @manahil__saeed Lala baat tu sahi ki hai lerki nahi, however  your bowling excite the cricketing fans more...that drift ufff ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamShaniera Bhabhi tusi pai jaan day naal reh reh k Jango honday ja rahay ho ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive Wasim Bhai matlab ye baat bhi public   tusi waqai champion ho, Uper say Jango Lahori ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deaths are decreasing Alhamdulillah  #covid19 is spreading dangerously? #lockdown #Pakistan #lahore https://t.co/P7FMA1rYcF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@F1 Bad Luck Max]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[              #MaryamNawaz #PDM https://t.co/4loRpLggcN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi Ap ki tareef? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharmilafaruqi https://t.co/ELAsSzoBGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@falamb3 We need people like you Sir. A genuine by heart true ambassador to our home land you are  more power to you  wish to meet you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArmeenaRK Weren't you feeling same before that as well?  #achasorry ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HamidMirPAK Hamid bhai hum say puch rahay hain ya apna weham door ker rahay hain  #achasorry ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi        #PDMTabahDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[       #RIP_PDM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PDM ki haqeeqat  #PDMLongMarch #FazalurRehman #AsifAliZardari #MaryamNawaz https://t.co/4ufp0QoP5a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fawadchaudhry:       https://t.co/yALwRMD5U5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[      #RIP_PDM #PDM #PDMTabahDe #PDMLongMarch #Zardari #PrimeMinisterImranKhan  https://t.co/VCz6c60CIU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[       #RIP_PDM #PDMTabahDe #PDM #PMIK #PrimeMinisterImranKhan  https://t.co/UETfMyBHZN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yaar kitna maza anay wala hai  #RIP_PDM #PDM #PDMTabahDe #Pakistan #PDMLongMarch #PMIK  https://t.co/0aAdHzvsv7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sarkon pay ghaseetnay wali PARCHI nikal lain chachu  #RIP_PDM #PDMTabahDe #Zardari https://t.co/5zahPV9DWY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Geo News Lifafiz Crying  Trying to make a sense out of #AsifZardari statements #PDMTabahDe ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hahahahahahahaha bus Itni he thi #PDM #PDMTabahDe https://t.co/Wmgvwnlx3l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RIP #PDM  #PDMTabahDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It made me laugh like anything  how #Creative #BreakingNews #artist https://t.co/PDqK2HdVit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LewisHamilton Hey Man! Coincidentally you've won 11 races each in 2018/2019/2020. Has it become your lucky number?  #F1 #F1Testing #MercedesAMGF1 #lewishamilton #FormulaOne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi Or ap ko buhat khushi hoi ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Internet working at your end? This result is of a 15 MBPS connection  https://t.co/HlisI521Dx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @haidersays:                       ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FaisalJavedKhan @iqrarulhassan Faisal Bhai waisay seat belt kyon nahi pehni thi ?  Masoomana sawal ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FaisalJavedKhan I just hope that it wasn't planted ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharmilafaruqi O bibi ye bilawal or Mariyam nahi hain, her jaga defend nahi kerna hota... Parhay likhay JAHIL... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sophwebsterxx @LewisHamilton @LewisHamilton you are going to get competition in 2021, best of luck ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Tallal_MNA  https://t.co/6qnl9SvENe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[48 vs 42  non political image  #Senate #SenateElection2021 #SenateElections2021 #SenateElections https://t.co/vmtAUTNueA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi  https://t.co/PD2RZ0IPMn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abhi mujhe SIYASAT nahi ati  #Senate #SenateChairman #SadiqSanjrani #ImranKhan #PMIK #PTIGovernment #MaryamNawaz https://t.co/0EC92HxnC7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaryamNSharif https://t.co/bo77pGb1hA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shoaib100mph Shoaib Bhai #TikTok ban ho gayi nahi tu is video pay likes baray anay thay ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi You are one of the top BLACK stains on the name of Journalism. I mean being biased can be more decent. #witch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wasimakramlive Wasim Bhai PM bhi kia kerain yaar her baat he public I mean ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kaisa diya phir bachon? Chalo Ab sab PAWRI kertay hain  #pawrihoraihai #Shafqatmehmood #schoolsclosed #SpringBreak #COVID19 #Pakistan #Lahore #punjab https://t.co/lSjy3bRYLF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schools on spring holidays in Lahore, Faisalab and few other cities in Punjab  KPK... #Shafqatmehmood #SpringBreak #schoolsclosed #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFarooqi Aj k paisay wapis kernay perain gay jo Imran Khan k khilaf bolnay k advance pakray hoay hain ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 2012 MNS stood as lawyer himself against PPP PM Yousaf Raza Gilani, whom he nominated today as his candidate for Chairman Senate. We've seen it all, Thank you @ImranKhanPTI #SenateElection2021 #SenateElections2021 #ImranKhan #MeraJismMeriMarzi https://t.co/seejUT9whD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sanabucha ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaminaAli_Alii You've won the tweet competition today with a margin  #epic]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>