<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The number of U.S. births in 2020 fell 4% from 2019, the lowest level since 1979. https://t.co/g9OFyQIVzn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyundai is recalling over 390,000 vehicles in the U.S. and Canada for problems that can cause engine fires. https://t.co/CS96iuyNft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Somebody had to provide it and I thought, 'Why not me?'" https://t.co/gZ0j2nBolx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Our health has become politicized," one mayor says. https://t.co/U6aqWgPXov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Authorities in India open the country's first drive-in vaccination facility in a bid to speed up rollout in COVID-hit Mumbai. https://t.co/Ps9UU34YRI https://t.co/XAItVBt2Kj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May 5, 2021, marks Mom's Equal Pay Day, or how far into the year the average working mom has to work to earn what fathers earned last year alone. https://t.co/ZQKeBHDqG8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Navy SEAL Eddie Gallagher, who was found not guilty of the charge of murder in the death of a young Islamic State detainee in Iraq in 2017, claims that he and other SEALs intended for the detainee to die. https://t.co/8xhVpBukny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Babies born to Black women in the U.S. have two times the infant mortality rate of babies born to non-Hispanic white women, according to the Department of Health and Human Services' Office of Minority Health. https://t.co/kEbLJ4NAE7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 5-year-old girl in Missouri did not have to look far to find a perfect match for the kidney she needed after being on dialysis for more than four years. https://t.co/pofuzkASaR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vice Pres. Kamala Harris responds to Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis' suspension of all local COVID-19 emergency orders, telling @ABC that any COVID protocols must be guided by the public health experts, period. https://t.co/Y3YdtCdsVH https://t.co/w8wniDCWvb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Derek Chauvin's legal team files motion in Minneapolis court requesting new trial on multiple grounds, including jury misconduct. https://t.co/igU75EwsdD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle is adding a new role to her resume in her post-royal life: children's book author. https://t.co/E2whw8iZ2L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Acting Metropolitan Police Chief Robert Contee called the drag-racing incident "embarrassing." https://t.co/0Ko6CMEvNd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pres. Biden gives COVID update:  - 220 million vaccine shots given as of last week - Over 105 million Americans fully vaccinated - 70% of seniors fully vaccinated - Cases down in 40 states over last two weeks - Deaths down over 80% among seniors.  https://t.co/unRy7V1JqF https://t.co/CVQ38j6QHZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two founders of a restaurant in San Diego are struggling to hire enough staff to stay open lateso they're offering an incentive. https://t.co/5SyANDzRmS https://t.co/N06utjEhJW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 infections and deaths are mounting with alarming speed in India with no end in sight to the crisis. https://t.co/knJIsOVFNs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pres. Biden gives COVID update:  - 220 million vaccine shots given as of last week - Over 105 million Americans fully vaccinated - 70% of seniors fully vaccinated - Cases down in 40 states over last two weeks - Deaths down over 80% among seniors.  https://t.co/IrDEm4EASc https://t.co/GmLnEIfMGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most of the contiguous U.S. experienced a warming trend over the last 30 years, NOAA says.   "The data is clearly showing the U.S. climate is changing." https://t.co/OOVNzBJZRU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britney Spears doesn't mince words about having her life repeatedly put under a microscope. https://t.co/lnC9kVZXYk https://t.co/3BNEaN8Iq2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Texas lawyer known as the DWI Dude has been sentenced to more than 15 years in federal prison for falsely promising Colombian drug traffickers hed get their charges reduced in exchange for cash. https://t.co/a7E5wMgKfV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billie Eilish was just two days away from headlining Madison Square Garden before she had to cancel because of the pandemic last year.  Now she's returning to New York City as one of the headliners of the Governors Ball Music Festival. https://t.co/vr0ygb08zl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pres. Biden says that if FDA approves vaccine for those 12-15 years old, "we are ready to move immediately," including shipping vaccines to pediatricians. https://t.co/gexeIy4QRj https://t.co/ldbyNVHmEy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BEARS BREAKING IN: Bears in Avon, Connecticut, were caught on camera opening the doors of a parked car and climbing in. https://t.co/72296OvXJT https://t.co/aqh3YLYBwH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials believe the woman stayed in the area by choice. https://t.co/T3aRJu3hAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The Army keeps trying to protect this name and I want to understand why," Mayra Guilln said of her sister Vanessa's harasser. https://t.co/CFR3hmBQs7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Truck drivers blocked access roads to Bogota, Colombia, as demonstrations against Colombian President Ivan Duque's economic policies resumed despite the government's withdrawal of a controversial tax reform proposal. https://t.co/GrKpvl3vc6 https://t.co/s1PB2BTz3K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I met her, and I saw a lot of myself in her. Once she trusted me, we just clicked." https://t.co/CYkZNLTUhL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police say a good Samaritan who jumped off a Maryland bridge to save a young child wants to remain anonymous despite being a hero. https://t.co/B97JmMODzH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[: ON THIS DAY: In 1961, the first group of Freedom Riders left Washington, D.C. to challenge racial segregation on interstate buses and in bus terminals. https://t.co/5fhj3FDAZr https://t.co/RKktXpPrah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I think it's really important for brands to design for all women, not just certain sizes or shapes or body types." https://t.co/9SguOenjtI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new mom says didn't know she was 29 weeks pregnant when she boarded the plane. https://t.co/qCpDPFcdCI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 9-year-old boy slipped past his parents and jumped onto the bag conveyor belt as a group of people checked their luggage at Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport. https://t.co/GnHJwQqeYR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCWorldNews: FOREVER HOME: Monyay Paskalides, 19, of Bradenton, Florida, has been adopted by her year-long caseworker after spending m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["There's no stage child, it is just him. It's almost like he's this old soul." https://t.co/u8C2wiPiFp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even as COVID-19 vaccines are rolled out nationwide, one state is reeling from a fourth wave of infections, with hospitalizations surging. Here's why: https://t.co/X4ngghrTq9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not everyone is bummed out by a rainy day. Cincinnati Zoo shared this footage of Fiona the hippo catching raindrops in her mouth. https://t.co/80jtzc1A1A https://t.co/bg1qT6KOxw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Navy SEAL Eddie Gallagher, who was found not guilty of the charge of murder in the death of a young Islamic State detainee in Iraq in 2017, claims that he and other SEALs intended for the detainee to die. https://t.co/HQbJnaxeHM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WELCOME TO THE WORLD: Video provided by the National Park Service shows a recently hatched California condor, the newest member of Pinnacles National Park's condor recovery program. https://t.co/2DjXWqAJL8 https://t.co/rOIKdm1goX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyundai is recalling over 390,000 vehicles in the U.S. and Canada for problems that can cause engine fires. https://t.co/ZlAqHEm9pF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new project aims to create a flexible floor, giving tourists a picture of how the Colosseum would have looked when gladiators fought there. https://t.co/1txI9sN1a6 https://t.co/GjzGxQgpib]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crist was the Republican governor of Florida from 2007 to 2011 before switching his party registration to Independent in 2010.  He became a Democrat in 2012 and has been in Congress representing Florida's 13th Congressional District since 2017. https://t.co/I4domqiMUa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ARMFUL OF LOVE: This dads triplet daughters insisted he make room for each and every one of them with a big welcome-home hug. https://t.co/I95rSfyDXx https://t.co/lmsLq46Y7A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerial footage shows some of the damage south of Dallas, Texas, after an EF-2 tornado with 120 mph winds moved through the area on Monday night. https://t.co/9rLFfq3zoo https://t.co/Rt5gJRchsA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nothing like a prominent life in public service to help your other career as a romance novelist. https://t.co/n3EtIGgqJV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCNewsLive: .@Ginger_Zee has the latest on new climate data for the U.S. from @NOAA.  "This data is like our new census poll. This is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Despite an increasingly vocal chorus of condemnations from the Biden administration and U.S. lawmakers of both parties, El Salvador's president and his allies are pushing ahead with what critics call a power grab. https://t.co/3ToST9kPfX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York City police searching for suspect caught on video attacking an Asian woman with a hammer on a Manhattan street. https://t.co/fuYO5qKp5o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Our health has become politicized," one mayor says. https://t.co/vaX39z1wtk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan's book is about "the special bond between father and sonas seen through a mothers eyes," and is based on a Father's Day poem she wrote to Harry. https://t.co/mk2pWcrp65]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Stiles, deputy chief of staff for Minnesota Attorney General Keith Ellison, said in a statement to @ABC News: "The court has already rejected many of these arguments and the State will vigorously oppose them." https://t.co/V7Nuomt51q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The long delay between signature collection (which ended March 17) and the recall election may take the wind out of Gov. Newsom haters sails.   What you need to know, via @FiveThirtyEight: https://t.co/g9uUqUjXwq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Derek Chauvin's legal team files motion in Minneapolis court requesting new trial on multiple grounds, including jury misconduct. https://t.co/jeV7FuQxpy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Acting Metropolitan Police Chief Robert Contee called the drag-racing incident "embarrassing." https://t.co/EyUmq2wOp2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vice Pres. Kamala Harris responds to Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis' suspension of all local COVID-19 emergency orders, telling @ABC that any COVID protocols must be guided by the public health experts, period. https://t.co/GYMndsCgz8 https://t.co/AVmi3wI93t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A man who fatally shot three people at Jewish sites in Kansas in 2014 has died in prison. https://t.co/qVISTtK93y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TOUGH TECH: British marines trial a jet suit as an innovative method to board ships at sea. https://t.co/nLPorG36FU https://t.co/UTbkIoMwbK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerial footage showed the aftermath of a house explosion and fire in Willesborough, U.K., which injured seven people, two of them seriously.  No immediate information was available regarding the cause. https://t.co/Ghrn4ub7pB https://t.co/T2IAixRsmG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden proclaims May 5 "Missing and Murdered Indigenous Persons Awareness Day."  "I call on all American...to support Tribal governments and Tribal communities' efforts to increase awareness of the issue of missing and murdered American Indians and Alaska Natives." https://t.co/FG9Kfxx9wQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCPolitics: Sen. Mitt Romney defends Liz Cheney as GOP leader Kevin McCarthy signals her days as conference chair could be numbered: ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["To all the women out there struggling with fertility, I feel ya." https://t.co/6N3DWQqr7r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ginger_Zee @NOAA MORE: Most of the contiguous U.S. experienced a warming trend over the last 30 years, NOAA says.   "The data is clearly showing the U.S. climate is changing." https://t.co/qxAYSYBowb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Republican California gubernatorial candidate John Cox greets a 1,000 pound bear at the start of a campaign rally in Sacramento.   Read more on the state's likely recall election: https://t.co/FvhlxurM0L https://t.co/KDvqiTAbQB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Biden administration will begin shifting how it allocates COVID-19 shots to states, moving doses from states with lower demand to those with stronger interest in vaccines. https://t.co/snB4CokKP8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wynn Resorts says it was granted permission by the Nevada Gaming Control Board to amend its occupancy and physical distancing rules because 88% of Wynn employees had been vaccinated as of May 1. https://t.co/1FxZkfGTaE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy announced a "Shot and a Beer program that provides a free glass of beer at participating locations to anyone over 21 who gets their first vaccination dose this month. https://t.co/rDYGgzj4H8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britney Spears doesn't mince words about having her life repeatedly put under a microscope. https://t.co/n5tmzO2fkb https://t.co/S0Nd8LqMWA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TUNE IN: @Ginger_Zee breaks down the new @NOAA data about how most of the U.S. has experienced warming trend over last 30 years.  WATCH LIVE: https://t.co/xR0qyDBuvw https://t.co/thgUV0WqBm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Asked by @karentravers about the next phase of COVID-19 vaccine rollout, Pres. Biden says, "Most people will be convinced by the fact that their failure to get the vaccine may cause other people to get sick and maybe die." https://t.co/65DAtdSQBT https://t.co/AX7wHVJVyQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two founders of a restaurant in San Diego are struggling to hire enough staff to stay open lateso they're offering an incentive. https://t.co/gnG90o7ZX0 https://t.co/GlHbVUFlaX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Texas lawyer known as the DWI Dude has been sentenced to more than 15 years in federal prison for falsely promising Colombian drug traffickers hed get their charges reduced in exchange for cash. https://t.co/zz9ZTJNA2W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCNewsLive: "There are a lot of younger people...who believe they don't need it. Well, I want to be absolutely clear, you do need to g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden announces initiatives "to bring the vaccine to people who are less eager" to get vaccinated.  "There are millions of Americans who just need a little bit of encouragement to get the shot."  Read more: https://t.co/bHRdGdUeIY https://t.co/3CoXv1JGV7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden says more vaccines will be shipped to rural health clinics.   "We know that vaccination rates are lower in rural areas, and that's why we're going to get vaccines closer than ever to rural residents."  https://t.co/bHRdGdUeIY https://t.co/l58MZxTV65]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden says he is instructing "all federal pharmacy partners to begin to provide walk-in hours." https://t.co/bHRdGdUeIY https://t.co/sFIQqnHII9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The Army keeps trying to protect this name and I want to understand why," Mayra Guilln said of her sister Vanessa's harasser. https://t.co/IGPPFUwUBF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden says that if FDA approves vaccine for those 12-15 years old, "we are ready to move immediately," including shipping vaccines to pediatricians. https://t.co/bHRdGdUeIY https://t.co/scjM0m4nwR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pres. Biden: "As we anticipated, the pace of vaccinations is slowing now that the majority of American adults have already gotten their first shot. But we're still vaccinating millions of Americans every day." https://t.co/bHRdGdUeIY https://t.co/co8bNwHlcr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden gives COVID update:  - 220 million vaccine shots given as of last week - Over 105 million Americans fully vaccinated - 70% of seniors fully vaccinated - Cases down in 40 states over last two weeks - Deaths down over 80% among seniors.  https://t.co/bHRdGdUeIY https://t.co/BX505ssopa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Pres. Biden delivers remarks on COVID-19 response, vaccination program. https://t.co/IujQcg1SXQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials believe the woman stayed in the area by choice. https://t.co/I4FPVRNJfh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House Republican Leader Kevin McCarthy signals that Rep. Liz Cheney's days as GOP conference chairthe third-ranking Republican in the Housecould be numbered. https://t.co/9mSJvtHrp7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As soon as I pulled the stickers out, the kids, of course loved it. What kid wouldnt want to see stickers on their teacher?" https://t.co/hjH98mHwW8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEW: Pres. Biden is setting new goals for vaccinations in America, calling for 70% of the U.S. adult population to have at least one shot, and 160 million Americans to be fully vaccinated, by July 4. https://t.co/Q85REQ7scL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BEARS BREAKING IN: Bears in Avon, Connecticut, were caught on camera opening the doors of a parked car and climbing in. https://t.co/oGgxM5HlZJ https://t.co/lWZHcaWTkh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stunning photos capture lava flowing from Guatemala's Pacaya Volcano. https://t.co/kvcMKyr9XL https://t.co/24UeaZhALf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCPolitics: On herd immunity, Psaki tells @karentravers the goal is to "vaccinate as much of the population as quickly as we can."  "W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BATHING BEAR: Four bear cubs wait patiently as their mother takes a bath in a backyard family swimming pool in Arcadia, California. https://t.co/C5LSRjM5zC https://t.co/Gr496JQ6An]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Truck drivers blocked access roads to Bogota, Colombia, as demonstrations against Colombian President Ivan Duque's economic policies resumed despite the government's withdrawal of a controversial tax reform proposal. https://t.co/MBJA5mUS3Z https://t.co/BRK4g4gBqs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheView: MORE: @SenWarren: You want parents to be able togo to work?You want women to be able to goto work?Then we need affordable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH LIVE: Press sec. Jen Psaki holds a White House press briefing.  https://t.co/hFPAX0BwMC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCPolitics: Nothing like a prominent life in public service to help your other career as a romance novelist.  At least that's the case]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Most of the contiguous U.S. experienced a warming trend over the last 30 years, NOAA says.   "The data is clearly showing the U.S. climate is changing." https://t.co/JgDxa7Qm31]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After a user selected a city and clicked "Apply," a PDF file written in Cyrillic was downloaded to their computer, and they were instructed to fill it out and upload it back onto the site, investigators say. https://t.co/7qTJKgu0Xc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police say a good Samaritan who jumped off a Maryland bridge to save a young child wants to remain anonymous despite being a hero. https://t.co/5yP9FtyesR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABCGMA3: Its been 220 years in the coming.    Rep. @EleanorNorton responds to push back from Senate Republicans on DC statehood bill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A vaccination card will be the ticket for a free brewski in the Garden State this month. https://t.co/dGyLSlnihc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indy's parents said their daughter has watched the video "at least 15 times." https://t.co/NXuQaenPnD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Unfortunately my friends  I think the world is more interested in the negative," Britney Spears says. https://t.co/EyHeP5U70H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The teenage killer who lured a friend into a bathroom stall at their suburban Miami middle school 17 years ago and cut his throat has died in prison. https://t.co/KuzRDgHfuU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new mom says didn't know she was 29 weeks pregnant when she boarded the plane. https://t.co/1i0SbWDODJ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>