<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The entire corporate media complex will be screaming this from the rooftops by summer.  We will be ousted and shunned from society. https://t.co/bDcSf71jPE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wish my crypto assets would go up faster. 25% per day isn't enough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RIP. I'm sure you'll be missed. This tweet is meant to be unironic. https://t.co/6QB6wZ2g8H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRNYcrypto You're a good guy Tony]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jackmurphylive: https://t.co/wM24gVYsnp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I predict Caitlyn Jenner will win the California gubernatorial race.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelmalice She didn't believe in Jesus, so there is actually a good chance she is in hell.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelmalice It's our generation's Pearl Harbor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What are you gonna do when they come for your guns?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Before you criticize doge for being a meme coin, just remember... all money is a meme.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Christ is going to come back with the sword.   A lot of people will be sorry they worshiped false idols like Fauci instead if Jesus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ziVnVS3RLG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hear on the news today that "herd immunity" in the US will likely be impossible because a large portion of us won't receive the vax under any circumstances.  Oh well!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2021: Our people cherish Star Wars more than Jesus Christ.   The West has become a cultural void.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alex Jones proven right again. https://t.co/ER7SkFrIFP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @David28787016: I use to like science before it became a mask wearing, Tik Tok dancing, death cult]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@revelation_free In 1954.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hOoooC3n94]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vx065ykeqN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine shedding is likely a psyop to breed mistrust between pro vax and anti vax people.   The last thing the controllers want is everyone unifying through these tough times regardless of each other's medical history.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm one of these men. https://t.co/VzGjv9xXLE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Kn8ZSVUVR0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QYOAXvO0rQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoyPeac74176377: This is a real man]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is everyone with a lisp quoting Star Wars today?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OrwellNGoode: Now it's ok https://t.co/HauEMOMcTU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JRNYcrypto: Breaking news: inflationary meme coin goes up $20 billion in market cap over night]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyPeac74176377 How dare you cover up that gorgeous face!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm 100% right about every prediction I've ever made. Half joking, but really though https://t.co/lTzQrmu7vc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Unprograms: Its easy to control those who fear death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People I know are cancelling future obligations in anticipation of bad side effects they'll experience after receiving their scheduled CoCo jab.  The masses are lining up in droves to get a shot that they KNOW will make them sick.  Propaganda is incedibly powerful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me2 https://t.co/aTU6s8vby6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If they can make you provide proof of vaccination to buy or sell in everyday life, what other medical records can they request to transact?   Where does the buck stop?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I believe this is fundamentally true. The same can also be said about the creation of the internet to eventually enslave people down the road.   That doesn't mean the internet is always bad or that you can't use it for good. https://t.co/RqcWvscRhB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden here covers the kid's mouth so he can't say anything or scream to someone for help. https://t.co/bf67RykGqB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prediction:  Bill Gates will come out as gay as a way to shield himself from further criticism and label all dissenting opinions of his endeavors "hate speech". https://t.co/Y65iRqXp8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A genuine pandemic doesn't need 24/7 propaganda to remind you it exists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Psychooooo https://t.co/aQQUlAOImy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CN0EkKh5Dz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @solana_daily: TOP NEW SOLANA PROJECTS TO KEEP AN EYE ON  From launchpad, to DeFi legos, to NFT, #solana ecosystem is expanding with an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#dogecoin https://t.co/spUPBk6ATD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @amfirstreelsv2: Nick Fuentes on the American Regime spying on perceived "domestic terrorists" and "extremists" (thread).  : @NickJFuen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: Thank God that quoting from the bible is now illegal  These cops are doing the lord's work arresting this man for preaching]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fake alien invasion hoax will occur sometime between 2025 and 2030.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Providing the internet is still around in 500 years, it's pretty awesome thinking about how intimately future generations will know their ancestors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRNYcrypto https://t.co/2tKB8KJjk4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They're now paying the COVID cultists to recruit new members. https://t.co/OuMjzEVHnB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRNYcrypto He's a world changing nerd archtype in every way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda divorce is living proof a marriage won't work when the wife can easily beat up her husband in a fight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PressResetEarth: @JRNYcrypto Bill Gates is a genocidal psychopath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/R3Bn0tdYJI https://t.co/qkcoB6jr1J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRNYcrypto Bill Gates is a genocidal psychopath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @christophelston: I had great conversations yesterday, and then this guy showed up.   Polyamorous Androgynous Man.  He came at me from b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy Biden just announced more stimulus checks. But only to those who prove they've been vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RitaPanahi: How did LeBron survive this violence? https://t.co/9cZhfPJM1Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HighImpactFlix BTC is about to whisper back in a few weeks, my friend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Vaccinated Man Licks First Doorknob In Over A Year https://t.co/cGjjOLdnms]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still kinda butt hurt I sold my doge back in 2014 for $0.00027.  https://t.co/wumlBnTHIO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Shut down gyms, force vaccination for access to society  promote beer/donuts.  There is a special place in hell for e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: 'I Have Changed My Mind And Do Not Want A Divorce From This Amazing Handsome Man' Says Glossy Eyed Melinda Gates After R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The brainwashing is working... a little too much. https://t.co/A5WVSbUh0S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doge pumping again https://t.co/c1GEOxYKqD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hahahaha https://t.co/PXTuoUHCM0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @travalacom: $DOGE is now live as a payment method on #Travala for bookings!   #DOGE token holders are now able to pay for 3M+ travel pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Jung4aYUv3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JRNYcrypto: PayPal going in deep on Crypto. Hopefully they add more coins by end of 2021. Coins they will likely add $ADA, $DOGE, $DOT,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mscarnivore Funny story, I spent 0.5 bitcoin on a water filter like 7 years ago. It was worth like 200 bucks at the time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/P47nzcQv0n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mscarnivore It took me 10 years to finally wake up my mom.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: ok https://t.co/hFNMufHBOg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just hope Christmas 2021 everyone worships our savior and spreads joy, and there isn't a mysterious bomb that goes off in downtown Nashville.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PatriarchPrimus: The Bible: Most Credible Set of Books in History https://t.co/9pdeIlV4vH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZNeveri: Holland  People having a party in a supermarket The only place where large gatherings are allowed... https://t.co/mRdYlWKFA8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Know_More_News: I'll be watching]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yo CZ follow me https://t.co/WqMblT1YEK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["15 days to flatten the curve"  Never forget.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timcast Just wait]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EthereumMemes: $ETH $3000 https://t.co/lHbHgmxGY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cz_binance: https://t.co/20eO0Yw694]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CerebralPi: John Oliver is doing a show right now on why the un vaccinated are dangerous to the vaccinated.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China is gonna f**k us up. https://t.co/6dqzC5kg0S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think you meant **was** inevitable.  Like if you bought ETH before the 2017 bullrun and HODL'd through that entire crash. Diamond hands pays. https://t.co/XIGysqNRtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Listening to lofi and being a sad boy tonight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoyPeac74176377: It hit me like a ton of bricks the other day...  I'm literally raising the future resistance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieEmmaUK: Klaus Schwab, Founder and President of the World Economic Forum in Davos (2016): "We will have a chip implanted under t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pro vaxxers are the cringe, uncool, unpopular kids running for student council president in high school. https://t.co/akYLbccfzI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OrwellNGoode: Have you got your hugging license? https://t.co/fILZ9VLK7t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iansmithfitness: This is what mental instability looks like. This is not what health looks like.  This is the same person who wont t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CasuallyGreg: He was also killed by his government. https://t.co/EDPkOJ1xCv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TDaCYYBfWw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what the feminization of society looks like. https://t.co/GWBHQC6QqF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reallygraceful: they took down all the confederate statues and replaced them with something way worse https://t.co/CICOJnP4Bx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just went hiking in MA on a trail in the middle of the woods. 75% of the people I came across were wearing a face diaper.  Why does it seem like as time goes on, and more people get vaccinated, the mask psychosis grows?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PFriggens Arrr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Know_More_News That's right, Only the gate keepers, goy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sometimes when me and my boomer dad get into arguments, we start accusing each other of complaining too much and acting like a communist ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vzpDL2RV3j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pfizer apparently admits that "roll up your sleever" shedding is real  So it begs the question, why are cases exploding after the jab rollout? https://t.co/iDaFcYANHd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: CDC Now Recommends Wearing A Seat Belt Even When Youre Outside The Car https://t.co/Q8BjhQirX0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays They're going to eventually have to write it off, scrap the dollar, and institute a CBDC like China is doing.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>