<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolutely https://t.co/S61dumGhDX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnjennings992 Yes, defund them all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PamLongCO: To say vaccine hesitant is to really convey PredatoryPfizer hesitant or Market-firstModerna hesitant or JJ Talc Tent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnjennings992 It's a corporate mouthpiece so the corporations should fund it themselves.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's that day to say #DefundTheABC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Bill and Melinda Gates: We ask for space and privacy for our family as we begin to navigate this new life. Can our famili]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/EjdV2XYJqU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lifebiomedguru: This is blatant fraud, there is no two ways about it.  One PCR Ct threshold for COVID19 "cases", another for vaccine "b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: My anger towards the unaccountable, state-empowered western MSM grows each day, heightened now by their dangerous fear-monger]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @the_Arkivist: Beyond scary. https://t.co/HpcngCmA78]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: Which option do you believe?  1. A "reset" naturally flows from the pandemic.  2. The pandemic was intended as cover for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kbeanie93: Let's carry out a poll that's not rigged:  Do you support or oppose Covid passports?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: #Nuremberg2 should definitely be trending.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @flattenedOA: what would you rather...?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Trump is bragging about JJ as a company, defending them, bragging about rushing this years ahead of schedule  is try]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Please tell every woman you know of childbearing age about the now hundreds of eyewitness accounts of immediate menstrual b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffsekerak: The Prince is dead! He wanted you dead. GOOD RIDDANCE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tanya_plibersek @ScottMorrisonMP What's next? Possibly Labor in power and definitely just as many stuff ups as now. The problem is politicians and government as a whole.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KikiwahT: The fact that they can get a vaccine ready in 9 months but have yet to cure cancer should tell you everything you need to kno]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RossCameron4: You know your government is acting in bad faith if it wants to inject a child with an experimental drug to treat a virus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McFadden1932: There is no doubt in my mind that SIDS is cover for vaccine-induced death.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @weaponizedword1: People blaming preexisting conditions on every vaccine injury are the same people whose first question to a rape victi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kategardiola @UrslanH @noamchomskyT What proof do you have for the existence of this virus?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeterHotez @MethodistHosp @TXMedCenter I imagine there will be a high turnover in staff for that hospital.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LoyolaTrue: @Notyour28981739 That's where the original slur, "anti-vaxxer" was born. Women whose children were killed or damaged by vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LisaPenney @Alec_Zeck Where is the evidence for spreading from person to person?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NellyTells I'm the type that has mostly loved being at home. But my home had never been a prison until last year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @weaponizedword1: Me vs. medical doctors on social media when discussing vaccines and vaccine safety  This is exactly what it looks like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am preparing for this kind of future for myself and my family as well. We are very set in our minds that we will not be taking any of the vaccines, not ever. https://t.co/geA8uRnMTG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@healthgovau So influenza numbers are the same as they have been every other year? No! Those numbers went sailing down after you introduced Covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VCS_Foundation_ @NCIRS @c4_cre With Gardakill, there won't be elimination. However, there will be a great elimination of fertility.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NCIRS @healthgovau @peripatetical @WHOCCFluMelb If Covid has replaced influenza, what is the point of the influenza vaccine?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @weaponizedword1: Lets dumb this all the way down....Who has more to lose, Pharmaceutical companies manufacturing billions of doses of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anybody have any helpful tips for toilet training a 7 year old? #autism]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love this idea! https://t.co/QjGdH1r4tF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SenatorWong Labor, pretending they're different. Pretending - it's in their DNA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NOSaintsfan08: @RealHughJackman @BillGates Ill start listening about climate change when the people shoving it down my throat stop fly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lifebiomedguru: When the "scientific consensus" has nothing to do with science, it is no longer a "scientific" consensus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shazamichelle: Akathisia: Drug companies have done little to publicise this potentially lethal side effect of both antidepressants and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@markjarthur I'm in one of the affected areas at the moment and there are so many. Next will be a big increase in snakes, which is way more scary.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: Somebody reading this is feeling discouraged, hopeless, and demoralised right now...  Keep your head up, focus on the positi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnpilger Safe and effective]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1eLXYiznh0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @benzosarebad: The corruption in psychiatry is so deep, it is not safe for patients to seek help from this profession.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP I'm sure they appreciated being thanked for participating in your murderous roll out of dangerous vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffsekerak: 1) Big Pharma is testing experimental, DNA-altering injections on children. 2) Your government has rendered Big Pharma imm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jonrappoport: My original position on the non-existent COVID-19 virus  https://t.co/vcKmM4EFuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Earthlingz963: @techreview This why we need to stop looking to academics, especially scientists for answers. Science isn't synonymous]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have no doubt. https://t.co/Eg2GcCIMDa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP Stay away from neurotoxins, particularly those found in vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP Genocide.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EwaMazierska: I wonder if masked women carrying banners saying 'Stop silencing us' see the irony of their statement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I have yet to see any evidence of a pandemic at all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alumilynn: Redoing this: Please RETWEET!!  Remember, its a private poll, so your answers do not identify who you are.   PLEASE partici]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NellyTells: When they say inclusive they only mean if you are willing to conform.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP Nothing to celebrate. Poor health everywhere.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @markjarthur: Job Flying Games Concerts  All things Ill quit immediately if Im forced to get the vaccine.   And if I missed someth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrAseemMalhotra: Where is the advice to avoid ultra processed food  low quality carbs for healthy weight loss  rapid improvement in m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: #Australia is looking pretty good here. The people need to really step it up now... https://t.co/syxlZonkF5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thread of the day. Such important information. Please read. https://t.co/SODzUaQZ10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDelingpole: Covid-19 was never the point. The vaccine was always the point - and the endgame. Climate change was never the point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AusAntiLeft: I learnt almost nothing at university,  work placement and personal online  study is where I gained most of the knowledge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @waynerohde: @Rebekah60291919 its bigger than this. I am releasing an article on Wed that shows WHO crafted a global covid vax inj comp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What does Pfizer know about its product that the consumer doesn't? Did they release all the data from their trials? https://t.co/BGHgLQ4DjE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I refuse to submit to their demonic demands also. https://t.co/3ewdc4Z2dv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicRogerson @janehansen2000 @DrPaulOffit @GregHuntMP @LightForRiley @AutismAwareAus Not surprised you're impressed by @janehansen2000 - you're both like two peas in a pod: averse to truth. https://t.co/EkKWhojPMt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicRogerson @janehansen2000 @DrPaulOffit @GregHuntMP @LightForRiley @AutismAwareAus You should be utterly ashamed of yourself for throwing our vaccine injured children under a bus Nicole. But I bet your bank account is big and healthy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look at the lies they tell when it starts going wrong. Four times the amount? I don't believe that for a minute. https://t.co/F37SiBR9EM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SulleyTruman I absolutely agree.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drjohnny__: Now this is the feminine empowerment weve been waiting to see in sports! https://t.co/Yl2Bc3eyxr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @judiannrocks: pro-tip: burn Stephen King books to stay warm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisWickNews: This speaks volumes!!! Pay attention. https://t.co/1PgPHT87Sa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@guardian Your work is shit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TABYTCHI: Bill Gates can eat a synthetic bag of dicks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SarcasmStardust: He knew they would come for him. He published the information anyway. Because it was important and the right thing to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffsekerak: The elites want to control you. The politicians want to enslave you. The preachers want to mislead you. The doctors want t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deralteGaukler @Charbrevolution You're shit scared too.  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Charbrevolution Rosewind is scared. She knows she has been on the wrong side, and what becomes of her when the vaccine nightmare is exposed?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is this reality? I have no words.. https://t.co/eHKjKLkTid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm feeling some despair that I'm at the point of thinking anybody who gets the vaccine, and is harmed, kind of deserves it. I don't want to think like this, but here I am..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lifebiomedguru: Shameless manipulation: Positive PCR tests drop after WHO instructs vendors to lower cycle thresholds. We have been pla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The people of Victoria need to lockdown Daniel Andrews. https://t.co/oakaJkiGLj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kaz_fitz: Controversial tweet:  If you are over 60 and expect my kids to forgo their childhood, rights and privileges so you feel safe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have thought for a while that the main purpose of Covid is to manufacture consent for war with China. I haven't diverged from that view. If there is a war, it's going to be terrible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WiseOldElf4 @PlumRemson The "it would be unethical" excuse is abhorrent and tells me that they know what the study would reveal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TungstenV: I won't be muzzled, or factory-pharmed. #FaceCrime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scouterriffic I agree]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pacifist322 Thanks. What a perfect song for the times we're living through.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scented444 This is so true.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blue_sky_4me Absolutely.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deefeinberg Thank you Dee. My son has better days and I hope your son does too. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CREATORS_CHILD Our family avoids them now. We will not be taking any of the c19 vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelleza @grhluna24 I can see the distress on his face. It's heartbreaking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnGre13255310 @grhluna24 Exactly. It's why so many parents fret about what happens when they themselves die. Who will care for them?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@port71wick I think this tweet and the big cry I had was me taking some time for myself. The day did get better for all of us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gilesbryant Thank you, I will have a listen today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catlady_cez @grhluna24 Thanks so much. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ekverstania Thank you for sharing this. I am hopeful for my son and that he will find peace as he gets older.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ARileyT1 @grhluna24 He is wonderful. I am hopeful that the world will become a little easier for him as he gets older.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TrustedTasks @scented444 We do have some wonderful days and I thank God for the peace my son has during them.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>