<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MarcBonten on election to the @_knaw Royal Netherlands Academy of Sciences https://t.co/N98Nt5gZil !  What a fitting recognition of a wonderful scientist and colleague.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @j_g_allen and thank you for also leading tremendous work in many areas but (speaking personally) especially to help many sectors of society reopen safely. https://t.co/ton9gJC7Xl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[super excited for this one!  His recent Science paper (different it seems from his talk) https://t.co/m734fEFube was mind-boggling. This should be good! https://t.co/BzUGnEVnvB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCDD_HSPH: THURSDAY 5/6 @ 1PM ET: Join Bryan Bryson for our final seminar in our 2021 ID Epi Spring Seminar Series.  He will discuss En]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apoorva_nyc: NEW: The herd immunity threshold for the coronavirus will stay out of reach, because widely circulating variants and persi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jimbryson: This is essential reading for everyone.   CDCs Guidelines for When Its Safe to Still Wear Lounge Pants - McSweeneys Inter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @victornizet: two-tailed tea test #statistics https://t.co/MdKfotFxvw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJKayWriter seeing your pinned tweet I am confused why you are calling for nuance and opposing rigidity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJKayWriter Not coming around. I've tried throughout to separate policy opinions from scientific statements. I have both]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@harphat well it seems to be motivated by the latter and mostly discuss the former as best I can tell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Follow the science" as a guide to decision making is incomplete if you believe is != ought. Something more like "incorporate the science" or "Decide how to accomplish your ends while incorporating the best science" or some other clunky formula]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also I've been thinking as the pandemic has worn on (and on) that the issue of trusting or not scientific experts on the facts is really distinct from the q of what role they should play in guiding decisions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting new essay that I mostly agree with, though not sure if astrophysics and medical science, for example, differ in kind or just in degree, in terms of the requirement for social practices to correct individual biases/blind spots. https://t.co/KCzixD90Sx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast @G_RegevY I disagree.  We should discuss offline.  That study considered all infected contacts regardless of symptoms or care seeking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast Agree.  That is why studies of all infections done properly by, for example contact tracing or random sampling, combined with viral load, or a proxy at least, are needed. Eg the Israel study from @G_RegevY that I linked above.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeattleCPA @ZoeMcLaren @AdamJKucharski @nytimes @mgmgomes1 Interesting q: do declining cases in Israel despite 50% 2 dose coverage and B117 require rethinking or can we account for this unexpected good news by seasonality, disproportionate coverage of high transmitters ie adults, natural immunity and remaining distancing esp of unvax ppl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeattleCPA @ZoeMcLaren @AdamJKucharski @nytimes @mgmgomes1 And a bit older but in same vein https://t.co/STyfv8JKnS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeattleCPA @ZoeMcLaren @AdamJKucharski @nytimes @mgmgomes1 Recent views here https://t.co/c2CiofODvI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeattleCPA @ZoeMcLaren @AdamJKucharski @nytimes @mgmgomes1 I dont think I have ever stated a HIT of 50%. In the very early days I talked about a final size of 40-70% based on the then estimates of R0.  Other reasonable estimates https://t.co/P6sJOH3fe5 and variants push estimates higher]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast Could be.  But efficacy against all infections is likely a lower bound]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @GaviSeth @UN_PGA @unicefchief @JeremyFarrar @MirfinM To be honest I was focusing on the vaccine part not the covid and amr part]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast Right but vaccinated infected shed less virus than Unvax infected. This will reduce transmission on top of protection vs infection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast Obviously need same evidence for other vaccines]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast https://t.co/2rMNkE0YXD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast https://t.co/YQMVuGnPKj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 @DiseaseEcology @hildabast But remember what matters for R is efficacy vs transmission for which infection efficacy is almost certainly a lower bound.  Preliminary results from several studies show much lower RNA and even less Ag positivity in vaccines (all Pfizer afaik)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GaviSeth: #COVID19 is fuelingasilent pandemic of #AntimicrobialResistance whichisthreateninga century ofmedicalprogress. It was]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Susannajd: There's a whole series of these, brought to my attention by @LanceTurtle  @Thushan_deSilva. This one is so good, I'm sure t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Memoriam: George R. Seage III, 19572021 : Epidemiology https://t.co/fgTgpMiVJV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillHanage @NoahHaber @ProfMattFox @CT_Bergstrom how could I have forgotten. One of my finest moments in science to be associated with Fig. S8)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It surely happens that agriculture influences human health https://t.co/y3TRMy8ny2 and it is also true that it could be happening and hard to detect. But to emphasize One Health so much when it is very clear that use and overuse in human medicine are major drivers seems a mistake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Recent excellent genomic work from Prof Sharon Peacock's group, @MarcBonten's group among others has failed to find evidence of strong links between resistance in animals and resistance in clinical isolates. @BillHanage wrote about this https://t.co/P5eccLzuZw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some years ago @BillHanage and I and @G_RegevY and our students pointed out the absence of strong evidence (while acknowledging challenges of generating it) https://t.co/me27nOVhkW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great that attention is remaining focused on #AMR a big problem. https://t.co/IiUTDYHZMo . But the relentless claims that this is primarily or largely a problem of agriculture are not evidence-based.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NoahHaber @ProfMattFox @CT_Bergstrom Oh and this which I think @BillHanage wrote because he thought of the title and had to write it https://t.co/P5eccLzuZw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great speakers @RadInstitute May 11 https://t.co/Wog8DKOT6K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Acertaintom @RoyalStatSoc @turinginst @DHSCgovuk @cholmesuk https://t.co/7v06YHcZ4N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillHanage: I am seeing a lot of anxiety around partial immunity through vaccination producing selection for escape variants. Here @col]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarlosdelRio7 @ndtv @angie_rasmussen Cant find the reference.   Would take w grain of salt tho obviously a terrible situation whatever R is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardGoldste16 I think they got me right but dont quite get most of them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeeDugatkin: Excited that my Nautilus article on Nikolai Vavilov is  live. There are very few people in my pantheon of intellectual ido]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: The risks of no masks outdoors is low. But...how low?  Turns out we can 'trick' our covid-19 risk calculator to make it rese]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalStatSoc: We're looking forward to the insights of @mlipsitch tomorrow, in a visiting lecture convened by our @turinginst @royalsta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do We Still Need to Keep Wearing Masks Outdoors? https://t.co/K4YT5mrIng]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pateixidor: "Generalmente soy muy radical en la defensa de las normas con un beneficio claro, pero ponerse la mascarilla al aire libre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abuttenheim Also I love that JAMA facial plastic surgery is on there because of the prefix while the actual top journals in many much larger fields arent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abuttenheim Well something-checking. The process of promotion by counting instead of reading might prompt questions on the expertise of those making the decisions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jd_mathbio Appreciate your consideration of the alternative hypothesis to my just being a dope. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not just cholent-hesitant, I'm anti-cholent. But pro-vax. https://t.co/l26KEQtHjd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The master of tautology speaks. https://t.co/dvWiIcPXDP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking virtually at @turinginst on Friday https://t.co/z19sLc4hqO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jd_mathbio But for better or worse, people are eating indoors in restaurants, shopping (hopefully with masks), and  having many other contacts. It is  possible, but incredibly unlikely given lack of evidence and physical principles, that outdoor casual contacts significantly add to R0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looks like a fascinating symposium on human rights, international cooperation, and COVID-19,  honoring the memory of a wonderful person and human rights advocate https://t.co/p92ft1suW4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rustyapples @Popehat Still think journalists should be talking a lot about this. Teachable civic moment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks @BhadeliaMD for adding nuance I should have added. https://t.co/RT4RRS7phP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pjligh To be fair the US has on the other hand pretty uniformly let people be outside with few or no restrictions within their own state. Europe more restrictive I think]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tonypaylow Like I said Im all in for interventions with a known or reasonably expected benefit.  But annoyance times 100s of millions is not worth it for a pointless ritual]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brianbreslin Less exercise and less enjoyment of spring which are both much needed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I must agree.  I am generally a hawk about maintaining rules with a clear benefit.  Outdoor masking has notable costs and really no evidence of benefits https://t.co/tYTDm9slVX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seems from the replies like the defense holds no legal water. Would be nice if the journalists covering it emphasized that point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@heidi_shaddix so if the eggshell skull rule applies (thanks to those who gave the reference), then why are all the media reporting this absurd defense without noting it is absurd?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[of a certain kind of abuse we can survive. It seems incoherent to have a standard that it's not murder if a different person would not have died under the same horrific abuse -- and I'm not saying that is true, only that this seems to be the defense's standard.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm willing to believe that the law traditionally has such a notion (or not -- hope some lawyers will help me understand) but if so it seems truly indefensible. We all have the preexisting condition of being mortal. We each have a different breakpoint for how much...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is there some bizarre legal notion of causality at play here that the force used would have had to be such that it would have killed anyone, not just the actual person it did kill? https://t.co/kig6wEtTWH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCDD_HSPH: THURSDAY 4/22 @ 1PM ET: Join Dr. Pia Abel-zur Wiesch for our ID Epi Spring Seminar Series.  Her sessions will be On the Inte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GYamey: Did you sign the Great Barrington Declaration? If so please do ask GBD to stop pushing anti-vaxx BS. OK? Along with Yeadon  Le]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just learned about this book forthcoming Nov 1. https://t.co/jlBI1mbmZt from @sandrogalea -- can't wait to read it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @deborahblum: This will be great. https://t.co/m2eouuKYSY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hugorojo: May we all be as smooth as @vivek_murthy @Surgeon_General was during his @CBSThisMorning interview today when his son wanted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DNABARCODE If this is to slow the spread they need to release infection and shedding data.  Seems to be setting a new low bar  no peer review, no scientific article just a press release was the old low bar.  Press release missing critical data is a step lower]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @morde: Did you miss our Science of Herd Immunity event and want to catch up on the discussion with @meyerslab @mlipsitch @parsonnt and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Announcement of a COVID Commission Planning Group https://t.co/pClnA8wRYZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCDD_HSPH: THURSDAY 4/15 @ 1PM ET: Join @DA_Barnhart for our ID Epi Spring Seminar Series.  She will be discussing Identifying Vulnerab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @G_RegevY: The BNT162b2 vaccine not only reduces symptomatic disease, we now show it reduces infectivity, asymptomatic infections and th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing @audmar @MonicaGandhi9 Many of these say little or nothing about transmission. But I suspect the number will turn out to be in n this range.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@celinegounder To be fair the evidence for this is extremely limited (2.6 OR with 36 discordant pairs and unclear how effective control for confounding) and goes the other way for B.1.351.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nasirfmusiqi Thanks for the update/correction.  Had missed these data.  Though waning is modest if any by d43.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBranswell For example in the JJ trial https://t.co/EfUyS4t9EL antibody concentrations continued increasing from d28 to 57 and 71 post a single dose. Same in mRNA vax?  Not sure, I haven't seen data, but possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBranswell And no evidence against the idea that one or two doses knocks down all variants substantially.  Finally, there is nothing here about people 4,8,12 weeks post first dose as Israel didn't do that. It is possible that immunity at that stage is better than in weeks 2-3 post dose 1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBranswell So in sum all numbers are small and thus estimates imprecise but for B.1.351 this is better than one would hope (partial looks better than full, though very imprecise) and for B.1.1.7 about what would have expected from https://t.co/Ig1gPyiqzh in terms of selection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBranswell For B.1.1.7 again all prior work shows a) is true (many fewer infections in partial or fully vaxed). This study shows OR=2.6 in partial vax, OR=1.5 in fully vaxed. Larger numbers in partial vax give p&lt;0.05 but these numbers are very close.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBranswell The study shows exactly this for B. 1.351; fully vaccinated people are much less likely to get infected (prior studies) but if they do (this study) 8x more likely than unvaccinated to get B.1.351. Numbers too small for partially vaxed but no evidence of more selection than full]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBranswell That doesn't make sense to me.  Evolutionary argument for stretching the interval is that a) highly effective vaccine after one dose knocks down numbers dramatically, reducing potential for evolution and b) immunity may select for variants, but 1 dose not much more than 2.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ddiamond: BREAKING: Trump appointees celebrated their efforts to get CDC to change its reports on coronavirus.  A small victory  yipp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @morde: Great coverage of our Science of Herd Immunity event this week in the @StanfordDaily , with @malar0ne @mlipsitch @meyerslab @par]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks @GYamey for this! https://t.co/t9MAJRpPgN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bachyns: I'm listening to this webinar right now--worth a listen for anybody who wants to hear a great group of experts discuss herd im]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[starting in a few minutes! https://t.co/m8KGCCekfF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Karl_Lauterbach: (1) Besonders wichtige Studie aus US, ua @mlipsitch Harvard Universitt, zeigt, dass durch Streckung 2. Dosis von Bi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCDD_HSPH: TODAY @ 3PM ET: Join @mlipsitch and other experts for The Science of Herd Immunity.  They will explain the science of and mi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kashanacauley: One of the most serious side effects of the vaccine is realizing that free healthcare is amazing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jlrauch: Join this years Polk Award winners @David_Culver /CNN @HelenBranswell /STAT @edyong209 /TheAtlantic and moderator @Laurie_Gar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boohanmugullah1 @NPR Hi Tim and Jen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jstreetdotorg: Stephen Miller "is one of the nations most notorious and well-documented bigots, and the architect of some of the darke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reliving a classic @npr April Fool's story.  New England Suffers Maple Woes : NPR https://t.co/8F9xSh6VdE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NoahHaber @ProfMattFox @CT_Bergstrom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeffCavanagh1 @adamtvaccaro @Ginpitz @YaleEMD a lot of the same issues raised here https://t.co/STyfv8JKnS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[very clear article by @adamtvaccaro with lots of input from @Ginpitz @YaleEMD too https://t.co/9UbRayYhYn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[April Fool's tweet from @stanford about herd immunity. Sorry, couldn't resist, said with love. https://t.co/bn21R8LmDz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@celinegounder @sarahcobey @DanLarremore @yhgrad Now published https://t.co/Ig1gPyiqzh]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>