<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDC_NCEZID: World #HandHygiene Day is May 5. Cleaning your hands with alcohol-based hand sanitizer or soap and water is a simple yet ef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hear why Dr. Alexa Mieses-Malchuk believes getting the #COVID19 vaccine is the greatest thing you can do for yourself, your loved ones, and the community. Get info at https://t.co/kquXVCXb4h.   English version: https://t.co/kZyLYbNHU3 Versin en espaol: https://t.co/lJzYb50N3I https://t.co/AV2ImyTv20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCemergency: Make sure your #mask fits snugly on your face to help prevent getting and spreading #COVID19. Masks dont work well if th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you know the signs of #asthma? This common condition can be critical, especially during #COVID19, but is easily managed with a few easy steps. Learn how: https://t.co/n3CMeP0Dsk. #WorldAsthmaDay https://t.co/iHvwlmogQi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FDA_ORA: Today is #WorldAsthmaDay, and one of the many explanations for #asthma being the most common chronic disease in the developed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACFHHS: #HeadStart staff can make the transition to kindergarten easier for families by talking with them about school health services.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Surgeon_General: It will take more than government to vaccinate America against #COVID19. It will take all of us talking to our friends]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The force is within you when you make the decision to get vaccinated, especially against #COVID19. #Vaccinations are our galaxys safest  most effective protection from the Empire of vaccine preventable diseases. https://t.co/X3Qup6byEq #Maythe4th https://t.co/gfWjlbEMqX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Heading to the tanning salon to get ready for the warmer weather? Know the risk!   Indoor tanning can raise your chances of mel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PHEgov: How can we encourage people in all communities to get vaccinated to or get early treatment if they think they have been exposed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HHS_ASH: If we work together, we can turn the page on this pandemic. Lets make sure our families, friends, and communities get vaccina]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HHS announces the @HRSAgov #COVID19 Coverage Assistance Fund (CAF) to remove access concerns  ensure everyone gets vaccinated against COVID-19 including individuals whose health plan does not cover vaccine admin. fees or does w/ cost sharing. https://t.co/cAhtFjmbdB https://t.co/eBeIzi1vky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #PublicServiceRecognitionWeek, we want to recognize the hundreds of thousands of public servants who have worked tirelessly to keep the country running during the #COVID19 pandemic. Thank you for all your hard work. https://t.co/AFQGeSIutm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Knowledge gained from the #HumanPlacentaProject (HPP) may one day help treat common #pregnancy complications. Join @NICHD_NIH for the virtual HPP2021 meeting, May 1011, to learn about promising #placental #research. https://t.co/UhQin6nR1n #MaternalHealthNICHD https://t.co/TV1RzhGh6y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today, HHS and national partners mark Asian Pacific Heritage Month by encouraging Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders to enroll in quality, affordable health coverage through https://t.co/UkTACLkiWf. https://t.co/ZRq5jBdTF1 https://t.co/JaBaweccuq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samhsagov: Everyone can play a role in #SuicidePrevention. Some warning signs may help you determine if a loved one is at risk.   Know]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: In the last year, FDA employees have done vital work including helping to combat the COVID-19 pandemic. This Public Service Rec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCemergency: If you have recently traveled, attended a large social gathering, or been in a crowded indoor setting, consider getting t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feeling #anxious ? Take a deep breath and learn these simple steps to stay in touch with your mind and body from @NIH: https://t.co/7X5YEwXtpt. #MentalHealth https://t.co/kpSiMNHCmF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: School systems  local governments: Help families prepare for their childs return to school. Remind them that children may hav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["People want to hear from trusted messengers, and often that means people who look like them": Dr. Lisa Fitzpatrick is encouraging #COVID19 vaccine acceptance by bringing her science-based approach to the streets of Washington, D.C.: https://t.co/j5bby3Ak14 https://t.co/1hqVAtICcb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Washing your hands helps prevent #COVID19. But there are times you just cant. Alcohol-based hand sanitizer is an alternative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hugging mom. Helping a child get back to school. Enjoying a dinner out with friends. There are countless reasons, big and small, to get a COVID-19 vaccine. What's yours? #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/qlQdf1iJrH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Children need vaccines, from infancy throughout childhood, to provide them with immunity from potentially dangerous infectious]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HHS_ASH: Thanks to our partners, we have made extraordinary progress in our fight against #COVID19. We are proud of our interagency par]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NIH: Tune in to todays #WeCanDoThis Live at 4:15 pm ET for a conversation on #COVID19 vaccines with Dr. Fauci and @EvaLongoria on #NIH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tune in to todays We Can Do This Live at 4:15pm ET for a conversation on COVID-19 vaccines with Dr. Fauci and @EvaLongoria on @NIHs Instagram Live. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/oL7tDc7Ug8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACFHHS: Foster care should be a support system for families in need, not a substitute for parents. Child welfare agencies, courts, and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer is coming, and theres hope on the horizon. Vaccines can help us move forward and get back to doing the things we love. Learn more about getting vaccinated at https://t.co/UY9hUPdMqy. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/Dg3Jsx5vEq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In his first 100 days, @POTUS addressed health care by increasing premium tax credits for those who get health coverage through https://t.co/UkTACLkiWf. https://t.co/9WocMCZfp3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you receive a Pfizer-BioNTech or Moderna #COVID19 vaccine, you need 2 shots to become fully vaccinated. This is why its crucial to schedule and attend your second shot appointment. Find details from @CDCgov about your second shot: https://t.co/2W0IF7XVuE. https://t.co/swvplgFKAk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tune in to todays We Can Do This Live at 4:15pm ET for a conversation on COVID-19 vaccines with Dr. Fauci and @EvaLongoria on @NIHs Instagram Live. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/9ymkJCRfhn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HRSAgov: Its hard to believe all the ways #organ, eye and tissue #donors save and improve lives. Discover your potential and learn mor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Surgeon_General: Want to help increase equity in #COVID19 vaccine access  help communities get #VaccineReady?   Check out the @HHSGov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Join millions of others in the U.S. and  #SleeveUp for your #COVID19 vaccine, so we can all get back to seeing our loved ones]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tune in to tomorrow's We Can Do This Live at 4:15pm ET for a conversation on COVID-19 vaccines with Dr. Fauci and @EvaLongoria on @NIHs Instagram Live. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/gkmVCz4X2S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today @SecBecerra announced that HHS, through @HRSAgov, awarded over $32 million to 122 organizations that provide training  technical assistance support to HRSA's Health Center Program-supported #healthcenters nationwide: https://t.co/8uwCSOHTFv https://t.co/Zk9SIt9Qwd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Today, @FDATobacco announced the agencys commitment to evidence-based actions aimed at saving lives and preventing future gene]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet some of the doctors, scientists, and volunteers who took part in #COVID19 research, from discovery to treatment. Tune in TONIGHT at 7 pm ET: https://t.co/gio6dRhQ4G. #NIHCEAL https://t.co/uAoq9rh8a7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HHS_ASH: Today, I met w/ the Black Doctors #COVID19 Consortium. They are dedicated to providing vaccination outreach to our hardest hit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For yourself, your grandmother, the owner of your favorite coffee shop. Getting vaccinated is about more than one person, its about an entire community. Learn more at https://t.co/Dv4hkrR4Cp. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/2GqpBS9Klo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HRSAgov: As we wrap up #NationalDonateLifeMonth, learn more about the path to saving and changing lives as an #organ, eye and tissue #d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2) If you need to talk to someone about finding help for depression, call SAMHSAs National Helpline, 1-800-662-HELP (4357).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1) Are you feeling down, or could it be depression? Here are some of the symptoms of #depression and how they compare to general sadness. Learn more from @NIMHgov about depression and how to treat it: https://t.co/JAB5YXcdbe. https://t.co/r5m8yJD8XX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #COVID19 rates are falling. The current 7-day average of new daily cases is 53,934, a 16% decrease from the previous week. If y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACFHHS: The #COVID19 vaccine is an important tool to prevent the spread of COVID-19 and end this pandemic. Find answers to your questio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samhsagov: #DYK: American Indians/Alaska Natives are at an increased risk for substance use.  Health professionals: Learn how to best a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCEnvironment: DO NOT stay in a mobile home during a #tornado. Go to a nearby building, preferably one with a basement. If there is no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you looking to find the facts and debunk myths about the COVID vaccines? Check out episode 3 of our podcast, COVID-19 Immunity in Our Community, featuring special guest Dr. Fauci: https://t.co/72va4fWCpY. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/OUKmqUb4y8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight at 7pm ET, BCAC and the We Can Do This Campaign will host minority health care professionals and community advocates in a discussion about vaccine equity in the U.S. Check it out at https://t.co/eY2Jw0jtSH. @BlackDoctor_Org #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/a4Clx1IZX1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nih_nhlbi: #DYK? 1 in 3 adults do not regularly get the recommended amount of uninterrupted sleep they need to protect their health. Le]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: New @CDCMMWR has good news: mRNA COVID-19 vaccines (Pfizer-BioNTech, Moderna) reduced the risk of #COVID19-related hospitalizat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Before you get vaccinated, take these precautions to protect yourself and others from COVID-19. Learn more at https://t.co/8rTWJ7z2Sb. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/slo7EVasPm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #HCPs: Are your patients asking about the Johnson  Johnson #COVID19 vaccine?  New tools are available to help you answer your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Some racial and ethnic minority communities have been disproportionately affected by #COVID19. Protect yourself by getting vacc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Community (or herd) immunity is when enough members of a community are immunized against a contagious disease, keeping most others protected. One of the ways to help start community immunity is by getting a #COVID19 vaccine when its your turn: https://t.co/pIoddVAKHH. https://t.co/8DQt9cvTY2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Many families routines were disrupted this year because of #COVID19 including having regular checkups and receiving recommend]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACLgov: #OlderAmericansMonth is just days away. Still deciding how to celebrate your community of strength? Not to worry! Our materials]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: If you have recently traveled, attended a large social gathering, or been in a crowded indoor setting, consider getting tested]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACLgov: ACL-funded Northwest ADA Regional Center has a factsheet, Healthcare  Face Coverings: Reducing Communication Barriers for #Dea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: Thank you to healthcare providers and frontline workers across the country for taking extra steps to care for children safely d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: If you are fully vaccinated against #COVID19, you can start doing many things that you had stopped doing because of the pandemi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us all month long as we observe National Minority Health Month! Were sharing tips and reminders throughout this month to help keep you #ActiveAndHealthy this April and throughout the year. Learn more from @MinorityHealth: https://t.co/6sgiGoBHwS #NMHM2021 #MinorityHealth https://t.co/opaSF6Wif9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HHS Secretary @SecBecerra announced national partners to combine to boost Black American enrollment at https://t.co/UkTACLkiWf. https://t.co/k7VZ2fy2ZR https://t.co/Rve5Zr7XvB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Being in the know when it comes to food outbreaks and recalls is key to protecting your family from health risks. Learn more ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: #COVID19 vaccines are now more widely accessible.  As of April 26, more than 140 million people in the United States had receiv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today, HHS releases new buprenorphine practice guidelines to get evidenced-based treatment to more Americans with opioid use disorder. Read more: https://t.co/HeaKTuSDXl https://t.co/OiR2L9HuIK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACFHHS: #DYK racial and ethnic minority and #AIAN communities are among the hardest hit by the #COVID19 pandemic? We can help them get]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HRSAgov: Has your practice explored direct-to-consumer #telehealth? Get tips on how to develop a direct-to-consumer strategy: https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trusted Voices on Vaccine Acceptance: To promote #COVID19 vaccine acceptance - especially in communities of color - Dr. Lisa Fitzpatrick takes her message to the streets of Washington, D.C., engaging people with truthful, science based information. Watch: https://t.co/j5bby3iICu https://t.co/LeiQaXgYyq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From healthy eating to hydration, from sleep to exerciseuse these six tips to have a healthy spring: https://t.co/EtMCFkFVCC. https://t.co/401TYjid3k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Are you looking for the latest news and updates on #COVID19 vaccines? Check out these podcasts, videos, and more to keep you in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FDAWomen: Are you a caregiver who administers medication or uses a medical device for a loved one?  Use these 4 tips for safe medicatio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Surgeon_General: NEW: U.S. announces plan to share AstraZeneca #COVID19 vaccine doses with the world. 60 million doses to be shared as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCemergency: Preparing for emergencies can be challenging for families caring for a child with autism or other disability. Here are so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 vaccines give us time  time to celebrate birthdays in person, time to hug loved ones, time to make new memories. Learn more about getting vaccinated at https://t.co/V4WmzVzFzw. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/3AQrEnSAL0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMartinCDC: #Malaria is the leading cause of preventable illness and death around the world, killing more than 400,000 people each yea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you know if your child is up to date on immunizations? Use this resource to see when your child needs each vaccine so you can stay on schedule and protect your baby from 14 serious diseases by age two: https://t.co/tA6GYew9ex. #NIIW #ivax2protect https://t.co/EA6yrgkkNZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCInjury: Addiction is treatable and can be successfully managed.  #Recovery is possible, and help is available for #opioid addiction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: Do you wear contact lenses?   Watch this video for 7 simple tips on keeping your eyes safe and healthy so you can avoid infecti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCemergency: It's important for everyone to use all the tools available to help stop this pandemic as we learn more about how #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NCISymptomMgmt: Controlling pain is an important part of your cancer treatment plan. Pain can suppress the immune system, increase the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone 16 and older is now eligible to receive a COVID-19 vaccine. Find out which vaccine is right for you and learn more about getting vaccinated at https://t.co/A0mIRIlLlF. #WeCanDoThis https://t.co/1NpLAzsue0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alzheimers_NIH: Old age does not cause #Alzheimers, but it is the most important risk factor for the disease. Scientists are learning h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NLM_NIH: Scientists have studied how to use mRNA to protect us from viruses for a long time. Learn more about what isand isntpart of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: CDC has classified SARS-CoV-2 variant B.1.526.1 as a variant of interest. Some treatments for #COVID19 have shown to be less ef]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HRSAgov: Pediatric #donors, their families, and the lives theyve made possible are in our hearts, this week and always. Learn more abo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join @theNCI and @CDC_Cancer on Monday, April 26 at 4:00 p.m. ET for an exciting, cross-platform social media event on Cancer Prevention and Screening, with a focus on #CervicalCancer. Stay tuned for more info. https://t.co/C2fBNEzUO9 #NothingWillStopUs #CancerScreening https://t.co/JxQESQCh2O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HHS_Global: Congratulations to the @ACTAccelerator on its year anniversary and all the achievements it has accomplished. @HHSgov is com]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Knowledge gained from the #HumanPlacentaProject (HPP) may one day help treat common #pregnancy complications. Join @NICHD_NIH for the virtual HPP2021 meeting, May 1011, to learn about promising #placental #research. https://t.co/UhQin6nR1n #MaternalHealthNICHD https://t.co/E0ZIzSZw0c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PHEgov: The Hospital Preparedness Program (HPP) bolsters health care preparedness in every state, territory  freely associated state i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HHS_ASH: Truly glad to support our friends @MinorityHealth in getting everyone to become #VaccineReady for National Minority Health Mon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While some people have no side effects after getting their #COVID19 vaccine, others may experience mild and common side effects. Here is what you might experience when getting your #vaccine. Learn more: https://t.co/6fVkG1pj4U. https://t.co/eHD0xf3H5s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) plays a role in vaccine safety monitoring, including #COVID19 vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In his recent blog post, @NIHDirector details a new study from Sweden about #LongCovid symptoms in healthcare workers who had mild cases of #COVID19. @NIH  https://t.co/ppHzqq4jR6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SecBecerra: Earth Day is a day to reflect on the beauty of our planet and its relationship to our health. A healthy planet leads to hea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCgov: If you are fully vaccinated against #COVID19, you can start doing some things again, like gathering indoors with other fully va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If youre trying to get or stay healthy, it can sometimes feel overwhelming to figure out what is and isnt beneficial for your body. @NIDDKgov debunks some common nutrition myths with reliable facts: https://t.co/vU1UIg5A6c. https://t.co/4oiNg7GmYC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samhsagov:  #TakebackDay is this Saturday! Make sure to take all expired, unused, and unwanted medications to a collection site near y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @US_FDA: How much does food waste cost you and the planet each year?   Learn ways to help you do your part to reduce food loss and waste]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>