<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AWKWORDrap: State officials will continue to violate peoples rights with impunity  Ron Keine was convicted and sentenced to death fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum We cant help but be annoyed by the dude who wears shorts when its freezing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marchforwetland: Staten Island, NYCelebrate Earth Day this year by showing up for an important local cause: the cause to Save Granitev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Will_Bunch: 1. You've probably seen this picture of Georgia Gov. Brian Kemp and his gaggle of white men signing the state's voter suppr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CraigSilverman: On Tues, NYT columnist David Brooks wrote a 900-word ode to Facebook Groups. Don't look for it in the Times -- it was p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AWKWORDrap: With Judas and the Black Messiah, and the NYPD officer's admission about targeting Malcolm X, everyone's talking about the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tmorello: Hey Joe! People in USA going hungry still waiting on stimulus checks but somehow we found the money to bomb Syria.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanRather: It's impossible to comprehend 500,000 deaths. I read about those who have died. Look into their eyes in pictures. I start wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tcburkejr: Anyone else realize Ted Cruz had no problem crossing a border to give his family a better life?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This right here  thanks for being YOU @NelStamp https://t.co/zxo0v3IiP9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: Everyone is trying to cancel Ted Cruz just because took a vacation at the Ritz in Cancun while millions of his constituents]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @miaraemcdonald: @SandyforCouncil @TxJailProject is raising funds to support folks in jail  their families across texas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hey_melly: I created this Mutual Aid Directory with other Texas Sunrise Movement members please share and boost   https://t.co/Ib5VCz6u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandyforCouncil Pinned to the top of our profile is a running list in English and Spanish. Tag us with more and we can signal boost, too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NativeOrganizer: With @RepDebHaaland as Interior Secretary, she will be the most powerful Native politician in the nation, and the firs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IENearth: Everything happening in Texas right now is absolutely climate chaos caused by climate change.  There are pockets of vulnerabl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IENearth: TEXAS MUTUAL AID THREAD:  We will update this thread as we find resources of folks doing direct mutual aid to their communiti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_400and1: +Hotel rooms that we have booked at Hotel Indigo where well provide food, toiletries, reparations and emergency transportati]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_400and1: +Canvas tents pictured here near a generator, campfires, and propane fueled heaters where we are providing reparations, elect]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_400and1: We need: +Volunteer drivers with snow safe vehicles to transport folx to hotels. +Volunteer cooks to keep the hot food coming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_400and1: If you need help or have donations, please contact us at 512-720-9037 or head to Rosewood Park.  #MartialtheBlock #Abolishthe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_400and1: Resources we have and donations we need, a thread:   +Beds at 400+1 headquarters in Orisha Land, where we are providing repar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: We made over 151,000 calls to senior citizens in Texas tonight. One of our vols talked to a man stranded at home w/out pow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: DALLAS RESOURCES:   Warming center serving Dallas, Denton, Ellis  Rockwall counties: https://t.co/g5BN1GfEUR   Donate to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: FORT WORTH  TARRANT COUNTY RESOURCES:   Warming centers, shelters and housing for families in need: https://t.co/8gzHXRk4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: AUSTIN RESOURCES:  Call 512-305-4233 for warming center  211 for transportation   Donate to: Austin Area Urban League: ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: HOUSTON RESOURCES:  Need help: dial 211   Warming Centers: https://t.co/vQhOPwlcob  To help:  Volunteer Houston https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @isamar_news: In the link below, we are posting the different organizations and businesses helping the community with meals, charging st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @isamar_news: Below are links to warming centers and free hot meals in the #RGV we will continue to update with new info when available]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: RGV RESOURCES:   For help: dial 211   To find a warming center https://t.co/dcmhozOSvp  To help: RGV Food Bank: https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ConorKenny: For my non-Texans, its hard to convey how fd our state is. Its barely broken freezing since Sunday. Half of Austin has b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PLEASE RT  SHARE:  A great running list of resources for the #TexasWinterStorm2021 #texaspoweroutage complied by @dox_gay  @itsa_talia   https://t.co/zKGdq0uYTi  #TexasBlackout #Texas #MutualAid #TexasPowerGrid #TexasStorm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @XaviercMiller: If youre in Dallas or Houston  need shelter fill out this form so we can contact you and get you a room ASAP. Zero jud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @irishrygirl: I bet if Texas renamed their power grid to uterus, the state would be regulating the shit out of it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PortlandDSA: Armed guards protecting free, edible food in dumpsters that will go to waste if no one takes it. This is not a sign of a f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KitOConnell: If you want to help some of the most vulnerable folks in #AustinTX during the #TexasFreeze, this is a verified fundraiser]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @al___jo: @OccupySandy @BostonJoan Ah sorry Austin Mutual Aid is the org name, mistyped]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @al___jo: @OccupySandy @BostonJoan Venmo austinmutualaidhotels to help cover hotel rooms  other supplies for the week for unhoused folk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Public_Citizen: Reminder: The Green New Deal is cheaper than a climate apocalypse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @evanasmith: Some of the many, many stories about the storm on @texastribune's homepage right now. This is journalism in the public inte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @byjayroot: Third night without power in the #Zilker area of Austin, TX. I have an 88 year old neighbor with no power, no gas. Nothing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanRather: The situation is dire in Austin. Were without power and heat with no end in sight amidst frigid temperatures. My wife and I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tell us about any mutual aid / community-led efforts responding to the #texaspoweroutage and how people can help, so we can help signal boost. #TexasWinterStorm2021 #TexasFreeze #texas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AWKWORDrap: Public defender @GalvinAlmanza took what she learned at @3strikesproject @BronxDefenders and developed a holistic approach]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maxberger And one is about to lose their majorities in the midterms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DanMartillo should be fired. https://t.co/rluwfc60DQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RIP #RickyPowell. One of the realest. A legend. Loved the people. New York Shitty Kid. https://t.co/7JtH6B944R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RBReich: If Redditors rallying GameStop is unacceptable market manipulation, what would you call it when greedy Wall Street bankers gam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#OccupyWallStreet all day all week. https://t.co/SbBPlR3UiX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mollycrabapple: I'm convinced that the way the US handled the pandemic was designed in part to liquidate small businesses and small pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mollycrabapple: I am gutted for every single bar owner who has had to shut down for nearly a year, but go through their life's savings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexanderMcCoy4: Just an observation about the media:  Weve gotten dozens of request from political reporters asking to be connected w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @daithaigilbert: If you have a friend or family member who is a QAnon believer then today is probably the best opportunity you will get]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TexasTribune: 1/ Dallas County officials halted a plan that would have prioritized COVID-19 vaccine doses for people living in the most]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @B20e: I'm an ER Nurse in Seattle. Last night @SeattlePD officers came to the ER to obtain a statement from an assault patient. One offi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepKClark: On the House floor, my colleague @CoriBush and I both called out the white supremacy at the root of the attack on our democr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HowardMortman: Abraham Lincoln bust ... White House ... 2:09pm https://t.co/V56sPU81Yy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katherineefoley: 4/x ...If vaccines only prevent a person from getting sick, they could *maybe* still give the virus to others. Which i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katherineefoley: 3/x To get Covid-19, your body has to be sufficiently overwhelmed with SARS-CoV-2. To get there, SARS-CoV-2 has to hav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: 8. https://t.co/JhoV1QDaTS heard from several other major RAGA donors.   @Yelp ($15,375) said it was "suspending and reviewi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: UPDATE: @KPMG tells https://t.co/Gl6evXRDcZ that it "is imposing a moratorium on contributions to Members of Congress who su]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: BLOOMBERG: "Facebook, Doordash Halt Donations to Republican AGs"   https://t.co/nl8rbL9P0v https://t.co/xuY0qMMnEI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: UPDATE: A few days ago @Walmart  said it would conduct a "review over the coming months" about its political donations  Now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuddLegum: UPDATE: In a statement to https://t.co/Gl6evXRDcZ, @HollandHart says "going forward" it will "not contribute to the election]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @SmithfieldFoods @Edison_Electric @RIAA @ItsDocumented Is there a spreadsheet of the total $$$ that has been pulled so far?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenboebert Hey @GooglePay, why are you allowing the woman who gave insurrectionists a tour of the Capitol on Jan 5 to use your services to collect donations? @slpng_giants]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: SoberingCNN reporter @sarasidnerCNN crying on air after seeing devastation at California 10 hospitals full of #COVID19 pat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what #DefundThePolice means. https://t.co/ErgWPC1NDy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MorganStanley @Cisco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: Solid move by Airbnb to Block and Cancel D.C. Reservations During Inauguration...   Moreover, We also will reimburse hos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maustermuhle: This is big: @Airbnb is cancelling reservations in the D.C. area during Inauguration Week. Existing reservations will be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkLevineNYC: BREAKING: New York City moving to sever Trump Org contracts to run 4 businesses in NYC Parks.  Covers Wollman Ice Rink,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Disney... 3/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Visa @RaytheonTech @gofundme @blackrock @SmithfieldFoods @UnionPacific @CMEGroup BP, Microsoft, Archer Daniels, State Street Corp, Signature Bank, @DeutscheBank, @UnionPacific, Smithfield Foods, Johnson  Johnson, @BankofAmerica 2/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Candidates who support the coup have been dropped by @Walmart, @Hallmark, @amazon, @Google @MarriottBonvoy, @bcbs_companies @Airbnb @ATT @AmexBusiness @dow @generalelectric @comcast @BestBuy @Verizon @jpmorgan @GoldmanSachs @WellsFargo @Ford @Citi @stripe @TysonFoods ... 1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pbump: From day before the election to day after the riots, 30% of the 10 Facebook posts with most engagement in a day were from right-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @slpng_giants: Bingo.   Dont thank @facebook for banning Trump now. Theyve profited mightily from the same rhetoric they booted him fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @slpng_giants: .@Facebook: Violence has no place on our platform.* . . . . . . . . . *unless youd like to pay $300 in advertising fees,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KCA207 @Psychomommy13 @FrankenforIowa It was called the "Fair and Balanced Act"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Psychomommy13: @FrankenforIowa 100%. Armybrat - grew up outside/had first job on Ft. Campbell - Fox was everywhere. You couldn't escape]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KrauseForIowa: @FrankenforIowa I have the same concern. Why? While visiting military bases across the country over the years, I've seen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @apuchine: @FrankenforIowa This has upset me for years that FOX is the only channel that is streamed to our troops. I should be rotated]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrankenforIowa: As the commander of military forces in E Africa, I asked the American Forces Network (TV) to replace Fox news during me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aaronlikethecar: The Supreme Court ruled that Amazon doesnt have to pay its employees to stand in line for up to 30 minutes after thei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emulvey2001: @RaySalemi @jaysbookman @EggerDC https://t.co/7oaOgH5dwv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaysbookman: Parler has sued Amazon for refusing to provide it web services, and conservatives have rallied to Parler's defense, claimi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CTZebra: More than 4400 people died of #covid19 yesterday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreeNewsome: Just so were all clear, Trump committed impeachable offenses from the time he was sworn in. What changed is he became a m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atrupar Hey @NancyMace, be careful, or @Hallmark might be demanding their donations back https://t.co/FtBVyILTNX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joshHuder: Something that completely evaded me when I initially read Rep. Mikie Sherrills accusation (that some members were giving re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuneMcMullen4: @ForwardLeaning @LLLwry @jsrailton https://t.co/nRkrV3P0Cn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernieSanders: Let's make it permanent by ending Citizens United, abolishing super PACs, getting big money out of politics, and moving]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joncoopertweets: FUN FACT: New York City has announced that it will terminate all contracts with the Trump Organization following the d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PaulCogan: Hitler was found guilty of treason and sentenced to five years in prison after the Beer Hall Putsch. He served nine months b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MEPFuller: Louie Gohmert just walked around the magnetometer.  You cant stop me; Im on my way to a vote, he said as he passed the c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jadeecee1: @LindstromCheryl @CNN These three? https://t.co/G82DZISWsR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamaalBowmanNY: He should tell that to kids across the country who have to walk through them to get into public schools.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EoinHiggins_: According to Ayanna Pressleys chief of staff Sarah Groh, the panic buttons in the Congresswomans office were all torn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hungrybowtie: In a Proud Boys telegram channel with nearly 30,000 subscribers. Thousands have joined since Parler went down. https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RailroadUnderg1: My niece's teacher doesn't help her with her hw. So today I got to help her with her homework on Zoom, from a prison c]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>