<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DMacPhersonLab: A postdoc position is available in my lab @fredhutch, a stellar place to train.  Projects available to understand new t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RemyDulery: Inhospital stay is prolonged and mortality is higher after #Covid_19 among patients with #lymphoma treated with Bcell dep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarenFreundMD @hboucher3 @TuftsMedicalCtr @tufts_id Congrats @hboucher3!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tmhohl71: I cannot think of a better example to argue for vaccination. Vaccination shows that you care about the people around you. Thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JAMANetworkOpen: In Hong Kong, a cross-sectional #COVID19 pediatric study involving 397 children showed that households, not schools, w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCDirector: Today,@POTUShighlighted how we plan to bring #COVID19 vaccines to people by meeting them where they are. To do this, we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kakape ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @martinhoenigl: Candida auris cases clearly increased in US during COVID pandemic. @tom_tchill at the @MRCcmm @neil_gow Workshop on Anti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SajalTanna: I have been caring for COVID-19 patients for over a year in Chicago.  COVID-19 in India is beyond my worst nightmares. Like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Having trouble finding a vaccine?  Just text your zip code to 438829 to find locations near you. https://t.co/AjeYh4CZEg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baby Yoda (aka Grogu) agrees - #GetVaccinatedASAP on #MayTheFourth   He needs to be protected as he is over 50 after all..... https://t.co/Lc1o3tlaY3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megtirrell: Pfizer plans to file for full approval of its #covid19 vaccine at the end of May, per its slide deck just posted for Q1 ear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@martinhoenigl @tom_tchill @MRCcmm Has this been published? - very concerning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @martinhoenigl: In US there is a 4-fold increase in azole fungicide use in agriculture. Will this translate to increasing azole resitanc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All of my @IDSAInfo colleagues - take a moment to remember a fallen ID professor and leader #RIP  #COVID19 https://t.co/MkLVapC8nZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tmhohl71: (1) I am saddened to report the untimely passing of Dr. Rajendra Kapila, Professor of Medicine at Rutgers New Jersey Medical]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May the force be with you on May the  fourth. #MayThe4thBeWithYou   Want to be strong enough to pull the ears off a gundark?  #GetVaccinated https://t.co/HDATRxAtCN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep talking to your patients, your family, your neighbors and your friends as it makes a difference when they hear get vaccinated from someone they trust  Every time your speak up you help get more of America #vaccinated https://t.co/uMuRABBMRg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WSMA_update: In the Seattle area, more people in their 20s are now being hospitalized for #COVID19 than people in their 70s. COVID can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @camwolfe: My little 2 vaccine study bunnies getting kiddy Pfizer dose #2  @DukeHealth   Eldest (7) asked me after: "dad, why dont all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVID19nCCC: Association of Clinical Factors and Recent Anti-Cancer Therapy with COVID-19 Severity among Patients with Cancer: A Report]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news  F.D.A. Set to Authorize Pfizer Vaccine for Adolescents by Early Next Week - The New York Times https://t.co/dc5pfQKVtW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[University of Washington @UW joins the list of schools that will require #COVID19 #vaccines for all students.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maiamajumder: When it comes to data, our values show in who we choose to count. This past year, "[t]racking the spread of the #coronavi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: If we did not have this background of vaccination, we would be completely overwhelmed right now, said Dr. @joshua_schiffer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenChuMD: Our results from a pilot study of an at-home rapid antigen test for flu with results in 15 min. Key findings: 73% sensitive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Viral genomes reveal patterns of the SARS-CoV-2 outbreak in Washington State | Science Translational Medicine https://t.co/WMNrgPX98v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey @EStohs - make sure your APPs see this! https://t.co/VCc4klvmiU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trvrb: Just as we can decompose the US #COVID19 epidemic into a B.1.1.7 epidemic and a non-B.1.1.7 epidemic, we can further partition b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tragic considering all we do to avoid wasting doses   CVS, Walgreens have wasted more Covid vaccine doses than most states combined https://t.co/aWoMpo3OJl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HutchIDScience: ICYMI - @fredhutch is hiring a Clinical Research Coordinator to work with @PergamIC  Dr. Liu and her #abxstewardship]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Adults who have recently tested positive for coronavirus may be eligible to participate in new investigational treatment stu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtmdphd: @ACasadevall1 ...with caveat that later use (eg ICU or ventilated patient) appears to still have benefit in patients with hema]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eliowa @hint Spindrift fan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Adityaiims ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheTxIDjournal: An important letter to the editor describing two cases of breakthrough #COVID-19 cases post-vaccine in SOT recipients,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KatesOlivia: It was an incredible and somewhat surreal experience to work on this project from the fall of 2019 to today. Thank you to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets continue to get more people vaccinated to protect those in our communities who might have limited responses to vaccines - the more of us that do it the more protected cancer patients, organ transplants and those with immunodeficiencies can thrive #VaccinesWork https://t.co/xb7zVWWxzl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocJeffD @SeattleCCA ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DocJeffD: We depend on one another for protection from CoV-19, especially people who might not respond to vaccine because they have a w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoshuaHillMD: JCI Insight - Antibodies to vaccine-preventable infections after CAR-T-cell therapy for B-cell malignancies https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Was identified as having an exposure to someone with #COVID19 by the WA notify app on my phone - got tested and Im negative.  A great system that can only help us identify more cases and prevent spread. #wanotify  Sign up if you havent already https://t.co/0Kk0RIVPgO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BogochIsaac: Effect of 1st dose of #COVID19 vaccine on reducing hospital admissions at day 28-34 (real world data from Scotland):  *Pfi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Boghuma: Case series CVST after Ad26.CoV2.S 12  All All &lt;60y/o 11/12 presented with headache  7/12 with intra-cerebral bleeding]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tmhohl71: How does the #ClimateEmergency promote human disease by #fungi ? Habitat expansion, among others...for a great perspective se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntiVaxWatchOrg: In order to stop the proliferation of life-threatening anti-vaccine disinformation, @Facebook, @Instagram  @Twitter m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HutchIDScience: Hutch IDS is hiring a Clinical Research Coordinator to work w/@PergamIC, Dr. Liu,  Dr. Fredricks (@HutchMRI). GREAT #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pavitrarc: Just posted: our preprint looking at #SARSCoV2 in longitudinal clinical specimens. Work led by Michelle Lin from @GreningerL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheTxIDjournal: Starting May 1, @TheTxIDjournal will have a new Editorial Leadership Group: Editor-in-Chief:  Mike Ison @MichaelGIsonMD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelGIsonMD: I am so excited to start to make changes at the Journal with a group of leaders in the field. We have some exciting cha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking forward to helping  @TxIDjournal and to working with such amazing colleagues at the journal #TxID https://t.co/nfjXSneg2d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoxbyMD: Vaccinating at Mercy housing Magnussen!! @kcpubhealth @scca @Fredhutch  Pro tip: have a relaxed sign in area where people have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paimadhu ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VirusesImmunity: After many months of planning and hard work by so many (incl. @hmkyale @Dianaberrent @wade_schulz @CharleszYaleMed @Aa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: Join me in signing this   https://t.co/JWVfCM824c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@choo_ek That is ridiculous - were there other comments that wanted you to address?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterHotez: Many thanks @KatyOnMSNBC @KatyTurNBC i offered that based on Israel and now New Hampshire in US we should not expect vi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KCPubHealth: Were offering 1000 walk-in vaccinations each day (no appointment needed!) Mon-Sat at Kent, accesso ShoWare,  Auburn Outl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More data that suggests cancer patients do not respond as well to COVID-19 vaccines - they SHOULD get them, but they need to remain cautious post-vaccination.   + getting family members and close contacts vaccinated can help prevent transmission. https://t.co/gq3KGTCnk8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GermHunterMD: This patient with mantle cell lymphoma on rituximab, bendamustine  cytarabine remained SARS-CoV-2 PCR+ for 268 days, cul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimLaheyMD: National study shows we are still not educating physicians who are representative of the communities they serve  #SDoH http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRealDoctorT Wow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Fred Hutch Biostatistician Peter Gilbert is leading the data analysis team for research comparing antibody levels in people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aprilkaurphd @RoxbyMD @Obliteride And I am #2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chansen9 @RealTimeCOVID19 From the original trial 28 days for full protection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulSaxMD @zeynep and the immunosuppressed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alexander_Tin: In addition to revising its guidelines for the general public, @CDCgov's updated recommendations yesterday also urged he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for having us and continuing to educate the public #RealTimeVaccineChat https://t.co/7L5ZYRF6S4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A10: I am most curious about when Novavax might become available. Wonder where it is in the system as it would be great to have another vaccine available. #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SHANINAKNIGHTON @RealTimeCOVID19 I wish people got a day off so they could get vaccinated - a vaccine holiday to help address this issue  #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewPaviaMD: A9 Agree with everything that's been said about improving access and convenience, but also it is easy to transport and s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JGPharmD: @PergamIC Agreed. Even with the negative impressive left by the JJ vaccine pause, there will still be plenty of people who e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[there have been a number of people who want a single dose vaccine.  Hard for those who work full time, those who work night shift, have large families, etc. to get time away - so a single dose shot can be helpful.  #RealTimeVaccineChat https://t.co/YTeBtoQ9R0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't compare efficacy from trials as they were done at different times - rates were higher for vector vaccines trials ( in areas w/variants).  There are all effective - although AZ appeared to be slightly less effective against B.1.351 #RealTimeVaccineChat  #RealTimeVaccineChat https://t.co/1d1ATrPh5e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewPaviaMD: The Oxford-AZ vaccine has pretty similar efficacy overall Note that the studies  in different settings and times. One  d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A6: It is also important to remember full protection doesn't occur until 2 weeks after second dose of mRNA vaccines, and 4 weeks after JJ dose  So consider the timing when you consider getting together too  #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewPaviaMD: A6 Being with a few people who you know are fully vaccinated is different than being with unvaccinated people, those who]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maricar_malinis: @PergamIC Yes, completely agree. Host factors need to be taken into consideration.#RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dr_Mike_Stevens: @RealTimeCOVID19 A6. Being vaccinated for #COVID19 helps you get a little closer back to a pre-pandemic life. See this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new CDC guidance here is very helpful for the general public.  But again if you are immunocompromised - I tell these patients to remain cautious. We need herd immunity to protect the most vulnerable and why need more vaccinated.  #RealTimeVaccineChat https://t.co/elH7zUfmOp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fact that JJ is back and in use will help to get more Americans vaccinated.  Having a single dose vaccine has major advantages.  The key is that the clotting is exceedinly rare ~1 in 1 million.  And risk of clotting if you get COVID10 is much higher  #RealTimeVaccineChat https://t.co/zCFW3ARD9G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dr_Mike_Stevens: @RealTimeCOVID19 A5.  The #JohnsonandJohnson #COVID19 vaccine is associated w/ VERY rare risk of thrombosis w/ thrombo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JGPharmD @mhtwt Like this idea too @JGPharmD   It may be that one is better than another for particular patients populations.  But for now - get the first one available to you!  #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SICUPharmD @RealTimeCOVID19 @SCCM I am cautious about this interpretation as the JJ vaccine is the only one studied directly in South Africa.  The data for mRNA vaccines is laboratory neutralization so isn't the same thing - plus JJ still protected against major complications with B.1.351 #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mhtwt @JGPharmD Great question - currently with the need to get vaccines out to everyone that is the first goal.  Studies are definitely ongoing to address this  #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewPaviaMD: A2 The good news is that being on cancer chemotherapy, rheumatologic drugs, or any other immune compromising condition i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A2: Finally, to close the loop on this question. Immunosuppressed patients should continue to mask up, social distance and avoid crowds. Being cautious is key.  Frustrating (I get it) but crucial  #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A2: For immunosuppressed patients it is also key to get family, caregivers, household members and close contacts vaccinated as this can be key to protection if they don't respond as well to vaccination.   See here https://t.co/lnNBfcF47w #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[too much to say so couldn't add #RealTimeVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A2: The data is still out for all patients, but vaccine responses in imnumosuppressed patients will not be at levels of the general public.  However - getting vaccinated is still key for these patients populations @NCCN guidelines for cancer patients here https://t.co/t7m1YfkKyX https://t.co/Ch7D1dAcQu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A bit late - Steve Pergam, MD, MPH from @fredhutch representing the immunocompromised host - great to talk to #COVID19Vaccines  #RTLNVaccineChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesEKHildreth: COVID-19 is still a public health crisis and will be until enough of us are vaccinated to end it. As long as significa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congrats to my brother in law @alderlab - who officially became a Professor today at @UConn   Amazing achievement for a stellar scientist (and a great dad too)  Now does he have a jacket with elbow patches? https://t.co/qsQkZUj5Q8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinEpi: This was an impressive, national effort across 24 sites and including our team at @umichsph. Excited to see these great resu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you arent following the @TheTxIDjournal - you are missing out on great content.  Excited to see where new EIC @MichaelGIsonMD is going to take the journal. #expectbigthings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drjootz: My husband is a PMR doc. Today he came home from work, proud that he was able to educate his vaccine-hesitant pt about #COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheTxIDjournal: Calling all the members of the #TxID community to start following @TheTxIDjournal.  We will be starting regular Tweets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheTxIDjournal: The April 2021 Issue is out!    Lots of articles on COVID-19 - epidemiology and management.  Other topics include manag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickKristof: I just heard that Navajo Nation, which has done a heroic job wrestling the coronavirus to the ground, is now donating extr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndrewPaviaMD What fresh horror is this?  @drkomanduri did you see this?]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>