<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[In this Mental Wellness Moment, Dr. Nicholas Mitchell provides advice on how to alleviate loneliness in yourself and others during the COVID-19 pandemic. #CMHW2021 #MentalHealthWeek https://t.co/DL7ouvDWzN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel good. I feel more comfortable, says Joseph Belanger, 44. His job takes him into a lot of peoples homes, so he made getting a COVID-19 vaccine a priority. I figured I should protect both myself and them. Everyone should get it done. #shotofhope https://t.co/xfgNq1tmUf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ab_vax Residents of the Regional Municipality of Wood Buffalo and Banff who are 18+ must book their vaccination appointment by calling Health Link at 811. The AHS online booking tool and pharmacies are not an option for this cohort at this time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get to know the signs and symptoms of heart attack and stroke: https://t.co/9MyyVPkKo5. https://t.co/Yn7MZFgJyX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ab_vax at the Camrose Community Health Centre, MacDonald Island in Fort McMurray and the Teresa Sargent Hall Montrose Cultural Centre in Grande Prairie or through participating pharmacies.   More information can be found at: https://t.co/myEaUI45JD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ab_vax Hi there. Thank you for reaching out. Limited walk-ins are available on a first come, first served basis for theAstraZeneca / Covishieldvaccine for Albertans born in 1981 or before (1991 or before for residents of Banff and Regional Municipality of Wood Buffalo)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFrenchWong @RealCdnSS @jkenney @RCMPAlberta @KayceeMaduYEG @ryanjespersen @TheBreakdownAB @sprawlcalgary @nenshi @kim_siever @kimpagegluckie @DruhFarrell Hi there, thank you for reaching out and for your concerns. The Government of Alberta and Alberta Health Services are working with local enforcement agencies to manage complaints. You can submit your concern using the form located here:https://t.co/x1W4kcYnsk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MemphisBlaze Hello, and thank you for your message. For questions about the EPH complaint process, please emailSafeHealthyEnvironments@ahs.ca.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oekle was eligible to be immunized as a part of the acute care immunization program, which is expanding to eligible patients at healthcare facilities across the province. For more information about the program, patients are asked to speak to their care team. #YEG #ShotofHope]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Book your appointment through AHS online, by calling 811, or at participating pharmacies. https://t.co/DwkoS1laTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertans 50 and older are now eligible to book for Pfizer  Moderna immunization appointments. Getting immunized against COVID-19 helps prevent serious illness, hospitalizations and death. https://t.co/KzONYRLWEi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, I like to be prepared. Id rather get the vaccine than get the sickness, says Karl Oelke, 72. He adds: Plus all my friends and relatives are getting vaccinated, and Id like to be part of that. https://t.co/q18UJfmkrt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone eligible in these communities can book through calling Health Link at 811. These appointments cannot be made through the AHS online booking tool or through pharmacies at this time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta has deployed additional vaccine supply to support the Regional Municipality of Wood Buffalo and Town of Banff. The age group eligible for immunization in these communities is now 18 years and older.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When wildfire danger is extreme, prepare for the worst and ensure your emergency preparedness kit is stocked: https://t.co/t1nAt9gEXo https://t.co/bGwsKoJ32T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobKohlman Good morning, Robert. Please connect with our colleagues in the Patient Relations department at https://t.co/wAQdxVDBKF or by calling 1-855-550-2555. They are here to help.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goodbyeAcadia Good morning, Tia: Please note, this account is not monitored by front-line healthcare providers. As such, we recommend you call Health Link at 811 for advice from a registered nurse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also eligible are child care workers and support staff from licensed child care programs including daycare programs, out-of-school care, preschool programs and family day homes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eligibility also includes school support workers including education assistants, bus drivers and custodians.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eligible Albertans include teachers from kindergarten through Grade 12 from public, separate, francophone, charter, private/independent/ECS operators, First Nations schools, substitute teachers, administrators and teachers working in separate roles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Additional Albertans are now eligible to book a COVID-19 immunization as part of phase 2C through AHS online, by calling 811, or at participating pharmacies: https://t.co/DwkoS1laTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I work on a COVID-19 unit and Im pregnant, says Michelle Lee, a Registered nurse. She has received her COVID-19 vaccine and she encourages others to also get it when they have the opportunity. Better safe than sorry. #shotofhope https://t.co/YUvE9lLbd2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feeling stressed or anxious? Heres an online toolkit designed to help: https://t.co/Vn7MrpXbML  #CMHW2021 #MentalHealthWeek https://t.co/GN7i7wzTwx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's #MentalHealthWeek, and it's a time to reflect on the small things we can do for our positive mental health. Now more than ever, we need check in with ourselves, our family and our friends. https://t.co/QtQVtckDXM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To prepare for this next wave of eligible Albertans, the AHS online tool will be unavailable tomorrow from 7:30 to 8 a.m. Bookings will begin at 8 a.m.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Child care workers and support staff from licensed child care programs including daycare programs, out of school care, preschool programs and family day homes are also eligible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eligibility also includes Albertans who work in support roles at schools including education assistants, bus drivers and custodians.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eligible Albertans will include teachers from kindergarten through Grade 12 from public, separate, francophone, charter, private/independent/ECS operators, First Nations schools, substitute teachers, administrators and teachers working in separate roles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomorrow at 8 a.m., additional Albertans will be eligible to book a COVID-19 immunization through AHS online, by calling Health Link 811 or through participating pharmacies: https://t.co/4sbyOxM4gV https://t.co/xzCuC39Cmt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChinookParkCBE @yyCBEdu Thank you, Chinook Park kindergarteners. We will pass this on to our colleagues at Rockyview :-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Edmonton Mayor @doniveson talks about his experience receiving the #covidvaccine #shotofhope https://t.co/6HHnz6XhZh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarieMcElroy7 Hi Marie. Thank you for reaching out. For this type of question, we suggest you contact Health Link at 811 for more information.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Corrected link: https://t.co/x8IgPSi2Ga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garysdeskcom @CMOH_Alberta Hi Gary. Thanks for bringing this to our attention. Here is the correct link: https://t.co/x8IgPSi2Ga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lisagrono @jkenney @shandro @YourAlberta @CFgetloud @CFCanada Hi Lisa! Thank you for sharing this with us. Do you mind if we used your son's picture in our social media channels? Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sweetness4713 Hi there. Thank you for reaching out. For information on eligibility for COVID-19 immunization in Phase 2B, including for those with diabetes, please visithttps://t.co/k1D6iMOdfz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Garner Patton, 54, was eligible to receive his COVID-19 vaccine as a part of the AHS long-stay, acute care immunization program. He wanted to get the COVID-19 vaccine so he doesnt have to worry about getting the disease. Im very happy, he says. #YEG #ShotofHope https://t.co/VeeoimTpkr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnmarkowsky Thank you John. We'll amend that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone showing cold or flu-like symptoms, even if these are mild, should stay home and complete the COVID-19 online self-assessment. Visit https://t.co/BdqfLt1Gu2. #covid19ab https://t.co/etfijKqzTn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 immunization appointments are available for those born in 1971 or before and First Nations, Inuit  Metis born in 1986 or before. Please share this eligibility chart widely with your social networks  book your appointment today. More: https://t.co/lozOFgWNl6 #shotofhope https://t.co/fbt0WUGyVD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im a healthcare worker and I work with patients. Its just more protection for myself, says Bonnie Carlson, 56, about why she chose to get the COVID-19 vaccine. #shotofhope https://t.co/irEGt0jdUs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel happy. I feel relieved, says Antonio Del Re, 88, about receiving his COVID-19 vaccine. It feels good. #shotofhope https://t.co/z7NPrbZbIK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shannon Dunfield, manager of AHS North Zone Indigenous, French Health and Diversity, gives the thumbs up as she receives her COVID-19 vaccine in Grande Prairie. https://t.co/tQXOsHyy0i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next week Im going for my second practicum as a healthcare aide. I want to be safe, says Evangeline Bona, 41. She has advice for others who are thinking of getting the COVID-19 vaccine when its their turn: Dont think twice. Just grab the opportunity. #ShotofHope #YEG https://t.co/KWXUWTTCvE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any COVID-19 vaccine you get will lower your risk of getting seriously ill from COVID-19. Itll also lower your risk of needing to be in the hospital. Learn more about the vaccines available in Canada: https://t.co/q0VFiVZQZn https://t.co/rIYu9XKUAV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not all cases of #COVID19ab require hospitalization. Many cases are mild and can be dealt with at home. If you are caring for a person who has been diagnosed with COVID-19, follow this advice to protect yourself and others in the home, as well as those in your community. https://t.co/CI3FIm93wA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CMOH_Alberta: Were making a small update to how youth born in 2006-09 (turning 12-15) with eligible underlying health conditions in Ph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is #NationalPhysiciansDay, and we honour the more than 10,000 physicians working tirelessly to care for Albertans during the COVID-19 pandemic and beyond. https://t.co/uUPJBrdjxG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone showing cold or flu-like symptoms, even if these are mild, should stay home and complete the COVID-19 online self-assessment. Visit https://t.co/BdqfLt1Gu2. #covid19ab https://t.co/sod0XnoRuS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cbrownrogers As walk-ins are limited, we encourage eligible Albertans to book an appointment using the online booking tool.   Any additional changes to Fort McMurray walk-in clinic hours will be posted here (https://t.co/9pPQtvpbPm) and on our social media channels.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cbrownrogers Hi Christie. Limited AstraZeneca walk-ins continue to be offered in Fort McMurray at our immunization centre. Walk-ins are available this weekend between 9:30 a.m and 3 p.m. and next Monday-Friday between 9 a.m. and 9 p.m.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its good science. Its good for me and its good for the culture. It doesnt have any down sides really, says Randy Schroeder, 56. #shotofhope https://t.co/KJhgWzeTgX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CayenneChai Great! Thank you very much.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CayenneChai Hi Natalie! Thank you for sharing this with us. Do you mind if we used your picture on our social media channels? Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shawn Briscoe, 55, knows why he signed up for his COVID-19 vaccine this month. So I dont get sick. #shotofhope https://t.co/841ijecECx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Up to 25 per cent of adults have fears or worries about needles. There are steps you can take before your immunization to help reduce anxiety. For resources, visit: https://t.co/6T61QVa5L4 https://t.co/sRvZkakydO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SHN006 Hi Sham! Thank you for reaching out. The vaccine being administered to those eligible in Phases 2C and 2D are mRNA vaccines (this includes Pfizer and Moderna). More information about the COVID-19 vaccine can be found on our website: https://t.co/kNA7cwJkSr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CrazyDo99574335 Hello, and thank you for bringing this to our attention. We value patient input and take all concerns very seriously. Please contact our Patient Relations department -- they are here to help: https://t.co/wAQdxVDBKF or call 1-855-550-2555.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DashOfV Hi there! Thank you for reaching out. The vaccine being administered to those eligible in Phases 2C and 2D are mRNA vaccines (this includes Pfizer and Moderna). More information about the COVID-19 vaccine can be found on our website: https://t.co/kNA7cwJkSr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@litui Hello, Aria, and and thank you for reaching out. To update your Alberta Health Care Card, please visit https://t.co/WC7E7jclSz.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Phase 2D includes Albertans born 1957 to 1971 (turning 50 to 64) and First Nations, Mtis and Inuit (FNMI) persons born 1972 to 1986 (turning 35 to 49), no matter where they live. #shotofhope]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Other caregivers included in this cohort include those caring for children 11 and under who have an eligible chronic condition but were unable to receive vaccine due to age, as well as household contacts of profoundly immunocompromised individuals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eligibility also includes designated family and support people of individuals in long term care, designated supportive living and licensed supportive living facilities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This includes frontline police, Alberta sheriffs, firefighters, CBSA staff, staff/residents who provide/receive care in facilities including frontline disability workers  those providing mental health/addiction treatment, pediatric group care or other licensed supportive living.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Additional Albertans are now eligible to book a COVID-19 immunization as part of phase 2C and 2D through AHS online https://t.co/DwkoS1laTH, by calling Health Link 811 or participating pharmacies. https://t.co/Q4MSzGcDI3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please continue to follow public health measures in order to protect yourself  others from COVID-19even if you've been vaccinated. This includes keeping two metres apart, wearing a mask in public, and staying home when sick. More info: https://t.co/BdqfLtjhSC #covid19ab https://t.co/DzXqq6eO5N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @doniveson: I am so grateful to have received the #AstraZeneca vaccine today! I encourage all Edmontonians to get vaccinated as soon as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are aware of fake text messages telling people to isolate for 28 days. AHS is not sending these texts, and the information contained in them is inaccurate. For information on isolation and quarantine requirements, visit https://t.co/JyQ49RIwBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realmarkwells @AHS_YEGZone another. Please let the triage nurse know so they can reassess your health concerns. You can also reach out to our Patient Relations team  they are here to help: https://t.co/PmB2WKmJOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realmarkwells @AHS_YEGZone Due to changing demands in emergency departments, these wait times may not be the time you will need to wait once you arrive at the emergency department. The provision of the wait times on the AHS website are not medical advice or a recommendation of one emergency department over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realmarkwells @AHS_YEGZone Hi Mark. Thank you for reaching out.Wait times can change significantly and immediately, without warning and therefore are not guaranteed. Patients will be seen in the emergency department based on their medical condition and the severity of their situation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To prepare for this next wave of eligible Albertans, the AHS online tool will be unavailable tomorrow from 7 a.m. to 8 a.m. Bookings will begin at 8 a.m.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Phase 2D includes Albertans born 1957 to 1971 (turning 50 to 64) and First Nations, Mtis and Inuit (FNMI) persons born 1972 to 1986 (turning 35 to 49), no matter where they live.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Other caregivers included in this cohort include those caring for children 11 and under who have an eligible chronic condition but were unable to receive vaccine due to age, as well as household contacts of profoundly immunocompromised individuals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[living. Eligibility also includes designated family and support people of individuals in long term care, designated supportive living and licensed supportive living facilities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This includes frontline police, Alberta sheriffs, firefighters, CBSA staff, staff/residents who provide or receive care in facilities including frontline disability workers  those providing mental health/addiction treatment, pediatric group care or other licensed supportive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting tomorrow at 8 a.m., additional Albertans will be eligible to book a COVID-19 immunization as part of phase 2C and 2D through AHS online https://t.co/DwkoS1laTH, by calling Health Link 811 or participating pharmacies. https://t.co/0OWqL9GmCl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Balraj Mann, 48, knows exactly why she signed up to get her COVID-19 vaccine in Edmonton. To protect everybody I love and care for, including the community. #shotofhope https://t.co/VJDZChtTgV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The rest of Phase 2C and 2D vaccine COVID-19 vaccine opens tomorrow morning. More info below... https://t.co/IrJo4FcRtm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ivereadthisblog If your symptoms worsen, call Health Link at 811. Call 911 if you are seriously ill and need immediate medical attention. Inform them that you may have COVID-19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ivereadthisblog Please check more than one site in the online booking tool for the earliest available appointment date and check back regularly. We ask that you cancel any booked appointments that you do not plan to use.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ivereadthisblog Hi, Anne:We are working hard to address the recent surge in testing requests. While appointments fill quickly, and some locations fill faster than others, new appointments are opened each day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeterPlansIt Hello, Lyla: For this matter, we recommend you call Health Link at 811 for their advice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alberta, we love seeing the photos you are sharing after you receive your COVID-19 vaccine. Please keep them coming and tag @AHS_media #ShotofHope https://t.co/9v7PjAjB0X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even if your symptoms are mild, stay home and fill out the online self-assessment to see if you need a COVID test. https://t.co/o6tKXDOXBz https://t.co/BZOTJ7CI9p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rapid testing is an important pillar of Albertas COVID-19 testing program, providing faster diagnosis to help reduce spread of the virus. APL has completed more than 100,000 rapid tests on those with symptoms and/or close contacts to date. Learn more: https://t.co/JfrUcPZw7u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albertans who qualify for COVID-19 testing may be offered a rapid point-of-care test when they arrive for their test appointment. Learn more about what you can expect if you choose to receive a rapid test in this video: https://t.co/mjcGWIn5fW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting the vaccine means looking forward to getting out, doing some patio work, getting out with the kids. Were looking forward to the grandkids, says Alan Johnson, 76. #ShotofHope https://t.co/ZFYZzg7Gzl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanyZhen Hi there, thank you for reaching out and for your concerns. The Government of Alberta and Alberta Health Services are working with local enforcement agencies to manage complaints. You can submit your concern using the form located here: https://t.co/x1W4kcYnsk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is National Day of Mourning. Join us as we remember our colleagues and Canadians who have lost their lives, been injured, or suffered an illness in the workplace. Flags are flying at half-mast at all our facilities in honour of the day. https://t.co/ZqL6ZMZE8t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I just feel good that I was able to get a vaccination, says Paddy Ehrhardt, 64. It helps me and helps others, right? #Shotofhope https://t.co/jVN2uHY3fi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RhondaVuch Awesome, thank you very much! Very appreciated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RhondaVuch @calgarytransit Hi Rhonda! Thank you for reaching out. Would it be okay if we used your picture on our social media channels? Thanks again!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MelyndaCrampton Hi, Melynda and thanks for reaching out. This account is not monitored by front-line healthcare professionals. Please call Health Link at 811 to speak with a registered nurse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wanted to get vaccinated to keep everyone safe: myself, my family, everyone around me, says Aimee Winegarden, 41. She received her first COVID-19 vaccine this month. I signed up as soon as I could. I couldnt wait to get this done. #shotofhope https://t.co/eUWr6chr9J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuneAndrews_YYC @youseepeeYYC @kim_siever @Crackmacs Hi June, thank you for reaching out and for your concerns. The Government of Alberta and Alberta Health Services are working with local enforcement agencies to manage complaints. You can submit your concern using the form located here: https://t.co/x1W4kcYnsk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone showing cold or flu-like symptoms, even if these are mild, should stay home and complete the COVID-19 online self-assessment. Visit https://t.co/BdqfLtjhSC. #covid19ab https://t.co/LMlmqb2EQ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The next time youre at the Calgary International Airport, you may see an unusual site. Alberta Health Services EMS has paramedics specially equipped with Segway scooters, to deal with medical emergencies. https://t.co/q6j1nmKcLg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AHS is concerned with the increasing number of cases both in the community, and in our healthcare facilities. We strongly urge Albertans to follow the public health restrictions, and in turn help us ensure the healthcare system is there when they need it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AHS currently has adequate capacity for both hospitalized and ICU patients. We are able to increase the number of ICU spaces if demand on ICU increases (as we did in November and December).]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>