<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 They are merely providing a foil for the government to implement a policy it has already decided upon - torturing children so they meekly accept vaccination.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: These people are psychopaths and shouldn't be allowed anywhere near any child at any time. https://t.co/B5htSwihVD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KeillerDon: Climate Con Now. The fake-news outlet that has captured the media. https://t.co/rJhaz5Wjdb https://t.co/6kYBQt79lF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: No tyranical government anywhere should be allowed to remain in power - they should be ousted by citizens and replaced. Thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: People who feel this way need to speak out and join together. Fear to do so is not a good option to choose. There are a lot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tan123: @ClimateOfGavin @OceansClimateCU Also you don't actually understand Earth's climate, and you're incorrectly assuming that CO2 i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanJamesSeale: @SimonPearson961 @debbie53deb No one should take ANY medicine that they don't need - and many don't Maintaining a Fit an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The lies are now the entirety of the political project. If they stop lying just once, it will fall apart, so now they must keep going, telling bigger and bigger lies, more transparent lies, more dangerous lies. Heaped one upon the other, they become self-sustaining. https://t.co/bkIs7ibqRs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1st, 2nd, 3rd, 4th, 5th . . . . . . it will never end. Get stuffed. I do not consent to enforced 'vaccination' for corporate and government profit - political and financial. Nor do I consent to democide in plain sight. https://t.co/h6KcYiWh7s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Ten days ago anti-lockdown marchers in London were gaslighted, guilt-tripped and defamed by a number of Inside the Tent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VanessaGray158: Another Fantastic video explaining how all political parties and Indian billionaires are involved in the scamdemic. htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BarryJWoods: My comment is now in it's sixth day of 'awaiting moderation" at the @GreenAllianceUK    Inside Track blog (home to green d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Roydini25 @Steve35387724 He was fired from SAGE. Supposedly. They lied about that too. They lie about everything. Literally.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shirley04101935 @DrTeckKhong Lies. Lies. Lies. Highly unlikely that these variants will evade protection from the existing 'vaccines'. Also zero chance that the variants will evade broad spectrum natural immunity. We have already passed the herd immunity threshold, largely due to natural infections. Criminal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTeckKhong: Perpetuum mobile ! https://t.co/mwStklcsYy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Nuremberg2 #NurembergCode #HumanRightsViolations https://t.co/FlzILHAmd0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @primalpeter1960: Dr. Reiner Fuellmich all the scientific evidence points to the inevitable conclusion that the pandemic is the worst cr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Dr Fauci admitted today that 32 per cent of Americans have had the 1st vaccine. Contradicts the 42% claimed by CDC. No data]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: Unlocking society is not enough. We need to unlock people from fear.   People for whom any risk is now too high.   We h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: As a small family business, its been a little lonely speaking out against lockdown, face masks and vaccine passports  W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: This is just one example of thousands of abusive messages I've received on Twitter since my video on Monday.  I'll ignore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkChangizi: Why cant you just be happy your family, friend, and entire society have been brainwashed? https://t.co/yuKajilitK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: I just don't get the people that can't accept many have been damaged by the AZ vaccine. It's as if they just can't adm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zero_to_here_oh: We need the biggest and broadest coalition ever assembled.  We must pursue civil disobedience and direct action on a s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@janekin24 They don't care. At all. People getting seriously ill or even dying is not important. Getting everyone jabbed is their single focus. We are dealing with certifiable psychopaths here. They will not stop unless they ARE stopped.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealJoelSmalley If people don't wake up and smell the coffee right now, this is going to get very, very serious indeed. DO NOT GET 'VACCINATED' UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealJoelSmalley: It's the vaccines what done it! The gall of this insidious being and his shills. https://t.co/gJdC6pgvV8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FatEmperor They are busy creating an entire self-sustaining profitable industry on the back of human suffering and death, 'vaccinating' against a disease (and its numerous, ever changing variants) which the vast majority of people are already immune to or are otherwise not vulnerable. EVIL.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Read down to Ferguson's unbelievable comments - this thing is becoming so transparent at this stage, it's stunning. They ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RogTallbloke: Article bemoans receding glaciers due to recent warming, but avoids the fact that the glaciers were equally receded when]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTeckKhong @MailOnline This is just outrageous, beyond all justification now. This jab is KILLING people and making others very ill, yet they keep pushing it as a 'cure' for a disease which does not affect the vast majority. We're deep in Nuremberg territory now, but they are relentless. Totally evil.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Copper find a home #SUSSEX   Active Husky aged 1-2 looking for a 'very experienced' adult home as o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TorbayTweets: @Elanders_Voice They are going full tilt to get everyone, including children, #covid vaccinated as quickly as possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MissingPetsGB: Lottie has been missing nearly 6 months  How does this little girl just disappear without a trace, without a single pos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Vincent find a home #LINCOLNSHIRE  Aged 1-2 looking for an adult home with large breed experience,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: The Danish Health Authority said it wont use the Johnson  Johnson shot, citing a possible link to blood clots. The m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Breathing Space'. Every bit as restrictive and effective as the breathing space your government gave to healthy people by forcing them to wear useless muzzles, I bet. https://t.co/Abv3boTB2d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, but if you're stupid enough to wear a mask, and you are even more stupid than that to attempt to do strenuous physical exercise with a muzzle on, then I have no sympathy. https://t.co/eynCIVmhh0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: You have nothing to apologise for @hughosmond and @Sacha_Lord. We are indebted to your brave stand against the governme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdoptionsUk: Please retweet to help Hugo find a home #Edinburgh #Scotland  Lovely French Bulldog aged 3, looking for a calm adul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexanderProud: I will not be asking to see any Covid passports or certification at Proud Group. Britain is famous for liberty. This is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @top1percentile: Vaccine manufacturers have interpreted FDAs grant Emergency Use Authorization to Moderna  Pfizer COVID vaccines as FD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: If you have never fought for anything else in your life, then let it be this   A domestic vaccine passport is not your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@McGiff @stoicmel @DanWootten Yeah, right, I was only saying this in July last year just a few days after the insane mask mandate came in, which 99% of people complied with. Our problems go back to last summer, when Covid was over, but we still let them scare us into submission. https://t.co/TiZbf6DDkE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @suzseddon: Should be in every shop window in every town up  down the country.   Do you agree? https://t.co/EpBMnLjwxq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LwCorrie: Just spoke to my mum, dad at the hospital awaiting brain scan.  Docs think it may be a mini stroke that caused the vision los]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidLloydWill8: The gov't  SAGE are claiming the vaccine has reduced deaths to 1.Yet covid disappeared in March 20. It was maintained]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: FASCINATING piece of investigative journalism on the origins of the #VaccinePassports (just sent to me)  - kinda self-evide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VanessaGray158: So Bill Gates wants to impose biometric id on all 7 billion people on the planet - for mass surveillance purposes - but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The lies. The deception. The illegal coercion. The deliberate harm. They energised the 'anti-vaxx', pro freedom of choice movement, many of whom were previously not against voluntary, uncoerced vaccination. https://t.co/343RE9rM66]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drdavidsamadi: COVID-19 is nearly a thing of the past in America. This will simply become a virus like the flu  cold now. We know how]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: DO NOT VOTE LIB/LAB/CON!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CaptainGStrouts: I expect people to take their mask off when speaking to me as a mark of respect and politeness and to ease my anxiety]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: They lied about OxyContin. They lied about Lipobay. They lied about Thalidomide.  They lied about opioid addictiveness. The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They introduced the muzzles in July last year when Covid had virtually disappeared and nobody was dying - with the specific intention of keeping the fear and the control going. If they keep mask mandates, then they don't intend to end this. More lockdowns/restrictions come autumn https://t.co/nPAJSFGEph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidjthunder By illegally coercing uptake of the most dangerous, most lethal 'vaccines' in the history of VAERS reporting (and probably Yellow Card) for healthy people who don't need them, they are committing wilful democide in the pursuit of corporate and/or political gain. Fact.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe it was her plans for complete world domination and depopulation that were too much for Bill? https://t.co/PHtzacgtVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @clim8resistance: Me in @spikedonline on the greening of Britain's armed forces.   https://t.co/5riglFTMy3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: They are now fighting over custody of the vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarlaSpade: All you have to do is stop wearing masks.  It's THAT simple.  When you stop wearing masks this ends.  I have NEVER worn a m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarlaSpade You would think it would be an easy decision. ONE person died yesterday *with* Covid. The risk is absolutely miniscule and masks do bugger all anyway. But no, they cling to their muzzles in the supermarket like their very lives depended on it. Sick of these freaks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: The lengths I would be prepared to go to in order to stop children being vaccinated might be viewed as pretty extreme.  B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: A safe vaccine does NOT kill people. Products which kill people are called POISONS. https://t.co/eQ8yLadKJG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SueC00K: This has been reinstated on YouTube now if you havent yet seen this analysis of the past 15 months by the well respected Dr J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dunibear: Decided to tip myself over the edge with the dog films and watch probably the saddest... Hachi, a Dogs Tale... 5 mins in and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jennifer_Arcuri:  the real @BorisJohnson gave up a long time ago...when he sold his soul to become everything he once told me he hated]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealJoelSmalley: For those who still think "we" are conspiracy nutjobs, there are some pretty experienced, accomplished lawyers amongst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @allisonpearson: On @BBCNews massive pessimism about opening up. Then the embarrassing fact -1 Covid death!   The disconnect between the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkChangizi: I have no idea what's in a vax and I don't care so long as I can jab it in me as fast as they'll allow me to show I'm a g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @a_webb: Does anyone else want to stand in the middle of a supermarket and scream wake the f*ck up!?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnFerris62 @RogTallbloke I decided to go away in the motorhome for a few days. Sat beside a canal with the van rocking, rain pelting against the windows, with the heating on!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NolullabyJohn: @JaneDryden4 Heroic Indian man telling his people the truth https://t.co/QUruw3sgP3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Theo7819 @CarlaSpade Yes, I believe they are rushing through #NetZero precisely because they know that very soon the public is going to realise that the 'weather' is not getting warmer and they are not going to be happy about sacrificing their cars and their gas boilers to prevent nonexistent warming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@he1entweets @Rat_Licker1984 @stoicmel They are an income tax. Abolish the NHS proportion of income tax then, as it is used to partly fund the NHS, a service charged for which has now been withdrawn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IanDunt They're threatening to send us back to square one using the EXCUSE of 'scariants'. If you haven't grasped this by now, you need to go back to square one and start relearning the basics of the Covid tyranny.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealJoelSmalley @zoeharcombe I'm so surprised, I really am. I expected it to be watertight. Solid, conclusive proof that 'the vaccines work'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealJoelSmalley: My colleague @zoeharcombe has written a diligent review of the Scottish COVID Vaccine Study preprint in the BMJ, findi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@airstripone84 It's officially stopped - but they won't be telling you that for at least another 10 years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BenIrvineAuthor: My night off. Normally I'd get a nice cheap hot meal somewhere and go to the cinema or watch footy in a pub. But I can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mattwridley No it flipping well isn't. It's neither. New variants are highly unlikely to evade the current vaccines and there is zero chance that they can evade broad spectrum innate immunity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[25 deaths and they discontinued the 1976 swine flu vaccine rollout. THOUSANDS of deaths from Covid 'vaccines' and it's 'meh, nothing to do with the vaccines' from the authorities. They want this mass vaccination rollout so badly that they are willing to kill us for it. https://t.co/DsMeaaRDQw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK @nicolatsproston Good. Proof that they're still human and not totally brainwashed into compliance with medical tyranny.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMailUK: Thousands of Cambridge students defy Covid rules for booze fuelled 'Caesarian Sunday'  https://t.co/xNc3KeYuXH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DancerDad: This is great to see. Actions speak louder than words @JuliaHB1  and many other who claim to be against masks but then stil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GlobalWarming is over. The planet is now cooling and indications are that it will continue to cool over the next few decades. It's going to become more and more difficult for the #ClimateEmergency fraudsters to spin their fake narrative - but I'm sure they'll try. https://t.co/2ICLkl5cPk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @noreward_norisk: Why are people waiting for permission to stop wearing masks?  Talking about if they dont come off this summer, theyr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealJoelSmalley: Israel had two distinct major COVID situations. Between Aug-20 and Oct-20, prevalence led deaths by about 2 weeks as e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MargotLJParker: Many GPs are STILL not opening their doors and patients are in despair. It should not be an obstacle course to see a Dr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Covid 'vaccines' will go down in history as probably the most lethal and injurious to health ever - but they are planning to inject the entire human race (including children) with the prospect of those who refuse being denied their basic human rights. Let that sink in. https://t.co/ZVEbRjk6Nh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[mass 'vaccination' with these Covid 'vaccines' - which are killing many thousands of people, more than any other vaccine in US history and a LOT more than the relatively safe 'flu vaccine. The Covid Vaccine Stakeholder Coalition is committing genocide - as the world does nothing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[of the global COVID response effort. They started promoting the vaccines before they were even out of clinical trials, McCullough said, which is against U.S. regulatory law."  Govts have colluded with Big Pharma, the Media and other major stakeholders to exclusively promote &gt;&gt;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["More than 15 months into the COVID nightmare, the evidence is beginning to suggest the U.S. government colluded from the outset with the Gates Foundation, CDC, FDA, the United Nations World Health Organization and Big Pharma to make the vaccines the central focus &gt;&gt; https://t.co/wtZKyBFWYp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: Gov. Ron DeSantis is signing an EO today suspending *all* COVID emergency orders. He's also signing bill to limit loca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @screenname87: Horrific that it's even being discussed. Some children will inevitably die.  As usual Britains clinicians stay completely]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YorkusMarcus: Every day at work now is an endurance. Every client asking me about the jab like its a normal thing to ask. About every 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkChangizi: Over the last year they built a Tyranny Machine, one always ready to be flipped on at the signs of a new virus.   The Tyr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rat_Licker1984 @stoicmel National Insurance contributions should be abolished. If you're not getting the NHS service you've paid for, then it's theft. We might as well all take out private health insurance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rat_Licker1984: My wife's uncle has a lump on his throat. Likely to only be a cyst but best checking it out. Spoke to his GP and was gi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boycott Poxy @MoxyHotels https://t.co/rkI0eKVKIp]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>