<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@DocMoschos @alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn I am sorry - this wasn't "the data" - and this isn't about "nitpicking" the data. This was an extrapolation (not "the data") from so few data points that simply adding = to &lt;= caused sensitivity to drop from 100% to 9%.   I dont see how this isn't a massive red flag of an issue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn Like I said, the rest of the paper is terrific. It is measured and balanced and very well done. The rest of the paper I'd hold up as an example paper on how to evaluate these tests.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn Yes. Absolutely. But why put the 3% number when it's obviously based on such an extremely small sample size. The small N meant that a change of a symbol from "&lt;" to "&lt;=" caused a change in sensitivity from 100% to 9%. Is this not a major red flag on the statistics there?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn That said, the rest of the paper  efforts into it are very well done. It's just the 3% piece that will catch any readers eye and immediately confuse the issue, particularly since it flies in the face of the rest of the paper - the rest was very well measured  informative.  4/4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn I wouldn't harp so much on this here except that this was pointed out many times pre-publication and yet this flawed statistic which made international headlines wasn't fixed. This is the type of inappropriate use of stats that leads to a lot of public confusion.  3/3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn One need only look at sensitivity at Ct &lt;29 (100%) vs. Ct &lt;=29 (9%) to see the sample size was statistically FAR too small to make the upward extrapolation to claim a 3% sensitivity.  If the addition of an equals sign in &lt;= moves the needle from 100% to 9% that's a problem  2/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 @jack_fergie @StevenJDunn It is more measured, yes. And clearly lots of dedicated work. But the extrapolation from 6 high Ct positives to then put out a (misidentified) sensitivity metric of 3% is, in my opinion, unfortunately irresponsible, scientifically reckless, and confuses the public.  1/x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@519Kustomz @DrMisialek @Pathologists @RapidTests @EllumeHealth @DxTerityInc @AbbottNews @Labcorp @KatNBCBoston @AbbeyNBCBoston @BrighamWomens @HarvardChanSPH yes. the FDA has done an extremely poor job at understanding this basic point. The sensitivity labels the tests get are based entirely on who the companies manage to recruit into their study and what their Ct values happen to be that day. Enables and leads to massive confusion]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DatelessJ @AbbottNews @CDPHE they are now over the counter so no longer require prescription or guides. Do fully on own now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jburnmurdoch: Brief thread on vaccines vs variants (vaccines are winning ):  [Some] people keep pointing to rising cases in places li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@loukreuzer @AbbottNews Oh. Yes. I couldnt agree more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@David_desJ @jasonfurman Would not want bulk to go to peoples homes. bulk packaging is for businesses, schools, w CLIA waivers etc   Point is, if US wanted to actually create tools for public health, we could... for cheap. But we have WAY too many barriers to enable it to happen efficiently.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@loukreuzer @AbbottNews Equitable access to tests does not keep a pandemic from ending  Thats like saying if you close your eyes, the sun goes down. No, tests are our eyes in this pandemic. We dont need them daily or even weekly when virus is controlled. But equitable access to a test is important.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine if we didnt work as a globe to eradicate Smallpox or nearly eliminate Polio. Those were and are global efforts and we are all SO much better for it.   Global Vaccine Access should be everyones concern in some (even if small) way. https://t.co/eZxppb1ymn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@David_desJ @jasonfurman And if the packaging was changed it could come down even more. Already the tests are sold in packs of 40 at $5 / test. But if you buy in bulk, it still needs a CLIA waiver (go figure...).   $5 is probably ~$2 above cost.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For @AbbottNews BinaxNOW it is $24 for the 2-test screening pack  2 tests in the box - can be used by two different ppl - However FDA says they be used by same person 24-36 hrs apart.   Its a bit of a poor take on the goal of frequent testing - but OTC is a huge step forward.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelmina_lab: This is how progress is made:  A new study about to start in UK.  Can rapid tests each morning following contact w a #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonfurman That was the deal w the FDA. I agree that they can be used as two different tests, but trying to stick w FDA message.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonfurman Supposed to be done as a unit test 24-36h apart.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Couldnt have said it better myself.  Now we need to see US Gov offer subsidies for rapid tests so all people can have access. testing in a pandemic is a public health good. It is for those around us more than for ourselves.  $24 is still far too high for a public health test https://t.co/ean7ghw6ze]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarlosdelRio7: @EricTopol @wsj_douglasj @michaelmina_lab @ggronvall Having rapid tests readily available is a game changer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jhuber: @michaelmina_lab Detect cancer early, when it can be cured.   (https://t.co/b2e2081ONI)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ConstantNot @JENNIFERANNL0VE @DrLaPook @CBS Thats the CVS I go to :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dr_James_L @DrLaPook @CBS Now OTC.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrotherJev @DrLaPook @CBS Yes agree. Testing is a public health good.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricTopol: The UK achieved containment of covid. But that's not enough. They are pursuing crushing it with free, rapid home tests, unli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @DrLaPook and @CBS for covering this important story.   We now have authorization for rapid antigen tests to be sold over the counter - w/out prescription. Next step - let's see the price come down so that access is equitable.   The Federal Government should subsidize. https://t.co/wzSNuqy6Sp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@519Kustomz @DrMisialek @Pathologists @RapidTests @EllumeHealth @DxTerityInc @AbbottNews @Labcorp @KatNBCBoston @AbbeyNBCBoston @BrighamWomens @HarvardChanSPH Of course, you may have noticed that every 10 Ct values lower indicates a 1000 fold increase in virus RNA. This is a feature of doubling with each PCR cycle. So, every 3.3 cycles is approximately a 10-fold change.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paimadhu: From the annals of vaccine inequity:  12 year olds in high-income countries might get vaccinated in a few weeks/months  72 ye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@519Kustomz @DrMisialek @Pathologists @RapidTests @EllumeHealth @DxTerityInc @AbbottNews @Labcorp @KatNBCBoston @AbbeyNBCBoston @BrighamWomens @HarvardChanSPH Each lab has different Ct values. So a 30 in one lab might be a 22 in another. Its much more important that the labs make an interpolated viral load, Bc the Cts are what can vary by lab.   But if you want a guide from our lab, Ct 40 = 1000, 30 = 1M, 20 = 1B on this chart]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LongDesertTrain @fascinatorfun @isaperena Yes. If they are being used to ask am I infectious right now the rapid Ag LFT work very very well. If the question is I have symptoms, do I have COVID they are not as good bc they are better thought of as transmission indicators vs medical diagnostics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LongDesertTrain @fascinatorfun @isaperena The PCR test is not at all specific to the infectious window of time. It is only specific to presence of viral RNA.   This lack of PCR specificity led to confusion by people thinking the LFT have a big loss in sensitivity. The problem is inappropriately defining the gold standard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@booradley31 @DrMisialek @Pathologists @RapidTests @EllumeHealth @DxTerityInc @AbbottNews @Labcorp @KatNBCBoston @AbbeyNBCBoston @BrighamWomens @HarvardChanSPH Its the day that someone first becomes Detectable on a PCR test - the day the viral load first passes the threshold for PCR detection.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LongDesertTrain @fascinatorfun @isaperena If they were using LFT only once they started getting symptoms like loss in smell - they were very likely already beyond their most infectious period. Rapid tests turn positive when virus titers are high. But transmission is very short, even though PCR  symptoms last weeks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fascinatorfun @jameshay218 @isaperena .@fascinatorfun the data has been very good for many LFT. Loss in sensitivity that has been in the media is almost entirely due to missing cases that remain PCR pos AFTER ppl are meant to be done w their isolation period. The sensitivity is very good when viral load becomes high.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nearlytoolate @jameshay218 @fascinatorfun @isaperena I wish people would talk about this more. Quarantine owing to an exposure has very poor compliance/follow through.  60 seconds each AM for 7 days would probably have quite high compliance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mlipsitch: Thank you @j_g_allen and thank you for also leading tremendous work in many areas but (speaking personally) especially to he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nataliexdean: The imminent FDA authorization of a vaccine for 12-15 year olds is great news, and adolescents should be able to access v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iainklugman: Thank you @michaelmina_lab -- this is my new favorite chart!  In one image it nails why we need serial rapid testing progr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@j_g_allen @CCDD_HSPH @HarvardChanSPH @mlipsitch @BillHanage @yhgrad @megan_b_murray @MauSantillana Thanks @j_g_allen. Likewise!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Craig_A_Spencer: When I say the US should do more to vaccinate the world, someone always says do these countries even have the cold st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoscherMarcus @redstarlondon @Alan_Wickstrom @profbuchan @TheLancet @c_drosten We dont see it. We see that if we follow people, then from the moment they first become PCR positive, on average they become Ag positive around 15 hrs later. By 48 hrs post first becoming PCR pos (following daily before that) Ag has 100% percent positive agreement w PCR.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WanOvi: Pueden los test rpidos sustituir a las cuarentenas?  UK comienza un estudio masivo para evaluar la eficacia de sustitui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brunobowden @samies177 Hahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JInterlandi Haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrMisialek: Great graphic from @michaelmina_lab that emphasizes the importance of rapid #COVID19 testing https://t.co/sZmjoJcWwI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCRCS: Thank you to all of our speakers and participants in the CRCS Spring 2021 #AIforSocialImpact Seminar Series!   You can watch ta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItsOhWell Requires heavy lifting beyond just the design - in fact Moderna already has a variant (b.1.351) booster in phase I trials w those who have and have not previously been given a vaccine. The trials are the long part - cannot, unfortunately, speed up immunity to measure too much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone wants this to be done and we all would prefer to pretend its over in vaccinated nations. But not dealing with this globally keeps everyone exposed.   I just don't want any nation to be taken off guard unnecessarily. Whether out of the worst of the pandemic or not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most SARS-CoV2 infections produces billions/trillions of virions inside the person.   Every day, there are Quadrillions of SARS-CoV-2 virus particles produced globally - mixing w immunity  We should assume terrible variants will arrive, prepare for them, and then hope they dont. https://t.co/KSuk5goZoV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TakethatCt @SteveW928 @djlc78 @StopCoronavir12 @bealelab Agree. We wrote about it in CID back in April or May last year and suggested we use the trends in the Ct values. Today, I only feel comfortable making any assessment of unlikely infectious if two tests are collected 24+ hrs apart  both w high Ct (assuming no other info)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. This. Thanks @EpiEllie   Unfortunately though, I fear its one more thing we will have to repeat, over and over and over... for so many more months still.... https://t.co/LwHBscbyNC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EpiEllie: Im so tired of talking about the pandemic and having to say the same things over and over.   The pandemic isnt finished and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andyaschmidt @samies177 :) haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tcely Didnt realize you could do that. Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TakethatCt @SteveW928 @djlc78 @StopCoronavir12 @bealelab And for that specific use do I need to isolate or which time period of contacts of this person do I trace it fails pretty badly (esp when it has a delay, or low access but thats a different issue).  Looking at the Ct and serial testing can help immensely. As can an Ag test]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TakethatCt @SteveW928 @djlc78 @StopCoronavir12 @bealelab For its intended medical purpose of diagnosing (its intended use on the label) PCR is of course stellar.  However, it is used in this pandemic for a whole different purpose which is rarely well-articulated. Really, its not usually for diagnostics, but rather public health.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TakethatCt @SteveW928 @djlc78 @StopCoronavir12 @bealelab I believe youre both right wrt what you each individually are discussing  PCR stays positive well beyond the period of isolation. Weeks+  For medical diagnostics it is great. For public health - to identify if isolation is needed, it is very poorly not specific w a binary output]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mine_leiva Any rapid tests there?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is really a terrific overview of public health approaches to testing and what we know about rapid tests.   By @vercheckt   (If you are like me, youll need to open in chrome and use the translate button.)  https://t.co/JjSDLE9bX5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@primatagabriel Thats simply not true at all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cmurali99 Wow, a year into this pandemic and you may have just provided the most rude response yet. Exceedingly poor consideration.   You asked me a question and I went out of my way to answer.  A ceremony is not Mass state law. Why should I know if Umass Amherst allows Ag for graduation?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeynep Yeah.... :/  At least we can still learn lessons that the rest of the world can put to use.  I bet that if a new pandemic started tmrw though, many would start debating from scratch once again. We dont know enough to act...   (When in fact we did know so much)  Disheartening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cmurali99 BinaxNOW if they allow for rapid Antigen tests. Can get it off the shelf at CVS and Walgreens now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@COVIDUpdate2020 Ha. Fair enough.   Elsewhere I have written about how lockdowns and stay at home orders are akin to considering the entire society a (false) positive.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think this person must be confusing me with someone that studies the fecal microbiome.   :) https://t.co/C6UxPvHeW9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I do hope the study progresses quickly. We have found in preliminary studies that testing out of quarantine using rapid tests CAN work well. And arguably much better since many in quarantine get fed up and stop anyway.   This will be an important study to follow. 7/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The difference between rapid molecular and rapid Ag turning positive is about 15 hrs. So if both are rapid, then if it is a high risk contact, Id prefer the extra 15 hrs. But only if rapid. A 24 hr delayed lab PCR would be a v bad choice for testing in lieu of quarantine.   6/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Although I am very much in support of rapid antigen testing, I would prefer, if accessible, to see rapid molecular tests be used for this specific purpose - at least for unvax contacts who will be in contact w high risk or unvaccinated. Or a rapid Ag 2x/day for 1st 3-5 days.  5/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So, studies like these, to ask:   Can 60 seconds in the morning using a test, for 7 mornings straight, be enough to keep me from having to quarantine for 7-14 days?  Incredibly important question that could/should have been answered long ago by CDC and others.  4/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A quarantine of an uninfected individual should be considered with the same concern as false positives - and false positives sure have gotten a LOT of attention. But unlike a false positive, you currently cant really get a confirmatory test to help get out of quarantine.   3/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is this important??  Quarantines take a major toll on individuals. Physical and emotional. Most contacts in quarantine never become positive and there are multiple contacts for each positive.  2/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how progress is made:  A new study about to start in UK.  Can rapid tests each morning following contact w a #COVID19 positive individual be used instead of a 14 day quarantine.   Ive been pushing for this type of study/policy for a year.   https://t.co/dPp0nyiXLZ  1/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VirginiaBuysse @wsbgnl @iAirborne To reply w dont have emotions  continue exerting all your energy solely on the pandemic feels a bit tone deaf. Many of us have barely slept for a year+ to understand this virus, create new approaches for control, guide policy, communicate w public and much more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VirginiaBuysse @wsbgnl @iAirborne No, youre absolutely right it may not be helpful but have some compassion. I am extremely sad at the situation.  Some of us have been exerting truly extraordinary efforts for 15+ months straight  are 100% burnt out. Worse, decision makers largely ignored experts, and the data.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kkoenig314 It is remarkable. I agree.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebrainsmind Youre correct. I should be careful when I use terms like that in writing on Twitter.  Perhaps better framing would have been  *extremely anticipated. Or *the most likely scenario or *highly predictable.   Thanks for calling it out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JusDayDa @apoorva_nyc Haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@apoorva_nyc Moved into another room. Now books. Maybe Ill move them back :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InfectiousPS Aw. Very many thanks for this comment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing Oh yes. Very true.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveW928 @TakethatCt @djlc78 @StopCoronavir12 @bealelab This an astounding back and forth that you all have going on. Days now! :)  Its one of the great things about twitter - and one of the horrible things when it gets out of civil territory...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @syramadad: Another reason to pivot from our de facto just-in-time pandemic approach to a just-in-case one as we wrote in @Health_Af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanmcn1 If there are any questions about whether robotics are going to be taking manual jobs....   Some scary and amazing stuff.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JMRothberg Couldn't agree more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the kind of thinking we need to start... today. https://t.co/KX2hQ8DABF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trvrb: There are effectively two #COVID19 epidemics in the US at this moment; one largely resolving epidemic comprised of non-variant v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YorkshirPuddin @deeksj he blocked me long ago...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bylenasun: On the one year anniversary of my mom's death from covid-19, my family suspects she would still be alive if U.S. leaders had]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PhilipC55476163 Yes. It is a constant problem in public health. The better it does, the less it is accounted for. The only items then that are accounted for are when the programs falter. It's a terrible narrow-view cycle driven by policy makers and, unfortunately, often the unknowing public]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrNickB_ObAnaes @DrJohnCurran @drvkeating @drdhanlon @EwanMacKenna @HIVTox @profmaryhorgan The purpose of stating the arithmetic is to suggest why rapid Ag tests look like they have low sensitivity.   It's not that they are missing the infectious. They are missing the post-infectious. They are simply much more specific than PCR to find people who need to isolate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @matthewherper: Eli Broad, whose gift established a science powerhouse, dies at 87 https://t.co/I8MNqS8Br0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rak3re Agree. Entirely.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iAirborne I was referring more towards the global response to help out. Its now trending to help. But we should have seen it on the walls long ago, amd acted. We didnt. Just like we didnt act proactively in the US. Always reactive.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattNoahSmith @MrC0nfus10n I honestly cant speak towards the politics. To me, this reflects a larger issue of only acting once 100% sure and thus too late. Weve done it to ourselves and to foreign nations. We are always steps behind, even though our scientific understanding means we could be ahead]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iAirborne Not preventable, no. Im not trying to suggest it was. But the global community is only starting to mobilize now. Didnt have to be this way. This has been foreseeable for a long time and better steps could and should have been taken last summer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrC0nfus10n No. We cannot. But we could as a globe have recognized the incredible risk nations like India have been at, anticipated it, and acted accordingly months ago.   Now its largely political optics and bullshit for foreign nations to pretend to help out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the tweet I am referring to nations, particularly high income nations just now starting to say oh, we should do something. And them as nations, scramble to make an appearance.   We could have done a lot this past year, for ourselves and the world. Weve done the bare minimum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. Of course we learned how to make vaccines and start getting them distributed. We have learned some things.   But we havent yet learned how to reasonably anticipate and make assessments based on what we already know is most likely to occur or w the urgency it requires.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel very distraught about what is happening w COVID in India. At moment, I am distraught (and extremely sad) bc this was 100% predictable.   Why in this pandemic do we keep waiting to see before we act. Once we are seeing, its always too late.   We havent learned a thing.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>