<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@heckyessica @AnnoyedinMN This is good stuff!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ermy50491031 @AnnoyedinMN Do it. Do it. Do it. It's refreshing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnnoyedinMN Haven't been wearing a mask for a while now in the north metro. Feels like I'm the only one though.  Glad there are more people out there who are stepping up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me?  https://t.co/sLwlK32JWb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Spoiled little brat. I'm so oppressed with my $100m+ in the bank. Life is so hard. You're a damn good baller, but a shitty representative of the USA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Polly_Incorrect @joeroganhq @joerogan @TuckerCarlson Asking seriously, do you never question the 'experts'? Do you just take their word and never do any research for yourself? If so, that is a very dangerous spot to be. A lot of 'highly educated' people say a lot of stupid things.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OhHeyMan420 @benshapiro I bet you would cut your arm off if the CDC told you it would prevent you from getting a runny nose.  #sheeple]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@parkersnedden @benshapiro I don't have the shot, nor will I and I have been living my life mask free.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GA Mom Slams Mask Mandate: Take these masks off of my child. https://t.co/szs6UyLyTk  Politicians don't care about our children.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS Is it FDA approved yet? Are there published animal studies yet?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@guypbenson If anyone is okay with this, you are part of the problem. At what point do you let "safety" rule over liberty? People can't see this is a slippery slope to absolute government control. Germany ring any bells? "It's for your safety."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oz6YIV1NcZ  Jack Dorsey's a Nazi  #TwitterCensorship]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#wheresKamala  #creepyjoe #BorderCrisis https://t.co/Glfb9dpEFM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@US_FDA @CDCgov And this is what happens when you rush a shot out that has not been tested thoroughly. I truly feel sorry for all you suckers out there who were so fearful that you might get sick that you possibly made a very poor choice taking and untested shot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is funny and sad at the same time. So many are scared of a flu that has a 99.8% survival rate.  #COVIDIOTS  #COVID1984 https://t.co/hGbw7DhJ9L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what I have to deal with? Thank you walz for inciting violence. Your ass needs to be recalled and BLM needs to be abolished.  #recallwalz #mn https://t.co/2FuSimGVbR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarmineSabia Completely agree.  #recallwalz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxNews So can we say walz incited violence for his reckless tweet? He threw every police officer under the bus. Police officers are not hunting down black people. The data does not support it.  #recallwalz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AutoOverload What's wrong? You miss bullying people? The nerve of an article like this. Guys like that fought for your freedom to be an asshole. Sheesh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CNN Thanks for your permission lord and emperor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Andrew38398093 @CDCgov If masks work, why have so many health care workers been infected? Masks are actually useless against Covid. Most who've been infected report they always wear a mask according to the CDC.15 days to slow the spread. The goal post keeps changing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharonvt75 @NicoleSganga There's a super big gap in your data. Please share last year's data?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So.... still not a single case of influenza for 2020/2021 flu season and only 3 people with the common cold (seasonal Coronavirus)? Right...? #covidskeptic #masksdontwork - except for the flu and common cold #covidcommomnsense https://t.co/lGKBZvyBXh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@anitarod10 @JaniceDean I'm so sorry for your loss. With that said, that was a decision that your sis-in-law made. Not Trump's fault. The old adage, your friends jump off a bridge... Cuomo knowingly put people with Covid into nursing homes and lied about it. That was wrong and directly killed people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec When is America going to wake up? Thus is so frustrating!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jPF7x75L8u This is the very definition of delusional. I truly feel sorry for this person that no one has ever loved them enough to be honest with them. Why are we celebrating men in dresses? Shameful. Feminist? I can't hear you.  #kataluna #PrayForAmerica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RickyRi42828133 @bimboubermensch @JackPosobiec Yep!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JenniferLoya19 @bimboubermensch @JoeBiden Unfortunately, every country already knows we are "led" by an L7 weenie.  #Bidenisweak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Streets4Dreamin @megynkelly It's called a joke. Lighten up preferred pronoun.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stevieboy5555 @Cernovich @JackPosobiec Define evil please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YN55GCCfnj  And people called Trump a tyrant and a dictator. Biden is openly telling you want you can and can't do. The government is going to make your decisions, not you. Trump never did this kind of crap.  #Biden  #tyrant #demhypocrisy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sourpatchlyds Interesting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Timcast Very interesting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: one of these things is not like the other https://t.co/qM9uUEy7Nm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SfDz11_07_14 @politicalelle @amazon But don't you understand? He has white privilege!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 Psalms 38:15 For in thee, O LORD, do I hope: thou wilt hear, O Lord my God.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 I'm so sad for you. I can't imagine the grief and shame you will bear forever. Typically, right decisions don't bring guilt. But you don't have to bear that burden alone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 First, I appreciate you being willing to continue this conversation. Most wouldn't. Second, unless your life was in danger, I can imagine the decision to murder your own flesh and blood would weigh heavy on your conscience.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @kaikahele The misinformation concerning this case. The facts weren't out, the video looked real bad and people lost their Shit without having any context or facts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @kaikahele He was super high on fentanyl! Like so high! The drugs killed him, not the cop. Autopsy stated that. He would have been dead regardless of the interaction between him and the cop. Facts matter in this case.i live in MN. I've been directly affected by misinformation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 I believe most abortions are ones of convenience. Takes two to tango. I agree with you though that men need to start being men and treat women with respect. They also need to take responsibility for their actions. Killing a baby is not being responsible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kaikahele @iheartlmc George Floyd was a criminal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 I can go on all day about the evils of abortion. Why doesn't that baby have rights. Don't their rights matter, or just your selfishness? I'm not ready to have a baby, it's not the right time, blah blah blah. If you are having free sex, expect a baby as a result.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 Calling BS on that. Absolute BS. Please!  You keep your distance  and don't go around them if your sick, like before people got all weird about masks. That is called common courtesy. You don't quarantine healthy people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 So let me ask you this? Someone on your street gets cancer and goes on chemo, their immune system is weakened. Does the whole street take precautions for the one, or does the one take the proper precautions?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 But... let's just kill babies because you can't close your legs and act like an adult. You would sacrifice your baby at the alter of your selfishness.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iheartlmc @irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 Can that even be proven? That is so ridiculous. Don't drive a car because you might kill some one. Don't eat or you might choke to death. As cruel as it sounds, it's primarily old people in nursing homes who are dying WITH Covid. https://t.co/AyhAFKsZJR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@irishrygirl @Whittymeg1 What about a baby's uterus? Doesn't she have a choice?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RB33973035 @JoeTalkShow @kayleighmcenany You can be wrong and still be talented. Two things can be true at once.  https://t.co/fUOZ74oHS4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pablo_honey1 @DanCrenshawTX Besides they don't work. Look at WI and MN data. Same results. One has mask mandates, one doesn't. Live in fear if you want to, but the government shouldn't pedal fear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeTalkShow @kayleighmcenany She's trending because she's got talent. The current press secretary, um... uhh...  umm.... let me circle back. She ain't no circle back girl.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BMeiselas Let me circle back to that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More states with governors who have common sense and who aren't caving to the doctrine of fear. Covid - bad. Living in fear, also bad. Let the people make decisions regarding their health, not the government.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sooooo... no influenza for MN 20/21 Finding this a little hard to believe.  #COVID19 #covidscam #livinginfear https://t.co/IbqKY0rqgW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@geojohwee @DanCrenshawTX Mr and Mrs are not destructive! Your "truth" is wrong, misguided, and dangerous.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Seebowman @Rejoicesongs @JackPosobiec Who does it prevent from voting? Please don't say the elderly. There are/can be programs to ensure the they have voter ID. I'm so tired of this lame as argument against voter ID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntsyNegs @IngrahamAngle If you watch CNN and the likes that is what you would believe. The majority of the GOP are not as portrayed by the media. You have crazies on the left and right.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Casey_Boy_Mom @IngrahamAngle Violent mobs took over Portland (for 90days or something like that), Seattle, Minneapolis and no one seems to care or remembers. Such a double standard. At least the Capitol riots were aimed at the right people. Politicians and not citizens. They make policy. D or R.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dabates94 @MauchDaniel @DonaldJTrumpJr I am/was, but my computer just crashed. Wall street journal has some cool info. I was going to attach a screen shot. I would ask though, why aren't other minority groups killed as often by police? Well, Hispanics are pretty close to the black population for police deaths]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dabates94 @MauchDaniel @DonaldJTrumpJr When you write 2.5 more times likely to die, you referring to the amount killed as a percent of the black population?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dabates94 @MauchDaniel @DonaldJTrumpJr How do you want the demographics to matter? People keep talking like black people are the only ones who are shot by cops and that simply is not the case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dabates94 @MauchDaniel @DonaldJTrumpJr But why?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bintaroboy @DonaldJTrumpJr It's always about color. Color, color, color. Cops kill more white people than black people. Where's the outrage for black on black murder. Little kids getting slaughtered?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MauchDaniel @DonaldJTrumpJr Cops shoot/kill more white people than black people. Facts matter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zVi3rfUwMD  This man deserves what's coming to him, but how stupid are some people? Text your vote? Seriously!  #ElectionIntegrity  #sheeple #1776 #BidenRemorse #recallbiden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MPRnews What the hell is 'structural racism'? Why do we keep voting these idiots into office. Somebody give me evidence of structural racism? Show me a law?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MPRnews This is an RNA single strand virus. It will never stop mutating. It's what they do. Let's understand the risks and move on. Herd immunity is the only stop to this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kbZL9XrqCW We could use a good dose of this kind of common sense. People keep looking to the Gov't for the solution to their problems when they are the cause. Gotta vote these clowns out. On both sides!  #VotersRemorse  #AmericansFirst #personalresponsibility]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@numbers_truth @Venezia1970 @DonaldJTrumpJr Hey Dan, another note. Was not purposefully lying. Really misread a story about suicides topping 800k last year, but missed the worldwide. I can admit when I'm wrong. Although I'm interested in how those metrics dropped with news of depression and suicidal thoughts increasing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@numbers_truth @Venezia1970 @DonaldJTrumpJr Never mind. I found it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@numbers_truth @Venezia1970 @DonaldJTrumpJr I'm asking this in all seriousness, Where did you get your numbers? The site at the bottom of your file doesn't work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Venezia1970 @DonaldJTrumpJr Oh and more people are dying from suicide and drug overdose in 2020 than from the Chinese flu. Should we hold the Governors who shut down their states accountable for those deaths as well?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Venezia1970 @DonaldJTrumpJr With your logic, your saying that Mexico's, Canada's, Italy's, France's, and so forth, leaders are responsible for the deaths in their countries?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Citizen2076 @SimonRTweets @DonaldJTrumpJr 1. Covid "caused" the deaths, not Trump. Are we to blame Trudeau for the deaths in Canada?   2. Governor's shut down their own state's economies, not Trump, hence the Governors are responsible for the job losses.   3. There were 30M uninsured under Obama.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So the Biden admin is really hell bent on screwing over Americans. What is the point stoppage? You people who voted for this clown only have yourselves to blame.   #WorstPresidentEver #LyinBiden #AmericaFirst #sheeple  https://t.co/ZvrvsTxMM5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm really wondering how Sleepy Joe is going to boost the economy and bring jobs back to America when he is going to raise taxes? It doesn't work like that.  #AmericaFirst #JoeBiden #taxes# #middleclass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zoop212 @DonaldJTrumpJr Come on man... you know... the thing... I suppose that counts as a complete sentence.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prijunankarrr @nytimes The WHO is just a bloated bureaucratic mess. I looked at their what we do page. We really don't need them to tell us the information we already know. I'd bet my bottom dollar most of my money is spent on admin cost. I'll look it up though. https://t.co/LIQobzffwx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prijunankarrr @nytimes So why was it insane to leave WHO? Just trying to understand.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kaWbTQ24J5  Killing jobs already! On his first day... Think about that for a moment. Your first day of work and you fire 11,000 people, affecting nearly 30,000 lives, you know wives, husbands, children. Wow! #WorstPresidentInUSHistory  #DementiaJoe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dem Rep. Bowman: Congress Must Stop Spreading the Myth of American Exceptionalism and Deal with Racism Throughout all Institutions https://t.co/zTFWvKQlOf via @BreitbartNews   He learned quickly to pull the race card. Which institutions exactly? #racism]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Should be diversity of thought, not diversity of skin color and sex.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So is Biden appointing people to his cabinet based upon their sex and color of their skin? How is this not considered racist and sexist? Every normal person out there, "I wonder if they were hired for talent, or for the color of their skin?".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepMondaire MLK would be appalled by the left as the left is not truly liberal. I can't understand why the black community keeps itself under the oppression of the left. You've allowed the Democrats to put you where you are at today. A bunch of crusty old white people telling u what 2 think.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Starting to look a little like the hunger games out there. Border around the Capitol, "leaders" who could care less about the people who elected them to their positions of power.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delingpole: Italian Restaurants Open in Mass Protest at Lockdown Rules https://t.co/34gvx7RSDW via @BreitbartNews   #lockdown]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FoxNews There's no such thing as "The Office of the President Elect".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BenfordLaw https://t.co/dTMti1LZQ1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I don't have much of a presence on the Twitterverse, so I'm going to post about Benford's Law and Biden's vote distribution. Let's see if Twitter is really as lame as I think it is!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FrankAmari2 @realDonaldTrump @mschlapp @AdamLaxalt That's all politicians! All!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charliekirk11: Out of 71,740 abortions in Florida:  .001% were due to incest  .065% to protect the mother's life  .085% due to rape  .6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BarrettSallee Real America supporting their president. Music to my ears.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This headline is a bit misleading once your read the whole story. #winning #Trump2020Landslide US Jobs Report December 2019: Only 145K payrolls added, 3.5% unemployment https://t.co/RKUKsEG5I7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stay strong there Jillian. A lot of people who can't handle truth. They just start the name calling and hurling insults.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @realDonaldTrump This is one of the dumbest things I've ever heard. And there's a lot of people saying a lot of dumb things.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 She literally sacrificed her child for a  little gold statue. So brave.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So... .Michelle Williams literally sacrificed her child for a little gold idol. So brave.   Hollywood Heaps Praise on Michelle Williams for Pro-Abortion Golden Globes Acceptance Speech https://t.co/jD2DzOeGGe via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders The corporate elite that provide jobs to millions of Americans.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila Crazy isn't it? Just simply indescribably!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Dont let Trump steal the next election   Demand Voter ID Now!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>