<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CorsIAQ: Shortly after Pfizer Shot #2!  I always wear my old #TragicallyHip mission cap for big events, and this one qualified.  But th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gbignami OK.  I will report back tomorrow .....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ten hours into Pfizer shot #2.  Arm barely sore and no other symptoms so far.  I even did 80 minutes of cardio this evening.  Starve this virus of its hosts.   Just Do It!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AStillwellPhD @MichaelEWebber @energymovies OK --- I am going to get on board.  The next indoor air quality class that I teach will end with a discussion of "Air At the Movies".   ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@futureproofr I hope not.  I have so many wonderful long-time friends in Ontario and east and know how difficult things have been there wrt vaccines.  Keep your guard up, @futureproofr.  It's a good life if you don't weaken.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JimRosenthal4 @Jan_KraakSD You rock, Jim!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shortly after Pfizer Shot #2!  I always wear my old #TragicallyHip mission cap for big events, and this one qualified.  But the nose is what got many comments in line and from staff.  Doing my part to starve this virus of its hosts, and maybe create a few smiles along the way. https://t.co/2z1twQCs3X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Off for Pfizer shot #2!  Just did another half-Milton shave to get a good fit of mask on face.  And yes, I will be wearing my clown nose on mask to celebrate this day with others getting vaccinated as we do our collective part to starve this virus of its hosts. Just do it! https://t.co/yGRLIwQmyk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A standard polyurethane foam clown nose stays securely on my mask if air gaps around the crease of my nose are effectively minimized and pops off otherwise. It has the added benefit of entertaining other shoppers.  No clowning around. https://t.co/vzeycpaGUa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Bingo. https://t.co/t8dUDs7YVs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcelHarmon1: @CorsIAQ Also Prosocial: Behavior w/ the intent of benefiting other people or society as a whole, that doesnt have to c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: Instead, they are going with upgraded filters in HVAC systems, portable HEPA air cleaners in classrooms, and open windows w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JusDayDa Thanks for the advice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really excited about doing my part to starve SARS-CoV-2  its many variants from its hosts.     Pfizer shot #2 tomorrow.  Bring it on!    Razor at the ready for a good morning shave to assure a proper mask fit.  Just Doin' It!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patriotic: "Having or expressing devotion to and vigorous support for one's country."  Get vaccinated.  Just do it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@edyong209 Typo.  What a great name!  Beautiful dog.  Looks like a cattle dog/Corgi mix.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just read a paper on a specific electronic air "cleaning" device w/ a "low emission rate" of ozone that is so high it is roughly equal to moving a home from an area of pristine air quality on the Oregon coast to amongst the most ozone-polluted cities in US. Just (don't) do it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And thank you as well, @polsiewski.  You have been a great facilitator, communicator, and leader on this issue. https://t.co/UzSNdvjn2e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IndoorChem: Publication highlight: Intake Fractions for Volatile Organic Compounds in Two Occupied California Residences. By @allenhgol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: Richmond Public Schools superintendent @JasonKamras (HS classmate) asked me whether to buy ionization systems for schools.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ Whatever the reason, humankind has not fared well in its wake. The reason we should not allow history to be rewritten is so that those who can make a major difference from the start do NOT repeat their mistakes next time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/  I agree 100% w/ @jljcolorado. Many of us saw the importance of transmission by aerosols in both the near and far fields early in this pandemic.  Those who  mattered were not qualified to understand transmission by aerosols, wearing blinders, or worse. https://t.co/QuGqSWr9Yl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TechKev @linseymarr Thanks, @TechKev.  Nothing was complicated back then.  It did make perfect sense and was so frustrating that those who really mattered could not see it and did not do their part to save us from where the world has gotten.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marinavance I know.  News on Brazil has somehow been lost due to the devastation occurring in India.  But it too continues to be ravaged.  Horrible, failed, belligerent,  IMO criminal "leadership" has led to a humanitarian crisis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@akm5376 I agree. India, Brazil,  other countries/regions should never have gotten to this place of devastation, loss, sorrow, death, and suffering. Too much of the world lacked leadership and  "authorities" wore thick blinders, refusing to take them off - to the detriment of humankind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Slow learners and sad that it took 14 months (and likely devastation of India) to come around to what has been obvious to so many for so long.  Let's hope that this recognition has some benefit moving forward. https://t.co/ffA64qtlRZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wennbergcaltech I know.  But that does not stop me from being a grumpy old engineer. :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidElfstrom @healthyheating Ditto on all fronts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JulietteBrod101 Depends on the size and amount of openings, outdoor wind speeds and direction relative to openings on building ( whether fans are used in openings).  Did expts on my own garage with door open.  Typically achieved 15 to 25 air changes per hour w/o fans.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatGeo: "Watching a creature dieone who is the last of its kindis something I hope never to experience again. It felt like watching o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Computer Science program in the Maseeh College of Engineering  Computer Science has an excellent cybersecurity group, cybersecurity graduate certificate, and award winning student team in Capture The Flag competitions.  Check out this panel discussion! https://t.co/V2e4slfncR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomgillpredicts Interesting. I have been called for jury duty 3 or 4 times.  Every time I have been the first person excused during jury selection. It's gotten to the point where I feel bad about always being so quickly rejected!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9/ The way to do it is to GET FULLY VACCINATED, wear a mask when not eating, minimize time in space (take out best)  for restaurants to increase ventilation  use one or more of: advanced central filtration, HEPA filtration systems, appropriate upper-room UVGI.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8/ I am still not a fan of going to indoor restaurants right now because of the need to remove mask  because some (many?) will not be fully vaccinated.  But the way to substantially reduce COVID-19 infection is not with barriers that (on average) have a minimal (if any) effect.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7/ In that context, it would probably be more effective to put patches of carpet on walls or fleecy materials hung from the ceiling to increase particle decay rate to materials with large surface areas (which I am not advocating).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6/  It does not appear to me that these barriers constitute more than a few % of the total surface area in the space (including walls, floor, ceiling, furnishings,  people when present) and would therefore lower particle decay rates by a tiny amount.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5/ Assuming that the barriers do not affect volume or deposition velocity (they might affect mixing and therefore could affect vd to some extent), then the key parameter is surface area, A.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4/ k = vd x (A/V).  vd is a deposition velocity, which is a function of particle diam, mixing conditions in bulk air, friction velocity near surface, and more. A = surface area.  V = volume of interior space.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/  Is there a benefit in terms of far field exposure?  Very minimal. Here's why. Indoor aerosol particle decay rates (k) to (integrated) indoor surfaces range from approx 0.2 to 10/hr for 0.3 to 10 um particles, respectively (higher for larger diameter particles).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ The risk of people letting their guards down thinking that barriers are somehow effective for aerosol particles is much greater than any benefit, IMHO. Technical answer next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/ Simple answer = very little for aerosol particles but possibly (in some cases) dispersion that reduces close contact dose. But depending on flow conditions, there can be a low pressure zone on the downstream side that leads to some accumulation of particles. https://t.co/FpZMabEsNk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pet peeves (still old school):  "Particulates" as a noun.  No! No! No! No! No!  "Particulate matter"   I don't care what any dictionary says, "particulate" is an adjective.    Probably a lost cause, but I still cringe when I hear "Data is".  A "data point is".  "Data are".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmalBakchan Congratulations, @AmalBakchan.  #HookEm! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashishkjha: COVID in India is awful  It will get worse before it gets better  My latest in Hindustan Times (@htTweets) on what went w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrakashLab: All the warning signs have been present all along. The international community needs to see this as a global crisis otherwi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One year ago today professor @tomgillpredicts of @UTEP  fellow alumnus  air pollution student of @ucdavis did his part to warn the public that #COVIDisAirborne.  He should have been on the television at least once per week, because he understands aerosol science. https://t.co/1k2FxvxKBK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's been an entire year, and Earl is still following her. https://t.co/6TJiGJuo8r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JudahWorldChamp @CDCgov Did an interview in OR last spring in which I asked business owners, building owners, or building managers to disable demand control ventilation  open outdoor air dampers completely. For those w/o mech ventilation open windows, doors,  use fans in windows for more ventilation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @phylogenomics: Truckee high school reports COVID outbreak, 150 students quarantined https://t.co/1ES6pFJmax via @SFGate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kevinrigbyjr Yes.  In fact, I met my future wife when we were both waiting for a physics professor who was late for his office hours.  I owe so much to his tardiness!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCECSpdx: Congratulations to Mechanical and Materials Engineering @MMEpdx faculty Elliott Gall for his promotion to associate professor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @j_g_allen: In car with others who are not yet vaccinated?  -wear masks -open windows -make sure AC is not on recirc mode  One year ago,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really proud of Antonie.  So well-deserved for her teaching and research excellence around technology management and ability to weave her skill set across disciplines.  #ShineBrightMCECS!  #ThinkBoldMCECS! https://t.co/FvWgoatQkz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really proud of @etgall.  Very well-deserved for teaching and #IAQ research excellence.  And he also has some @ut_caee in his background.  Onward to the next chapter.   #ShineBrightMCECS  #ThinkBoldMCECS  #HookEm! https://t.co/io5Kq5inDQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really proud of Avi.  So well-deserved.  Great teacher and transportation engineering scholar.  And he also has some @ut_caee in his background.   #ShineBrightMCECS!  #ThinkBoldMCECS!  #HookEm! https://t.co/oacwQ84QDP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so proud of Alex, and the guy in the brown shirt sitting next to him.   Seriously, major congratulations to Alex.  Great teacher, researcher,  mentor.  #ShineBrightMCECS  #ThinkBoldMCECS! https://t.co/DYvPVqZL36]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBSNews: JUST IN: Brazil surpasses 400,000 coronavirus deaths https://t.co/EZwRf3BVcJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @itosettiMD_MBA: 41 cases of Indian variant discovered in Israel, including in 5 schools - health ministry asking for education ministry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: France detects first cases of Indian COVID variant -ministry https://t.co/LQml48dQJ1 https://t.co/HojGKGrGWZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: Great example of how schools can invest properly in indoor air quality for immediate  future health benefit. @UofT upgra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PSU_cepe: With @CorsIAQ @MCECSpdx and guest speaker @Wymelenberg @uoregondesign this 2-day event on June 9  10 will translate scientif]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCECSpdx: Congratulations to Electrical and Computer Engineering @EcePdx faculty Roy Kravitz for his promotion to Senior Instructor II!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Poppendieck Well said!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCECSpdx: Congratulations to Electrical and Computer Engineering @EcePdx faculty Tom Schubert for his promotion to Senior Instructor I!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is exciting to me. @MisztalPawel was hired into my old faculty position @ut_caee  even occupies my old office ( its historic white board) at the research campus.  His work is of such high quality and is so impactful. Great to see Pawel soaring! #HookEm!  https://t.co/PODdup24VU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ashishkjha This is too good.  Nice job by @ashishkjha.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GuidoPinamonti I see this as symbolic (the human torso of the rabbit) as good people taking in mistreated greyhounds to comfort them for the remainder of their lives, and the rabbit head symbolizes forgiveness  love despite what may have happened in the past.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarshallJulian @LucIntPanis Excellent work, @MarshallJulian, @joshapte, and colleagues.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCECSpdx: Are you ready to get back to the gym?  "Without adequate risk-mitigation efforts and vaccinated clientele, gyms and workout c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ReginaRyerson Exactly.  So much there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ran into this amazing sculpture today.  A rabbit w/ human form is caring for a greyhound.  As a dog lover who loathes greyhound racing, this one really moved me. https://t.co/mrNX0WvT5I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SuzanneMHume I believe the happiness, joy, and stress part.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ Teaser - 1st slide of my 15 min workshop summary.  Complex system w/ a lot going on: sources, transformations, fate, engineered controls, occupant perceptions  behavior, measurements, exposure, health effects, policies, environmental justice. GR8 topic. Interdisciplinary! https://t.co/eeXNPy2R3a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1/ Fantastic final day of our USEPA-sponsored @theNASEM workshop on Indoor Exposure to Fine Particulate Matter  Practical Mitigation Approaches. 19 speakers, 12 hours of presentations  QA.  All sessions to be posted in approx 2 wks.  Stay tuned!  https://t.co/Q4y7dC5Yix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IndoorChem: Tomorrow is the third and final session of @theNASEM workshop on Indoor Exposure to Fine PM. This session will focus on mit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For the 9,999th time, plants may look nice but they remove no more than minuscule (not measurable) amounts of VOCs etc. from indoor air. The amount of plants necessary to remove measurable amounts would cause many other problems.   https://t.co/QE0DMLyqrE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @linseymarr: Key points from new Lancet Commission report on schools: 1 Check HVAC system every 3-5 yr; monitor CO2 to ensure performanc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffmanLabDU: Excellent new guide on healthy #school buildings. Should be mandatory reading  discussion by all #K12 school boards, dis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShellyMBoulder: on designing infectious disease school resilience into school buildings: Im betting your gonna want to read this new r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honored to have worked on this w/ @j_g_allen, @ShellyMBoulder, @linseymarr, and several other key contributors.  "Designing infectious disease resilience into school buildings through improvements to ventilation and air cleaning"   Just do it!  https://t.co/KQzXtEXUaK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashishkjha: This is awesome if true  US Govt will share up to 60M doses of Astra Zeneca vaccine with the world after a safety review  I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TRECpdx: Congratulations to Avi Unnikrishnan of @CEEdeptPDX @MCECSpdx, for his well-deserved promotion from associate professor to full]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MisztalPawel: Fascinating guest lecture by Hagen Fritz @TheHage in my #IAQ class today! Thank you Hagen for sharing your inspirations a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marinavance @NSF Congratulations, @marinavance!  This is so well-deserved.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good academic mentoring https://t.co/RkxPHwHsrb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come on, folks.  Finish your meal if you want the entire country to have a really good dessert.  https://t.co/H0mtjIVAAE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The final session of our @theNASEM workshop on Indoor Exposure to Fine Particulate Matter  Practical Mitigation Approaches is this Wed from 8 a.m. to noon Pacific Time.  Closing w/ practical  proven mitigation approaches, folks. Listen in. Just do it! https://t.co/Q4y7dC5Yix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@happyhexer Glad you got dose 1, @happyhexer!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Menthol-Plus: a major category of cigarette found among concept descriptor cigarettes from Mexico  Allure  peril.  Nice article by Jim Pankow's team in Maseeh College of Engineering  Computer Sci @Portland_State  Joanna Cohen @JohnsHopkinsSPH.    https://t.co/jUOAbsrqLq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FisherParton No, but I do speak Texan.  :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanplogal Beautiful. Our first dog was a border collie, second an Australian shepherd, and third an Australian cattle dog.  I love herding dogs, too.  So amazingly brilliant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More transmissible variants + low vaccine rate + public letting its guard down = bad things happen.  "Not enough people have been vaccinated and adherence to public health guidelines has fallen off a cliff."  Yep.  https://t.co/zBBLYoJ8fa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The face of a 17 year old #AustralianCattleDog who still stares down her human for just a bit of that almond milk yogurt.  Yes, she got some. https://t.co/wrBbUqNpDI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chambersfw1 I agree.  Stagnation point and streamlines around the barrier.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take by Fran Lebowitz.  If plastic barriers protect us from virus-laden particles, then we should allow smoking again in restaurants, and "there seems to be a lack of understanding of what air is."  I would modify to ---- how air  aerosol particles in air move around objects. https://t.co/24mxCsxVtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jhansonPortland ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kprather88 Been there, @kprather88.  Sometimes it is important to take a sabbatical from twitter. A twittatical.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gloomy  wet day in Portland Oregon.  But we have had a lot of sunshine  some amazing colors in SE Portland this spring. https://t.co/2qnbjrw6z6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JATetro My modeling of outbreaks suggests a cumulative deposited particle volume of as little as 1 to 10 picoliters of PM4 has caused infections. That's total deposition in respiratory system. For nose breathers, approx 75% in nasopharyngeal, 20% in alv,  5% in TB.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2/ At one time they were all PhD students or post-docs  (@poppendieck) in our indoor air quality program @ut_caee. And that's just a start of a much longer list of our grads who are doing  will keep doing great things in the IAQ field! Super proud of all + their advisors.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>