<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Frank Luntz  Kevin McCarthy. Not only are they friends. They are roommates. https://t.co/nYGXxV5bya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you missed our premiere of Tucker Carlson Originals from the Fox Studios Lot on Friday evening - then catch it tonight at 7pm ET on Fox News Channel.  Also, the first episode is available now on @foxnation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Tucker Carlson Originals right now. Heres how. https://t.co/1T4UFgd8k1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres our conversation with Outkick.  https://t.co/8IAvKsj11g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our new series Tucker Carlson Originals will be available first thing Friday morning on @foxnation  Episode one Chicago in Crisis" reveals a city on the verge of collapse. Get a first look at the ENTIRE first season from the Fox Studio Lot in L.A. tomorrow @foxnews at 8pm ET. https://t.co/fbslnawaDW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demographic change is the key to the Democratic Partys political ambitions.  https://t.co/L3t1l9cYOM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our debate with the Governor of Arkansas, a man who vetoed a bill which bans doctors from prescribing puberty blockers to children.  https://t.co/g5izzkasZI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Todays full Piers Morgan interview drops at 4pm ET on @foxnation https://t.co/eohtmBEI4u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A must-see interview Monday afternoon on Tucker Carlson Today only on @foxnation Go to https://t.co/1ZFVJlnqyn now to see it first when the episode drops. https://t.co/y6tB7xLKSq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Piers Morgan gives his first interview since the Meghan Markle feud and walking off the set of his show.  Monday on Tucker Carlson Today  dropping at 4pm ET on @foxnation   PRESS RELEASE: https://t.co/Ycbe6gWMs4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it possible that the food we eat is being engineered in a way that makes us addicted to it? We had a long conversation about this with Michael Moss on Tucker Carlson Today and you can see the full interview at https://t.co/YmNAZYRNyA https://t.co/IvsVc8z0r9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Tucker Carlson makes his debut on Fox Nation. Get unrivaled commentary and discussion on the issues you care about in Tucker C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting Monday https://t.co/HJjUpTyUsc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Tonight is live from El Salvador in 5 minutes on Fox News at 8pm ET. https://t.co/OSUJ2DfjD2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are live from El Salvador.  We just finished sitting down with President Bukele for our new Tucker Carlson Originals series coming soon to Fox Nation. There were also many newsworthy moments well share tonight at 8pm ET on Fox News. https://t.co/YMv7nZFdEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This afternoon, the Department of Defense issued a press release attacking this show: Press secretary smites Fox Host.  Like were a hostile foreign power. Remarkable. Well respond at 8pm ET on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Seuss was never a major literary figure, but his memory matters more than ever. The battle over what Dr. Seuss stood for  over what it means to be racist  will have consequences that extend for generations. If we lose that battle, America is lost. https://t.co/PXzBABcRJv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres a new trailer showcasing just one episode of our new Tucker Carlson Originals documentary series.  We cant wait to release this new series in April only on @foxnation https://t.co/GKKxo86VOe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Systems of oppression, such as those at Yale or Harvard, remain untouched by the profound social upheaval happening elsewhere. We have a plan to change that.   https://t.co/Sw0T7lkRyq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our friend @MarkSteynOnline 's tribute to Daily Beast staff critic @justinbaragona We hope you enjoy! https://t.co/KBw9PY3WDA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We told you in November that we were doubling down on Fox News, and Fox News on us. Tonight we want to tell you what that means. https://t.co/im9tXjQYSX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An exciting announcement from the team behind Tucker Carlson Tonight.  Well share even more details tonight at 8pm ET on #FoxNews https://t.co/gbNCyQ6LCY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fox is the last big news organization in America that differs from the rest. On Fox, there are still journalists who are willing to think for themselves and are brave enough to say so out loud. The oligarchs hate it. And they want to shut us down for good.https://t.co/L5Rjopd2Hf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The greatest music of all time.  https://t.co/1MFa2yxrAX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: Publication day for The Power Couple!  https://t.co/mc5bSKh6sD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dwarf King will vacate his musky lair at CNN. Meet the people at ATT, the owner of CNN, who think its OK to silence Americans. https://t.co/VGAgI2qeI3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This show will always be the sworn supporter of cheese.  We had Green Bay Packers legend Brett Favre on the show to help state our case.  Watch. https://t.co/OzJyhtBaNK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Reddit Revolution exposed everything we needed to know about Wall Street oligarchs and market manipulation. We spoke to @ggreenwald about it earlier.  https://t.co/b2yYKf0LTd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Wall Street really hates is outsider trading, the idea that people from outside their world might be getting rich. Thats the one sin they cant abide. @stoolpresidente Dave Portnoy understands this better than anyone.  https://t.co/Ikp7CNMnrE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This show is fighting back as the Biden administration and Democrats plan to change the country at a record pace. Watch. https://t.co/pJOHsBC3ol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden declares war on America's new enemies. https://t.co/qWW7aih1Iq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dem leaders have decided that 74 million Trump voters didnt simply back the wrong guy or have the wrong opinions. No. The threat they pose is graver and more dangerous than that. These 74 million Trump voters are in fact terrorists.  https://t.co/9BQ16wqSOJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shortly before he was assassinated in 1935, the populist Democrat senator Huey Long of Louisiana had a flash of insight. If the U.S. ever winds up with a fascist government, Long said, well have it under the guise of anti-fascism.  https://t.co/kFHyKtjK6e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exclusive: shocking statements by Biden's DOJ civil rights pick. https://t.co/5CzhwPa3WH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN Dwarf Kings Morning Call: Stop Fox News! https://t.co/PD0rG5mbXy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 1/2: Don't question the Coronavirus vaccine. https://t.co/haEGpLusth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 2/2: Don't question the Coronavirus vaccine. https://t.co/npng6H9JdF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's DOCTOR Jill Biden To You! https://t.co/szFTBZxI3o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's tonight's open: https://t.co/FfZBncnSox]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Tucker Carlson Tonight PR: This is a lie. We never ID'd any voice or aired audio recordings of CNN executives. Check out tonight's segment which is of Marcus Mabry on camera. Facts First, right? https://t.co/zeBNaF99a3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker: Elites are using identity politics to preserve class system https://t.co/DL78G8juuu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A special thanks to Mark Steyn for filling in this evening.  A fantastic show. Check out the open if you missed it. Im back for a special, all new Thanksgiving show tomorrow.  https://t.co/OCwq6QLoYa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An update on our reporting on Sidney Powells voter fraud investigation.  Watch. https://t.co/ho6Dkv0IXf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is why America is great. https://t.co/YTdrzbPWuW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is new information about dead people voting in the General Election. Well investigate tonight at 8pm ET on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We heard you. Its hard to trust anything you hear at this moment. There are conflicting versions of virtually every part of the story. Heres what we know is true right now. https://t.co/gSEGecWPCf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our first response to all the news you heard this weekend. Don't miss the show tonight at 8pm ET on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More on this tonight. 8pm ET #FoxNews https://t.co/A46EQrNSlB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is and has always been a living indictment of the people who run this country. That was true four years ago when Trump came out of nowhere to win the presidency and it's every bit as true right now. Our ruling class is disgusting. https://t.co/0JLb6L5AFR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The final Tucker Carlson Tonight before election day starts in about 30 minutes at 8pm ET on #FoxNews.  We hope youll watch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The missing Hunter Biden documents suddenly reappeared, but we still have a lot of questions. https://t.co/8Oo6WxZa7R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Damning Hunter Biden documents suddenly vanish https://t.co/B2qsajZlID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our reporting on the Biden corruption scandal is not over yet. Tonight, we have new recordings of Biden business partners.Plus: part of our conversation with Tony Bobulinski that we didnt show you last night.Tonight at 8pm ET on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hunter Biden's ex-business partner Tony Bobulinski: "I remember looking at Jim Biden and saying how are you guys getting away with this? Aren't you concerned? He looked at me, and he laughed a little bit, and said 'PLAUSIBLE DENIABILITY.'" https://t.co/IxbND1IbWV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The media has suppressed Tony Bobulinskis story. He is about to share details about his meeting with Joe Biden for the first time. It is just minutes away at 8pm ET on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tony Bobulinski says he met with Joe Biden about China. The media have suppressed the story, but its real and it matters. Voters have a right to know the details. Bobulinski sits for an extended interview Tuesday night at 8p ET on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Setting the record straight with Whoopi Goldberg https://t.co/PaqZNad3gc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["You gotta sell cocaine, I can just file a claim!" https://t.co/P5XTtEH7J8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Burisma told Hunter they wanted "to close down any cases/pursuits against its top official in Ukraine. Watch our report here.  https://t.co/oJssXS6ADq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The show has obtained new Hunter Biden emails that expose corruption. You will not want to miss tonights report. Tune in at 8pm EST on #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In suburban Wisconsin, the white supremacists struck again. And once again, just like we saw in Portland, Kenosha  Minneapolis, they were disguised as Joe Biden voters as they threw rocks into peoples living rooms  attacked police officers. https://t.co/CKgQwoC6W1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 2/2: Amy Coney Barrett represents everything that made our country great. Therefore they despise her. https://t.co/19aXxiOR8x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 1/2: Amy Coney Barrett represents everything that made our country great. Therefore they despise her. https://t.co/9qoKjY6uLr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Left-wing megadonors like George Soros have been busy installing radical district attorneys across America. Watch. https://t.co/uquGFcecZM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chinese whistleblower to Tucker: this virus was made in a lab  I can prove it. https://t.co/CGFZb2YRM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Audio: Cuomo and Cohen Part Two https://t.co/BLJOUny0JC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TONIGHT. New audio of Cuomo and Cohen. 8pm ET https://t.co/CcbbsCn20t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New audio: CNN Chief Jeff Zucker cozies up to Michael Cohen https://t.co/CS4I2o6b6T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN Chief Jeff Zucker secretly gave the Trump campaign debate advice before a debate in 2016? Hard to believe, but yes he did.  Youll hear the recording and more, tonight at 8pm ET on Fox News.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Audio: Chris Cuomo confides in Michael Cohen. https://t.co/SbHoPQx9Tm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PART 2: Voters have started to blame Joe Biden for the chaos. Thats clear in the polls. Suddenly Democratic leaders are worried and they are frantically trying to distance themselves from the terror they created. https://t.co/abC32JCtE3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PART 1: Voters have started to blame Joe Biden for the chaos. Thats clear in the polls. Suddenly Democratic leaders are worried and they are frantically trying to distance themselves from the terror they created. https://t.co/azMtE1Ri8v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kenosha devolved into anarchy because the authorities abandoned the people. Those in charge, from the governor on down, refused to enforce the law. Theyve stood back and watched Kenosha burn. Are we really surprised that looting and arson accelerated to murder? https://t.co/oul2KUiDi3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Bidens job is to soothe your fears about what the left will do to the country. The most radical mass political movement in American history has found a frontman who seems like he should be feeding pigeons.  https://t.co/VrftncMyPN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #DNC2020 they did NOT want you to see. https://t.co/r5ENjoDwsJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bidens Not Jokin https://t.co/nv7AP1jthf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The country isn't shut down enough, says Joe Biden. Don't lift the lockdowns.  Not until people learn how to vote correctly. https://t.co/i8yCk6qj6S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The DOJ has concluded that Yale University systematically discriminates against Asian and White applicants. There's not really any question on the evidence. Shut up, say Democrats. Stop talking about this. Its not a real problem. https://t.co/dotWVop0pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[C'mon Man! https://t.co/cqDDP2ZlAy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone know why the NRCC is using ethnic slurs? https://t.co/he7Au7yZ0e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker responds to intrusive reporting by The New York Times. https://t.co/xj4z69G9cA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[City of Seattle to workers: undo your whiteness. https://t.co/Jv7TrUqD7V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have every right to fight to preserve our nation, heritage and culture. When vandals like Tammy Duckworth and Ilhan Omar tell us that were not allowed to question their patriotism, as they scream about how horrible this country is, we have every right to laugh in their faces. https://t.co/0xjVtUaG3P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats are pushing the lie that moral value corresponds to skin color. Some races, they tell us, are inherently good. Others are inherently bad. This is the very definition of racism. Its poison. https://t.co/eM0t1XnEZn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SenRonJohnson: Modifying my substitute amendment to preserve both Columbus Day and the tax dollars of hard-working Americans. https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump may lose this election.  https://t.co/stBWFjsrN9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most Americans assumed theyd never live to see a moment like this. It happened. It is still happening now. Where are Republican leaders when we need them most? https://t.co/iZNDuFit9C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There must be absolute equality under the law. https://t.co/RiUNqtaGaT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New tourism ad in from Americas newest neighbor: The Nation of CHAZ https://t.co/2FowsblzPY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome to CHAZ. Enjoy your stay.  https://t.co/zcAo9eUNzg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is not a time to submit. Just tell the truth. Watch if you missed tonights show. https://t.co/Jdb0YkGM3Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is America being ripped apart by total lies destroyed by cynical media manipulators and unscrupulous politicians who understand that racial strife is their path to power? You can decide whats really going on. https://t.co/LnVo3agj57]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When the mobs came, they abandoned us.  https://t.co/JftkUTC1Oz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you express an opinion our leaders dont like, they call it violence. When criminals commit acts of actual violence, they call it speech. In other words, the game is rigged.  https://t.co/1VuyVC581Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: The Trump Admin is on the brink of resuming U.S. funding of the World Health Organization. https://t.co/NCm2BZctRc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you were sincerely trying to help the country, youd be focused on effective medical treatments for this disease. The media is ignoring promising treatments, in favor of promoting ever-more-oppressive social controls. https://t.co/QS5wMdSch2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last month, NYC Democrats said Coronavirus was nothing to worry about.  Watch. https://t.co/Urr1S1XJTW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Press wont blame China for the Coronavirus.  So what was the press saying about the virus when it was still possible to contain it?  Watch. https://t.co/oKya4kMjMh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well have much more on this important story tonight at 8pm ET on @foxnews  https://t.co/ByUcA3N2Hj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We must remain calm but not complacent about the Chinese Coronavirus. We addressed it on tonights show. We hope youll watch if you missed it. https://t.co/elhyObX1oV]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>