<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[It beggars belief that the majority of people will still believe  trust a politician as opposed to a professor of pathology? If you truly want an accurate explanation of #covid  the measures we have been forced into watch this. https://t.co/QUUAZeUEYN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Truthse84833901: Well said that guy after he plays the message  https://t.co/AGFPRoedXB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Never believe anything you read/hear from our UK news. There's a reason why newsreaders are paid more than our PM - it's because they are selling you a story! https://t.co/AyHR9zT4v6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jen70717630: My friends friend age 70 has  had 2nd jab, she actually supposedly had convid last year. Now her hands keep going into pai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @prisoner1968: BBC TV news presenters get an average salary of  360,000 a year. Including Newsnigjht presenters for a programme that ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When will the public wake up to the fact that it will never be in Pharma's interest to have a healthy population? Better to have drugs that cause further side affects requiring a different drug? https://t.co/sWzq6T2ESB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Davidt525 https://t.co/ZD2uH4Oep3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gedhurst: It seems to me that Covid created the excuse for the Lockdowns, for which the solution is vaxxs and vaxx passports. Anyone el]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulleczx10 @PaulMainwood Sadly, the majority have accepted the coercion to take the jabs, when ALL known clinical data demonstrates that there has never been any clinical need to jab those under 60.  Facts don't lie. Politicians do. https://t.co/2JSyf1vkkq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernieSpofforth: If you have never fought for anything else in your life, then let it be this   A domestic vaccine passport is not your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeidiJaster Comparison with past vaccines  drugs in general is mind boggling! https://t.co/zJqCa4AcRv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marybethpf: BREAKING: Judge will not hold Elmhurst Hospital in contempt despite 80-hour delay from his order to give IVM to patient get]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deeply worrying report here from an NHS board member. https://t.co/t6Eta8pfd7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@redundantuk I totally agree. Perhaps the adverse affects of regulated drugs as reported by FDA are also misleading? Without clinical need no one should take ANY drugs. https://t.co/jWW0a3JWEb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmigaHarrison @YardleyShooting Want to travel to a foreign country then no passport no entry to a foreign country. Don't want to travel abroad - no passport necessary. A passport is unnecessary unless it enables something. What will a global ID card enable? If it doesn't enable then it's not necessary.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marybethpf: Great news: judge has ordered immediate IVM treatment to Chicago patient. Dismissed the hospital motions to toss the case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is so so true!! https://t.co/paNgq2oY2E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oldbid45: Anyone who hasn't listened to this - it's worth the time! https://t.co/ekvkjW0qV9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffreyPeel: I've tweeted it a few times. But needs repeating. This piece by Dr John Lee is one of the best critiques of the folly of l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Danfrancesco9: The average mans guide to the interpretation of statistics... https://t.co/OxkqGSulf7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahJaneguru I know  I would have hoped that the safety threshold for the un-regulated jabs would have been far higher compared to licensed drugs that have gone through all the clinical trial hoops.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if the covid jabs have a black box warning? Just curious if historical safety precedent for new drugs are being repeated for the jabs? https://t.co/s0YRj5ERyU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In USA $400 billion is spent on prescribed drugs, yet it costs $500 billion to treat the adverse affects that have quadrupled over the past 20 years. And this is from regulated drugs not experimental emergency approved jabs. Of course the jabs are safe - BBC/Govt says they are! https://t.co/oXmh4HWuzK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: BREAKING- The C0V -1D jabs are so safe that just 722,732 adverse reactions have been reported to the MHRA including se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FlorinInteriors: @MattHancock Can you provide the independent safety data first and you've been asked twice in the Commons for data reg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Every time we follow the money it leads us to Bill Gates... https://t.co/kS2mciBc1N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine having to go to a court to force a hospital to treat you with a drug that is on the WHO's list of essential medicines  has had billions of doses prescribed without problems? Why don't they want to treat covid? https://t.co/dleoIwjKIy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elizabe32413720: https://t.co/tGwrH5fsr3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The only disruptive risk to pharma profits are healthy people.  The biggest objectors to vaping (a safer alternative to tobacco smoking) are the Pharma industry. https://t.co/3oraj1tIIa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stephenj_colvin Spot on Stephen. When you've spent 30+ years creating a scenario where UK food consumption is reliant on EU trade you don't want the UK to have the ability to buy elsewhere via trade deals that circumvent EU production.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can anyone tell me the difference between this time last year when the "answer or solution" to #covid was going to be vaccines  today? Nothing has actually changed despite the jabs?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If covid is so contagious that 6 feet social distancing is necessary  masks need to be worn then why does it take a 6 inch swab inserted deep into your nose to test for covid? Surely a saliva test would suffice for such a dangerous virus?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I fully expect this article will be erased soon, as the public can't know what the doctors know.  The public can only be told what the Govt wants! https://t.co/HPnGXfdtCN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If 80% of adults have been "protected" by the jabs  parents believe they are protected, then why would parents risk jabbing their children who scientifically have never been at risk from #COVID  There are no long term safety data as Stage 3 clinical trials won't end until 2023?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[History can teach us a great deal. The comparison between the swine flu jab/harm caused  the #covid jabs is deeply worrying. Usually ANY drug would have now be stopped more so an experimental one? https://t.co/HPnGXfdtCN https://t.co/baAP12tZxp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Humble_Analysis: There are five nations in Europe which have vaccinated less than 3% of their population.  "Surprisingly" cases are dec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dwightd6: Please ask him to contact me on here. https://t.co/VfjERgvvSL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bet not many people know this? It would appear that even public petitions are screened  if public opinion differs from those that influence/pay the petition companies. https://t.co/9jWbpSjARs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is why I say to people that choose to wear a mask that it's actually an intelligence test!  The Govt wanted to test how stupid  compliant the population were. https://t.co/AD9igzIwcW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @darrenmark69: Dear @BorisJohnson if 21st June 2021 does not end everything associated with coronavirus act, be it social distancing, ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BSimonward: Too true ! https://t.co/QinhagtuI0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jen70717630: Think about it.???? https://t.co/qExc8ccqU6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YorkusMarcus: How do they know that the jab 'lessens symptoms'? To know that, we need a group who've had covid, jab them and then give]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @infofoundationx: Spoke to funeral director yesterday. He said all these deaths from the pandemic must have been handled by a private co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LynnBrittney2: Retweeting the truth about India. It's serious but not for the reason the media are telling us. https://t.co/WxzashuzLo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I suspect that this is just so right. Frankly I haven't the heart to say to people face to face that it will take 3-4 years for ANY long term affects of the experimental jabs to be known. The reported short term affects could just be the start? https://t.co/mJY4diWerE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DottiMillotti That man certainly has his grubby hands in many pies!! Feel he should be in the next James Bond movie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The great replacement? Vaccines to replace our natural immunity. Plant food to replace meat. Green energy to replace fossil fuels Note how all of this isn't consumer/innovation driven, but global policy driven by dubious fears propagated by media  politicians.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The magic words "I am exempt" is the key to not wearing a mask. There is nothing anyone can do to force you to wear one.  It's totally your choice  always has been. https://t.co/JZZrkTqRvn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a very valid  crucial point. The harsh reality is NO ONE knows the long term effects of being jabbed  that includes MHRA  Govt  Pharma for the simple reason no long term tests were undertaken. We are those tests I'm afraid. https://t.co/fAcdp3hlH2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichaelRosenYes I'm not sure to be honest, but I'm certain none of them rely on MSM news (we all remember the Chinese actors falling over) so I suspect they will rely on global data such as this: https://t.co/TaV4Jpmzrv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surely it's time for the public to end this bollox? Don't they care? Are they really all that dense? I can now see why the EU decided when it was formed to not rely on democracy for its power as the public are too easily manipulated! https://t.co/Pn2a69TesH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doesn't this combined with #covid make people suspicious? Can't help but think that we are all being treated like mushrooms - kept in the dark  fed a load of shit! The media/social media are totally complicit. https://t.co/OTO90ddpIn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLongerGame: Just spoken to two nurses at City hospitals who inform me blood clots have risen exponentially and many of the elderly ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCarlVernon: So, you can sit inside a pub in Scotland now, but you can't order alcohol.  I despair. Especially for people who still]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: The most important article/analysis you'll read today  - or most any day I think:   https://t.co/pgSONHg0X7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Evidence based medicine" is usually "Pharma paid for good evidence medicine" The Mafia pay off the police  judges. Pharma pay off doctors  scientist  medical journal editors. A great article! https://t.co/mHzwUvrL6X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How much of UK's foreign aid budget is used to buy Pharma's products? I ask because Bill Gates made comments regarding the UK's cut to foreign aid. Are we just being fleeced? https://t.co/9qCg27szfv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK usually has 650,000 annual deaths with an average age at death of 81.  Dying of old age was deemed normal  acceptable. The declared UK #covid deaths number c. 130,000 with an average age at death of 83.3 Dying of old age is now renamed Covid  https://t.co/dtY4VCAgOJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EwaMazierska: When the BBC feeds us with stories about Covid in India's hospitals, it is worth reminding that of India's more than 2.3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paulrey99: @LibertyLins @MattHancock @nadhimzahawi Vaccines are the root of the problem India now faces. They should have stuck w/ Iver]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fascinating figures! You can't disguise burials. Date of deaths/cause of deaths sure but NEVER funerals. https://t.co/HqI2zyGJtP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When 500,000 - 1,000,000 march in London  the @BBCNews doesn't even report it, then you know that everyone should question everything  anything this Govt says. We are being played with MSM complicit in reporting ONLY what the Govt wants. A BLM march would be front line news!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Leonine35: Both give advice on vaccination programme but one is censored. One ex footballer who enjoyed lockdown in Turks and Caicos an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Demo2020cracy The worldometer data appears to contradict the media reporting? https://t.co/h8ehZ6DF39]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Alternatively if you check the data? By helping would that mean selling them the jabs? https://t.co/JmabCYahE3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy78: Don't believe in conspiracy theories... https://t.co/EIiXXiH0pX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EntelechyInc: Isn't it obvious?! At funerals,you get people discussing what the corpse died of. Sudden, was it? Just after the jab, you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlisonBlunt: 45) ..'reconstructed model of a fictitious new virus. The question of how to develop a working vaccine against a virus, of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Superb thread that highlights how the corona virus was not discovered, but conveniently "reconstructed" Sars-Cov- 2 still hasn't been isolated to show it actually exists as a pathogen. https://t.co/vMXwPoLvXa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: For Telegrammers.... @WHO beans spilled....  https://t.co/Y81GJQHAx3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jen70717630: Plus the thousands who don't get reported. Died in their sleep of a sudden heart attack, just a coincidence they'd had the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidjthunder It's pertinent to reflect on Bill Gate's business model of computing. An single operating system used by the majority of global computers, where invariably the consumers don't even get a choice. Vaccines appear to be following a similar path. Vaccines passports accomplish this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would welcome anyone to explain how the "clinical need" to jab healthy under 60's exists? We all know that the jabs deliver a degree of adverse events (up to death) but getting back to normal isn't a clinical reason. https://t.co/SLF5UBJA4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nick_the_geek78: Can you look at this table carefully and explain to me why on earth do healthy &lt;60s need to be vaccinated?? https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deeply worrying thread. If you needed "deaths" to justify #covid where would be the easiest places to obtain those "numbers"? Pertinent to add that deaths outside hospitals have increased dramatically  av. age of "covid deaths" is 84+  Makes you think? https://t.co/SV9g1CtnKQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @skieurope1: The Facebook group for Covid 19 injection victims has been removed. It had 100,000 members. Instead, go to https://t.co/3cd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Alternatively listen to a scientist who is retired  not beholden to Big Pharma or losing his career? https://t.co/c0QduaMh3p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KismetandHope: My wife said she'll have to take the jab if work tells her or lose her career. A few months of slowly presenting evidenc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @geezerpaulr: My wife has been going through my mums medical notes in preparation for a pre inquest hearing tomorrow. The wonderful NHS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eileeniorio: Flu season ends without ever beginning.   People say with a straight face "well that's because we wore masks and were soci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SimonPearson961: Reported serious adverse reactions now above 600,000. That is 1 per 60 people who have been jabbed. I am personally aw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CypriotLondon: Are you not having the vaccine? No, Ill wait until the trials are over in 2023 before I make a decision Room of vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @noreward_norisk: Question: WILL YOU PUBLISH VACCINE RELATED DEATH NUMBERS?  LISTEN TO LIAR JOHNSON.    I DONT KNOW IF WE ARE ABLE TO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very good point! Also the House of Lords, where they are much older and at greater risk. https://t.co/KeFWMO6naZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is frankly shocking. With any stage 3 clinical trials it is usual  imperative that the data is known and acted on accordingly. It is known, but this Govt aren't reacting to anything except their own agenda. https://t.co/YLsZY7PhpB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimHowe73500437 Deeply worrying that so much censorship is occurring. Never thought I was living in North Korea or China.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @annaberu: Be prepared to say I told you so. A LOT.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimHowe73500437 12 hours - I got 12 days after I appealed and my initial 7 days didn't commence until the appeal decision was decided. Facts it would appear are now secondary to the objectives of mass jabbing and whatever follows. https://t.co/FXvY7XHHyU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch this and be educated. Listen to Boris  be duped. Your choice. https://t.co/c0QduaMh3p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So when those celebs/actors being paid  to promote the jabs said "but I don't want the jab" the response may have been " we're not paying you to have the jab, we want you to pretend you're having the jab" https://t.co/NEksSChUKE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MissHarrietLucy: If all those kicking off about the super league could please show this much passion about the fact we are no longer li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TonyMar68854421: This is our last chance, take notice of Dr Mike Yeadon https://t.co/EDKMylkwa7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: We have been in the so called pandemic for 399 days now.  Anyone ever see someone drop in the street in that time ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Replace "travel" with "going to the pub" "eating out" or "socialising" and you begin to fully understand why lockdowns were implemented. The objective was always jabbing the young not protecting the elderly  vulnerable. See it now? https://t.co/biVV3XYfW7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrAdamAneevit: I don't need to be protected from the dangers of Covid.  I need to be protected from the dangers of Government.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CromwellStuff: Seems Israel havent learned from the early 1940s. Segregation by covid vaccinations are in full swing there, separate do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How many patches does Microsoft send out every year? What could possibly go wrong? https://t.co/RowFUBMI0z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: Russian Roulette. https://t.co/GMF0MQg50E]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>