<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @geoff_buxcey: So do businesses get to recoup from the city what they lost from the closures? https://t.co/gAA5bdvnZV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: Trudeau government carves diplomat exception because of Vienna Convention but ignores Canadians Charter rights.  https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vickytc76 @angelalambert14 Brief and clear James Lyons-Weiler, PhD - Pathogenic Priming: Coronavirus Vaccine Safety Warning "Historically, vaccines for coronavirus have had a terrible safety record. There is a condition known as Disease Enhancement due to Pathogenic Priming." https://t.co/d2zsUjgHEQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @buaman1st: @angelalambert14 You cannot give informed consent as the trials are essentially still in progress,  FDA have covered their a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angelalambert14: Page 115 of the Pfizer Vaccine pages of information about the Covid vaccine states theres a risk of VAED - Vaccine as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sharon75571311 @elitesbewarned Oh wow, everywhere! Our cat would have a field day pulling them out!! He's very curious ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelissaLMRogers: @JulieDzerowicz @HoCChamber A UBI will continue to destroy Canada.   Say no to Bill #C273]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliceOnGuard: As of Feb 22, new Emergency Orders made by the Federal Government, travellers are now required to quarantine in approved]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sharon75571311 @elitesbewarned @RobAdam74497148 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it the same in Canada?  "Federal law prohibits employers and others from requiring vaccination with a Covid-19 vaccine distributed under an EUA (Emergency Use Authorization)." #Pfizershot #Moderna   https://t.co/h9WLg3VeWe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Liannabelle1 It is!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sharon75571311 @elitesbewarned @RobAdam74497148 Vanilla, nice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chillie2: Question: when are we going to stop accepting state sponsored child abuse? When are we going to stand up for our kids?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: https://t.co/dvzImc4epA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sas_tomas: Mark my words Canada ...if this passes, the level of hardship in our country will become UNFATHOMABLE!   I lived, survived a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: https://t.co/22lH0wgexO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @grammadeb196: @chillie2 .04% have died from covid worldwide the media has spun Covid BS to Make The Covid Human Zombies forget about ev]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rafkom @chillie2 These 2 videos by Ivor Cummins summarize that. Disregard the mocking faces on 2nd video..  Viral Issue Crucial Update Sept 8th: The Science, Logic and Data Explained https://t.co/sAFice3L70  Crucial Viral Update Jan 4th - Europe and USA - Covers it ALL https://t.co/ZQMXfK9C5q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pizdapalace @chillie2 @kimmieM1973 @DFisman ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AwesomeBiota This wouldn't be happening if ALL the stores/business were open all the time....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sharon75571311 @elitesbewarned @RobAdam74497148  I use unscented dryer sheets!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elitesbewarned @RobAdam74497148 @Sharon75571311  I don't...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nywolforg Look at those eyes!!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nywolforg: Wanna go howl at the moon? https://t.co/VV3C4NIKsp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliceOnGuard: You asked, we've answered.  Keep your questions coming and we'll address them in our #QuestionTuesday posts. https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NMaZjJ71ff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rick_ppc @TrueNorthCentre ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rick_ppc: @TrueNorthCentre Just send a bill to the city for lost revenue. That should work out to far more than $165,188.73. What's goo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garden_nome1: @TrueNorthCentre All businesses shutdown by Toronto Board of Health should send invoices to cover all costs associated wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrueNorthCentre: The invoice came from the Toronto Board of Health.   Most of the amount, totaling $165,188.73, was from Toronto Police]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is challenging the constitutionality of the entire emergency order thats been deployed at a provincial level. https://t.co/2mIORKvE67]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobAdam74497148 @Sharon75571311 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier Original link not working, this one does  https://t.co/gdLFdM2tZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fljl2Frank @randyhillier Original link not working, this one does  https://t.co/gdLFdM2tZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CitizeNonymous @randyhillier This one does!! https://t.co/gdLFdM2tZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@troyrmichaud @randyhillier The original link is not working, this one does  https://t.co/gdLFdM2tZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kisslady69 @jonesca2011 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewKChannel: @randyhillier (You have a right to refuse the test) https://t.co/Sj2U9rxbRq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@belowthesurfac2 @randyhillier https://t.co/gdLFdM2tZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier This link works better  Protesters slam lockdown order - North Bay, ON  #canada #ontario #quebec #Alberta #cdnpoli #onpoli  #NoMoreLockdowns https://t.co/gdLFdM2tZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: More and More people are speaking out, While the Major media  do their utmost to suppress coverage of the facts. Thanks t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cricrifi: Yesterday, my friends returned from their 6 wk long stay in the US. They had 2 negative PCR tests and were allowed to continu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GenuineBenny: What kind of person forces a child to wear a mask for at least 6 hours a day ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GenuineBenny an evil one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CCFR_CCDAF: The Canadian Association of Chiefs of Police make it very clear why they denounce handgun bans. They ONLY affect legal owne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mcclure_jim Animals. It took me a while to see people...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelissaLMRogers: Its called CONTROL when people tell you how to live   #Canada #Ontario #Quebec #Covid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: Defending himself and "colleagues and friends John Edmunds, @JeremyFarrar, @mlipsitch, @c_drosten, @uksciencechief and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Imperial Model and its Role in the UKs Pandemic Response  https://t.co/MJxY3bN9ji]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LatarianOrwell Aha, so I wasn't imagining it. I've noticed the same trend when FF on the recorded shows.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkChangizi: Blows ... your ... mind. https://t.co/ioHtmh0mtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Imagine93700999 @kirstiealley love the owl!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlbertaLeonidas: Trudeau and LPC refuse to condemn genocide.  Same people that want to disarm you  Same people that want to remove your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chillie2: https://t.co/T092HUZjQO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You value freedom? Read this article...  #cdnpoli #abuseofpower #hotelprison #canada #quebec #calgary #illegaldetention #toronto #ottnews https://t.co/LxcQOmLUnV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SChad71593015: Folks It's a violation of the Charter. If you're a Canadian citizen, you MUST be allowed into CA DON'T have to participa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Batesy1973 2/2  "We have written another 60-page dissection of the Drosten PCR protocol. [...] 20 peer reviewed papers showing catastrophic problems. " https://t.co/PpnkmT7brx https://t.co/aHeCCFsisI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Batesy1973 I'm not a teacher, but I disagree with testing children. There's no reliable test.   Paper by 22 scientists/physicians asking a retraction for the Corman-Drosten Report (on which PCR protocol is based), citing 10 major scientific/methodologic flaws  https://t.co/1iWCtemEk8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Batesy1973: Any teachers on here who disagree like myself, with testing everyone in schools?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rpoconnor @epdevilla $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rpoconnor: DEAR DR. @epdevilla:  Why do the Leafs get to dine indoors, go to the gym, and play hockey when you believe those activities]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SJ_Muay_Thai: @JCCFCanada Great. But what about the testing before right of return? Family of four cant shell out thousands of dollars]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goutch: @JCCFCanada https://t.co/4dZEtgeYly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@19828384 @OrlaghOKelly1 @JCCFCanada NO, the government has NOT demonstrated the need for such action.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @giadison: @JCCFCanada https://t.co/BUfSKeaK9y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: New Covid travel rules violate Canadas Charter, a new article by Justice Centre President John Carpay, for the Epoch Times]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: Travel and hotel quarantine legal questions answered.  https://t.co/YElSGfWgqi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["If you are detained or receive a ticket as a result of returning home, please contact the Justice Centre by filling out a case submission."  #cdnpoli #Illegaldetentions #onpoli #ontario #Canada #quebec #calgary https://t.co/8DuUydCh9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 EFUSE THE COVID TEST AT AIRPORT / Land Crossing  Watch Chris: this is how you assert your rights. refuse the test and quarantine and skip a 2 hour line up! made friends with the police too! https://t.co/sUR3TbC3cX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelissaLMRogers: @CP24 REFUSE REFUSE REFUSE  If youre a Canadian citizen you DO NOT need to do this!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 REFUSE TO DO THAT.   State that I'm a Canadian citizen (or Resident) and this is a violation of our Charter Rights Section 6 and a violation of the Emergency Act Section 14.1 so I'm going to be declining your test today and the quarantine at a hotel.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: Justice Centre News Release: Legal challenge on Albertas Bill 10 in Court today  https://t.co/pYl4vqXkgF https://t.co/vEsW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@canadiangirls99 You're correct. I stopped drinking pop years ago. All of them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @canadiangirls99: Why would any white person drink Coke after we learned this week they literally hate us ?  Coke: the official sponsor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisWickNews: It blows my mind that people who get tested with the PCR test for this virus, never, absolutely ever , ask how many cycl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisWickNews I'd say the majority of the people getting tested has no idea about what PCR test cycles are.... #covid #PCRtest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisWickNews: Guess what would happen if we stopped social distancing and NOT wearing masks tomorrow?  ...Nothing... Absolutely NOTHI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation "What about the collateral damage caused by lockdowns? Mandatory lockdowns are leading to the deaths of countless individuals through cancelled/delayed medical operations, suicides, drug overdoses, loneliness and isolation in nursing homes, and more." https://t.co/Z3QOJsCmBX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vintagecacia: @fordnation Such a LIE!! The  OTHER terrible health effects far outweigh the benefits of any sort of lockdown !! Rest ass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarcHaneberg: @karen02792224 Ive never had anyone say a thing about being maskless.   Id say 80% of people want to also, I see it in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Clare57138402 @thereds8 @karen02792224 @CanadianTire No idea, stopped shopping @CanadianTire years ago, awful customer service.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ev0l @karen02792224 Do it then ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karen02792224: I only share this because as an introvert, I understand that the idea of being singled out and ostracized in public can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karen02792224: Ive been denied service once and it was at @chaptersindigo before knowing they were willing to break the law over mask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karen02792224 @chaptersindigo Thanks for sharing Chloe!! I will not shop at @chaptersindigo either. I don't wear the mask at any store. You are right, there's many businesses that respect our rights and the exemptions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karen02792224: Successfully completed all 5 stores for errands without a mask today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HopeStill17 yep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaskLass: It seems like we have a lot more curves to deal with now than we had a year ago  https://t.co/8gn0ykKp3f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @freedom_fanny: @Scscottish @MelissaLMRogers @MarcGarneau I had friends that had a plan for isolation and they were allowed to go home o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelissaLMRogers: REFUSE the Covid test and Quarantine at the airport. We must all do this! Its a violation.   #Canada #Ontario #Quebec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Corrupt_19: @chrissaccoccia1 @KoenSwinkels When are these judges going to start shaming these officers who issue the tickets? The polic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrissaccoccia1: PEARSON AIRPORT showing YOU how to DEFEAT the "mandatory" covid test and any potential "hotel quarantine" and skip the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexpiersonAMP: Ever get the feeling that the fed gov doesnt have ANY data to back up any of the wrong headed decisions that have been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look for article "Seniors Dying After COVID Vaccine Labeled as Natural Causes" at the articles . mercola . com site. It's being censored here...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarolHusband: I support @randyhillier ; his courage, his resolve; his determination to regain our freedoms; his constant work to rid us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SheilaGunnReid: GraceLife says that the government can keep arresting pastor after pastor for preaching every Sunday and the next Sunda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stevelanebitch: Is @fordnation going to rob kids of their summer sports like baseball, soccer, Football and so on? https://t.co/dokJRgm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: The PPC is seeking candidates for the next election. Will you stand with me? https://t.co/dgDoC1uhLn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaskLass: The little child is at it again. For all of you that know me and have been following me for a long time , I trust you all rea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["REFUSE THE COVID TEST AT AIRPORT  this is how you assert your rights. refuse the test and quarantine and skip a 2 hour line up! made friends with the police too! "  #cdnpoli #CanadianCharter https://t.co/sUR3TbC3cX]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>