<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[We are an hour away from the event COVID-19 Vaccine Development  Roll-Out: Addressing Disparities  Hesitancy While Preparing for Challenges Ahead.  Get your questions ready and be part of the conversation: https://zoom/us/j/99480640590. https://t.co/xmmGMSzKgz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We invite you to be part of the event COVID-19 Vaccine Development  Roll-Out: Addressing Disparities  Hesitancy While Preparing for Challenges Ahead  When? Tomorrow at 6:00 p.m. ET Where? https://zoom/us/j/99480640590 https://t.co/MrmnDclPPU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Te invitamos a participar del evento Cmo hablar con nuestros seres queridos del COVID-19 presentado por @UnidosUS este Jueves, 6 de Mayo a las 11:30 a.m. PST / 2:30 p.m. EST  nete a la conversacin a travs de https://t.co/Gb8ED2bwEu  Te esperamos! https://t.co/ab0L0kQGEm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Properly wearing a mask that covers your nose and mouth, and that is well fitting, continues to be one of the best ways to stop spreading the virus.   #PreventCOVID https://t.co/ByZ9Ug8afN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont miss  the FB Live event for Pandemia Episode 5: Vaccination among Hispanics.    When? 4/29 at 2:00 p.m. ET    Where? https://t.co/slp0kGpT5U  @LatinoCommAIDS @WeAreUnidosUS https://t.co/w7m0ay4MOW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Join us today, April 28, from 12pm-1pm for a discussion with Joseph Seia for #NationalMinorityHealthMonth with @cereatfredhu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What side effects did you experience after getting the COVID-19 vaccine? #PreventCOVID https://t.co/Y0cdpB5LPa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID variants: preventing infection is key. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/qSM446TEq2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Dr. Larry Corey of Fred Hutch to speak at "COVID-19 Symposium: Strategic Planning for Crises" during @theNASciences 158th An]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID variants: What you need to know. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/18PEL1fbUz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NIH: ICYMI: Yesterday, @NIHDirector joined other public health experts on Twitter to answer your questions on #COVID19 vaccines. Read t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @COVID_19Network: Acompanos en esta conversacin en lnea que abordar maneras de volver a la normalidad para mejorar nuestra salud me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Te invitamos a participar del evento El Impacto de COVID-19 en nuestra salud mental: estrategias para enfrentar mejor la pandemia presentado por @UnidosUS maana jueves, 4/22 11:30 a.m. PST / 2:30 p.m. EST. nete a la conversacin a travs de https://t.co/wlaPqwpWyS. https://t.co/5qWUyDq0dX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were you unsure/worried to receive the COVID-19 vaccine at first? If so, what helped you get over it? #PreventCOVID https://t.co/ivkRD7Zf8R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID variants: What you need to know. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/vtaJr8759d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the Recent #HIV  Vaccine Research Findings Really Mean. Read more: https://t.co/YFbgsidTOX via @RollingStone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have witnessed how important effective messaging is in public health emergencies, and what happens when this is absent, says CoVPNs @imstephaunelite. Read about his trailblazing public health career in this @SoSeaEmerald profile: https://t.co/6MaY99tNDw #CoVPN #PreventCOVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SoSeaEmerald: I also hope this pandemic has put into plain view that racism is a public health threat. Addressing racism and the impac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can people receiving both Moderna vaccine doses still spread the #COVID-19 virus? A @PreventCOVID_19 study involving 12,000 students at 20 colleges nationwide seeks the answer. Read more in this @washingtonpost story: https://t.co/xHGvSknhy7 #CoVPN #PreventCOVIDU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Today, the FDA and CDC recommended a pause in the use of the Johnson  Johnson vaccine. Heres what you need to know: https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What helped you decide to get the COVID-19 vaccine? #PreventCOVID https://t.co/9IuGWfQP1I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its really important for communities to follow the science, says @imstephaunelite. There are Black scientists, Black physicians, Black healthcare providers who are working at all levels to make sure we are not left behind in this process. Watch: https://t.co/UPN2eWci4h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @imstephaunelite: Such a great collaboration and amazing effort. Thanks again for supporting COVID-19 education and confidence in the sc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us TOMORROW for the COVID Conversation Clinic: Update on COVID-19 Vaccines in Black Communities.   Our panel will discuss important topics concerning vaccine distribution, differences between approved vaccines, and new developments on the horizon.   https://t.co/1hgl8cxVvV https://t.co/ecPT6odrlP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The COVID-19 vaccines are good news for protecting people, but properly wearing a mask that covers your nose and mouth continues to be one of the best ways to stop spreading the virus. You may also want to consider wearing two masks, which can offer additional protection. https://t.co/Ux7yVxTK6w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Be part of the COVID Conversation Clinic: Update on COVID-19 Vaccines in Black Communities.     When? 4/13 @ 6 pm ET / 3p.m. PT    Where? https://t.co/1hgl8cxVvV  Get your questions ready and be part of the conversation.  @Cobb_Institute @blackdoctor_org @NationalMedAssn https://t.co/IZLfbbwRYS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thankyou @BillGates for shining a light onsystemic racisms role in the pandemic last year and the need to reach peoplewho are usually left behind. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/6CznVkRsvi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us as our panel of COVID-19 vaccine experts will discuss important topics concerning vaccine distribution, differences between approved vaccines, and new developments.      When? 4/13, 6 pm ET https://t.co/1hgl8cxVvV  @CIC4Process  @blackdoctor_org  @NationalMedAssn https://t.co/bvViqh1ipJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People ask about the differences between the #COVID19  vaccines, but it might be better to consider their similarities. They are all really good at preventing serious illness, hospitalizations and deaths, says CoVPNs @imstephaunelite. Watch: https://t.co/J87QTc0sNz #CoVPN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillGates: Dr. Stephaun Wallace (@imstephaunelite) has spent the last year helping make COVID-19 vaccines work for everybody. Stephaun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID variants: What you need to know. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/kjnWiPBGeL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can people who have gotten the #COVID19 vaccine still spread it to others? A new study tracking infections in vaccinated college students and their close contacts will be the most thorough look at the issue, says Dr. Larry Corey of #CoVPN. https://t.co/IiAoRnTTPr #preventcovidu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NIMHD: Today is #WorldHealthDay! The #COVID19 pandemic has highlighted health inequities that exist both in the U.S. and worldwide. We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Making #COVID19 vaccines accessible to everyone  especially communities of color  is going to take a ton of hard work. One]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: About 20% of Fred Hutch researchers have active projects related to the #COVID19. Read more about these studies, and their m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNC_SOM: Want to get your #COVID-19 vaccine and help your community? Help UNC SOM researchers find out if the vaccine not only helps pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lleg el momento de vacunarnos contra el #COVID19  https://t.co/bBC1slbboE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honest, authentic dialogue is critical for justice that will secure equitable access to the COVID-19 vaccines for #BIPOC communities, say Dr. Michele Andrasik @FredHutch and Dr. Sandra Quinn @UMDPublicHealth in a Perspective in @NEJM. #CoVPN #FredHutch https://t.co/VE936muyZK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is a protein-based COVID-19 vaccine? Learn more here. https://t.co/bP7qiX9sY3 https://t.co/ImcdJ8pjHd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Natural protection from COVID-19 gets boost from a single dose of vaccine: https://t.co/kZDPwqBL8Z via @fredhutch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why does standing six feet away from others help? https://t.co/XotkV3aaRW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us for HVTN Community Cafe Episode 3:  Reimagining HIV Vaccine Research in Communities    When? Thursday, April 1st  at 1:00 p.m. ET    Where? Through Facebook Live or Zoom  https://t.co/5M4rYwe6KG  Invite your friends and colleagues and be part of the conversation. https://t.co/p7nf4NKxoM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TAGTeam_Tweets: Join TAG + @PreventCOVID_19 next Tues, Apr 6 @ 3 PM EDT for our #webinar, "Community Update on Current  Future #COVID1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aprilkaurphd: We started our @PreventCOVID_19 transmission study this week! #PreventCOVIDU  Countless hours put in by @k_stephensonMD @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How does an mRNA vaccine work? https://t.co/lNc1zu1NBt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We will explore some of the innovative and dynamic ways HIV research staff are tackling community engagement post-COVID.  https://t.co/5M4rYwe6KG https://t.co/qD5sJdckr4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: A new study from the Hutch-based @PreventCOVID_19 will offer the Moderna #COVID19 vaccine to 12,000 students willing to swab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: A new study from the Hutch-based @PreventCOVID_19 will offer the Moderna #COVID19 vaccine to 12,000 students willing to swab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @k_stephensonMD: It's a good day when Dr. Fauci announces our study at a @WhiteHouse press briefing. Many thanks to Larry Corey, Myron C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @k_stephensonMD: Excited to share a new project! Very proud to lead this  @NIH @PreventCOVID_19 study with co-chairs @DrJRMarcelin and D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How do Protein-based COVID-19 vaccines work? https://t.co/6UmRYjfeUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: AstraZeneca to publish full U.S. trial results after rare rebuke over 'outdated' data. Dr. Larry Corey shares his insight wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is today!   Be part of the FB Event Pandemia Episode 4: Vaccine Rollout in the Hispanic/Latino Community.    When? 3/25 at 1pm ET    Where? https://t.co/XUTmd8iGk1  @LatinoCommAIDS https://t.co/r2OmmZZQGH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[S parte del FB Live Enfrentando los Retos del COVID-19. Un panel con expertos de la comunidad Latina sobre el COVID-19, las vacunas, salud mental, la desigualdad en la salud pblica y ms, presentado por @NIH   Cundo? 3/27 @ 2:00 p.m. ET Dnde? https://t.co/exw8vpNZtO https://t.co/wxhYjlr4TR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will it hurt when I get the COVID-19 vaccine? https://t.co/xjif1avg34]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont miss  the FB Live event for Pandemia Episode 4: Vaccine Rollout in the Hispanic/Latino Community.    When? 3/25 at 1pm ET    Where? https://t.co/XUTmd8iGk1  In partnership with @LatinoCommAIDS https://t.co/PCNHzL9G4n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the COVID-19 vaccines were a sandwich, this is what the sandwich of a COVID-19 vector vaccine would look like. https://t.co/jrSahYcmUL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In episode 4 of the Pandemia discussion series, we will discuss COVID-19, provide an update on vaccine efforts, and the implications the vaccine might have on medical mistrust within the Latinx community.   When? 3/25, 1pm ET    Where? https://t.co/XUTmd8iGk1 @LatinoCommAIDS https://t.co/JjEIxq9iHj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One vaccine dose or two? We need to our best defenses against the variants https://t.co/aRhnacUcWe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnson and Johnson has announced favorable results from its study of an adenovector vaccine against COVID-19. But what is a vector vaccine and how does it work? https://t.co/kjbFlMeBkJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NIAIDNews: COVID-19 NEWS: 2 studies presented at #CROI2021 had encouraging results for monoclonal antibodies (#mAbs) for prevention of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: One year ago, on March 11, 2020, the World Health Organization declared the coronavirus a pandemic.  These stories offer a loo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Today is National COVID-19 Day and also the day the @WHO declared COVID-19 a pandemic. The purpose is to help the United Sta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New COVID-19 Viral Vector Vaccines are in development. Discover how they work here. https://t.co/qgtycifupb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Join the @naamnw and the @PacSci on Saturday, March 13 for It Takes A Village to hear Dr. @imstephaunelite of @PreventCOVID_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CoVPNs Faith and #Diversity Work Engages Key Communities Impacted by #COVID19 -https://t.co/PWfMNs3m3J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Should I get the COVID-19 vaccine if I have pre-existing health conditions, a history of allergies, or if I am taking a specific medication? https://t.co/NA8UwdRY9M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @greaterthanCV19: THE CONVERSATION #BetweenUsAboutUs is starting! @wkamaubell  Black docs, nurses  researchers answer YOUR questions a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abordando Mitos y Hechos del COVID-19. Mito: Debes creer todo lo que lees en internet sobre la prevencin del COVID-19.  FALSO! En este video te explicamos por qu.   Para obtener respuestas adicionales a preguntas frecuentes, visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX https://t.co/aCQb0aegEx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are there any effects of COVID-19 vaccines on pregnancy, the developing fetus, or infants? https://t.co/b0PNHG0ZFV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Addressing COVID-19 Myths and Facts. Myth: The prolonged use of medical masks causes oxygen deficiency or CO2 intoxication. This is FALSE! Watch the video and learn why.   Visit https://t.co/bP7qiX9sY3 for answers to the most common questions. https://t.co/bUIDQ4IkWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us for HVTN Community Cafe Episode 2: How COVID-19 Efforts Can Help End HIV.      When? TOMORROW! Tuesday, March 2nd @ 2:00 p.m. ET   Where? Through Facebook Live or Zoom  Invite your friends and colleagues and be part of the conversation. https://t.co/P7yPrbPwB1 https://t.co/qL7Uk3Cy7u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is the current status of COVID-19 vaccines research in children and adolescents? https://t.co/WXwkeeVZlF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will the COVID-19 vaccine modify peoples DNA? To learn more about COVID-19 and find more Frequently Asked Questions visit https://t.co/BPTUBoss1t  #PreventCOVID https://t.co/unvHk6leAF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Ep. 2 of HVTN Community Caf, we will explore how community engagement in COVID-19 research can inform ongoing efforts in HIV research. We will engage this conversation from the perspective of individuals of the trans experience.  Register here: https://t.co/P7yPrbPwB1 https://t.co/2JNSxlJu1t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Por qu es importante la representacin de la Comunidad Latina en los estudios para las vacunas de COVID-19? Porque este grupo es afectado desproporcionadamente.   Aprende ms: https://t.co/bxKIOtJ6PE. https://t.co/qfUHSjE1Qh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are proud to be a part of Its Up to You in partnership with the @AdCouncil and the @TheCOVIDCollab to ensure Americans have the facts about the COVID-19 vaccines. Get the latest info at https://t.co/lrHIgfjUej https://t.co/EDKjuqgYg6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Last spring, as COVID-19 began to tear through American cities and was disproportionately affecting communities of color, Dr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is it important to keep wearing a mask, practicing social distance, and other preventive methods after taking the COVID-19 vaccine? Dr. Stephaun Wallace explains on today's episode of  'My COVID-19 Vaccine Study Journey'.   Have questions? Reply/DM. https://t.co/gcE3a7E88w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We now have hard clinical evidence that our current vaccines will work as well against the UK variant as they have for the variants circulating in the U.S.  https://t.co/GfgqsLE0u3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[De qu est hecha la vacuna del COVID-19? Contiene el virus?  Para obtener ms informacin en tu idioma sobre el COVID-19 visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX #PreventCOVID https://t.co/lcIicAue0y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: The coronavirus can take many paths to reinvading a persons body. Most of them shouldnt scare us. @jbloom_lab spoke with @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @imstephaunelite: Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center is working hard to overcome vaccine hesitancy, bust myths and educate the commu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three reasons to continue COVID-19 vaccine research.  Visit the following link to learn more about other frequently asked questions: https://t.co/Fa9SxW1BPi https://t.co/o49De4qPPz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La Administracin de Alimentos y Medicamentos de los Estados Unidos (FDA) otorg una autorizacin de uso de emergencia para dos vacunas contra el COVID-19 fabricadas por Pfizer y Moderna, pero Qu significa esto y qu sigue?   Visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX para ms informacin. https://t.co/XFGex31Ckl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seattle Times columnist @christykarras, who tested positive for COVID-19 during the pandemics early stages, shares her incredible story one year later and acknowledges @FredHutch and Dr. Larry Corey for their help on her journey. https://t.co/dGneKYKjws #CoVPN #PreventCovid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In today's 'My COVID-19 Vaccine Study Journey', Dr. Stephaun Wallace shares his experience after getting his second shot as part of the Novavax COVID-19 study and explains how he felt. If you have any questions for Dr. Wallace, please share them on the comments or via DM. https://t.co/180HaR4Eth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Join us Tuesday, Feb. 23, for #HutchScienceSays, our monthly researcher roundtable, to meet scientists who are leading vacci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us tonight at 7:00 p.m. ET for 'Islam, COVID-19, Vaccines and Mistrust: Black History Month Edition'.Invite your friends and colleagues and be part of the conversation. #PreventCovid https://t.co/31ankRtg6x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A year after I first wrote about recovering from COVID-19, heres how my life has changed https://t.co/5aRr3jYSUV via @seattletimes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have two approved mRNA COVID-19 vaccines, but there are still things we hope to learn from the research studies.  Visit https://t.co/BPTUBoss1t to learn more about other frequently asked questions. https://t.co/B576o2vVST]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fredhutch: Dr. Larry Corey discussed vaccine development related to COVID-19 variants with @USATODAY . Read more here:  https://t.co/Z0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Para encontrar ms vacunas seguras y eficaces para la Comunidad Latina, necesitamos voluntarios como t. nete como voluntario en los estudios de las vacunas de COVID-19 y aydanos a terminar con la incertidumbre.   Visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX hoy. https://t.co/gJOPVbv1Le]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Addressing COVID-19 Myths and Facts. Fact: Licensed vaccines have an excellent track record of safety.  Visit https://t.co/5HkcwXna4C for answers to the most common questions. https://t.co/CrCptTVCOn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Porqu necesitamos seguir con los estudios clnicos si ya hay un par de vacunas?  Visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX y regstrate para ser voluntario en los estudios de la vacuna contra el COVID-19. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/VRHtQJajwZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Recibiste una vacuna COVID-19, y ahora qu? Visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX para ms informacin. https://t.co/yKduc7zRAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abordando Mitos y Hechos del COVID-19. Mito: El COVID-19 es como la gripe estacional. FALSO! Descubre las diferencias entre el COVID-19 y la gripe estacional mirando este video.   Para obtener respuestas adicionales a preguntas frecuentes, visita https://t.co/6cGHAROjtK https://t.co/xLCMuqGHXt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are there any data from volunteers who got pregnant or who were breastfeeding during COVID-19 vaccines studies? https://t.co/HbSBtqSZxH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La vacuna del COVID-19 modifica el ADN de las personas?   Visita https://t.co/rIPInif7uX para ms informacin sobre el COVID-19 en tu idioma. #PreventCOVID https://t.co/HNwK1PXjJ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the heroes taking part in the #CoVPN phase 3 Moderna COVID-19 vaccine trial @uc_health in Cincinnati as researchers raced to find a safe and effective vaccine that is now being used to help end the pandemic. https://t.co/89gXUhadzl #HealthcareHeroes #universityofcincinnati]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>