<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 04 May.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/kwzUp1UFAh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 586 148 the total number of deaths is 54 511 the total number of recoveries is 1 509 656 and the total number of vaccines administered is 339 655. https://t.co/os5T7EEuCg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 03 May.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/nqSoNNEUPH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 584 961 the total number of deaths is 54 452 the total number of recoveries is 1 508 558 and the total number of vaccines administered is 329 098. https://t.co/KT9IL1rEUD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The first batch of Pfizer vaccines have landed at OR Tambo International Airport. https://t.co/eOlrWWBkfl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 02 May.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/FdYq5OLzgJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 584 064 the total number of deaths is 54 417 the total number of recoveries is 1 507 778 and the total number of vaccines administered is 318 670. https://t.co/y67mZbFKsP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media Statement: Update on Status of Delivery of Market Doses of Pfizer and Johnson and Johnson. https://t.co/V64JGPJFll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 01 May.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/F1Jlv8ugTn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 582 842 the total number of deaths is 54 406 the total number of recoveries is 1 506 732 and the total number of vaccines administered is 318 670. https://t.co/0WNhkTonxo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNICEFInnocenti: How can we achieve #VaccinEquity, @DrZweliMkhize  His response on our #LeadingMinds panel last week   @HealthZA #Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 30 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/dc8gBMmCiI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 581 210 the total number of deaths is 54 350 the total number of recoveries is 1 505 620 and the total number of vaccines administered is 317 656. https://t.co/4EGoUIMGLZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 29 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/tymdEBSr6B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 579 536 the total number of deaths is 54 331 the total number of recoveries is 1 504 426 and the total number of vaccines administered is 307 591. https://t.co/90J5HupkOv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 28 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/OKtiOWKDRl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 578 450 the total number of deaths is 54 285 the total number of recoveries is 1 503 611 and the total number of vaccines administered is 298 153. https://t.co/qsMeGiFe52]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VG5GkYwynK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 27 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/nZToXjlLtt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 577 200 the total number of deaths is 54 237 the total number of recoveries is 1 502 986. https://t.co/JapUZ68mQW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 26 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/jw9fhXY3sw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 576 320 the total number of deaths is 54 186 the total number of recoveries is 1 501 880. https://t.co/W4e83qHted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Statement on the status of vaccine rollout in South Africa https://t.co/UdZn8VAT4f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 25 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqa0Ht5 https://t.co/DSoCaJzmFD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 575 471 the total number of deaths is 54 148 the total number of recoveries is 1 501 185. https://t.co/a36N3sWMkH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 24 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/Fhb1ex1cpA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 574 370  the total number of deaths is 54 125 the total number of recoveries is 1 500 360. https://t.co/UmPILHlcFf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 23 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/Ijembh8dSb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 572 985 the total number of deaths is 54 066 the total number of recoveries is 1 499 110. https://t.co/HkTR4ZtwR9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 22 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/ktqHXo4n1W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 571 348 the total number of deaths is 53 995 the total number of recoveries is 1 496 756. https://t.co/4fgN1pYZYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 21 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/2vewP0VCEI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 569 935 the total number of deaths is 53 940 the total number of recoveries is 1 495 864. https://t.co/mfcQIfhPB8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 20 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/wmKJM1spqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 568 366 the total number of deaths is 53 887 the total number of recoveries is 1 494 630. https://t.co/C5d6rF7Wcr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GautengHealth: The Minister of @HealthZA @DrZweliMkhize is today visiting Charlotte Maxeke Hospital.  https://t.co/75rb5DOFss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But it really is a good news story that not one life was lost or injured and I highly commend the swift action taken.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To move so many patients within a short space of time and I am happy all of you are safe. We do need to appreciate the risks of stocking high volumes of alcohol containing sanitiser and PPE- we have never had to stock so much before in facilities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im here to support and I convey my gratitude to everyone who participated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is distressing to see so much infrastructure destroyed but my biggest worry was the patient as the biggest problem is carbon monoxide poisoning from smoke inhalation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Minister has commended the swift actions of the management team who managed to evacuate more than 800 patients.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Minister has arrived at Charlotte Maxeke Hospital and is getting a briefing on the hospitals disaster management following the fire. https://t.co/EvcBPblPau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 19 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqa0Ht5 https://t.co/6rddVr7geH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 567 513 the total number of deaths is 53 575 the total number of recoveries is 1 490 876. https://t.co/kNfhvKHbfh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Engaging members of NUPSAW as stakeholders at Lentegeur Hospital. #WCVisit19April https://t.co/aR77ddYegX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also accompanied by the Premier and MEC at the Mitchells Plain Vaccination site.  #WCVisit19April https://t.co/NkTFAJT97U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanwinde: [WATCH] We have just arrived at our vaccination centre with @DrZweliMkhize  https://t.co/hO3RtiCCAM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HOD Dr Keith Cloete taking us through the Mitchells Plain Hospital Vaccination Centre #WCVisit19April https://t.co/1WbOwAG48C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Assuring the Premier of the Western Cape @alanwinde that NDOH @HealthZA has procured enough vaccines for the Province. The Province can continue to focus on their plan which looks good at this stage. #WCVisit19April https://t.co/l2mvWUkkdf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An oversight visit will be conducted today, 19 April 2021 to assess the readiness of the second phase of the vaccine rollout in the Western Cape. #WCVisit19April https://t.co/kphDFGpOsD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 18 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqa0Ht5 https://t.co/OUsM119RPp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 566 769 the total number of deaths is 53 736 the total number of recoveries is 1 490 143. https://t.co/ewVMq6vlb2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 17 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqa0Ht5 https://t.co/Iz6cXf1pAk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 565 680 the total number of deaths is 53 711 the total number of recoveries is 1 489 457. https://t.co/4tFoC7LQ38]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 16 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/7WZ092GJoi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 564 355 the total number of deaths is 53 663 the total number of recoveries is 1 488 572. https://t.co/JWZvU9oiYM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Steps to getting vaccinated for senior citizens 60 years and above  #COVID19VaccineSA #IChooseVaccination  #CoronaVirusSA https://t.co/ORL1iTQLnJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is the registration guide to the Electronic Vaccination Data System (EVDS) for senior citizens aged 60 years and above.  #COVID19VaccineSA #IChooseVaccination #CoronaVirusSA https://t.co/6kshbT8WPy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 15 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/2Cvh9G0exL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 562 931 the total number of deaths is 53 571 the total number of recoveries is 1 488 060. https://t.co/ADMcsNnAgo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the link is as follows:https://t.co/uoXYXXtSZq  Members of the public are urged to access these draft regulations and send comments by 19 April 2021. Comments can be sent to the following email address: NFCcomments@health.gov.za.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT AND URGENT PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT:  As announced by the Minister of Health Dr Zweli Mkhize, the National Department of Health has published the draft Regulations for the establishment of the No Fault Compensation Fund on the Departments website]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 14 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/ZpS9h0vJQF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 561 559 the total number of deaths is 53 498 the total number of recoveries is 1 486 873. https://t.co/OQjZoz2ASA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 13 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/oDMm2L4e7z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 559 960 the total number of deaths is 53 423 the total number of recoveries is 1 485 315 and the total number of vaccines administered is 292 623. https://t.co/eZbjJuUP8S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We therefore urge South Africans to be supportive of our experts and scientists as they work under enormous pressure to give us answers on this worrying development so that we may proceed safely with the global vaccination programme. https://t.co/MgAb5IWLwB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the extremely unlikely event that Johnson and Johnson rollout is completely halted, we will not have any impediment to proceed with phase two of the rollout with Pfizer. https://t.co/0gGe06t4kl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I humbly call for calm and patience as we ensure that we continue to be properly guided by science in ensuring the safety of our people as we rollout the vaccine campaign. https://t.co/TR3LRV8Ase]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In South Africa, we have not had any reports of clots that have formed after vaccination, and this is after having inoculated 289 787 health care workers under the Sisonke Protocol. https://t.co/mrQ54W9RWr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have determined to voluntarily suspend our rollout until the causal relationship between the development of clots and the Johnson and Johnson vaccine is sufficiently interrogated. https://t.co/qYq50IvV9L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Statement by the Minister of Health, Dr Zwelini Mkhize, on the FDAs Temporary Suspension of Johnson and Johnson vaccine rollout in the United States. https://t.co/DTnUK0a2li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 12 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/94n4xNHNHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 559 113 the total number of deaths is 53 356 the total number of recoveries is 1 484 356 and the total number of vaccines administered is 289 787. https://t.co/Yip5hvjCYG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 11 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/1aBYc0m5r5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 558 458 the total number of deaths is 53 322 the total number of recoveries is 1 483 296. https://t.co/zafxTPjkJA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 10 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/XDBaY0FPoc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 557 527 the total number of deaths is 53 256 the total number of recoveries is 1 482 682 and the total number of vaccines administered is 288 406. https://t.co/9iaeTEjmQL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ANCNECMember Cde #ZweliMkhize inspects the work done to confront the sewer challenges at the Rooikopen, ward 11, Lekwa Municipality ahead of the community meeting. https://t.co/lTu1rSzQx9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ANCNECMember Cde #ZweliMkhize, has inspected the Rooikopen Pump Station in ward 11 which he launched a few years back at COGTA https://t.co/lGqTQpVpzs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ANCNECMember Cde #ZweliMkhize, in Gert Sibande Region today. https://t.co/70RqApSIU4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 09 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/FI60hzt7RC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 556 242 the total number of deaths is 53 226 the total number of recoveries is 1 481 637 and the total number of vaccines administered is 288 368. https://t.co/a4XnGt0vy4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 08 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/iqai6fzZTX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 554 975 the total number of deaths is 53 173 the total number of recoveries is 1 480 632 and the total number of vaccines administered is 283 629. https://t.co/GOaqxHeQWt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inspecting the vaccination centre at Charlotte Maxeke Hospital with the Premier and MEC. #IChooseVaccination https://t.co/nj4mcJk028]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Embarking on a countrywide tour to assess the readiness of Provinces for the mass vaccination campaign. Starting today at Charlotte Maxeke Hospital in Gauteng Province- a significant start as we celebrate Charlotte Maxeke in the year of her 150 birth anniversary. https://t.co/jQnSuimNzn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 07 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/gbK2hqRJS1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 553 609 the total number of deaths is 53 111 the total number of recoveries is 1 479 821 and the total number of vaccines administered is 278 909. https://t.co/Y4Q5K3K06B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovernmentZA: COMING UP at 10h00 | The Minister of @HealthZA, @DrZweliMkhize  and WHO Director in Africa, Ms Matshidiso Moeti will host]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 06 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/Ow1iTiwWIx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 552 853 the total number of deaths is 53 032 the total number of recoveries is 1 478 820 and the total number of vaccines administered is 272 438. https://t.co/vYj5W5fGVh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 05 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/MTycFdfUDl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 552 416 the total number of deaths is 52 995 the total number of recoveries is 1 478 088. https://t.co/nJVaXC9fwG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 04 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/dWSRhg7Ma6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 551 964 the total number of deaths is 52 987 the total number of recoveries is 1 477 363 and the total number of vaccines administered is 269 102. https://t.co/ODK2knsfxb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 03 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/kal0IbDkEy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 551 501 the total number of deaths is 52 954 the total number of recoveries is 1 476 605 and the total number of vaccines administered is 269 102. https://t.co/3kIw2Q77mA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 Statistics in SA as at 02 April.  Use the COVID Alert SA app to protect yourself, your loved ones and your community. Start using this privacy preserving app today. Add your phone to the fight! Download the Covid Alert SA app now! https://t.co/8YKEqaiiRF https://t.co/HnRuDFsQmx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As of today, the total number of confirmed #COVID19 cases is 1 550 724 the total number of deaths is 52 964 the total number of recoveries is 1 475 398 and the total number of vaccines administered is 269 102. https://t.co/OH4Fx06QAo]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>