<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClaerB: As promised, here's a thread about the new #breathingspace arrangements for people in problem debt in England and Wales, as dis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealJoelSmalley: https://t.co/b37L9VqZvF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sam_J_Griffin: Where is the uproar about my beautiful cousin? Where is the huge outrage and pouring of despair? Where are the vigils an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Retired paediatrician Dr Ros Jones thinks healthy children do not need a Covid vaccine.  "As a society, adults are responsib]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RayArmat: @elleprovocateur https://t.co/tOR407Fxik]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LynnBrittney2: NHS Board Member whistleblower says they had great doubts about the 'vaccines', "but in a nutshell, what we were told in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsForAlI:  | BREAKING: The return of secondary school pupils to the classroom has not led to a spike in Covid-19 infections, maj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCashny: We'd be in a much better place if more people distrusted their formerly trusted media and instead went to primary sources for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: Gates divorce - smoke and mirrors?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @martina_ant79: @YardleyShooting https://t.co/fhcTcpBSGS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: When a crucial Sage report is ignored, this goes far beyond caution, and questions need to be asked about when this advice wa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joeyjojojunior_: @WeWillBeFree82 Today is the last date for evidence that we can all submit regarding how we feel on health passports.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Dansefton88: @prisoner1968 Lol if people think June the 21st is the end, they havent grasped the covid bill is up for another vote on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ToleratingR: @YardleyShooting I should add that the pressure to take it has been intense. Mandatory is coming I'm told.   I had to have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillRaeWalker: "We are 28 doctors  researchers  have written a debate article in which we, based on medical knowledge, explain that S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @crbarnes001: @EmaPrintPattern https://t.co/DDE14K4eDO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: @Freedom49503795 @Demo2020cracy Everything done for you here with links to evidence. Takes 2 mins https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3 #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Freedom49503795: Urgent: Apparently our govt didnt like it that 50000 ppl responded so they cancelled it and are going again with a de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Update:  https://t.co/el9Z6G1gVc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HayleyWinchest @tone_we @Dr_RohenKapur @1984cov Thats terrifying!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Intelligent history students of the future may well ask, "But what were the journalists doing while all of this tyrannica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: SURVEY:  Should the media in Ireland debate me publicly - and take me down a peg or two? Would that not be massively in the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LNathan123: @LockdownLazarus @Hidinginplains8 Thousands of pilots were given notice last week. Cheap holidays are over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlexBerenson: Hey, Im getting vaccinated this weekend and then going for a hike! Or maybe Ill just die instead.  Stuff happens, right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LostTogetherCda @robinmonotti2 @dickbreeze Is this written before or after he came out against the narrative?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crbarnes001 Ok thanks yes I genuinely hadnt seen any.. This article says its due to headaches but  I guess they are playing it down? Why would doctors send them to AE for just a headache ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThinkingSlow1: @T4Recovery https://t.co/O3wSNTTqS0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crbarnes001 Any evidence of this please?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic @PeterAn36324304 How about all the hormones from contraceptive pill? Is there a remainder in water supply?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @D16584667: @ZubyMusic @PeterAn36324304 Lowering of testosterone has been speculatively linked to phthalates in plastics. Phthalates hav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Question......Wondering where we are on finding out about the vaxxed being dangerous to the unvaxed from shedding whatever it is that theyve been injected with?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: There's nothing nuts about vaxxing kids, it's the necessary step to implement the vaxx IDs. They could not care less if]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bruceyjackson @MavNGoose1 @lensiseethrough @Telegraph @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston A mask wont stop a virus particle because its too small, it doesnt work  its not needed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trevsayers: @lensiseethrough @UsforThemUK @JuliaHB1 @allisonpearson @thelucyjohnston How about you report some of this information next]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: Vaccine certificates "could unleash demons that we'll be living with for years", argues @clarewenham in The Economist htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robinmonotti2 @dickbreeze Need some subtitles on that vid my French isnt good enough!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: You have until MONDAY to object to passports! If you objected before, you have to submit again-this is new review!! 50]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: #INDIA: Protests against the WHO's #Covid19 testing:  "There is no Covid19 in our village!"  https://t.co/gnCTxsu1Il]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: @mattwarman @SikhForTruth @michaelgove @nadhimzahawi @BorisJohnson Your Government claims to have 'informed consent' f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: @mattwarman @SikhForTruth We don't believe you. Your colleagues have all lied about passports  breached the Nolan Pri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HedgeFolk: "In the absence of a signed consent form from parents/carers, we will invite the young person to self-consent for the above]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BSimonward: Compulsory  coming to a place  near you very soon . Testing on kids now ! Soon your kids . Is that what you want ? If you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neiltricks: @allisonpearson Have you heard the vaccine minister on @talkRADIO this morning with @JuliaHB1. He couldn't confirm mask wea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LevanaLomma1: A vaccine "passport" will do NOTHING to stop the spread of COVID-19. What it does do is create a platform for a new world]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Tell me this isn't a conspiracy. What's the power that turns them all into ventriloquist's dolls saying the same thing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elizabe14729684: This will be worth a listen.Thank you @Unlocked_UK_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NicholsJoy: @SandraWeeden @summerbreeze712 https://t.co/96kWfzR68z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Simon__Jordan: Truth Vs Propaganda. You are being lied to. Just as with China, with Italy, with Brazil.......this is panic porn, and if]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpeechUnion: The @SpeechUnion's General Secretary @toadmeister welcomes the Home Secretary's request to police chiefs to stop recording]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: https://t.co/bz1u2tgjmI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Vaccine passports for domestic venue entry are one of the most illiberal and authoritarian ideas ever floated by a UK go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrBradCampbell: Trust the science actually means  trust someone else. Trust your gut, use logic, and be open-minded. I trust the 24]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: Its official. The 29th May is the BIG one in London. #uniteforfreedom https://t.co/fZGuWus71u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @threadreaderapp: @dpsisi Hallo, the unroll you asked for: 1/ Hello, my name is Gal, I am an Israeli citizen, and I want to https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: 13/ Lastly, I believe that Israel is the "pilot" that should serve as an example and *justification* for the whole world. If t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: 11/ My message is simple: either the vaccine is effective - and then all the limitations have to disappear from our lives. Or]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: 6/We live under increasing coercion, discrimination, marking and division into two civil societies-according to the "green mar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreeFromTyranny: @JamesMelville  Please support #MedicalFreedomBill and share!   Ends 6th May 2021 at 3:54pm...  #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BtSIsrael: The world's leading human rights organization, @HRW, published a report yesterday saying that Israel is committing the crime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kate_hammer: #Birmingham #Walsall please RT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gbdeclaration: 1. Is there a middle ground between lockdowns  with school, business and office closures, curfews, and isolation  and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: So, reading the Bible in a Christian country is not allowed now? What did our great-grandfathers sacrifice their lives]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: 22/: Let me be clear: it's us, your enemies, who are currently defending your rights. It's us who are risking our careers a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @deekay366: @socialHATchat @FrontineF @GongGotha @SahariIvsa @SAHPRA1 @DrZweliMkhize Funny how I've done a year without a sniffle then a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: You have been warned! Children as young as 12 'will get Covid vaccines in September when they return after summer as go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Covid restrictions. Collateral damage.  1 year on:  500,000 more kids with mental health issues 4.7m people on NHS w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Looks like a #London date for a defence of inalienable human rights and freedoms? https://t.co/0fL1yUwQFF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LearnLeapLean: @nick_the_geek78 @MScrobogna Here, we are still average! https://t.co/l42ge4Gq0Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lulabella0: 3/4/21- Dr Ryan Cole Telling the Truth about Covid- Share this Everywhere https://t.co/dRFf0ZPTN4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrTeckKhong: Dr Helen Westwood, a GP, wrote to her MP Sir Graham Brady in March with some concerns about the vaccines and the potential]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NellyTells Yep  it makes me cross]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PerformanceBare: @BBGRichie listening to u talking about the gentleman who died. Today it was the funeral of one of my friends - she di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pedaru_karmen: Retweet worldwide please!   German justice under attack!  The Judge at the AG Weimar Christian Dettmar  was searched thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InProportion2: Interesting thread. Coolly arrives at some dark conclusions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fergy1999: @profnfenton What I also find very disturbing is that the UK changed the death law so that Covid deaths seem to not need any]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkAVFCUTV: @beverleyturner https://t.co/2SH31vaVSh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RayArmat: The editor of prestigious BMJ: "#Science is being suppressed for political and financial gain. Covid-19 has unleashed state c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_InThisTogether: "It is obvious that #lockdown strategies failed...Lockdowns have...generated enormous collateral damage....The central]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @numbr06: @Francis_Hoar Perspective on India &lt;200,000   In the EXACT time frame India has lost 809,000 people to Flu/Pneumonia (4X the d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MHilltobe: @talkRADIO @JuliaHB1 @Iromg  First image is from gas leak in India, May 2020. Second image being used to say covid surge is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FlyfreEllie: @FrontineF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BangoBilly: https://t.co/fkdUUbSizS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rainbowandsteel Warning! The link takes you to phishing spam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Major panel discussion - no holds barred!  https://t.co/MEJbiLuIFk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: And these four from Chester https://t.co/9yNJn27nnj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: I also interviewed this very middle class couple from Windsor who attended the protest.. https://t.co/CYCKxKaXfD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HegKong I agree, the problem is that the population has been brainwashed to believe all ages are at serious risk, so need jabs. The other line is that it is selfish not to have one .. lots of people believe they are doing their bit ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newironweed: Kate Shemirani and Dr Kevin Corbett - 'Do You Really Think You Are Safe In This Country?'  #BritishNursingAlliance  @KPCRe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterHu65796484: @leadbyexample12 @mmjblair @blackswan_t2 We have never needed lock-downs or vaccines. Ivermectin works far better than]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InProportion2: @doctor_oxford That's alarmist. For 7 weeks now  * all cause mortality (grey) below avg (dotted) * deaths "with" c19 (gr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LynnBrittney2: Unlike protests by climate activists this week, today's London march was ignored by the mainstream media. A few tabloids]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FrontineF: #londonprotest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Live video stream from march https://t.co/jUzmKYACf5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Find it galling when you put up something about reactions to the AZ vaccine and someone says in reply: "but I'm fine".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking! https://t.co/RvIUczBjrf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @13orangesbc: If youre against Vaxx passes - pls share - MEP proposing amendment to REJECT Vaccine Passport  #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @berniespofforth: The Simpsons doing their thing 2017. Cat Flu is coming!  https://t.co/b1jzjG7ygg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcrclaims: Taiwan the most sinophobic nation on earth didnt fall for the #PCR scam. Just a coincidence of course. https://t.co/1KaoV7k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chasetherabbit: @PoliticsForAlI @Rob_Kimbell @Telegraph Phew I will sleep better tonight knowing the disease with 99.9% survival rate h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @richardintheuk: @PoliticsForAlI @Telegraph If Britain is no longer in a pandemic according to government scientists, then why are pubs]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>