<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@B_Lopman @AdamJKucharski @KayokoShioda @EpidemiologyLWW @joshuasweitz @pssinatl @kbratnelson @CheTranquiloID @msy_lau Mh, we don't see it go down, honestly. I don't see as much of an increase in fall as I expected but no decrease from spring 2020 to December 2020 in NYC in our surveys. Also, very low rate of seroreversion in our longitudinal cohorts over that time frame.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just came to the office, thinking I would have a conference call at 6am. Now I found out its at 7:30am. 90 minutes of productive time added to the day!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OLeitenbauer @ArminWolf Nein, ist es nicht. Muss man sich erst in Echt-Zeit anschauen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HiCryoEM @SciReports Congratulations! That's awesome!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@10queues Yes, I am. I hope you are doing well too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOL, @10queues, you made it to John Oliver! https://t.co/5JdvsHmAV7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Traveleve2 Cheers!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@katha_esskultur Wars ein Spike oder Nucleocapsid-basierender test?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For everybody worried about getting an mRNA SARS-CoV-2 vaccine during pregnancy: https://t.co/WJpQrQVftU https://t.co/LdEzodV6B6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@macroliter Lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macroliter: The humoral immune system chasing the Spike RBD https://t.co/QnopESkKtt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@inselmit2bergen @harphat No, was my mistake. Thanks for pointing that out, @harphat !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[L452R nd E484Q are the RBD mutations we are worried about in B.1.617. We need more data with wt isolates but this is reassuring. https://t.co/sJp2PW73C7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@harphat Dang, typo. I'll delete and retweet correctly!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very nice data regarding B.1.617. https://t.co/DMQoJi8jfm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Martin_Moder Genau!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SvobodaLab Kozel!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sigi_maurer: Gestern wurde die neunte Frau in diesem Jahr von ihrem Ex-Partner ermordet.   Jede gettete Frau ist eine zu viel. Jede ve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DoNuT_1985 Aber echt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I guess that will backfire badly for IHU_Marseille https://t.co/qO8u0Yrvy1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MicrobiomDigest: Wow.  The @IHU_Marseille is suing me and @BorisBarbour for attempted blackmail and extortion.   Meantime  @echabriere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nice! https://t.co/BZXaaH3nE6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @littlewisehen: Auch Drachen mssen regelmig getestet werden... https://t.co/Qy1BfzpCE7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stuartjdneil @macroliter SII is excellent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sassybibrarian @K_G_Andersen @NathanGrubaugh I agree with that sentiment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@K_G_Andersen @NathanGrubaugh P.1 is pretty competitive......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @K_G_Andersen: Trajectory of the "CA" variant (B.1.429/427) here in San Diego.  Another scariant bites the dust. https://t.co/IWqgsx8Qwr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1899fmHeinz @docjosiahboone LOL, sorry, Sturm Graz.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @David_RMartinez: Check out our #preprint describing a broadly neutralizing RBD antibody, which protects against SARS-CoV, bat pre-emerg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FNikitik Here is something a number of authors from these scientific studies wrote: https://t.co/AvY16azhfM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FNikitik https://t.co/tCCTOshsJg https://t.co/UlM4oveiFm https://t.co/3oFOmVIxI0 https://t.co/eJmMaEz2Xq https://t.co/ki3ZlMYjID https://t.co/4f4rDrrQkO Knock yourself out. There are many more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FNikitik Depends on the country. And the science says you do not need to.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TischCancer: Join @MiriamMerad and @florian_krammer for IUIS-EFIS Webinar: Immunology in the time of #COVID19: achievements, challenges]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HaighKatharina I am not sure. We actually did have issues with supply of other plasticware.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HaighKatharina Dude, we are using thousands per day, and especially during the hot phase of the pandemic here in New York in spring 2020 we used huge amounts every day. But so far we did not have any shortages.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RufusSG @andrew_lilico Here is actually a nice study on replication competent AdV5 in humans: https://t.co/fNvNLPW18A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alhahn15 @KindrachukJason Exactly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jpjviro @KindrachukJason Not many, replication active Ad5 has been tested as vaccine in humans as well and its fine. But still.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KindrachukJason Seriously? WTF!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lakdawala_Lab @RogueRifter At some point we will do mostly paperwork and no research anymore. Its very frustrating.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Most765 Because the US did not change the guidelines. European countries did. I hope the US will as well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ellie__Jameson That's awesome!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GirardotMarc @OZmandia @jengleruk LOL, OK. You just ruined the effect of the blood pressure medication I took this morning. Bye now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GirardotMarc @OZmandia @jengleruk I am sorry, where are the 55 million coming from?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GirardotMarc @jengleruk I am not sure how you are connecting this to vaccination?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ulfhammarstrom Not a good idea. Two weeks after the second shot is reasonable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KurtadikarKetan Well, then the latest case numbers would be good news.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikhailspivakov No, they decided to test it that way. A two shot JJ vaccine regimen is still in Phase III separately. Should have results soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jengleruk Sorry, I grew a very thin skin lately. You are blocked. Have a nice day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really hope that India's wave has hit its highest point. But I am worried that the slowing we have seen in the last few days is just because they are maxing out on testing capacity. https://t.co/VuC4wulZJY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is very important for people to get their 2nd shot of vaccine (except for JJ, or if you had confirmed COVID-19 before, then one is enough).  I find this trend that people only get one shot very alarming. Immunity in this case is incomplete and may not last as long.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JesseVentura86 @ManfredNelles @Krefelder78 @Sander_Lab @EricTopol @VivianaSimonLab Nein, es spricht nichts dagegen. Aber die 2. Dosis ist in dem Fall unnoetig.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarcosMaurelli @TurkeyMedia I think you are misunderstanding the concept.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ingomar_gutmann @twee24at @art18bvg @Dailymama_org @opentrons Net bei hunderten ELISA-Platten pro Tag ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CardiacPack83 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are running out of pipette tips....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The only epidemics I like: Epidemics that did not happen https://t.co/4RAhz4e9tQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bealelab @KurtadikarKetan @abledoc @pash22 Yep, needs confirmation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[According to this preprint, B.1.617 is causing a 2-fold drop in neutralization of convalescent sera and sera from  Covaxin vaccinated individuals. While this needs further confirmation, it is a good initial sign. https://t.co/ygFAQZYUkG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HarmitMalik @aeonmag LOL, love the title]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChelseaClinton: Very glad to read this and looking forward to Vice President Harriss speech @UN today. The United States should be a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well deserved! https://t.co/G6ATjknx2O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaRo09459337 Deutsch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@abbanatic Ja, immer wieder. Ich hasse Typos, aber sie passieren.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianMcAdams20 LOL - no way to get rid of typos.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am preparing for my emerging viruses course and I am updating the course material. Last time I held it was in 2019. Students are given a 'Case' which they need to present in the end. I just found this pre-pandemic gem. https://t.co/BOpHJkvfwT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Frank79593327 Ganz ehrlich, wenn das nicht so gemeint war, dann ist es einfach wahnsinnig schlecht gemacht.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Traveleve2 90% Schutz gegen Infektion. Wenn du dich doch infizierst, kannst du es wahrschinlich nicht weitergeben. Wenn wir Leute finden die sich trotz 2 Impfungen infizieren sind die Ct Werte meistens so hoch dass wir nicht mal voll sequenzieren koennen. https://t.co/QHXt19ka9I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Traveleve2 Da gibts kommerzielle Tests dafuer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Traveleve2 Du kannst schaun, ob du AK gegen das Nukleoprotein machst (IgG, mus nicht IgM sein wenn du ein paar Wochen wartest). Das waere dann eine Indikation fuer eine Immunreaktion auf das Virus. Nukleoprotein ist im Impfstoff naemlich nicht drinnen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASlavitt: Important statement regarding support for India in combatting COVID-19. https://t.co/BMblXBkSIE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drseltsam Guter Spruch. Stimmt eh.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2) Es waere schoen, wenn sich Patienten deren Lunge nicht mehr funktioniert Luft von Amazon bestellen koennten. Oder Indische Spittaeler. Sicher, Satire darf alles, aber sie muss auch gut gemacht sein. Das hier ist nur pietaetlos.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1) Ich hab jetzt einige dieser #allesdichtmachen Videos angeschaut. Die meisten sind schlecht, ein paar wuerden vielleicht auch zum Nachdenken anregen. Aber einige, wie dieses hier von Katharina Schlothauer, sind einfach nur grausig.  https://t.co/PyoxaCnBt8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Traveleve2 Du kannst schon schauen ob du fuer N seroconvertierst. Kann auch sein dass der Spike AK Level rauf geht.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Traveleve2 Gute Besserung an deinen Sohn! Ich hoffe die Infektion bleibt asymptomatisch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_lilge @NicolaWerdenigg Kuenstlerisch kann ich ihn nicht kritisieren, ich bin weder Schauspieler noch mache ich irgendeine Art von Kunst, bin also nicht vom Fach. Sachlich braucht man ihn auch nicht zu kritisieren, weil er sagt ja nichts sachliches oder konstruktives oder irgendwie sinnvolles.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HCStrache1 Ist das Satire?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iskratsch LOL, sicher!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bealelab: These people are utter charlatans. https://t.co/JQb3w9gFjd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Die Tomaten von der Oma wachsen schon. https://t.co/lPELpfhvrM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GermanyinIndia: Defence ministry to airlift 23 oxygen generation plants from Germany @IndianExpress reports. IAF spox Babu says units]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AB_Algaissi: Saudi Arabia sends 80 millions tons of liquid oxygen to India!  We all together in this   https://t.co/fnf7hmNO2l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BNODesk: NEW: Data shows more than 1 billion doses of COVID-19 vaccines have been administered worldwide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrPhiloponus @WolfgangMueckst Lol, halb fuenf ist einfach noch zu frueh zum tweeten......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Herr Dr. @WolfgangMueckst, wenn Sie was brauchen, melden Sie sich einfach.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soibal1 Ich wuerd 3-4 Wochen nach Abklingen der Infektion warten.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As expected https://t.co/ozEVsqEzmq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BenBCDE @franzikafka @florianaigner https://t.co/3B8vPrOt9o Paper sollte hoffentlich bald rauskommen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bonniealba @franzikafka @florianaigner Nein, der Impfschutz haelt ZUMINDEST 6 Monate an, laenger hat mans noch net testen koennen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DNoisternig @franzikafka @florianaigner Ich glaub schon, dass das der Fall ist aber es fehlen halt die Daten um das zu beweisen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Vinceblackshad1 @docjosiahboone @docmarton @DanielaLitzlba1 @Bettina52850076 @DNoisternig @MartinKalop @Traveleve2 @AlgeMartin @isabelledaniel @neuwirthe @pklein82 @SebRei @semiosisblog @mariodujakovic LOL, schoen der Sarkasmus. Das fehlt mir oft in den USA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@franzikafka @florianaigner Momentant schauts so aus als muessten zumindest die mRNA Impfstoffe nicht angepasst werden. (obwohl die Firmen natuerlich angefangen haben, angepasste Impfstoffe zu testen). Pfizer hatte gegen B.1.351 keinen Effizienzverlust in Suedafrika (kleine Zahlen, dennoch).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonathanDworkin No neut titers yet but in terms of immunity I do not think B.1.617 is worse than the other VoCs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_b_meyer: The observation that some B.1.617 lineages have "lost" E484K shows that the mutation alone or in this context doesn't increas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julianlewis2012 Lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@edrybicki @NatureNews Its sad. I think local vaccine production is really key.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@isabelledaniel Ich haett da jetzt viel dazu zu sagen, aber ich hab einfach die Nerven dafuer nimmer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@isabelledaniel Ich wuerd mir einen guten, vernuenftigen und schrittweisen Oeffnungsplan der dann auch durchgezogen wird wuenschen. Ohne dass die Laender und Buende in der Halbzeit querschiessen. Aber ich glaub das wird halt nur ein Wunsch bleiben.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Am I surprised about this? No. Am I very happy about this? Absolutely! We are getting there. https://t.co/wTQ02rK2Ci]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>