<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccines are safe, effective, and work. When its your turn, get the #COVID19 vaccine. Learn more about how to get vaccinated in your area: https://t.co/uveLPUwA6Z https://t.co/PYR6kxiaht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les vaccins sont srs et efficaces. Quand votre tour viendra, faites-vous vacciner. Pour en savoir plus sur la faon de se faire vacciner dans votre rgion : https://t.co/d1KP9Dd24u #COVID19 https://t.co/6Q049eEAWK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JulieDzerowicz: It was an honour to host Min @PattyHajdu last week at a Davenport Health Townhall! Thanks to the Minister for virtually]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TonyVanBynen: This #MentalHealthWeek is an opportunity for us to #GetReal and understand our emotions. COVID-19 has been difficult and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YaaraSaks: On this #MentalHealthWeek lets have the conversations we need to reach out, access help and support, and be there for one a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SoniaLiberal: This morning your #Brampton MPs had a productive conversation with Peels Medical Officer of Health, Dr. Lawrence Loh. We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mary_ng: Goodness! Looks like C3P0 got his vaccine and R2-D2 is up next! May the fourth be with you ! #VaccinesWork      #MayThe4thBeW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TonyVanBynen: Chewie, were staying home!   #MayThe4thBeWithYou  #StarWarsDay https://t.co/sRB9CdlDPJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The force is strong with each of you. We will make it to the other end of this pandemic, with resilience and public safety measures. #MayThe4thBeWithYou https://t.co/Ongn42tHXK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chacun et chacune dentre vous possde une grande force interne. Nous allons vaincre cette pandmie, avec rsilience et en respectant les mesures de sant et scurit publiques.Que la force soit avec vous! https://t.co/EJ6OQsV5V8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today marks the start of the 70th #MentalHealthWeek! As we continue navigating the challenges and changes caused by the #COVID19 pandemic, more Canadians are struggling with new or worsened mental health issues. You are not alone. https://t.co/FaYRyuSFyz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aujourdhui marque le dbut de la #Semainedelasantmentale. Alors que nous continuons  faire face aux dfis causs par la pandmie de #COVID19, davantage de Canadiens sont aux prises avec des problmes de sant mentale nouveaux ou aggravs. Vous ntes pas seul. https://t.co/QZatYniGuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May is dedicated to celebrating Jewish Heritage, as we honour the inspirational role Jewish Canadians play in communities across the country. Canada is not immune to violence  antisemitism. We must stand against hate and intolerance, and choose compassion every day. https://t.co/Xttjvypel5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clinical trials for #COVID19 vaccines have been taking place since the spring of 2020 and millions of people around the world have already been vaccinated. #COVIDvaccine https://t.co/H6q5DKw5uq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les essais cliniques des vaccins contre la #COVID19 ont lieu depuis le printemps 2020 et des millions de personnes dans le monde entier ont dj t vaccines. https://t.co/A3nyVbdaHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cathmckenna: I  responses to your challenge @PattyHajdu - and will tweet some out that were sent to me.   What's your #MyWhy for gett]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SoniaLiberal: Yesterday in the #HESA, we heard from Min. @PattyHajdu and her officials. @CPHO_Canada stressed that we must continue fol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CMA_Docs: Today, we celebrate the inspiration and hope physicians provide to us, while acknowledging the burdens that they, and all he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KamalKheraLib: What an honour to be at @BIC_BSIA vaccinating our community members at the pop up clinic with our healthcare heroes in #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We all have a role to play in denouncing discrimination, so this month and throughout the year, lets embrace the diversity that makes our country strong. Lets lead with compassion. 2/2 #AHMCanada2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May is Asian Heritage Month, a time to recognize the immense contributions of Asian Canadians and celebrate their rich and diverse cultures and history. The rise in racism against Asian communities is unacceptable, and we must do better. 1/2 https://t.co/yU1GaNEUrS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Although these times are anything but normal, physicians have shown incredible selflessness, courage and strength, despite unimaginable challenges during the #COVID19 pandemic. On behalf of all Canadians, thank you! #NationalPhysiciansDay @CMA_Docs https://t.co/zC2Lcn7Ico https://t.co/ibDmFxHVId]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les mdecins ont fait preuve d'altruisme, de courage et de force incroyable, malgr des dfis inimaginables qui sont survenus au cours de la pandmie de COVID-19. Au nom de toute la population canadienne, merci! #JourneNationaleDesMdecins @CMA_Docs https://t.co/QIM0BgiYnh https://t.co/tDoj3QbkNv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theres a lot here for everyone! What part of #Budget2021 are you most excited about? Let me know in the replies below https://t.co/TDVyM1iH5W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenOConnell_: Last week, Minister @cafreeland tabled #Budget2021, our governments ambitious plan to invest in Canadians, the environme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great new video by @CIHR_IRSC telling the story of decades of scientific research in mRNA vaccines! Watch the full video here: https://t.co/zyUqCRgf4E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jadore cette nouvelle vido des @IRSC_CIHR au sujet des vaccins  ARNm. On y raconte lhistoire fascinante de dcennies de recherche scientifique. Regardez la vido intgrale : https://t.co/YTIIYwiciS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are working towards a more equitable Canada, for everyone. The recovery plan in #Budget2021 will make sure that women, Indigenous people, racialized Canadians, people with disabilities, and LGBTQ2S+ Canadians will not be left behind. https://t.co/MezEMKt4qJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cathmckenna: This #NIAW2021 week, #MyWhy for getting vaccinated is so that I can see my parents as soon as it is safe to do so. I miss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nous avons annonc que 2,25 millions de dollars pour deux projets dans le cadre du Fonds de partenariat dimmunisation. Ce financement permettra  des acteurs de confiance de la communaut scientifique et des soins de sant de diffuser des renseignements fiables sur les vaccins. https://t.co/nV1Zep3kwA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today, we announced $2.25 million through the Immunization Partnership Fund (IPF) for two projects to support vaccination efforts. This funding will help trusted leaders within the science and healthcare communities share credible information on vaccines. https://t.co/4P3Se3U7Jr https://t.co/KG06Y7xPWj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mary_ng: #Budget2021 s'agit du budget le plus favorable aux entreprises dans l'histoire du Canada.   Les #PME canadiennes sont les pili]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mary_ng: #Budget2021 is the most small business-friendly Budget in Canadian history.  Canadian #SmallBiz are the backbone of our econom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Small businesses like restaurants, hair salons, and local stores, and the people that work for them, are the cornerstone of our communities and the backbone of our economy. We know the value of small business growth and supporting local, thats why Budget 2021 is here to help. https://t.co/bY7GUewQKc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now more than ever, we need to protect the right to healthy and safe workplaces. On this National Day of Mourning, lets remember the many health care and front line workers who have become sick or died working for all of us. We must do better to create safe workplaces together. https://t.co/emxdXjtTE1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Il faut en faire plus pour protger le droit  un milieu de travail scuritaire.  loccasion de la journe nationale du deuil, souvenons-nous des professionnels de la sant et de premires lignes qui sont devenus malades ou ont perdu la vie pour nous protger. https://t.co/YUGhk50FGz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Carolyn_Bennett: When I was a little girl I got measles, mumps, rubella and in grade 10 I got chicken pox  my dad got very very sick w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Carolyn_Bennett: Polio has been virtually eradicated because of the wide dissemination of the life-saving polio vaccine.   Vaccines sav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Budget2021 invests to make life more affordable for young Canadians, places them at the centre of our recovery, and creates new opportunities through education, apprenticeships, and training https://t.co/bXdFdwEYoK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This made-in-Canada solution to rapidly share and investigate detailed genetic information of viruses will give Canadian scientists the critical information they need to tackle #COVID19 and future infectious disease threats. @GenomeCanada https://t.co/BIrNCU59x9 https://t.co/1OMFjjDS58]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cette solution canadienne dchange rapide des donnes et de recherches dans les donnes gntiques dtailles des virus donnera aux chercheurs canadiens linformation indispensable dont ils ont besoin pour lutter contre la #COVID19. @GenomeCanada https://t.co/bYuwd5S7NX https://t.co/LVUvB1rH04]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACSP_Canada: Il y a des tonnes de raisons de relever sa manche pour recevoir le #vaccinCOVID! Peu importe pourquoi vous le faites, chaq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CPHO_Canada: There are many reasons to roll up our sleeves and take the #COVID19Vaccine! Whatever your reason, every #COVID19vaccine, i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FureyAndrew: Being part of #TeamCanada means helping each other when we can. As nine health care workers from Newfoundland and Labrador]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McDonald4Avalon: And theyre off! 9 frontline healthcare workers from this province have graciously taken off to #Ontario to help  alle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: Wheels up for Toronto. Health care workers from Newfoundland and Labrador are now en route to Ontario, where theyre set]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: Dcollage pour Toronto. Des travailleurs de la sant de T.-N.-L sont en route vers lOntario pour aider les gens des pre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Budget 2021 will build back better with a feminist and intersectional lens by: - supporting women entrepreneurs - strengthening diversity in Canadas corporate institutions - creating new opportunities for skilled tradespeople - national early learning and childcare https://t.co/L6e19MHtDF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OmarAlghabra: This National Immunization Awareness Week, we reflect on the importance of getting vaccinated.   Vaccines are our best we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @melaniejoly: Donner  FedNor son indpendance ne leur donnera pas seulement un plus gros budget, mais aussi un plus grand contrle sur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @melaniejoly: Making FedNor a standalone agency will not only result in a larger budget, but it will also provide greater control over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This pandemic has shown us the importance of vaccination, not just for preventing illness and disease, but for allowing us to be closer to the people we love. For #NIAW2021, tell me your #MyWhy  your reason for getting vaccinated. https://t.co/55EMprGcZu https://t.co/NmU6rJbxCO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cette pandmie a dmontr limportance de la vaccination, autant pour la prvention des affections et des maladies que pour nous permettre de se rapprocher de ceux quon aime. Pour #SNPV2021, dites-moi  #MesRaisons  vos raisons pour vous faire vacciner. https://t.co/DsbRbKI145 https://t.co/xCnQI62Cf1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for the update on the situation in the Region of Wood Buffalo, Mayor @DonaldKScott. The federal government stands ready to support the people of Fort McMurray and surrounding communities however we can.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Merci pour la mise  jour de la situation de la rgion de Wood Buffalo, Monsieur le Maire @DonaldKScott. Le gouvernement fdral est toujours prt  appuyer, de toutes les faons possibles, les gens de Fort McMurray et des communauts environnantes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CIHR_IRSC: With the #COVID19 variants of concern continuing to spread, Canadian researchers are unifying to learn as much as they can,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HedyFry: Congrats Min @PattyHajdu on getting your first #COVID19 vaccine dose.   #cdnpoli #bcpoli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ActuaCEO: My date with AZ:) Extremely grateful to all pharmacy staff working loooong hours to make this happen. Also its April and Im]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone deserves a safe place to call home. #Budget2021 is investing $2.5 billion into affordable housing, with projects for specific groups most impacted by COVID-19. We are focused on entirely eliminating chronic homelessness in Canada https://t.co/Lm6SV85gdE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID-19 has highlighted the inequities and racism that Indigenous peoples, and Black and racialized Canadians face every day. We are investing over $313M towards fighting racism  empowering communities, to bridge the gaps that hold Canada back from reaching its full potential. https://t.co/ftYe3WodNd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cdube_sante: Trs heureux pour vous @PattyHajdu . Keep the good work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernJordanMP: The best vaccine is the one youre offered first.   Happy to say it was my turn to get the AZ vaccine today. Huge thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congratulations, Wataynikaneyap Power! Thanks for helping us meet our goal of reducing Canadas emissions by 40-45% before 2030. With $17.6 billion set out in #budget2021 for a green restart, there is plenty to go around for clean, green innovation  https://t.co/PW8CnmFiVr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: Ctait notre tour de nous faire vacciner aujourdhui, alors cest ce que Sophie et moi avons fait - et on en est bien c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: It was our turn to get vaccinated today, so thats what Sophie and I did - and were glad we did it! Find out how, when,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My vaccination story:  Easy  Quick  Painless  Exciting  Mon histoire de vaccination:  Facile  Rapide  Sans douleur  Excitant https://t.co/13nMouRSep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GouvCanSante: 2) Lorsque ce sera votre tour, faites-vous vacciner! Faites-le pour vous, pour vos proches et pour votre communaut. Pour]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GouvCanSante: (1/2) Aujourdhui, la ministre de la Sant Patty Hajdu a retrouss sa manche pour recevoir son #vaccin contre la #COV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovCanHealth: (2/2) When it's your turn, get the shot! Do it for yourself, your loved ones, and your community. Find out how to get vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovCanHealth: (1/2) Today, Minister of Health Patty Hajdu rolled up her sleeve and received her #CovidVaccine shot!  Thanks to our heal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mclaudebibeau:  ce jour, +de 11 M de doses de ont t administres aux iens. Le #BUDGET2021 va nous aider  traverser cette pandmi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mclaudebibeau: To date, more than 11 M vaccine doses have been administered to Canadians. #BUDGET2021 also includes investments in the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marcomendicino: J'ai eu ma premire dose de #AstraZeneca ! Rapide, facile et sans douleur. Heureux de faire ma part. Merci  Lauren et]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marcomendicino: Got my first dose of #AstraZeneca! Fast, easy and painless. Happy to do my part. Thanks to Lauren and all the healthcar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanielleLarivee: Canadas Health Minister putting her money where her mouth is and taking whichever vaccine she can as soon as she is e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gary_srp: Congratulations Minister @PattyHajdu!   Thank you for everything you've done to keep Canadians healthy, safe, and informed th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CMA_Docs: ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CIHR_IRSC: Congratulations @PattyHajdu on getting your #CovidVaccine! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IRSC_CIHR: Flicitations @PattyHajdu!  #LesVaccinsaMarche]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernJordanMP: Yes!! Congrats, friend.   Youve worked so hard throughout this time to help keep us healthy  calm. So happy to see y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WinnipegRHA: You are very correct @PattyHajdu, congratulations.  Eligible and still contemplating?  Now is the time to book your app]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I got vaccinated to keep me, my family and my community safe. #mywhy https://t.co/1guEfxeVue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best vaccine for you is the one in your arm! Today was my turn to receive my first dose of the AstraZeneca vaccine. Thank you Bryan at Mountdale Pharmacy for helping me join the millions of Canadians who have received their first dose of #COVIDVaccine. 1/ https://t.co/jtxFp2K3W8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Je me suis fait vacciner pour me protger, protger ma famille et ma communaut. #mesraisons . 2/ https://t.co/7ksa46Ybcd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Le meilleur vaccin pour vous est celui que vous recevez! Ctait aujourdhui mon tour davoir la premire dose dAstraZeneca. Merci Bryan de la pharmacie Mountdale, je fais maintenant partie des millions de Canadiens qui ont reu leur premire dose dun vaccin contre la #COVID19. https://t.co/41aCNJ5xuM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OmarAlghabra: La priorit absolue de notre gouvernement est de protger la sant et la scurit des Canadiens, et notre rponse  la pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OmarAlghabra: Our governments top priority is protecting Canadians health and safety, and our response to the COVID-19 pandemic is gu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Climate change is one of the greatest threats we've ever faced, but it's also a massive economic opportunity. Budget 2021 recognizes that creating jobs and growing the economy means protecting the environment. https://t.co/WDt3Mh4PPs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les changements climatiques sont l'une des plus grandes menaces auxquelles nous sommes confronts dans le monde, mais ils reprsentent galement dnormes dbouchs conomiques. Le budget reconnat  la croissance de l'emploi pour les Canadiens passe par la croissance verte. https://t.co/3z4kVil2jH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TerrySheehanMP: Un grand merci  @melaniejoly pour cette importante engagement! Cest une immense victoire pour le nord de lOntario. M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrSamirSinha: Deeply honoured to be appointed to serve on Canada's National Seniors Council by our Ministers for Health @PattyHajdu + S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Atayeshe: We must realize bodily autonomy for all!  Pleased to join @actioncanadashr along with @karinagould  @MaryamMonsef for the Ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SoniaLiberal: I got my vaccine! #BramptonSouth, the best vaccine is the one that is in your arm. Book yours as soon as you are eligible]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Budget 2021 is here, and there are some big ticket items! This budget is about finishing the fight with COVID-19 and coming out stronger on the other side. Check in every day this week as we go through the excitement, sustainability, and equality that #Budget2021 has to offer. https://t.co/PCm5Ur6EKn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TerrySheehanMP: Thank you Minister for making this happen! This is a major win for #NorthernOntario and thanks to @PattyHajdu @Lefebvre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FP_Champagne: Aujourdhui, jai reu ma premire dose du vaccin AstraZeneca! Je tiens  remercier les chercheurs, les scientifiques et]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FP_Champagne: Today, I received my first dose of the AstraZeneca vaccine! I am immensely grateful, and a special thank you to the resea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SenatCA: Le comit reoit la ministre @PattyHajdu en tant que tmoin.   Visionnez : https://t.co/PHAsqxMUqy  #SenCA #SOCI #ESPT https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SenateCA: Committee welcomes Minister @PattyHajdu as a witness.   Watch: https://t.co/WGCDdsjZtr  #SenCA #SOCI #PTSD https://t.co/HzgNz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @melaniejoly: We know that Northern Ontario businesses have specific needs and have been hard hit by the pandemic. To help them, we have]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>