<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFugelsang: The people who preached herd immunity in 2020 are now the reason we won't reach herd immunity in 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you like waiting an hour in line for mediocre and overpriced food? @BuschGardensVA is the place for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Police Department To Avoid Future Errors By Replacing All Equipment Officers Carry With Guns https://t.co/AH7SxsL0GY https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mommajessiec: I got the Pfizer vaccine and pso pfar pno pside effects.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Covid Announces Plan To Move Operations To Texas Full-Time To Escape Burdensome Regulations https://t.co/Wi26rEWANz https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StephenAtHome: Matt Gaetz never took COVID-19 seriously because she was a little too old for him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealAlSnow: I just got kicked out of flat earth Facebook group because I asked if the 6 foot social distancing had pushed anyone ove]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntiVaxxParent: Why do people turn a blind eye to the downsides of vaccines?! A close friend of mine got the COVID vaccine and died in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @provaxtexan: Yup exactly https://t.co/cr9OiwCdVD https://t.co/R4gpGpVTVl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neiltyson: The Universe is under no obligation to make sense to you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DCdebbie: Matt Gaetz majored in political science, and got a minor across state lines]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My New Year's resolution is to be more punctual.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz   https://t.co/tB17vqtXJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz   https://t.co/tB17vqtXJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @macrotargeting: this'll clear him for sure. https://t.co/A1AoclJAlO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz You got it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RightWingCope: Matt Gaetz has some explaining to do  https://t.co/MImdy7HUj8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Foone: FUCK https://t.co/FwfLIWhp4V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@guelphgirlchris @Desbearado Ive never heard of this before. Where are you located? Who is the cars manufacturer?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@guelphgirlchris I would raise absolute hell. If its a manufacturer warranty, I would look at the warranty terms to see if thats specified anywhere. Thats crap and theres no way in hell Id let that fly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kmcdonovgh: My secret talent is shutting the fuck up when I don't know anything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fibulaa1: I have a disease called its nice out so Im drinking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @butterwise: Congratulations to Rush Limbaugh on one month of sobriety.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MeCookieMonster: Me no cry because cookie is finished. Me smile because cookie happened.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialKat: Thrilled to announce that Ive given up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dmc1138: Cant wait for everyone to be vaccinated so I can start fist bumping people in the face again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lindarchilders: Tucker Carlson showing how long hed last in the military.  https://t.co/VosDBySHZ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BestLucasEubank: any restaurant that stops serving breakfast before noon should have its food license stripped, i do not trust you psyc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eDh8rxgyIg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RationalBlonde: hear me outinstead of Meghan, we interview prince Andrew. and instead of Oprah, its the police]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mythicpolitics: When the only Deep State you ever find yourself in is depression https://t.co/ZodO3aGBqO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cfree94: $3600 per child on these stimulus checks hmmm https://t.co/UFqJSs2Xxp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vicky_dollysmom A Talkboy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tony_ferraro7: the girls who organized the prom dress facebook groups should be in charge of distributing the vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Williesillie2 Ignorance is bliss...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HomeWithPeanut: Emergency contact? I don't even like being a regular contact.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotHoodlum: Ive been to Newsmax, QANN and Fox - no one has the inauguration on?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Covid Announces Plan To Move Operations To Texas Full-Time To Escape Burdensome Regulations https://t.co/Wi26rEWANz https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattmfm: The Republican Party, in two tweets. https://t.co/TBodJ1Zk20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @noampao: Texas               Me on a first date                        Opening up way            too soon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mmkrysiak Michigan &gt; Florida]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thenoahkinsey: Texas just lifted its mask mandate.  I guess not enough people froze and died in February to the governors liking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BettyFckinWhite: Oh, its still March. You guys wont believe the crazy dream I had.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @colindickey: Covid: https://t.co/T8tOC5IlQ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ADHDeanASL: No, officer, I DONT know how fast I was going https://t.co/JAYfFYNL06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kristen_Arnett: me telling my computer ill update everything tomorrow https://t.co/5NIGfcJfB7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RyanSchocket: taylor swift when she tweets "not a lot going on at the moment" https://t.co/0GvLY81FQz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mtgreenee God created man, who created gender reassignment. So, by proxy, god created the ability to choose your own gender!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino Anyone who is sane agrees.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thereidfeed: Tax refund HIT https://t.co/5M7sOTICfX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MyLastChance8: Just put the final touches on the house.  Now it feels like home. https://t.co/GZsbHxUTya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aaronadams1997: Virgin olive oil? Im sorry, I just think I need olive oil with a little more experience. Olive oil that has already we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StorySlug: I'm calling on Joe Biden to double the height of all flagpoles so they can be even further away from half-staff.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mrjohndarby: neighbor: have you seen my cat?  schrodinger: maybe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ManMadeMoon: Ted Cruz heading to Cancun- https://t.co/EOyN5URq7d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Williesillie2: I hope Rush Limbaugh dies again. That was fun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntiVaxxParent: Did you know that vaccines kill 200% of people they are given to? #AntiVaxx #StayWoke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Grounded Plane Makes Snow Angel On Tarmac https://t.co/985XXEWNtw https://t.co/rjl7HsnJBl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chalestay: If we get the day off to celebrate Presidents, we should get the day off to elect them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vexedinthecity: Once again, white people's OJ Simpson gets away with it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JasonNotEvil: Time to eat healthier.  *Puts breakfast burrito in the juicer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ham_why: Sex is great and all but have you shared your favorite music with someone and they loved it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pjayevans: Trump was found not guilty by the people who are also guilty ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pattonoswalt: I just hope this impeachment trial gets to the bottom of who riled up that violent mob waving all those Trump flags. What]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hog_mild: Mean Girls implies the existence of Median Girls, Mode Girls, and Range Girls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StorySlug: If Donald Trump has taught me one thing over the last couple years, it's that law school must not be as difficult as I was a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NelsonforWI: Ron Johnson, looking for any actual voter fraud https://t.co/VvF9sQJ3wM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UncleDuke1969: do not fuck with Detroit roaches https://t.co/GrpCKd2tTN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamgreattweet: When youre lost in IKEA  https://t.co/c42zBian6c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BettyFckinWhite: If Brady wins its only because of Dominiom software.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RyanSchocket: what my pizza rolls see from inside the microwave https://t.co/GavZzw7cQR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ConorRyan_93: me trying to follow the hostess to my table at the Cheesecake Factory  https://t.co/mhB6LKCIiF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FBChimichangas: Only you can prevent wasted chimichangas.  Only you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mtgreenee This isn't about them, this is about things that you said and did. Actions have consequences @mtgreenee, but I don't expect you to have the self-awareness necessary to realize that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thereidfeed: Republicans to Trumps dick every time its their turn to speak #Impeach https://t.co/tkkQZybKZc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thereidfeed: Pete Buttigieg on his first day as transportation secretary about to increase the speed limit  https://t.co/Eri6hUKS4R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@my15minuteswit1 @ThunderChief00 @billyeichner Oh no, you asked for unbiased proof. The sound of crickets is all youre going to get in return.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cosmocaitt: The FAA looking at the SN10 paperwork https://t.co/VKleZ6y2Rg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTomFrieden Unfortunately, the people that need to see/understand this the most are the people who lack the basic reading and comprehension skills necessary to do so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thotsofdoglol Give it enough time and a preventable disease will do it for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lons: I haven't gotten the vaccine yet but if I DID, here's how it would've gone... https://t.co/q2Gb0kTv8c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobinhoodApp Well this aged like milk...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thenoahkinsey Geppetto did such a good job with this one! He almost looks like a real boy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matchu_chutrain @RepMattGaetz @LouDobbs @FoxBusiness Trumps dick up his ass makes it difficult for him to stand like a normal person.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@apollozac For the tracking tech in the COVID vaccines!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Biden All-Female Communications Team Won't Tell Nation What's Wrong, Nation Should Already Know https://t.co/ausOAlNPwc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMirror: 15 people infected with Covid and several seriously ill after going to cat's birthday party https://t.co/0mgh3CHDcs https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tachyon100: @Chiv1984 Me painting https://t.co/nzYtvkLbiA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@w_terrence I never understood why your bio said you were a comedian. At least youve finally said something funny.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheTweetOfGod: Larry King will NOT stop with the questions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NYinLA2121: Biden: White Supremacy is a stain on our nation.  Republicans: https://t.co/EU1xvpREOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GQMagazine @danjlevy So far in 2021: Biden's inauguration was highlight of January. This will clearly be the highlight of February. https://t.co/8BXRAnP8bE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheAdamRozak Nah, to be disappointed they'd have to have self-awareness. I'm sure they're still talking about a secret plan for Trump's second term in some murky corner of the dark web]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surviving  Futures Clarity  Can't wait to finish out with my two favorite @jimmyeatworld albums!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GamerGeekGuy91: Trump Followers: Inauguration Cancelled.                                                    Everyone Else: https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamgreattweet: Donald Trump is making history by becoming the only president to be impeached more times than hes been elected preside]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Amazon Suspends Parler From Web-Hosting Service After Google, Apple Remove App From Stores https://t.co/ECJLVSZy1U https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @travisakers: MySpace announces Donald Trump has been banned. https://t.co/S8Kpeld3CN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ErrolWebber @realDonaldTrump Were you born 4 years ago?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheOnion: Josh Hawley Condemns Pro-Trump Rioters For Upstaging His Own Theatrics https://t.co/1fDHKBJurI https://t.co/Pj241nQJkP]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>