<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@katejhewson Meridian is good I think? That's what we have in a massive pot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[50 000 words! Ah these milestones make it feel reeeeeal! #amwriting #firstnovel #firstdraft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ok, its been unreal but I must mute this now. Ive had a great time learning about cereal from people all over the world. Youre fun sometimes Twitter x https://t.co/LuGvER0DcR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tezilyas: Join me and these other brilliant comics for what is likely to be one of the last few virtual comedy nights in existence!  Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TreasuresPod: We are always looking for more people to interview... if you love somewhere/wish more people came to your special place *]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bananacabaret: WERE BACK ! Weekends from Friday, 21st May  Lineups include @themiltonjones @DaneBaptweets @MaisieAdam @seannwalsh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TreasuresPod: We cant quite believe it but were at 22 patrons! We cannot believe how many people are jumping in our little nerd famil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im so sorry to anyone who has been voting for me and then disappointed. They should really tell you that youre a US politician if you have never been to the US]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*smashes head into a wall for eternity* https://t.co/Y8LbZIpd0o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dave_boon Her husband is not aware hes her husband]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why did none of you tell me Im a US politician? https://t.co/km7MLEmvTG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry your police team didnt win tonight. Stupid VAR (probably?) but hey look theyll get them next time would you like a biscuit? #DontWatchItButTryingToHelp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Special_Hijabi Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres what Ive learned this weekend: people really REALLY feel stuff about cereal https://t.co/LuGvER0DcR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Willduggan: New interview from me and @lauralexx? Of course! Its Sunday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NoiseNextDoor: We dont know WHAT you mean... https://t.co/8yQTdbFvJd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you like the way I observed this phenomenon then youll like my funny book where Ive observed many good things and made them into jokes: https://t.co/IuRV1jjvO3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im seeing my niece for the first time in a year today. Shes 1 and her Dad is a gardener so I made him for her  https://t.co/M7Cqk4isa2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cant believe this is my most successful tweet since Klopp  https://t.co/LuGvER0DcR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jasminem980 Yes I did! Although, I also brought the seeds inside an 2 have now germinated! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wtf when did cereal go landscape? https://t.co/aqs9ymVCPB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Free palettes recycled and lined with saved compost bags. Just waiting for my compost order for the main planter and my tomatoes and sweet corn can go in ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My mental health has been fried this week so I took the day off and made myself a herb garden https://t.co/QsyAHnOWrw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@benjaminpmoore It's very cosy. I can already see myself rewatching it because I like the characters and just want to hang out with them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchblossomb yes, sadly I think it would have been pretty much just you and me in the Zoom call. Bit of a bummer but online ticket sales just didn't happen now that things are opening a bit again :( xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starstruck (BBC iplayer) is like the BEST biscuits. I sat down for one and 90 minutes later I'm sat here panicking about when they're all gone. Beautiful comedy. WONDERFUL looking show. I'm in love.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Faybe1989 @yespaulineeyre @brionyred @JulietteBurton @hannahwarman @johnbond75babe @diaryofamaddie @IamRichWilson @sianharries_ @MCabournSmith @ZoePaskett @harrietkemsley @samanthabaines @SharonRobertsUK @VixHamBarritt @JennyBede @YurikoComedy @Isysuttie @NadiaSohawon @JenBrister @Wendy_Wason @bronactitley @kiripritchardmc @sueperkins @suziruffell @PRVix @CamilleUcan @KerryAGodliman @lucyportercomic @Hayles_Ellis @CharlieVMartin @savencomedy @rachelparris @NiamhAWalsh @Roisinconaty @FunnySuzyB @LouSanders @maddy_anholt @tiffstevenson @ShappiKhorsandi @tweetyedmondson @rosejohnno @SuzanneShaw @KlassMyleene @RachelFairburn @AngelaBarnes @lolwordcomedy @MaisieAdam hahaha give in to that feeling babe! non-essentials get jettisoned when you're in pulling back together mode. We're still just all here, chatting nonsense and showing off. We'll still be doing that when you are interested again x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TreasuresPod: Get those out of offices on: It's holiday time for us and those pesky banks! Pull up a comfy chair and get stuck in to ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@meadowgroove It's the support for self employed people who have lost their income. Like, instead of furlough pay I think.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hate that I felt guilty applying for the SEISS grant. Really racking my brains like "do I need this". Er, yes, you eejit: you lost 80% of your income. Yeah, but I *could* cope without it so... should I?  That I feel like this and then Cayman bank accounts exist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PopeLonergan Its not no reason: youre writing a book]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want to take my brain out and soak it in milk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When my therapist told me I need to face my fears, I'm not sure she meant write a sitcom about the worst thing I've ever been through. Jaysus and I thought the stand up special about it was hard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KateWilliamsme ooh smashing. bought. thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marknelsoncomic Mine works, and also I can plug into it so it extends upstairs for my phone as wifi but can be plug in internet when I'm streaming.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is an actual scene from Scandal https://t.co/W1iCJGsKFx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hehehe little knitted duck family! https://t.co/t63uSlhG3H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Spudfish83 awww shucks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This photo might not look like much but its v nice for me: posting that book that I writ too people in the USA, posting welcome packs to new patrons in Australia and it pretty much sums up the last 12 weeks. Cool. https://t.co/E9hTMnQdyZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TOMORROW is the very last online Knee Jerk... if you've not seen it, and you fancy a night in with a screen and a glass of wine, then please do join me: https://t.co/PTMnJs9Ld4 https://t.co/ThibwIhJTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChloePetts: I'm incredibly happy to be performing a few dates @brightonfringe this year (!!!!). You can get your tickets here: https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHighton Matthew that thanks is perfection. Man I cant wait to do cinema club again with you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MattHighton: In case anyone wondered what Matt Hancock took out of his pocket before his jab. https://t.co/oNsftvZ0YH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RufusHound @SeveredSonsDnD I accidentally gave an orc the night of her dreams with a nat 20 on a shag roll and I had to retire my character so he could go off and live happily with her]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@benjaminpmoore Not  confirmed but its looking good ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@benjaminpmoore First one is in June :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They begged and then pleaded and they got me back, turns out I wasn't doing anything else that year.  See me live(ish) before then though with my final online tour date tomorrow night: https://t.co/PTMnJs9Ld4 https://t.co/6eyt3yWJtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yay! USA babaaaay! https://t.co/DxvxFtxbaW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lorlyjane: We have a proper day out with @lauralexx and @Willduggan from the National @TreasuresPod and we pay a visit to #MySpecialPla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have I made enough flat breads for 2 people? https://t.co/8VLUrw4Eor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TreasuresPod: Ding ding ding! Our 16th patron has landed! That means just 9 more until we can double the number of Years  Years episod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shes divine https://t.co/F2JWjgV91O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Showing no signs of giving up on her duck protection https://t.co/FXFPdZxJzu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its finally raiiiiinnnniiiiiiing!      ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh no, the wifi is down. I shall have to take the day off work.  But Laura, youre writing a novel, so... you just need to be able to write?  SHUT UP FOOL. How will I procrastinate betwixt each and every paragraph?  Just dont?  ItS pArt oF My Pr0ceSS!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Depressing that after all the missteps this year keeping people, you know, alive, the thing theyre getting him for his wallpaper. Its Al Capone all over again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We only broke a door handle and it was 1200 so smashing up the whole law for 20000 seems decent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actually, sounds cheaper than Fox  Sons tbh https://t.co/TSggaWVYG7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When we rented a flat we werent even allowed to repaint it the colour it already was. If Johnson gets his deposit back Im going to be raging]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sarah_K20: What a lovely bit of post that arrived at the weekend. Thanks @TreasuresPod  https://t.co/JUzYXjMleR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @liam__bolton: Tea towels want to live on the floor. Throw them anywhere, they slowly roll off that onto the floor. Hang them over the c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaydeadams: Thank f*** for Winkleman. https://t.co/SCA8vhEeLX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aWLgGrIVgt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/H7uDMNBvX9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I made a duck tonight. Maki likes it  https://t.co/2NuIGTcIu3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really like Twitter and the kindness of strangers  thank you  Im cheering myself up by bothering a dog who really doesnt want to be bothered! https://t.co/ucLbBmUxhu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FixatedOn Ooh thank you! That sounds great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@meowmixtapes Yes please!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EddieStoneComic Ive got my fingers crossed for adoption if all works out but we will see what the world holds! Big love to you xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YellingAtSoccer I started that last night weirdly! I loved the first two episodes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EddieKristan Oh! Thats a great idea! Thank you xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Vermicious_Lid I reckon its along similar lines!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IamKateWynne Hahaha! I have another 5 years before I can watch that due to the my brain doesnt let me watch things people have said are good until they are long gone rule]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kempshills2 Love to you too xxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EddieStoneComic Ugh! It is! Its such a gut punch on the wrong day, isnt it? You spend so much time being ok about it and then your light entertainment catches you off guard. Sending a lot of love xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyway. RIP Blackish I was really enjoying you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hate that it upsets me. I hate loving a sitcom and then resenting it even though its just a lovely carefree sitcom. I hate that this nice thing is the thing that kills me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh god can there just be ONE tv show that doesnt have a pregnancy storyline?! Just ONE SHOW I can watch without having to watch the but we werent even trying! Episode. Oh just ONE SHOW. One.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TreasuresPod: Hello. Serious question. Would you listen to an episode of National Treasures Podcast that was all about Will shaving his]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_RosieGlow_ Oh thank you! Both out of a packet ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How come magic hour works on ALL OF INSTAGRAM BUT NOT ME?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My make up looks perfectly normal... until I step into the sunset light and I look like a c3po manic! https://t.co/T3HSlapiXF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Faybe1989 @brionyred @JulietteBurton @hannahwarman @johnbond75babe @diaryofamaddie @IamRichWilson @sianharries_ @MCabournSmith @ZoePaskett @harrietkemsley @samanthabaines @SharonRobertsUK @VixHamBarritt @JennyBede @YurikoComedy @Isysuttie @NadiaSohawon @JenBrister @Wendy_Wason @bronactitley @kiripritchardmc @sueperkins @suziruffell @PRVix @CamilleUcan @KerryAGodliman @lucyportercomic @Hayles_Ellis @CharlieVMartin @savencomedy @rachelparris @NiamhAWalsh @Roisinconaty @FunnySuzyB @LouSanders @maddy_anholt @tiffstevenson @ShappiKhorsandi @tweetyedmondson @rosejohnno @SuzanneShaw @KlassMyleene @RachelFairburn @jaydeadams @AngelaBarnes @lolwordcomedy @MaisieAdam @yespaulineeyre Ah babe x you do know that the fact you feel like reaching out and getting help is a massive strong step dont you? Its so easy to sit and spiral but remembering theres better is a majorly clever strength you have going on xxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MisterABK I have never ever ever been more professionally jealous of anyone. Sue Perkins AND mtg in the same project? Oh god damn I wish I was you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MisterABK WHAAAAAATTTTT???!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I like how Pringles neg you, like: the more you eat the harder they are to get out yeah scrabble around up to your elbows you disgusting worm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iszi_lawrence @JoSarsby @robinince @StellaGraham @SkepticsGuide I was so happy seeing you on a doc about pirates recently! You were great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Full video is here: https://t.co/NayHPGN23x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you tired of everything being clever and edgy? Why not watch one of the 11 episodes of @TreasuresPod now available on YouTube where neither of those things happens very often. https://t.co/8vl5IJ9tya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its cheese on cheese on cheese and some cheese to go with the cheese with some cheese and a cheese cheese]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UH OH ITS JAFFLE TIME]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Re whether he said it: The fact a lot of us can really, honestly believe it's the kind of thing a leader of the country would say is either:  A damning indictment on our leadership A damning indictment on where the media portrayal of our leadership has led our trust  Or both]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have ONLY TWO online versions of Knee Jerk left on my virtual tour...  TONIGHT "at" The Stand and FRIDAY "at" The Helmsley Art Centre.  If you're not coming, then it's imperative you retweet this to help find your replacement.  https://t.co/036nEd89ia  https://t.co/PTMnJs9Ld4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Company = his own career natch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally figured out who BJ reminded of https://t.co/7v3uOVJDHj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone over there is DEFINITELY casting spells https://t.co/ItZYlWDwuK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ImpatientUK: TUESDAY: - @lauralexx is doing another online gig, this week shes gracing the stage at @StandComedyClub . Were looking f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Aanjaa4 @noringerk https://t.co/0Rhe7cLBPQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NaomiGComedy Yup!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know you all dont want to hear this, but, as someone on the outside, you all seem VERY stressed about Line of Duty. Like, more so than this pandemic thingy. Are you sure youre enjoying it?]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>