<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 This shooting is another make-believe crime. It couldn't have happened because Toronto has a strict gun ban.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 It's neither a wave nor a forest fire. It's a hoax and a lie of such a grand scale that Hitler and Goebbels would be envious. #Covidisfauxvid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidMilley22: @CP24 I have yet to come across anyone I know who has even been sick with a cold or flu on the past year.  Shut the fuck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2abetter2morrow @newsmax Why won't the media admit that the mayhem at the Capitol (NOT "Capital") was the work of anti-Trump agents provocateurs? Real Republicans never used violence.  On the other hand, violence has always been the stock-in-trade of the Democrats and their #Antifa and #BLM shock troops.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KamVTV: We tried the 3 week trial of the Biden Administration and would like to cancel the four year subscription. Its just not going]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Brewski2020 @denisebatters Canada already has very strict gun control. What it doesn't have is strict urban gang control. The Trudeau government's anti-gun measures target mostly small-town and rural people. Perhaps it will come as a surprise to you but they aren't the ones shooting up our cities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS As long as you are in office,  President Xi will always call the shots. Will you be wearing kneepads if you make a state visit to China? Your veep can show you how to wear them. She has lots of experience.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrAndyNgo: Unmasked has debuted at no. 1 on the Wall Street Journals bestselling hardcover nonfiction and combined nonfiction lists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation Please stop addressing us as "my friends". We are not your friends and you certainly are not ours. Hundreds of thousands of out-of-work Ontarians would rather be gainfully employed again than be insulted by expressions of faux friendship. Open up the economy now. #Scamdemic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shelby67GT @CP24 The attack on saying "Merry Christmas" has been in full swing for a long time. The tyrants of the politically correct left won't be satisfied until they have outlawed and expunged all vestiges of Wrongspeak. I hope that Aunt Jemima has a very merry Christmas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ggill1972 @JeffTeravainen @CP24 How did you determine that "99% of billionaires are white men"? The world would not necessarily be a better place with more women and minorities in positions of power and influence. Power corrupts and no one is immune from such corruption because of their sex or race.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffTeravainen: @ggill1972 @CP24 What a dumb thing to write. Its called being a billionaire its got nothing to do with the race.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ssandrasaha @CP24 This is neither a case of white nor male privilege. The overriding factor here is money. If you have enough of it, you can buy "justice" no matter the colour of your skin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DougDoyleBaker @WBrettWilson Human beings are the number one killer of people in North America every year.  If we want to save people, then we should transition away from human beings right now. Actually,  that's already being done - under the guise of "social distancing".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WBrettWilson: Hypocrisy.... https://t.co/SK3PlqV9ap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoooPapa: @TRW_81 @Deborah171717 Joebama didn't get 80 million votes, change my mind. https://t.co/pgWk6OlEv8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @inky_mark: This is shaping up to be the winter nobody got sick  unless you got COVID-19 - The Globe and Mail https://t.co/w2AWdSca37]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepArrington: The same Democrats who told you we don't need a wall at the southern border, won't take the wall down protecting them at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: Just a reminder that when it was introduced, income tax was only supposed to be temporary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CherylDJones1: A pillow salesman just dropped more proof about fraud than the entire Bill Barr Justice Department ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Roman_Baber: Please go in to the weekend positive  optimistic. @fordnation can no longer deny that Lockdown is deadlier than Covid. Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sharon75571311 People who are rushing to get the vaccine should demand to know what's in it beforehand. The figure  of  70% would be cut in half if people used their brains instead of allowing themselves to be manipulated by fear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: BREAKING NEWS: Trump Supporter and Mother of Two Fears for Her Life and Her Childrens Safety After KATHY GRIFFEN DOXXES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bret_Sears: Joe Biden didn't get 80 million votes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bret_Sears: Progressivism is the fist step towards communism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TGiviens @DailyCaller How anyone could be happy and grateful about a "victory" obtained by the most massive electoral fraud in US history is unimaginable.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stclairashley: Your child is not trans because he put on a dress or tried on makeup.   My little brother used to eat grass as a kid but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aubrey_huff: Now lets play this game with masks....where are we in 2041? https://t.co/AsHT2X4gkQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aubrey_huff: My Instagram is so censored I may as well not even post. Surprised my Twitter account hasnt been canceled.   Fucking crim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpaceCorpsUS: Doctors Who Discovered Cancer Enzymes in Vaccines all Found Murdered https://t.co/PnZAwddx3L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Tjierra @CP24 The agents provocateurs who engineered the so-called "US Coup attempt" should be arrested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marabscott @This234c @CP24 It was more likely a mob of agents provocateurs that stormed Capitol Hill. The incident had "false flag" written all over it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chris50950571: @CP24 LOL I'm sure when I see everybody getting robbed and shot in Brampton and Mississauga it's Proud Boys doing those]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hammy4002 @buttzfly @CP24 An ideology doesn't burn down buildings or bully the disabled.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: Bill Gates can fuck right off.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CanArm2011 The only hockey equipment that Ron MacLean owns are knee pads.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CanArm2011: In case you were looking for a reason to vomit in your own mouth...here's one spineless douche stroking another spineless d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chris_RoyMtl: I got arrested for not wearing a mask today. Police Officers weren't interested in hearing about the scar tissues in my l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PHump72 @fordnation @TorontoPearson Dougie didn't destroy the province single-handedly. He was merely following orders from his globalist masters at the #WHO and the #UN.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sharon75571311: Hey, if your account got nuked in the last purge and you're starting over, tag me and I'll help you get back your follo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: BREAKING REPORT: Oregon GOP claims Capitol riot a 'FALSE FLAG OPERATION designed to discredit' Trump, supporters...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: So Facebook's oversight committee has just announced today that it "made a mistake" when the company censored studies sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bret_Sears: COVID-19 is a HOAX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AbbyJohnson: Wonder if Biden voters wish they could circle back to November 4?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NnwNws @Bell_LetsTalk Many of my friends have worked for Bell. They describe the firm as woefully short in the compassion department when it comes to how it treats its own elployees.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NnwNws: @Bell_LetsTalk Interesting when Bell doesnt extend the same support to their own staff ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bret_Sears: Canada needs to end all immigration at very least until the lockdowns are ended and unemployment gets to a reasonable level.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GLJ02497614 @KenPaxtonTX @GOP @GOPLeader @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @HouseGOP @FoxNews @RNC Was the so-called insurrection at the Capitol the work of Republicans or was it caused by leftwing agents provocateurs?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 As usual, the MSM tell only part of the story. They need to point out that the destruction of the family farm is tied to the implementation of globalist agricultural policies designed to concentrate food production in the hands of a few multinational agribusiness firms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 If there is a snowfall like the blizzard of '99, John Tory will call in an army of social workers and declare that snow is racist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aubrey_huff: I found it! I finally found it. I give you the dumbest tweet in the history of Twitter. Congrats @peanutpollino! https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aubrey_huff: This tweet cost me 4,000 followers since it was posted. @jack hates truth spoken on this platform. https://t.co/RykujYJ85d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aubrey_huff: Can we now all agree that #Covid_19 was used to create fear to lock us up in our homes in order to force mail in voting so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michael_house9: @CP24 ALL viruses mutate. This is normal. https://t.co/UfpGr6iwya]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 There's only another decade of the fear campaign to go.The sheeple will keep wearing their useless masks and will bow to every new restriction on their freedom unquestioningly. Very few will die of COVID-19. Most will die from terminal stupidity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bluemoonusa17: @CP24 1st case of highly contagious horse shit called CP24 still going strong and spreading as rapidly as ever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pattee_bregg @AP4Liberty Why would Biden supporters need guns anyway? If they or their property were being attacked by a gang of illegals, surely they could just call the nearest social worker for help.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toshafreitag: @CP24 Sorry to read this. But dont believe everything you read. Theres more to the story Im sure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 Dying after testing positive for COVID-19 is not the same as dying from COVID-19.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Flo_2021: Americans, welcome to the garbage we Canadians have had to put up with for the last 5 years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LempaLyn @LeaderMcConnell Those crimes were committed by Antifa and by agents provocateurs. Their purpose was to besmirch the reputation of the duly elected 45th POTUS and all GOP members by posing as Trump supporters. The "insurrection" was a late-game, deep state dirty trick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlackfullaRoar @jwhaifa @donna_jacobsen No great surprise. The United States has already had a man as First "Lady".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClayClayChucky: @jwhaifa Oh look @cnn @nytimes Biden  his wife arent holding hands. I expect a full story on how she is pissed at him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DC_Draino It wasn't an election; it was a coup.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RyanAFournier: Guess what.  Trump is still going to live in their heads.  Rent free.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michael_house9: If OToole cant stand up for an MP in his caucus. How will he stand up for us?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uncw808: Is anyone else slightly more terrified for tomorrow than excited? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hoosiers1986: I dont believe Joe Biden is mentally fit to be President.  Do you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bgirl0001: It means were phucked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClimateMalware: https://t.co/VESYhSyo80]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkDice: What exactly is the downside to Trump pardoning Jullian Assange and Edward Snowden?  The media complaining about for two days]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Roman_Baber: Key point in Dr. Schabas' letter to @fordnation is that Public Health Ontario is using the Case Fatality Rate inappropriat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Why does in take 35,000 troops to paint 12 circles on the pavement for the 12 people who will attend the inauguration?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DSBW2MM: https://t.co/P0RURAZsgu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bigboy2scoops @AbbyJohnson There is no constitutional right to abortion.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AbbyJohnson: Yay for Missouri becoming the first abortion free state!!! May there be many, many more to come!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CP24 The Covid religion is killing freedom of speech.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @Charles39712047 Tomorrow will be one of the darkest days in U.S. history. The most widespread electoral fraud ever will result in the inaugurations of an illegally elected President and Vice-president.  Every politician who accepted this result unquestioningly is a partner in crime.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @4gradsBama: @senatemajldr Shameful that Washington, DC is locked down, with armed military as an illegitimate President is sworn into o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thomas17576153: @senatemajldr Do we really need 25,000 armed National Guard?  Where were they when our cities were burning.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ashley88817465: Why didn't O'Toole crucify Trudeau for going to the Barbados over Christmas/ New Years' holiday????? I would have expec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CampaignLife: #Prolife MP Derek Sloan was set up  wrongly attacked because a white nationalist made a donation to his #CPC Leadership]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: Canadian politics in the Trudeau / Singh / OToole era.   Are you looking for something different?  #PPC https://t.co/Kz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KamVTV: The world isnt falling apart, the veil of the worldwide corruption is lifting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: They can fence in, militarize, and blockade  Washington DC in a week ... but cant do the same to protect our southern border]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeibtNaomi: Its 2021 and Germany has re-introduced arrest camps for dissidents - quarantine detention camps. Dont get in the shower.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Most Popular President In History To Be Inaugurated In Secret Behind Giant Wall Guarded By Thousands Of Soldiers https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chicago1Ray: The minute Bidens sworn in the world's a more dangerous place that's a fact]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Joe Biden is about to set the world record for the most military troops to ever attend a U.S. inauguration - and a 2nd world]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtracey: Downtown DC is essentially under military occupation and nobody in our bold, adversarial watchdog media apparently finds this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chicago1Ray: All Outgoing Potus leave the incoming a letter in the top drawer of their desk   My guess is Trump's gonna say " You didn']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: This is getting fun. https://t.co/7cr94u4O4o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wolfpack197721: So if youre in DC they are checking ID to get in and out?! Imagine if we voted like that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NRA: SHALL NOT BE INFRINGED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @How9876543210: The Dems will vet 25,000 National Guardsmen but they wouldnt audit/match 25,000 absentee ballot signatures]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnnyHaig: Very brave of @erinotoole to come out as the first openly Liberal leader of the Conservative Party of Canada.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tony59589591: "I'm confused. They want us to have the vaccine but it doesn't work well enough for the lockdown to be lifted? Are we to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: I live here and can confirm this is true.  Something isnt right here. It honestly looks like they are setting up for a m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hoosiers1986: I consider @JoeBiden to be an embarrassment to the United States of America!!   Do you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: With lockdowns, curfews, stay-at-home order and other authoritarian measures, we now literally live in a police state.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>