<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@lucyjanebonham And you buy all these things on your own time which a few nectar points wouldnt even cover the true cost of your time.......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seriously mother of god #LOD I cant sleep after that..... I need to know who.......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neverstops1 Brilliants stories!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: Friday Night Dinner star Paul Ritter dies of brain tumour at 54 https://t.co/RzkdDUxejm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neverstops1 @chefsantoshshah Rose Ill join you in going!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TRYING SURSTROMMINGS! https://t.co/jpGGBeFNLg via @YouTube  @Pipskin @ChrisMoyles  watch this on the fish!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well thats a new one... throwing in the sponge.... think youll find its towel @BorisJohnson #bj #spongevscovid #oops]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PaddyMcGuinness: Ive finally lost it in lockdown!  #isthisthewaytobarnardcastle https://t.co/QHuuxirL63]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neverstops1 Now you wish you had a stationary obsession like me hehe!!!! X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neverstops1 @PMGilmartin @trishadurie @KevinFrediani Download plant snap app its fantastic!! Helps me so much rose!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IndyFlint: Can someone tell the press outside St Thomas Hospital that they arent social distancing and should probably be at home? Ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neverstops1 @wagamama_uk Awesome work ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cindylcourtney: I am an NHS nurse and not social media savvy - I only have 106 followers  Im OK with that. I want to show how Covid-1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shikichef Your daily tweets really make me smile! Thank you chef!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tehbus My father had only one kidney, no spleen I cant believe how selfish these people are. I feel your pain. Stay safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tehbus Theyve said we can go to stores so if you are able to travel take the right procautions and shop as you would if youre not in the isolating groups which the vast majority of us shouldnt be. Just do one big shop.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im so confused Im sat at home at as Im fortunate to be able to work from home and there has been a steady movement of people in and out of my estate in their cars all morning.... what are people not f*cking getting about lock down.... it cant all be full of key workers! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinSLewis do you know whats going on with cover for you insurance underwritten by @axainsurance their phones all have a fault dial tone.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yess  https://t.co/RH3xtKvDh5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lucyjanebonham: If youre worried about social contact at restaurants, salons, etc., you can still buy gift vouchers. Lets support our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@greateranglia Tried calling the other day but left on hold for ages I had to go to work!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@greateranglia I have submitted photos 3 times if my defaced ticket to get delay replay after a nearly 4 hour delay the other week... yet again you wont pay..... what else can I do??? Ref Reference GA/DR/20200122/BKKG yet again shocking service #greateranglia #wheresmymoney]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoneySavingExp Squash!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaffronBarker: Please read this all!!  For every retweet of this post @Ubisoft_UK will donate 1 to @AlzResearchUK up to 30k so Im sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SealShoreWatch: Its official Grey Pupping time has arrived here on the Norfolk Coast. Please keep your Distance if visiting the Coloni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Waiting for the lovely ladies to arrive for Spanish Tapas evening in the sunshine.... @brockmansgin with @fevertreemixers clementine tonic... a perfect start to the evening! Happy bank holiday all... #gin https://t.co/qKTzFv7KKN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching people find their allocated seat on a train is highly amnusing, the ability to read numbers and count goes out the window and mild panic if someone is sat in their seat....  #trainlife #allocatedseat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NorwichFoodies @norwich_market @Retro1702  youd like this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @premierinn for your help rearranging my booking at short notice due to miscommunication within my Business, definitely restores faith in big businesses #thankyou #mondaykindness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well I did it, first ever running race, 10km down, it hot weather  wasnt pleasant but Ive done it! Thank you to all the wonderful support, the marshalls and music along the way, oh and a special thanks to https://t.co/Dnz1W0u5aK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Retro1702 @runnorwich Awesome job!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An amazing evening watching Toruk by @Cirque...... #outout #london #cirque #weekend #roundtrip @ The O2 https://t.co/eBQUUmUsTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sometimes prospective and a reality check is needed! These men are wonderful x https://t.co/7LtWmAeIUP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super tasty Mexican for dinner with more rose sangria. Guacamole and chips, yucca, black beans, fish tacos and chicken quesadillas all delicious and tasty and needed after 18km walked today. #foodie #mexican https://t.co/1XhwwHJ3U2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weddding Spam Alert..... So bloody proud of my beautiful at talented friend @daylebayliss getting married to the wonderful and late running Chris! Such a perfect day a wedding in the park and my first baseball game https://t.co/POkuHihJwq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It maybe technically 4am. ACM home but Ive had an amazing evening with sarah.howat having cocktails and wine with amazing views and super tasty pasta! What a view of Manhattan!  #nyc #adventures #traveller #jetlag https://t.co/SCVHWU0ahQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love my new carry on bag.... well we all know it had to be mulberryengland also very proud of resisting the duty free Mulberry store! #nyc #mulberry #traveller #jetsetter #weddinginnyc https://t.co/hsnkQIckQP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super tasty Mexican tapas dinner... yes we over ordered but there was a doggy bag going home.... #food #chilli #mexican #jivekitchenandbar #alocholfree #tacos #loadedfries #slaw #nachos https://t.co/UcjQfE5Z0p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After 4 days of trekking and camping weve crossed the Inca trail to Machu Picchu. Yes you can just visit Machu Picchu but the experience and the sights of the last 4 days are utterly https://t.co/7UEMCl7QKY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Day 1 food, after eating or not eating plane food it was a relief to have proper food! Delicious passion fruit local drink to start, then we share ceviche, jungle potato and local corn  https://t.co/jzOCuxjuQj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Least 4 of my 5 a day here..... yum!!! #incatrail #machupicchu #wine #juice #travel #thisgirlcan @ Heathrow Terminal 2 https://t.co/eHcQeiSLCj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sunday Roast with these beautiful ladies... roast lemon and thyme chicken with roasties, pigs in blankets, red cabbage, carrots, braised leeks and broccoli. With mixed fruit pavlova for https://t.co/zHeLckx3uN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sunday spring flowers  ..... #springflowers #upcycling #selfcaresunday #sundayroast #sundaytable #freshflowers #tulips #mumsfavourite @ Norwich, Norfolk https://t.co/88Qhvk3a7a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Retro1702 Christmas is the only time hes allowed out!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Treated myself this evening to a wonderful local tasting menu by the very talented @FoodbyJLawson and it didnt disappoint. His philosophy of food to provide nutrition to the body. His https://t.co/X7VBH4ihE2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spot of lunch and maybe a cake....... https://t.co/PlZMDoZI3x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love overhearing people trying to understand a menu and where a dish comes from... the couple need me have score nil points this evening! #foodie #menuchoices #overheardinarestaurant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another delicious meal from Alice and Jamie @moremountain. Sage and Parmesan arancini balls, followed by spiced duck and then white chocolate parfait and bubbles.... #foodie #chalet https://t.co/R4IDF8cU2w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Such tasty food yesterday..... haggis scotch egg for mid afternoon! Dinner of walnut and Brie salad, slow roasted ribs and slaw followed by pear and apple crumble and custard!!! https://t.co/3OKYMwkQon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delicious lunch looking at the mountains.... busted knee means a rest day for me today but time with the beautiful Sara #foodie #snowboarding #ladiesthatlunch #wine #foodporn #lunch #tasty https://t.co/cnPIX9LI8d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a day... sun was shining and riding with these guys is always a pleasure! #snowboarding #holiday #morzine #girlboarders #crazypeople #bluebird #snow #extremesports #dodgyknee @ Morzine https://t.co/u75UIMxbua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stunning meal @moremountain plenty of vino and were currently demolition the cheeseboard playing cards against humanity.... #foodie #foodieabroad #france #chalet #moremountain #foodporn https://t.co/7p9sYKKxKy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brilliant catch up with the wonderful people last night, cant say the hangover was particularly pretty....  #fridaynight #ootn #friends #mizkan #catchup #wineandgiggles #sauvignonblanc @ https://t.co/weuB7kC3PH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lovely lunch yesterday in Windsor shame out the weather. Gorgeous crayfish and coconut salad @meganmickwebb #foodie #foodieontour #foodporn #tasty #avocado #crayfish #gogoswaterfront https://t.co/4FR3r4loSQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh what a view.... less than a mile in 90 minutes.... missed lunch  #traffic #standstill #m25 https://t.co/nX3A8qMBXp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spring flowers to brighten a rainy afternoon....  also does anyone else get tulip droop problems, if so how did I stop it!!  #firstworldproblems #daffodils #tulips #springflowers #myhome https://t.co/nbaSXwbN9K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When lucybonham makes post @parkrunuk flapjacks.... OMG these are good.... #cattonparkrun #friendswhobake #flapjack #postrun #thisgirlcanrun #tasty #bakeporn #parkrun #fuel #tasty @ https://t.co/S8GFrf9ZYO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neverstops1 @PenguinUKBooks Shall I bring up this might hurt? (Adam Kay tales of a student doctor) or Ive just finished @dollyalderton which is a great]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stephenfry: What if #SantaForgot? Believe in breakthroughs again this Christmas by watching and sharing this short animation I made wit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So nice to wake up in London and not be going to work.... off for brunch which is far nicer! #brunch #london #notworking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Comment from my sister in law.... we dont need to set an alarm... we have children! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProudlyNorfolk @AdnamsNR1 @lucyjanebonham thank we may need to taste test.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Retro1702 @McDonaldsUK Maybe dont have McDonalds lol!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In need of salad in my life... a winter warmer salad. Grilled sweet potato, rainbow chard and feta, dressed with sesame and chilli soy dressing so simple and tasty. Thanks https://t.co/BRJaONh8zm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Walking to work on this beautiful autumnal morning..... stunning views down the Thames at Kew.  #commute #norwichtolondon #workingaway #walktowork #kew #foodie #viewsn #nofilter #autumn https://t.co/Xz9ofCWb2n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fancy tasting my pickle in 15 product..... Get yourself down to the below  @tescofood stores on Friday (5th October) between 11am-6pm to taste my creation.... also its on offer at 1 so https://t.co/wxU08deO1L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So naughty but so good!! fererro rocher waffle.... just what was need! #tasty #foodporn #sorrynotsorry #outout #puddingout #chats #foodie @sweettoothhoney @ Sundaes Gelato https://t.co/cKCanRh3wj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Favourite place...... southwold #sunnyday #sunday #coastwalk #icecream #sundayroast #seaside #chelseabythesea #relax #happyplace #seaair @ Southwold https://t.co/NZbWKLg5b3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great way to start my Birthday weekend!! lucybonham and rosie! #3dayweek #spa #birthdayweekend https://t.co/Fp3dg2F7Or]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy 2018 to my amazing family and friends! So many adventures to look forward to already! https://t.co/gFjvMpCobz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last park run of 2017 and a very muddy one completed with lucybonham  #parkrun https://t.co/Wqx3ipDv6x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPD_UK oh and now after 20 mins of holding you cut me off.... great where is my parcel someone has lied and signed for it when nobody was in!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPD_UK so arrange parcel to be delivered to a local shop after I found out nobody would be in.... yet a ghost with my surname signed for it where is my parcel you are ruining Christmas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super tasty festive turkey boa, house pickles, trotter nuggets (amazing) and who could say no to https://t.co/zdM0Bmz6d0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@anyahindmarch I regret buying your bag, broke within a few months and been waiting since September for a repair! Take some lessons from @MulberryEngland for customer service please! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love @TheRoyalArcade at Christmas time so festive! #christmas #royalarcadenorwich #festive https://t.co/Qfx2JtGJgj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1st of December and the start of my favourite time of year!! #happychristmas #season https://t.co/yjUlCbFj4T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Awesome agenda today......  @thefoodpeople https://t.co/C8CtLZuBUX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways I am still waiting for the money you owe me! Its a very simple case! I would like money in my account next week!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super excited to be given these by my lovely friend lucybonham, as a Percy pig fan I have https://t.co/LCUiqBSXs8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways I was originally told if I went to a BA flying airport I could pick up compensation sadly I live 130miles from one.... how does that work? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways You keep saying that...... how long does it take you owe me money.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways @British_Airways youve broken your contract with me... I will be looking to take the matter further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways Can this be speeded up? Youve been sat on it weeks, not a difficult issue I agreed to move and you compensated me for it but yet no money!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still @British_Airways havent paid my compensation nearly month after giving me a non working compensation for changing flights  #annoyed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolutely stunning four course meal @mellfors_max plus wine and added extras from the kitchen https://t.co/48mWP5xypr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Day 1..... 23,115 steps #Sweden #Stockholm #Holiday #awaywithdayle #steps #sights #colours @ https://t.co/AuefHi8paT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonights meal can only be described as a #meatfeast starter was an amazing mix of charcuterie, https://t.co/2hH0gBR3ku]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miso sirloin steak with salad and of course #kewpie mayonnaise #Japanese #tasty https://t.co/WpREvmD2UU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A little treat to keep me going this afternoon! Absolutely love mochi ice cream didn't get any https://t.co/G7smY4ApC4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways Well I hope the revised figure takes this into account as I went out my way to help, what is the ETA of a decision?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways The investigation consists of checking if I used the compensation card... how hard is this investigation to complete ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow @British_Airways still no compensation after your own compensation card didn't work.... last time I do you any favours..... joke!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gone are the gorgeous summer morning skies as I commute j to London now the grey looms, winters https://t.co/RO8nBxBEGq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing dinner tonight at farmyardrestaurant ... first time I have visited and it didn't https://t.co/JiylBptUwv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@British_Airways It was 125 voluantary to help you guys out. I would like to have the money asap as the card you gave doesn't work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So @British_Airways I move flights to save you hassle I get 125 compensation card which doesn't work! Screwed over again by you! Thanks!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whoop!! Back on chilly london with all my baggage! Sadly have gained a cold and sore throat! https://t.co/CqI9YwZW11]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tasty @leonrestaurants breakfast box with extra avocado after morning HIIT #tasty #Leon #workingaway @thebodycoach https://t.co/oWbktiHrrp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Working lates today means I get a full HIIT session in this morning @thebodycoach #sweaty https://t.co/nWJFGVRY0A]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>