<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@corbieres99 what is a bulb you fucking cunt fucker??!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: When can we stop pretending that the UK and USA are 'free countries'?  It was a fun myth while it lasted, but let's be hones]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RubyDoobyDoo1 https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EndUKLockdown1: Sky News running with a 'fears of low compliance' narrative regarding the lockdown today.  Fantastic to hear, this is e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: The 'News' is now toxic, damaging to those who watch it. I still do (someone has to monitor it) but, as a psychologist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kbeanie93: Because people are done with this BS  https://t.co/LPglw1c2lp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ukcolumn: Years ago I met an elderly German lady in Bournemouth who lived through rise of nazi regime later married British soldier. Sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emmakennytv: British public have been coerced to stop seeing the people they love  Tory MP Charles Walker  Channel 4 News https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JaniceW78256134: The time for silence and compliance has ended.  This is not just a fight against criminal coronavirus laws, but a figh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BarbaraHutton: Protest the lockdown  COVID restrictions in every city, town, village every Saturday until this is over. Join other gro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hoosiers1986: Im so ashamed of the Republican Party!  Are you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GowTolson: Our hope of defeating the woke left-wing died on 3 November 2020. The main stream media combined with big tech now controls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boblister_poole https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @boblister_poole: Whats Happening WithTwitter? Second Day Lost Three Hundred Followers Again? Never Been Blocked, Careful What I Say in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kbeanie93: Now my followers are disappearing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MucciTina https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MucciTina: Isnt it kind of amazing how a person who was once a stranger, can suddenly, without warning, mean the entire world to you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chapman020 @Hondapie https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chapman020: So we can legally lock decent law abiding tax paying British families in their homes,but we cant stop unknown non tax payi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GwendolineSper1 https://t.co/pudkgK2uZ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GwendolineSper1: Horrendous Global experiment that is doomed to failure, too late for the collateral damage that is now significant  h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingBobIIV @DickDelingpole https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KingBobIIV: Also, changed my bio to be safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RSBNetwork @RubyDoobyDoo1 https://t.co/pudkgKk6nA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RSBNetwork: Hello! Weve had enough here of this Twitter.   Its clear that people who think like us arent welcome here, so were out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StandUpX2: @Stat_O_Guy LETS MARCH TOMORROW IN THE THOUSANDS 12PM CLAPHAM COMMON  if youre fed up of lockdowns, new legislations, 97%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lumidek: Stalin, Mao, Pol Pot, and similar comrades have "only" cleansed tens of percent of their nations. Rick Klein, a self-described]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @realBradBrewer: When you tear out a man's tongue, you are not proving him a liar, you're only telling the world that you fear what he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@truemagic68 'Most people believe the President's actions/behaviour have been reprehensible' speak for yourself David!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @truemagic68: Congress needs to think carefully about impeaching President Trump  escalating unrest. Most people believe the President']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @patcondell: #Trump did nothing wrong. He didnt incite any violence. The people who condoned months of rioting, burning, and looting in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @calvinrobinson: This has been a terrible day for free speech and for democracy.  Apple, Google, Facebook and Twitter deplatformed the U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AriFleischer: Censoring other peoples points of view never ends well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: Pelosi wants to remove Trump before he releases a ton of declassified corruption.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Free Speech is under attack right now ...  The Republican Party (Cricket sounds)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: "I just see children deteriorating on a regular basis. I can only speak about my own - I have a teenage daughter and her men]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MucciTina are you on parler?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MucciTina: Fact https://t.co/yCxapWjHSm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simondolan found it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jihadwatchRS: Of course. Swamp creatures love each other. https://t.co/mhS4YtsaKC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @spikedonline: Lockdown is responsible for the greatest transfer of wealth from poor to rich in history. It's boomtime for billionaires,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Pye: So Twitter, Facebook and Google are no longer platforms.  They are clearly publications and should be treated as such.   Bi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Walkabout24: Your mask protects you from free speech.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: In ONE YEAR, the Left has normalized:  Shutting down businesses  Shutting down churches Force masking citizens Censoring]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hardlyperennial @AlixJoan1 @hughosmond the lockdowns are working, they're designed to shut down small businesses, depress and demoralise us to make it easier to control us, nothing to do with a virus, The Great Reset]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @imatriarch: They arent just trying to deplatform us. They aim to defame and defund us so they can ultimately destroy us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RavenStarrz: I was 4,100 followers today now I'm at 2,998, I'm about ready to leave this sh*thole called twitter...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simondolan are you on parler?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bringbacktrump: I'm moving onto Parler.   This is my account. https://t.co/N2U381XUHi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newsmax: .@trish_regan says "you can't have your cake and eat it too and these tech companies want exactly that." https://t.co/VlT7z8dr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: A major political party and massive multinational corporations are removing their political opposition  Its a cultural coup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieOliverUK: Complete and utter nonsense and smokescreens by @MayorofGM Im sad to say! Even based on what myself and 3 ex senior GM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conceredtrace: This man was the reason I woke up! I hated him like most British did! But he respected my freedom of speech. Since then]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidJHarrisJr: Now theyre going after Tucker!   https://t.co/NdFehNT1p3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brady6111: Parler https://t.co/KIiZZUvLja]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JakeWri38029870: there is Anti Lockdown protests happening this weekend both Tomorrow Saturday and also Aswell on sunday in London , Ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OmegaJak @ClarkeMicah ????????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: BREAKING NEWS: The Trump Family has been INDEFINITELY BLOCKED from Facebook..   The Tyranny we warned you about has bega]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage is this Murdoch telling you what to say who is funding GBnews?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Throwdown2208: @Nigel_Farage So long as you are promoting Blair I'm no longer interested in what you have to say.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: I dont want to live in East Germany.  Click below to watch my latest video.    https://t.co/jgVKlM9s0b https://t.co/Wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage you were praising Blair, sellout!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClarkeMicah weird how so many people virtue signal wearing their masks in the open air or in their cars, I wonder how many of them were Remainers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClarkeMicah: I wear this mask to protect the other trains . Maurice the Masked Engine at Paddington Station. https://t.co/BC8HQpVH8g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBabylonBee: Congress Upset As They're The Only Criminals Allowed In The Capitol https://t.co/Zfy9duC1Fd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RavenStarrz: Pence needs justice... https://t.co/OOrMginw9t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: The mirage of freedom.  .@Telegraph cartoon for 9th January 2021 https://t.co/gegrMDkrhM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: Democrats can build a wall after all!  * against their own citizens. Against foreigners -- not so much. https://t.co/OkTn4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Throwdown2208: Make the most of the majority you won't be getting it again. @BorisJohnson  https://t.co/FrKOh6Qco7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NewtonClarkeUK: Twitter is ablaze with talk about whats going on in the US.    At this stage I couldnt give two sh*ts. Im far more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Morriga31157967: ARE YOU AWAKE?? https://t.co/Z1XXIGE8DE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BILDERBERG_GP: Brexiteers...so, now Sky news stoop to new depths on Trump..Bercow introduced as 'Pelosi's friend'. Why am I not surpris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Have you noticed that the Fake News media has completely forgotten about COVID for the past 3 days while bashing Trump and hi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @17cShyteposter: It took just over 3 years to go from banning the first person from the internet to banning the President of the United]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: According to the BBC these are young women clapping outside Chelsea and Westminster hospital. Last year that hospital]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Iromg: Some London radio station reported that @boroughmarket was rammed with people today. Absolute rubbish. Its deserted. They shoul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaisyAdeleleo: The way that the U.K. Police are behaving is abhorrent!  How dare they force their way into peoples homes and make accu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@101Maurice i saw a woman change her baby's nappy then dropped the dirty one on the floor of a car park]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @101Maurice: Whilst parked in BQ car park I noticed a couple in a car the other end eating a McDonalds. Next time I looked up they'd go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CKeirns: OMG! New images of Trump supporters firebombing a limo in DC!  Just kidding. This is liberals at Trumps inauguration in 2017.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Dont you love these phonies who got paid huge paychecks to be in the Trump administration for 4 years - then they suddenly p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hall_roger: Kudos to this gentleman challenging the police sitting down having a coffee, when he and all of us can't. Are these police]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecoastguy: True, this. https://t.co/X8dwAbCiVY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lankyman90: Londoners get off your arses and vote this idiot out. https://t.co/fcrDIYZAaD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Pye: And people take these jobs. I wouldn't be seen dead doing this https://t.co/yJAxSsJpW7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kbeanie93: No but the public are https://t.co/1nFr3LSHgy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tonyangelcyn: Ill say again is it time come for the English to take back control of the homeland? The British establishment have lost]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @p_beejal: BBC living up to its name - The Bullshit Broadcasting Corporation. https://t.co/0KL9kxqx2f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: Stop this fear-mongering.  99.7% of people overcome SARS-Cov-2 with their own immune system.  The current mortality rate i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Millie__Weaver: Welcome to the USSA   Theyve already-  -Stolen your vote -Shut down businesses -Enforced lock downs -Allowed internet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JakeHepple1: David Kurten for Mayor of London  https://t.co/vSAI2waUdq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ukcolumn: Zuckerberg now censors standing US President Trump. The implications are that Global Corporatists now fully in charge of USA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinDaubney: BREAKING: @SadiqKhan declares a "major incident" in London, orders Londoners "not to mix over the weekend"   Standby fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @netpol: Derbyshire Police - infamous last year for their excessive interpretation of covid regulations -  have fined two women 200 eac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristophGottel: Moderna Admits: mRNA Jabs Are an 'Operating System' Designed to Program Humans https://t.co/rTaPT3alvg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@14Kekkadivvy @London19721 and all white women are being trained to reproduce with brown or black men, nearly every ad has a white woman witha black husband]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @14Kekkadivvy: The native white British population is getting smaller each year but we have a "housing crisis" and these overpriced card]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreezePeach49 I see one or two generally though everyone is wearing a msk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeibtNaomi: The Left used to be the most vehement critics of Big Pharma, Big Tech, exploitative corporations and self-serving lobbyists]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>