<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Jens Lehmann has been sacked from his role as advisor to Herthas Berlins supervisory board for racist remarks in a WhatsApp conversation about ex German international Dennis Aogo.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mail: Mikel Artetawill make late calls on Lacazette and Tierneys availability for Arsenals Europa League tie against Villarreal. https://t.co/iAdZ396fXa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mirror: Former Arsenal player Sol Campbell has emerged as a leading candidate to become the next England under-21 manager]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buy Hector. 30m and we talk https://t.co/bOoksBcRhe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal U23 need a draw in their last league game to avoid Relegation. They play west Ham away on Friday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AFCMet: PODCAST! In this episode of Kanu Believe it. I discuss the good win against Newcastle and how it is a much needed confidence bo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Villareal account saying the kid has grown and doesnt want to be humiliated again like in 2006  2009.  https://t.co/EuoqXRQ8e0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arsenal: Afternoon, lads    #UEL https://t.co/OlFp11D4si]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jose Mourinho has been appointed as manager of Roma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Santi Cazorla (Mikel Arteta) I'm great friends with him and whatever good happens to him and the club I'd be happy for them because I'm a 'Gunner'.' https://t.co/5BGXdsCzjU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sky Sport:  Ek to make 1.8bn Arsenal bid by end of week https://t.co/LD5tjvQL5e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Telegraph: Daniel Ek is due to make a formal offer to buy Arsenal this week  https://t.co/dniAT1Z6fx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leno talks on the TL. Leno himself confirmed last few days that he has 2 years left on his contract and he is open for everything ie. Stay at Arsenal or start a new adventure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#KroenkeOUT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Afc_Lord If so then you know they are selling 100%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Daniel really had the funds and with Henry and Bergkamp on his shoulders along with fans protest then the pressure is going to be immense of the KSE. The summer will be interesting, curious to see if the KSE try to appease the fans by huge spending.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Henry (Arsenal takeover) Daniel will not move away. He will be waiting to see if they are willing to sell.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thierry Henry confirms @eldsjal reached out to him and Dennis Bergkamp and they both listened to what he had to say in regards to plans for Arsenal in the future]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thierry Henry talking up @eldsjal on Sky MNF and says he has an honest man and reveals they have plan to involve the fans]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Charge sheets said he messaged Maupay on Instagram, saying:  "You think you will get away for injuring Leno? No way in hell bruv... But dont worry you will be safe you wont be hurt. Its more fun watching you feel pain when your loved ones go through suffering."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 19-year-old Singaporean, Derek Ng De Ren, has been charged in courtfor threatening to kill Neal Maupay on Instagram. The threats were June and July 2020 via Instagram  "I will kill you and your family" https://t.co/FaOTvMz9vH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@afcjames19 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Santi Cazorla I dont know why the (Arsenal) fans have been so good to me as Ive only done what I did at every club, trying to do things the right way and bringing something to the table, and the love they gave and still give me is priceless. https://t.co/XpWrIUeMt3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arteta (Martinelli) I love Gabi so much. More than all of you together!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a picture https://t.co/q8vsISF0e4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So from Artetas presser, looks like Luiz, Tierney  Laca will be out of Villareal game on Thursday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arteta says David Luiz injury is NOT good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsene Wenger on beIN says football need to control owners who wants to just make money out of clubs. He says PSG and City owners wanted to improve the standard of their teams rather than making money out of their teams]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsene Wenger says what is happening at Old Trafford is a revolution in football. He says fans are the most important factor in football https://t.co/rP2Qy9mBht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Needed Auba to score today. Lets see on Thursday now, would personally start Chambers/Gabriel at CB instead of Holding/Gabriel. What do you think?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal wins in the premier league this season;   8 away wins 6 home wins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Willock is bored https://t.co/bxalDPjnYH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Capoue who needed a stretcher as if he has been shot to avoid a red against Arsenal is currently playing for Villareal. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a ball by Martinelli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Luiz hamstring gone. Holding on Thursday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unreal scenes at Old Trafford. Wow  https://t.co/9oFtTE0RAm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gabriel is a totally different player when he plays alongside Luiz compared to Holding. Everything about him is composed with Luiz.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have now scored 3 goals in the league this season from our midfielders.   - degaard vs Spurs  - Xhaka vs Chelsea  - El Neny vs Newcastle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Luiz made that goal with that pass to Hector]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Go Gabi https://t.co/KKxXrAcp06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That comparison is a true reflection of how bad Arsenal have been in the past 5/6 seasons. Constant buying of players who are good with high wages. Cant sell them so just releasing them somehow to avoid their wages for a year or 2. The club is in a mess from top to bottom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apart from Everton  Leicester obviously.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not a huge fan of Arteta currently but that is one of the most embarrassing comparison. Lol. All of those teams are so far ahead of us in terms of quality so obviously they dont need to spend hugely etc. https://t.co/YTuwCbmeZA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tbMXojrYhs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arteta said on Wednesday that Tierney  Laca are in contention for playing at Villareal.   He just said it is unlikely Tierney  Laca will play in the next few games.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At a stage where everything is so bad that I dont even care if player X or player Y plays, Its same shit again and again. Not fussed about today, all eyes on Thursday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ryan, Bellerin, Luiz, Gabriel, Xhaka, Elneny, Ceballos, Willian, Odegaard, Martinelli, Aubameyang.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aubameyang  David Luiz both start. Willian also in the starting lineup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LatteFirm: Launch month! 4 main features to look forward to:   Press Pass - with journalists  broadcasters.  Fans Forum - for ever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#KroenkeOUT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11th in the league table in May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eJVj48D2NB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/LLLCL3xRkZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best opinion on yesterdays game https://t.co/1dApB7hXoe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AFCMet: PODCAST! In this episode of Kanu Believe it. I discuss the really bad performance against Villarreal, how Arteta got it wrong a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arsenal: Enough is enough.   #StopOnlineAbuse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodnight Gooners. It was a tough watch but we are somehow still in it. Lets hope the luck is till with us next week because we need that at the moment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant believe I want David Luiz to return to the starting lineup. The defense has been poor since he got injured.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emery (Arsenal penalty) It was not a penalty. It a serious mistake (the ref) that hurts us a lot https://t.co/6RMNO1rTMv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Martinelli brings energy to the team and energises the team with the pressing. Obviously Auba wasnt fit to play tonight so lets see with how Auba/Laca feel for next Thursday. If both are not fit then Martinelli needs to start]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont know what is next for this football club man. Our manager is very young and not up to it the big task it seems. Weve got loads of very average players and got very bad owners. Relying on 3 very young players to carry us all season. Looks and sounds depressing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We were also very poor second half Mikel https://t.co/k6aRsC7atT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gerib_17 Thats exactly what I said tonight. I was willing to give him till end of next season but having serious doubt now especially  last month performances and results]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honestly speaking a month ago I said I would give Arteta next season before judging based on the uprise in performance after December but last month including today has made me rethink that. We have been absolutely terrible for the last 1 and half month.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Man Mari dropped a terrible game, Holding lol I cant talk, Chambers  Xhaka terrible, Partey and Ceballos the less said the better. degaard and smith Rowe nonexistent. (Think the players felt the pressure on the game and crumbled.).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pepe was our best player then Saka. Cant believe how shocking the rest were]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 positives going into the second leg. We are somehow still in it and Ceballos wont be there to fuck us again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United destroyed Roma. Huge favourites for the cup.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bradley_bissett Which one? Both red cards are correct decision. Ceballos shouldve been sent off in the 46th min but referee gave him last chance so it was very clear next foul was a second yellow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant believe they rewarded us with the penalty. Saka put his legs to touch the defender and went down. But we take it but I would be livid if it was awarded against us. Referee managed the game poorly throughout]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honestly speaking we are very lucky to be in the tie and with hope going into the second leg especially after our red early second half. Lets see second leg but actually fuming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We were terrible all game, they were very average all game. Arteta selection was terrible, Emery panicked at half time and didnt go for the kill. The referee was also terrible. What a shit match all through played by 2 very average teams]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a terrible game of football]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How many time is Ceballos going to risk of throwing us out of the Europa League. Against Olympiakos, Benfica and tonight fuck off man]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ref card is on Arteta. Ceballos is a liability and the warning was there in the first min of the second half where he should have been send off before. And Arteta still left him on the pitch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No changes at half time it seems]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Changes man. Make changes right now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bring Auba at half time for Ceballos, shift degaard to play along with Partey and bring Smith Rowe behind auba. We need changed at half time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know our form is shocking but to play like that in a European semi final? I cant believe it. Wrong passes all over the place, no movement, nothing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Humiliating first half. Villareal are still playing in first gear and already 2-0 up (because we always gift opponent childish goals). We are all over the place]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal arrive at Villareal stadium https://t.co/7IPbjQzPLv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alcacer, Chukwueze  Moreno front 3 for Villareal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Luiz  Auba on the bench. Laca  Tierney miss out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[False 9 it seems. Hmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisWheatley_: Arsenal XI vs Villarreal: Leno, Chambers, Holding, Mari, Saka, Xhaka, Partey, Ceballos, Smith Rowe, Odegaard, Pepe  #UE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pablo Mari https://t.co/fZlSrB5afL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He needs to bring his hospital bed with him then https://t.co/LfCC1cqZAu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last time we played Villarreal in Spain, we drew 1-1 and Adebayor scored that cracking goal. Goodnight and hopefully we have a good result ! https://t.co/wJwi8I6scv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marcos Senna says Villareal deserved to play against Barca in the champions league final in 2006 https://t.co/vU9PgmSXqW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Kane interview all over the media tonight saying he wants to win the biggest prizes in football. Think its very clear he will push to leave Spurs this summer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think we have no choice but to win the Europa League this season, anything other than that is a massive failure (especially with our league season). But the rewards is so huge is we manage to win it. (ie. getting back to the UCL for the first time in almost 5 seasons).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GGiXajWfKU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arteta says Tierney has been working like a beast everyday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arteta says Aubameyang, Lacazette and Tierney all are in contention for tomorrows game]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ceballos Im learning a lot in the Premier League but I think La Liga is better for my game https://t.co/26vEGYdpos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aubameyang is available for the Europa League semi on Thursday night even though he is still not fully fit after malaria. https://t.co/HNFBnruoyd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsene Wenger talks about the possible takeover deal to buy Arsenal and adds  If I can help Arsenal, I will do it as well" https://t.co/eQfaSbpIAa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GFFN: Arsne Wenger on Spotify owner wanting to buy Arsenal: "The best deals are the ones where you come out and nobody knows about it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickAmes82: Strong statement from KSE but gather that  as you'd probably expect  it hasn't altered the appetite of the Ek/legends gro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny how we keep hearing since the summer in media that KSE facilitated 45m to buy Partey as if its huge achievement. You have been here for more than 10 years and you brag about facilitating 45m for a player. Fuck off lol]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>