<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Besties, I am tired. Goodnight and sweet dreams.  https://t.co/NzYQnIDVPQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheyStation omg I love a good parallel between Data and myself ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yeah, this is how I edit videos, dont judge me. I like chaos.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess who just lost a Data post because I accidentally pressed upload before I was done editing   And while Im short on Data videos in my drafts, too. I do not have a copy before this version. Whomp whomp. https://t.co/nOANbwT1Ld]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you ever look at yourself and say woah you REALLY need to relax because thats me everyday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeekyGwendolyn: https://t.co/VSxSIpxsw5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown Thanks Julian!!  https://t.co/MjXm7rEUF8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheTartanTart Omg wow hes so   *screams*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni you understand him so well, so true bestie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AccidentalTrek Oh yes, exactly!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @3rdtechnician: saddest little baby in the room!!!!!!!!! https://t.co/XlGUFAD8Bi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lanielabens: If you love comic cons get vaccinated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karam_ba_: data #StarTrek https://t.co/O6S1egUzoQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni nah you're overthinking it, it would make a good thing better]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[me when I'm making fanart https://t.co/3SzCFXLWY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni dude that would be so rad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alright, thats all the gushing about Data and The Big Goodbye for today. Such a fun episode. Goodnight! https://t.co/tIFwRXo0Wk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Datas first instinct is to protect his friends. Seeing this clip again now having seen Datas full character arc, yeah. Hes really wonderful. #dailydoseofdata https://t.co/BYrC2rkCRR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Data, how is it possible for you to be that cool? #dailydoseofdata https://t.co/7zRsGAP66P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im not saying ALL of my problems would be solved if I had a suit to cosplay Dixon Hill Data, but many of my problems would be solved by being able to cosplay Dixon Hill Data https://t.co/beEzuTJi7o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ribbonthing: Me when I have a bad day and go on star trek twitter to feel better]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kiraswife1 awww yay! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheTartanTart haha thank you, Im glad you enjoyed the edit!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rewatching The Big Goodbye, and I just love Datas enthusiasm for cosplay.  #dailydoseofdata https://t.co/XZbBf6lEPj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @Memyselfandt1ni for drawing Data for me! I love him so much &lt;3 https://t.co/J9WaOCoGIs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DahkurArt: 37/55 of my women of #StarTrek portrait series is Soji.  #StarTrekPicard #Soji https://t.co/6DoUBD8sLW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown I am looking...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni Thank you bestie  https://t.co/h16QlsVpOv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fresh Hell edit!  @BrentSpiner https://t.co/nLfM5X2SOw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trophymad Sending some love your way!  https://t.co/xRMNSCEkbw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My brain when it became obsessed with Data https://t.co/zCKEAHRbVB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ani_obsessive: Visual development art by Aurlien Predal for Moominvalley (2019), dir. Steve Box, Gutsy Animations https://t.co/s7M6AH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning!  https://t.co/3kO82GIr6w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rjt_presencing Yeah, thats okay. Thank you for asking!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodnight! https://t.co/aoZ2gDVE3Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mr_Picard Im sorry, that dudes a jerk  https://t.co/VWBgsI7RDz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eatatquarks: Watching "Data's Day". Data choosing, of all the insults in the English language, to call Geordi a "lunkhead" during his e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni THWACK https://t.co/ZzuMZ8SHEZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeekyGwendolyn: https://t.co/fUFGODu3yX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni He had his sea legs...argg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think Data is a pretty swell guy. #dailydoseofdata https://t.co/PFyFnYKOck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lieutenantkeira Congrats!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NoContextSpiner meme format https://t.co/9mAhwWwDKo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmmaOfTheImpact You look so cool!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @latimes: A number of factors have fueled Californias turnaround from national epicenter of the pandemic to having one of the lowest ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown very important information, thank you for sharing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sovnknown: ATTENTION!! Data is cute. Thanks for attention https://t.co/GELatMV4sp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh, heres some puppet content, folks! Im getting a little better at maneuvering it!  https://t.co/ZYoiKsSM62]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tara_oshea: united we stan https://t.co/Z9POD1VWKc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HHJurguPKQxPEJ5 Yes, exactly! Brents performance is so funny and charming.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FawcettLouisa @BrentSpiner shhhh Louisa, youll break his concentration!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tngimagebot: https://t.co/Rk2VD6YjVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[me clocking into work &lt;3 https://t.co/UiYG0GkAG8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown hes okay, I guess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gil Godwyn, my beloved  https://t.co/Rjgjutxeg4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HHJurguPKQxPEJ5 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@secuninja yeah, my phone flipped it in selfie mode. I'll put it on wrong next time so it looks right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellenieanna Thank you Ellenieanna!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But Ode to Spot, I will, I promise. Whenever the next time I have the patience for contacts is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone: Do Ode to Spot in your cosplay!! Me: Oh whoops, I forgot that when I was in costume.  Me: I did, however, remember to do a lip sync to a MLP song. #dailydoseofdata https://t.co/DyAT4ODaNX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robertdmcneill: Support @JBillingsley60 and give someone some warm feet!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rjt_presencing Im so sorry ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trophymad Thank you! It was a pretty good day ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mr_Picard Exactly. I come across people on a daily basis who still wear his merch. It didnt disappear overnight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni DAMN RIGHT.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellenieanna Thank you!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sovnknown: hey I finished my Gil Godwyn fanvid  https://t.co/FSVaaZQoZv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OYE COMO VA https://t.co/5fLS4oX2xK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Piximom00 Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ivykaelinart: letting the days go by https://t.co/pXaci6JeS6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xana_nouille omg the hearts so sexy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @leenfiend:  pretty boy https://t.co/gqWgJBQCRD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@positronic92 What? No one likes you?? I did not receive that memo, and I already like you! Whoops ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rjt_presencing Oh no, I hope Sammy will be okay. He sounds like the sweetest bunny in your Sammy updates. Keep us posted!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cxptainjaneway Good luck!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rashiduzzaman82 Yeah!!! Im so happy to hear that! Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alizonnetje Thank youuu! https://t.co/feAf4heMXX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mr_Picard Thank youuuuuuu ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FabulaSagitt Dankeschn Fabula! Ich werde heute mit viele Leckereien sehr verwhnen sein. Das ist mein Plan!  Ich drcke dich auch! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FawcettLouisa Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SwiftofOpal Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown Thanks Julian! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheyStation haha thank you bestie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ErdtrabantMaria Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@positronic92 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MadamSeraphina https://t.co/ZSN3tujRyu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HHJurguPKQxPEJ5 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow! Brent wished me, specifically, a happy birthday today! How sweet of him! Thanks, Brent!  https://t.co/UfdKZMZhJO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blainebowden @misskiranerys Thank youu!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni IIm guessing like toilet paper over his hands or something?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sovnknown: Star Trek: TNG Wardrobe and Makeup Test, 1987 [Part 1] Brent Spiner performing Data playing William Shakespseare's Marchant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@misskiranerys Thank you! My favorite part is hot night, wind was blowing  Im so proud of this edit. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OliverKuhlmann1: #StarTrekPicard #raffaelamusiker @ItsMichelleHurd #digitalart https://t.co/UgsZEfKLut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning besties!! Hope you all have a wonderful day. #dailydoseofdata https://t.co/CWZ84GMhzm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sovnknown @shrederoni Oh yay! I found it now. Thank you Julian. I just...his voice...wow...its so nice. I love this footage. https://t.co/EQUaF2ahai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni Yeah from what I remembered it was from The Tempest, but the footage seems totally gone from the internet...maybe Im making this all up in my head?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni Oh, I almost forgot about that test footage! I always loved it. Shakespeare!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shrederoni: when u take a good selfie https://t.co/7Nkx321ash]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shrederoni At least the last thing I get to see is a pretty face ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>