<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Have you heard? New music from @maya_delilah, @swearthatsdeema, @archives_nia, @bb_sway, @dairyfuckinfree, @WillowKayne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @melinskers: calling peoples' opinion of me "fan theories"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jem_Collins @SPAJournalism Happy to help!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Fusing classic RB sounds with a fresh new take on the genre, @_tianablake is the ever-growing artist ready to take her]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: New music from @ZoeWeesOfficial, @LittleSimz, @wolfalicemusic, @Smooth_boiiiiii, @m1llionz, @UnknownT9, @_TSBOY @alunaa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @djoblig: 44 men 5 women   Here are some names if you need help @WirelessFest   @shaybomusic @MsBanks @Saweetie @stefflondon @coi_ler]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Here to decode fact from fiction, Catfish UK hosts @JulieAdenuga and @Oobahs spill the tea on the new show, shady dates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Get your fresh music fix with a bunch of brill new tunes from emerging artists in this weeks Undiscovered. Featuring @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vickygrout Looks so good!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Get your new music fix from our pick of the best rising artists in Undiscovered  This week, hear tracks from @georgia_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Occupying a transcendent musical space, French-Senegalese artist, @hotcocoacartel, is using her voice for self-reflecti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl throwing up in the hedge next to my table at 7pm on a Monday. Welcome back to the pubs ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Meet Maeve, the Cayman Islands born, genre-blending musician as she reveals her dream dinner party guest, plans for an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: .@CharlotteOC  reveals her most vulnerable and honest work to date with Here Comes Trouble. She speaks unguardedly of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hgvandepeer: The journo-sphere will fully make you feel like you need a book deal, a staff job for The Guardian, 68 national bylines an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And todays unexpected pitch comes from... https://t.co/jSuJJJlPMr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bethmayashley: sometimes it makes me mad that journalists are never portrayed realistically in TV/film but then who would want to watch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @desukidesu: me: onion rings and a bottle of wine for the table  waiter: white or red?  me, trying to impress my date: whichever onion t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Radio host and broadcaster @jackxsaunders co-signs three emerging artists to watch in 2021 and speaks on the story behi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alainacastillo5 @NotionMagazine such a good watch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paigesimsss @LOCKmagazine eyyyyyy well done!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: DIGITAL COVER: "See Nobody" hitmaker, @WesNelsonMusic speaks with Notion as we unearth his story, how he found his soun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@frances_4ever @NotionMagazine @parshally_there @jaclyn_oconnell Great chatting with you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @frances_4ever: thank you aimee phillips / @NotionMagazine for interviewing me for this fun article!! wanted to share some of my faves f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Need new music? We've got your back. Stream @LilNasX, @beabad00bee, @BeckyHill,  @_elderbrook, @jungle4eva, @easylife,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@camillaackley Exciting times! What are you writing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidjonsson__: thanks @NotionMagazine for the cheeky feature.. talking all things #industryhbo  more  https://t.co/VaJl057nZz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pitch pawfect https://t.co/Sgyc3Yv3u7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulbridgewater Who?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dua Lipa went OFF in her #GRAMMYs performance. Choreo evolution has been real]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excited to be on the #britawards voting academy this year! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: DJ and radio presenter, @EmeraldRose, gives an insight into how she maintains a healthy work/life balance, shares some]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charlottelawr: for notion by lukey @NotionMagazine @lukeraymondt https://t.co/miWCNdPthy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jodieharsh @NotionMagazine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I chatted with the awesome @_girlinred_ about retaining autonomy on her debut record + road tripping with her dog for this week's @NotionMagazine big feature  https://t.co/KTX9ng6U2E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maisiehpeters ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: .@maisiehpeters speaks on her new single "John Hughes Movie" and upcoming debut album, reveals the qualities of a hit s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgia_twinn @NotionMagazine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @georgia_twinn: tysm @NotionMagazine for the sick pics and kind words, I had sm fun! Make sure to check out their piece on me, you might]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Toriwest_ @Bricks_Magazine Congrats!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New music Friday https://t.co/SMkiXQr2EK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@misszing Murder on the Dancefloor - Sophie Ellis Bexter!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alimkheraj: my plans from june 21 https://t.co/htfhcURJJD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jackremmington: I will literally never ever say no to a night out ever again in my entire life and that is a promise]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Roisin_OConnor @LelandOfficial UK Hun lives in my mind rent free]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hattiehattie Felt this in my soul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gemtriesharder Dua Lipaaaa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamhousni d'accord!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Heartbreak On The Dancefloor' and 'Back To Earth' are my faves of the unreleased tunes FTR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just got an early stream of @SGLewis_  'times' album and boy does it make me miss the dancefloor! A beautifully cohesive record. Those twinkling synths could break my heart]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurasnapes YES! THIS!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SGLewis_ Love the record! 'Back To Earth' would have gone OFF at festivals this summer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@livycoare @CarolineIntl Best of luck!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lauren_mcgaun Congrats!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One for writers! https://t.co/YfsCvpta1n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obviously streaming the new Dua Lipa as soon as I wake up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: "Good Love 2.0" hitmaker and Notion's One To Watch for 2021, @PRIYARAGUMUSIC, speaks on her inspiring musical journey,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IceCreamEaterrr: i can not wait to start going out again!!!!! I WANT TO FUCKING DANCE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rosegray_ @NotionMagazine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosegray_: Notions 1s 2 watch for twenty twenty 1. some lovely words, thank u @NotionMagazine @aimeephillips94 https://t.co/bf7hj36keQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arloparks So well deserved!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_EthanBeer Everyone looks very uncomfortable here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaylynHarmon: As an ex-social manager, idk who needs to hear this but CREATING the social media content and MANAGING the social media c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickklowe ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chatted with the lovely @arloparks for Notion about her beautiful debut album and got some book suggestions! https://t.co/mHf7GPXY8w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: .@arloparks speaks on the experiences and emotions that inspired her debut album Collapsed In Sunbeams, the importanc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: London rapper @Ocean_Wisdom fronts a special edition digital cover with @beatsbydre.  Ocean wears @beatsbydre Flex Smok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Providing a voice to a disenchanted generation, @babyqueen is on a mission to change the meaning of pop music.  https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're looking for a digital designer to join @NotionMagazine! https://t.co/h432Vx2Bfm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join the @NotionMagazine team!  https://t.co/ObPJR28tlT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: Describing itself as a fully immersive digital entertainment platform, Hydeout: The Prelude presents somewhat of a so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: ONES TO WATCH 2021 Notion has picked the 10 musicians we expect to make big waves this year. Find out who made the li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rosegray_ @NotionMagazine Such a sick mixtape ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: .@dontworrybeviji  is the new @DirtyHit signee mixing alt-pop with lo-fi indie and grunge to create a potent sonic cock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toludadaa We love to see it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JonathanMeres: Idea for TV show: The Masked Author. Aspiring writers, get publishing deals, based purely on merit and regardless of how]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cerysimo Yessssss!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@livycoare Love the chaotic vibe of this video every time I watch haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britain is breaking its promise of better bee protections by allowing a bee-killing poison banned in the EU to be used on our fields! Lets build a massive buzz to stop this. Sign  RT: https://t.co/hc2Z35HgJS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClashRobin Well done!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[literally ANYTHING would be good right about now https://t.co/h3RH8czvey]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lucyj_ford: https://t.co/jA6ECXf9u3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FionaSturges I always remember it as the acronym 'Rhythm Has Your Two Hips Moving' lool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fuelledmedia @AcklandNancy would be great for this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy New Year to my electric blanket ONLY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nattykasambala Good luck with your next move! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: "Tomorrow isnt promised so any chance you get to experience music with people you love, you have to take." @SGLewis_ o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Notion 88 cover interview with @charlottelawr is now up in full! Loved this conversation https://t.co/Ns2I5LQcfm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@camillaackley Vaseline to soften the inside heels Ive heard works]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TB to when I interviewed @ToveLo for the Notion Pride cover back in the summer https://t.co/fjr40v7vjl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: We've rounded up our favourite tracks that have helped us through this bizarre year. Find out if yours is on the list!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SGLewis_: I just wanna go dancing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SGLewis_ Impact was sick ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elleevans98 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @grantrindner: this spotify AI thing is stupid if i wanted to be negged about my music taste i would simply text any of my friends]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS! https://t.co/DA3RGiLwGU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotionMagazine: 2020 has been one hell(scape) of a year, but at least we've had these albums to get us through it.  https://t.co/3vy1zQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@indiajordan8 Aubergine has moved from chorus line to main character in my life this year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustHedyJ @hellogiggles Congratulations!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twcuddleston My mum makes a banging sweet potato and lentil nut roast (moist rather than crumbly). But Sainsbury's plant based wellington also slaps]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>