<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Just got this through the door. Today is #WorldAsthmaDay and I'd very much like to be vaccinated against Covid-19 as soon as possible but sadly already living with a respiratory disease means this government doesn't consider me a priority #asthmaticsatrisk https://t.co/XjUqffoz06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Relationship goals https://t.co/kwEltDAlHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_questmaster Correct! More on that tomorrow ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpiffyUserName1 No, but it's got Tinhead from Brookside.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoleyMole01 https://t.co/Frd05vB6st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SAT 5 MAY 2001:  "Woke up 9.45am. Went to town, bought DWM and a 4 pack of E240 tapes. Watched A Question Of Pop (BBC1 6.30pm), now it's the Lottery with old Rod Stewart.  Taping the first part of The Top 100 TV Characters later (Ch4, 9.00-11.10pm), surely Who will be high up?" https://t.co/a1vERHG7Dv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["No timewasters" is ironic because I watched this film a couple of years ago and it was a complete waste of my time https://t.co/pMQx3fsTyB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandmanJazz Sorry, I didn't see you down there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoleyMole01 @DWMtweets Everyone's a critic these days.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidwhittam I plan to make that the final episode, as a never-ending live stream.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh, and when I say I'm a big Doctor Who fan, I don't mean I'm important or anything, I just mean I like the show it a lot and enjoy affectionately taking the piss out of it at any given opportunity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've had a few hundred new followers in the past few weeks (thank you!) so I suppose I should introduce myself.   Hi, I'm Pip, I'm a big #DoctorWho fan and I've been trying to get my fan art into @dwmtweets for the past two years.   For some reason they don't take it seriously. https://t.co/xTjDeksGYQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Look casual lads" #DoctorWho https://t.co/TveSNogmAV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How it started               How it's going  #DoctorWho https://t.co/CVzzweewQF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Look casual lads" #DoctorWho https://t.co/ndUZEOk64z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Abort, man, abort!" #DoctorWho https://t.co/OGQv394PQm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think this is what they call a "one-percenter" gag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I see Austin Powers is trending https://t.co/Id27zsP4Pn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellardent And AFTER THAT you're watching a 16mm film telerecording of a PAL 625-line master videotape which has been physically  digitally cleaned, geometrically altered, restored to its original framerate, with a colour signal restored from a 1970s NTSC 525-line domestic video recording. https://t.co/6gO5WMcN2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Are The Movellans Watching Today? (Tues 4th May) #DoctorWho https://t.co/kK2g4lQPfF https://t.co/LgrUWGzafA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pos2OnsfUG https://t.co/8Fla0uVaei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*are at it again. I've offended myself now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The terminally offended at at it again https://t.co/R5zjqW9xrX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOOK: Even more footage of The Coolest Guitar Solo Of All Time (don't @ me) and we still don't see what happened to Prince's guitar. I like to think it rose all the way to Heaven where he caught it and carried on playing. https://t.co/AgwWyqFKTj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@derJOgelle Carry On Emannuelle. Don't search it out, it's dire.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@almurray It's so funny seeing Basil frustrated at every turn. Sybil doesn't trust him, Mrs Richards can't hear him, Manuel can't understand him and the Major is just plain senile. You're rooting for him but you just know he'll never win.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And I've used this one quite a few times: https://t.co/jCtjlXy4bM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["That particular avenue of pleasure has been cordoned off" is a particular favourite of mine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Communication Problems has just started on BBC1 for probably the millionth time and guess what? IT'S STILL JUST AS FUNNY  #FawltyTowers https://t.co/QcauGCE9Li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mildhorror "I'll be back!"  "No, you won't!" https://t.co/A4ZOq7cfEw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These two moments are hands down my two favourite moments in a cinema of all time. I lost my absolute shit. Everyone lost their absolute shit. https://t.co/jxfsc1qI6E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Film4 are showing Masters Of The Universe (1987). My earliest clear TV memory is watching its "network premiere" on Christmas Eve afternoon in 1990 on BBC1. I loved it. Funny how 'Teela' (Chelsea Field) bears more than a slight resemblance here to Leela of the Sevateem... https://t.co/OFBWo5pWZl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rev_Magister The missus helped me with the wording.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellardent They must be Bob Holness stans. https://t.co/wcZ1N8zV2w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same energy #DoctorWho https://t.co/HMrPAGALa9 https://t.co/Ql3sCh1fJe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@claytonhickman Ooh that's lovely. And why have I never spotted these lads? https://t.co/OwAokQHDrr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep it light Mary, keep it light https://t.co/VctrKhZkWr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Revolution* of the Daleks. I keep bloody doing that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For anyone interested, the Blu-rays of Fury From The Deep (standard) and Resolution Of The Daleks are currently 9.99 at Amazon (DVDs are 7.99). #DoctorWho https://t.co/cDcs4elZQD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0hMySt4rs Sexier than? https://t.co/nVxtILtnrR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jamie_Bate1 And yet a quiet, nice guy by all accounts. He died of motor neurone disease back in 1985, only 52, great shame.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 Great minds! https://t.co/GLkhnUfbI7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Must be a Bank Holiday" #DoctorWho https://t.co/zEHXn1Yg36]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CRennie1999 We wait and we wonder]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Are The Movellans Watching Today? (Mon 3rd May) #DoctorWho #MelanieBoosh https://t.co/Jzqnz0Z9Hf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How #LineOfDuty should have ended https://t.co/ghgpKGCMld]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ah, Telegraph lady is back for one last #LineOfDuty hurrah - yes, Nigel Boyle was good as Buckells, but the "stand-out performer of this series"? Really? Kelly Macdonald gave an acting *masterclass* last week - the detail, the nuance, the emotion she packed into just two words. https://t.co/KofSwVQvap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["And H is... Ian Buckells!"  The nation:  #LineOfDuty #LineOfDutyFinale https://t.co/b7IXmLZYdF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@richardmarson2 Free sofa though https://t.co/gFLubD3b44]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So hang on, Witness Protection comes with a beautiful cottage, hot partner and cute pet thrown in? Where do I sign up? #LineOfDuty https://t.co/qqIlttvkRl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uV2rwGoAE4 https://t.co/5z7b2GiOwP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminded of this quality piece of journalism: https://t.co/uRJ5ZXU1rn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bleeding cool? Bleeding the life out of print magazines more like. Don't follow these jokers. https://t.co/3HpQIrRz7j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Final cover art with added Balaclava Men #LineOfDuty https://t.co/88phySF8MF https://t.co/J05mVzPscT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That lad clearly needs to drink more water. https://t.co/e4E9iwBkpw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two years on and I still think of this often https://t.co/YYQId08J7Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A minute's silence (sort of) with Alan Partridge #ThisTime #AlanPartridge https://t.co/xSSZf0RI0H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Are The Movellans Watching Today? (Sun 2nd May) #DoctorWho #BuenosTARDIS https://t.co/I5Yyu12XOa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WEDS 2 MAY 2001:  The big news that day:  "Randall  Hopkirk is coming back!"  The other big news that day:  "Put 10 in bank." https://t.co/v8owoza5Zh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@retro_tube I've never been Alansplained before.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Yes, I know. It's just a joke." https://t.co/br7GCyqHBT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/14ZLI4EICT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ijr1970 Mestor was played by Edwin Richfield, who had played Captain Hart in "The Sea Devils".   You're thinking of Michael Kilgarriff, who played the Cyber Controller in "The Tomb of the Cybermen"  "Attack of the Cybermen", as well as the eponymous "Robot" in Tom Baker's first story.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same energy #DoctorWho https://t.co/jD0MTAW9te]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gculloty87 @matryer Isn't that Lawrence Fox?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matryer Any of Rebecca Front's characters. She's just brilliant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BUT THAT'S JUST NOT ENOUGH https://t.co/tBr3dkQUZU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@damnfinelad Yes indeed, he was paid the handsome sum of 42,000 which enabled him to buy a flat he was renting and reduce his debts. Hurrah for Pedigree Chum!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paramore1979 It was all Cheeky Monkey's fault for putting him off.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[100% legit folks  https://t.co/coHM44rq4Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OMG JOE BEASLEY'S BACK!!!  #ThisTime #AlanPartridge https://t.co/EkgLiXVtEV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BACK DUE TO UNPOPULAR DEMAND  What Are The Movellans Watching Today? (Sat 1st May) #DoctorWho #SolidMeatyNourishment https://t.co/fWAfnflywv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I might as well say this now, Sue Cook has pulled out" https://t.co/6Vqd70C2GQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Benlindsay3000 Well it's all there at the drop of a hat on DVD/Britbox of course, but I think the Twitch runs and lockdown livetweets have demonstrated the value of scheduled repeats.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BTW, incase anyone's interested (yes, all three of you) why my 2001 diary thread has gone quiet, it's simply that I was revising for my GCSEs at the time and wasn't writing down anything worth tweeting. There's something marginally worth mentioning tomorrow though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hellothisisivan Rod Stewart probably]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Sv4NiHWdZE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whydontyoutube That aired in March 1992 so yeah, probably that.   I used to love watching MeDinner repeats on Paramount Comedy in the late 90s but sadly it seems to have been largely forgotten now, which is a great shame as it's very much a forerunner to TV Burp.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Emily_Rosina It's such a beautiful piece and you all really did it justice. Great seeing you on sax too, so talented! I'd have loved to have contributed but alas when it comes to singing I've got a voice like a chair scraping across a tiled floor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whydontyoutube Not wishing to be contrary, but the original Shooting Stars pilot - with Ulrika - aired on BBC2 as part of At Home With Vic And Bob during Christmas 1993, four months before this episode of MeDinner aired on ITV.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JENNIE: So you've had the Giant's Causeway with Jenson Button... ALAN: I'd love to see that. JENNIE: Balmoral with Morgan Freeman... ALAN: I'd love to see that! JENNIE: And North Wales with Amanda Holden!" ALAN:   #ThisTime #AlanPartridge https://t.co/TVc9fsYqLf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My new notification sound  https://t.co/z1WuxH9Zq5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The sound of Alan's knees cracking had me wheezing but this almost brought on an asthma attack  #ThisTime #AlanPartridge https://t.co/Cw5F6PHCum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well this is just the lovely wholesome content we all need just right now. Congratulations everyone!  #ValeLockdown https://t.co/Qq7QgafZaS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaddyFreeland But do you have a whole box dedicated to them?  https://t.co/cBpbdA9ohm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ IT'S ALAN PARTRIDGE DAY  https://t.co/4eaiiHWd3E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Think I'll pass thanks https://t.co/vX3Gfi14fQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you've just mopped the floor and someone with dirty feet walks all over it #DoctorWho https://t.co/wggEteqjBE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whatsonthetapes @neilsmiles @Glis And a slither of in-vision continuity https://t.co/E50Y9eM3jl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neilsmiles @Glis Fingers crossed for ad breaks! https://t.co/EMuTp9ScGk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhoHats More chance of Tom coming round to my house to read the book than me getting a bloody jab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A few months back I spent the best part of an hour on the Internet trying to figure out the exact date I met Tom Baker on his famous autobiography book signing tour of October 1997. Of course it never occurred to me to check the ticket hiding in THE MIDDLE OF THE BLOODY BOOK https://t.co/S149TK6CHV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DimensionsInJen Well spotted! As for taste, well, my (non-Who) DVD collection is largely British comedy so it is pretty broad as you can see.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Changing Face Of Rose Tyler #DoctorWho https://t.co/2lpWBSbYc2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actually I think it's a "Best Of" collection cos I don't think he could legally get away with calling them hits https://t.co/Dge6wr7Iz8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0Vs74fGLLx https://t.co/T1j0uvzFr6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ianiansymes You're not wrong  https://t.co/RbmzohUBu3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ianiansymes @Davetweetedthis Just a bit of culinary fun with mates ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ianiansymes @Davetweetedthis A very rare release - only five copies exist!  https://t.co/NGU6yrhh06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mumoss Look on the bright side, at least nobody has ever repeated Celeb.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>