<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@sonic_1515 Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mrmar80 @GamingGuruBTips Thanks! I just checked and its on sale in the NA store too, but I havent decided yet if I want to grab it now or come back to it later.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips I wont be playing the DLCs for Immortals right now, but will definitely go back and play them soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@b_tben Thank you! I have plans to play the others, so thats great to hear! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips Blair Witch then Immortals Fenyx Rising]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips Thank you!    Yes, I plan to play Last Light and Exodus eventually, but it probably wont be within the next few months.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Platinum 63 - Metro 2033 Redux  Im so glad I decided to give this game another try after quitting it last year. I really enjoyed it!   #PS4 #PlayStation #PlayStation4 #PSshare #PlayStationTrophy #PlatinumTrophy #TrophyHunter #TrophyHunting #Metro2033 #Metro2033Redux https://t.co/JtWeM5x7xs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres some random pictures of my babies, if anyone needs a smile  https://t.co/1R8reQCDd2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TexasJase Thanks! I bought so many super cheap games during that Indie sale on PS in March, and theyve all been a ton of fun!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finished up my first playthrough of Metro 2033 Redux in Survivor mode. Im glad I gave this game a second chance because Im really enjoying it now. I have to do a second playthrough in Spartan mode  farm some kill-related trophies, then Ill be finished  on to my next game! https://t.co/TC0iL9HwGN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thegamerMOON: My *Bank Holiday weekend plans  How about you? https://t.co/nCTjLKMhUF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Helexzura ...told itll get better doesnt usually feel true in the moment. Just remember people love and care about you, and the dark does eventually pass.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Helexzura Im sorry to hear youre dealing with that. Depression has been hitting me hard the past few months so I get it. Nights are the worst, especially when my husbands already gone to bed  I cant sleep  I just feel super alone. I know being....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 No I havent. I actually bought Metro Redux (which includes the definitive versions of both 2033 and Last Light) so I could play them before I played Exodus, but then I never ended up playing any of them.  If I enjoy 2033, Ill eventually play Last Light and Exodus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips You can do it! I think I did it in four or five days. If you follow the psnprofiles trophy guide, you only have to keep replaying the last few chapters for all the different endings. Good luck and have fun!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im going to try to play Metro 2033 again. I started it last summer but only played the first two chapters. Im hoping Ill enjoy it more now I accidentally deleted my save data from before though, so Im having to start over   #PS4 #PlayStation #PSshare #Metro2033Redux https://t.co/LigwGcSc7Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dru8376 I need this but with cats instead of dogs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A few more pics from AER: Memories of Old because its a pretty game   #PS4 #PSshare #AERMemoriesOfOld https://t.co/tGuIqSUqYC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dru8376 Do it! It was fun ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaurbaughJason I really liked it too! I havent played Rime yet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaurbaughJason Thanks! Mooseman was enjoyable. Some of the puzzle solutions were a bit obscure, but it was fun.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cyb3r3ll4 Ugh that sucks, but at least you still got to enjoy it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips Thanks ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Platinum 60 - Drowning  Platinum 61 - The Mooseman  Platinum 62 - AER: Memories of Old  Knocked out several of my Indie games these past few days. All of these were really great games!  #PS4 #PlayStation #PSshare #PlatinumTrophy #TrophyHunter #TrophyHunting #IndieGame https://t.co/ClIY0uJbBy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AER: Memories of Old   Such a beautiful game   #PS4 #PSshare #AERMemoriesOfOld https://t.co/cMiOt18epg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@csmitroyalfan2 Escort missions. Especially when the NPC walks at the slowest possible speed and stops to look around every 5 steps. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AtlasFae I too am a member of the No PS5 club lol. I totally forgot that it was a PS5 exclusive for a few weeks and mistakenly let myself get so excited ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im am  Ignore my typos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im sad I cant play Returnal yet, but Im am so HYPED for all of you who are playing and loving it!! I love seeing all your posts! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 Oh, looks like Abz isnt free anymore, my bad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Adele_gamemissy Badass Congrats on the Plat!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liquid_gaming_ Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 Abz doesnt have a platinum, but it only took 2-3 hours to complete and is definitely worth playing! Plus its free on PlayStation right now I havent played Vampyr yet though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ABZ - 100% Completion   This game was so mesmerizing and relaxing, and I loved interacting with all the ocean life    #PS4 #PlayStation #PSshare #PlayAtHome #FreeGame #ABZU #TrophyHunter #TrophyHunting #IndieGames https://t.co/QFiPfD0wei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 Yes, I earned the Plat for it. Its a fairly easy and short one if you look up a guide to help with finding the collectibles. Best of luck and have fun! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/Sjk1I68vWs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hott1d @Kmkz_666 Congrats!! Do you have a special game in mind for number 300?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fightincowboy Im super jealous! Enjoy!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abz is such a beautiful game!  https://t.co/36bOive0Nk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 I love Aveline! And I thought AC Liberation was a great game - I played it a few months ago and really enjoyed it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IPlayPS5 This game is so great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@croseburns That color ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips Awesome! Enjoy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cyb3r3ll4 Thank you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips I followed the trophy guide on psnprofiles   https://t.co/kKo1wD03qd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elscarface1 Thanks ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Platinum 59 - Virginia  I really liked this story and the animation. The ending was pretty open to interpretation and I enjoyed reading theories about it online after I finished the game.  #PS4 #PlayStation #PSshare #PlatinumTrophy #TrophyHunter #TrophyHunting #Virginia https://t.co/yPzGa2g3FN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The May PS Plus free games should be announced later today. Fingers crossed for a great selection]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PSACCESSFANS @NathanDitum It says Ive already done the survey ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@b_tben Ive got a GameFly subscription for at least a month, so I will probably end up playing Nier Automata soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@b_tben I know!! I keep putting off buying it because I already have so many games I havent played, plus I keep hoping itll be a PS+ free game. And yes, I agree about Godfall (I dont have a PS5, but I wouldnt pay for Godfall if I did) ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 Hes not on Twitter. But trust me, hell figure it out because I absolutely wont be subtle about it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And by dropping hints, I mean saying yo, buy this game  I wont be subtle. I cant wait for this beautiful game!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If nothing changes, Kena: Bridge of Spirits drops 2 days before the 13 year anniversary of when my husband  I started dating (yes, we still celebrate our dating anniversary). If he doesnt buy it for me Ill be so sad, so I guess its time to start dropping hints now https://t.co/KJJtRjDCZv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@b_tben Id love to see Nier Automata but Ive been saying that for months . Maybe a Star Wars game since the free games will drop on May the Fourth? And I feel like Godfall might be a possibility for the PS5 game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TexasJase Thanks! It was a lot of fun ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips Congrats! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mOowkear ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MonkeymafiaG Ive done all of them now. Primal and 4 were the first two I played and I loved them both! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@96Namb @GamingGuruBTips Thats not a bad idea ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer Thanks! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tristam99 It was really great! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BullSharkNL Thanks! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZeroSpace11 Thank you! Not sure whats next, Ill probably play a quick little indie game while I decide what bigger game to play next. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirliftsalot96 Thanks! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hyde323 I want to play that so bad, it looks so fun!! But Im trying to play through some of the games I already own before buying more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fennelyguy Thanks! So do I!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liquid_gaming_ Thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaySeventyNine Congrats!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaySeventyNine I bought it over a year ago but Im too chicken to play it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Platinum 58 - Far Cry 3 Classic Edition   Another great Far Cry game! Im officially finished with Far Cry until 6 comes out.  #PS4 #PSshare #PlayStation #PlatinumTrophy #TrophyHunter #TrophyHunting #FarCry3 #FarCry https://t.co/nVUfvE94Dw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thegamerMOON It was great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liquid_gaming_ Same, it was a lot of fun!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hyde323 Ive already played 4, and all the others. FC3 was my last one! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Almost finished with Far Cry 3. I just have to grab a few more collectibles!  I have no idea what Im playing next though ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer Happy Birthday!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally out of my depression funk and really enjoying Far Cry 3   #PSshare #PS4 #PlayStation #FarCry3 https://t.co/WssqlKCAbk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cyb3r3ll4 Congrats Nina! You deserve it! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itsTunksy I got the same notification and was so happy! That person was vile. https://t.co/ZF3BYnN9ck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThePracticalEsc @lepslair Im sorry for your loss! Its so tough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lepslair Same. One specific animal actually. This pretty girl was my everything. https://t.co/WiXTdhdrwe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer @THQNordic I voted yes just because that would be awesome lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer @THQNordic That would be awesome! Ive earned the plat for the first three (I havent played much of Genesis yet) and would love to play another. Strife def needs his own game!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fennelyguy Im looking forward too. Feels like Ive been waiting forever though lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Phillip91gamer Same honestly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally! https://t.co/9GDyIMovgd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 @SaurbaughJason @GamingGuruBTips Youre right! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaurbaughJason No I dont have a PS5. I kinda feel like I knew it was a ps5 exclusive but maybe forgot? Idk ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yall, I somehow didnt realize Returnal was a PS5 exclusive and thought Id be able to get it on PS4. Now Im heartbroken!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips I stopped just to look up a specific trophy one day and it closed out on me ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GamingGuruBTips Its so annoying!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 Im not very far in - Ive only managed to play a little bit because depression has been kicking my ass these past few days  I think the mission Im about to do it called Mushrooms in the Deep. Im really enjoying it so far!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PlayStation: We stand with the Black community as the verdict has been reached in the George Floyd trial. This is a first step, but the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@imtheirwifenow I think its great that companies, regardless of size, are speaking up about social issues like this. It shows that they care more about whats right and about driving positive change than staying quiet about these issues in hopes of not losing any customers/money.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@u_wot_m8te I think it looks great but I always worry Ill be disappointed when I drop that much money on a game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FinalFae But my backlog... Ive been seeing a lot of hype about it so itll def be added to my wishlist though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@u_wot_m8te I totally blanked on Returnal when I posted mine  Ill actually probably purchase it before I purchase Nier.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleGamer1 I just started this a few days ago and was thinking the exact same thing. Its a beautiful environment.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>