<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@IYKYH1878 Yep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JacobsConnects: Our nuclear laboratories  test rigs in Warington, U.K. are helping @U_Battery  @WECNuclear to develop advanced #nucle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @deneils: Keep reading about the power of @Twitter so looking for as many people as possible to RT  share this true story.   Ive been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug @UpperGwladysBlu Looks promising, hopefully a better ending ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug @UpperGwladysBlu https://t.co/rmmBrCsOJl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @StanCollymore ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lpoolcouncil: As the sun sets on what we hope will be the first of many dances this summer we just wanted to thank the people who helpe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paultrantrainer @theesk @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti On the savoury trail tonight, kung pao chicken https://t.co/uKLzOh9BaM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paultrantrainer @theesk @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti I remember the days when I would have cursed the rhubarb juice for impinging on the delicious custard  Id love that rhubarb now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk Thats brilliant, congratulations both! And more bottles required!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Barry1878 I think every proposed development requires consultancy to review plans in that area for UXB. But its not cheap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JacobsConnects: #OurJacobs team at @NASAKennedy transported the Space Launch System core stage from the barge to the Vehicle Assembly B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnShaw_71 Yes, ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @paultrantrainer @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti @theesk  do you have these recipes written down anywhere (possible book deal incoming)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ALANMYERSMEDIA @PaulClews2 Didnt he have the Bentley then?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @paultrantrainer @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Youre going to need a bigger table ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @paultrantrainer @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti https://t.co/graYlJvSpz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @paultrantrainer @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Two?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@teenytinysuz @theesk @paultrantrainer @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Thank you Suz - It is/was delicious, but very rich!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paultrantrainer @theesk @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Too late Paul ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @paultrantrainer @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Would love to know myself ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @paultrantrainer @teenytinysuz @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Anyone for Sachertorte? https://t.co/6wBKVQjyLN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zsk For the moment, but I expect it will come back in another form later. UEFA/PL need to stamp out the so called big 6 wanting to protect their future cash flow at the expense of wider football, but I dont think they have the appetite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Everton: Statement From The Board.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thechicoazul: BREAKING: Newcastle United to become seventh EPL team to join breakaway for new European Super League. The North East out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul @r4chaelc1878 Saw him in the round at the NEC Lovesexy tour in 1988.  One of my favourite artists, also slightly different - to get to the stage (centre of the venue) he was put in a flight case and pushed to the stage from the dressing room. Sign of the Times album and video are classics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland #BHAEVE becomes #BEHAVE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bluenose69 @Barry1878 https://t.co/ogyxPqU5tR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @teenytinysuz @paultrantrainer @thechicoazul @CBobblers1878 @pbsportswriter @ric_wee @DaveJCritchley @GregOK @toffeedoug @laithwaites @RonaldKoeman @lubanliverpool @Glendronach @Rothiemurchus @MarineAFC @TalkingTheBlue1 @Doritos @MrAncelotti Not elegant, and obviously an after rather than a before, but the fish pie was fantastic! https://t.co/5Y4c9SFwcX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Holdentheblue @Byrdsman75 @Paddy_Boyland I clean broke my tibia and fibula (quite a few years ago now, having managed to collide with a milk float  whilst cycling), plate screwed into tibia, which was later removed once the leg had healed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Holdentheblue @Byrdsman75 @Paddy_Boyland Its the second bone in the lower leg, behind the shin bone (tibia), not as bad as the tibia, or both, breaking.  Tibia will act as support whilst the fibula is mending so hopefully will be the 3-4 youve suggested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Will_Fuzz @LlSTENlNG_PARTY Didnt Julian Cope chase Dave Balfe around Rockfirld with a Stanley knife?  There seems to be an underlying trend if true?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul https://t.co/QcOmbZ7Oio Its a fantastic piece of kit if you appreciate your coffee beyond the Nespresso offering short cut.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TeleFootball @mcgrathmike No.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul Normally find a way for an accident to happen to facilitate the upgrade, but these are such a classic but basic design, all the parts are serviceable.  Damn you Gaggia!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul Ha! No, but when I used to partake, Cohiba Siglo VI were my preferred choice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul Never experienced it, but the reviews Ive read suggest it is better, and the doubt that those reviews have now introduced means I must have it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul Ha! Phillips bought Gaggia and dumbed the Classic down post 2015, however they saw the error of their ways and the revised post 2019 version is now the benchmark, although my better half probably wont understand that justification to pgrade! https://t.co/5UCwXVImno]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul Gaggia Classic (pre 2015), along with an Iberital MC2 bean grinder.  Heaven]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @CazooUK And with much reduced due diligence!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @CazooUK Spacs proving to be very de rigueur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnShaw_71 The leap from when they were in The Tourists to Sweet Dreams was amazing, moving to synths and their stand out videos.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jvblueboy @ALANMYERSMEDIA @PaulClews2 @bt_uk @ALANMYERSMEDIA try using https://t.co/BmIMAKVWsY this should tell you whats available to your property.  Another useful checker is https://t.co/5s4G8SJpN8 which shows what speeds you should get.  The last open is provided by OpenReach, despite the BT retail branding.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk @win_n10 @rmcfadzean @jsrailton Perfect!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ALANMYERSMEDIA @PaulClews2 @bt_uk I dont think they can do that - OpenReach invest the money to connect the property to their network, they then have to offer access to all the suppliers as above not just BT retail; it may be that other suppliers have not yet got their act together.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ALANMYERSMEDIA @PaulClews2 @bt_uk This intrigues me - what makes you think that? OpenReach provide the network that is available to multiple suppliers to use including not just BT retail but others such as Zen (see https://t.co/Vr3y4cirzK for the full list]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ALANMYERSMEDIA @PaulClews2 @bt_uk Have avoided BT retail for the last 20 years.  Now with Zen - cant fault them, UK based, excellent customer service.  You'd still have to deal with OpenReach with the install, which may still be an issue from what I can see?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BallysBoots John Deacon of Queen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug So many on Twitter posting this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug Over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zsk Grew up in Portsmouth, Mum lives in Hilsea.  Spent a lot of time in Southsea, Grandfather had a tailors and ladies outfitters on Osbourne Road]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mainlyoasis Why no  credit? Jill Furmanovsky?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StuartHumphryes Here you go: https://t.co/wwGz1fjwQd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Have they specified the length of the extension required?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Everton @CazooUK Got it! https://t.co/uA2NfPqN2I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug @theesk @geoff4jones @DoEfc I think thats a minimum period TD, not a maximum.  An aside - Jenrick called in the Cumbria coal mine proposal this week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Because it will be PRS licence free, you have to pay a fee to use licensed music ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland @thechicoazul @_lauraaj96 @GreethamKyle @DefoNotAda @MeatballMc1 You broke the rule!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland @thechicoazul @MattJFootball @TheBlueRoomEFC @FanzoneMicky @RoperCarl @bencrawford94 No reference to VAT law allowed please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scousescene: Peaky Blinders Season 6 filming in #Liverpool.  https://t.co/JgrKcIRyUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @benfenton: If I were a bankable TV presenter who was about to join a controversial new TV news service, I might make a big to-do on my]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheDesKelly @istevejansen When two worlds collide, this is quite unworldly.  Mick Karn was immense, repeated with his work with Gary Numan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mr_Dave_Haslam Roy Wood, Ringo Starr, Lulu, Mick Robson, Bianca Jagger (?)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Vertigo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karengillan Not new, but different https://t.co/gNO2HPGB81]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@empiresend Thanks Ian!  That was brilliant!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@empiresend Amazing track!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeminiRick @LlSTENlNG_PARTY @empiresend https://t.co/HuDkHdz8iX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeminiRick @LlSTENlNG_PARTY @empiresend Nicholls?, yes it is!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LlSTENlNG_PARTY @empiresend Parkgate, Wirral]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Azzurri1878 Hinchcliffe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug Another 3 to come ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug This tweet coming back to haunt ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug Same here, but too many games where weve clung on and either drawn or lost it.  I just hope we get to spank WBA on Thursday.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffeedoug Weve been here before ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JacobsConnects: #DYK we have reactors capable of safely handling materials that are 150 million degrees Fahrenheit (that is, 10X hotter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thetoffees_com: #OTD in 1980: William Ralph 'Dixie Dean' sadly passed away.   433 games  383 goals  Most goals in a single season (6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@almannarino @ThePopBreak @nilerodgers and @CHICorg at @glastonbury 2017 https://t.co/vajvUuTMg1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OfficialOMD Grew up in Portsmouth, cutting my teeth on AM, became a big fan, and went on to look at your back catalogue - and staggered that someone would write about an oil refinery. Came to the Liverpool  in 86 to study, have lived on the Wirral for 26 years and now fully appreciate why!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OfficialOMD Peter Saville - was this album originally released on Factory, or was it after that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thechicoazul @grandoldteam @tomchitty Great piece but missing a trolling opportunity regarding the cruise terminal , banter that is now probably lost in the mists of time and relevance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FrankOnTheRadio Gloves]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland @LucasDigne Another bottle @theesk !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JacobsConnects: Jacobs was selected by @NDAgovuk for the Sort and Seg innovation competition. We're bringing artificial intelligence,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk A momentous number of days, with hopefully more like it to follow.  Not sure how the relevant Government department announce it, but I have added them to the Foreign office travel advice email alerts!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk One of a number? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IYKYH1878 As if by magic... https://t.co/0gPLbphShY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just added Planning Committee to Everton on #Vimeo: https://t.co/gBQemeZmEh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LiamThorpECHO Excellent - thanks Liam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LiamThorpECHO are you covering the planning committees deliberations of the Goodison Park application as well as the Bramley Moore application?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Everton: APPROVED: A detailed planning application for a new 52,888 capacity stadium at Bramley-Moore Dock has been approved by Liverpo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Everton: Liverpool City Council's planning committee unanimously approve our application for a new stadium at Bramley-Moore Dock.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cotters84 @theesk https://t.co/ktfVLeTBbx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cotters84 @theesk Although I believe the person shown as Joe Dunne is actually Steve Radford (a rugby supporter...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cotters84 @theesk He later recovered his position, by confirming he objected to the Stanley Park Development. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DowntownFrank: The @Everton Bradley Moore Dock development is up for planning permission today. Its much more than a stadium. Its a ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MelaniePrentic2 @goal Including 7 hat tricks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@prenno Wheres @thechicoazul when you need him ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@benrathe To how many decimal places ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>