<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/pLABAoUsyi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ianbrown Some of the best tracks, ever!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andy798001 @AustralisPiper @MaidelK @Casper101Susie @4Real75215148 @PrismPrime @GOPimpIosion @SlayckPhoenix @CrashDa67833245 @flatearth_truth @mhanno76 @gordosgarage66 @HenryLindeman9 @TheGamingGround @nasty1_not @JonAnon15 @ScottyWtfReally @William95147321 @SOVERIEIGN_ONE @coyotedirty @GeorgePitner @RuffusMD @overit_miss @ElainaMusk @Worried_Canuck @Mocha63825993 @AdrianoMazzola @agvBruceAdams @axterixo @Americascallin1 @CouldYouSeeIt @CanAditude @d_essere @DickPower369 @Dhread @333DESPIERTA @DariusVolket @DeadpoolDzviti1 @EelcoBB @_FEtruth_ I wouldn't waste your time with these people buddy. They're lost souls set out to cause frustration in people.   We know the truth  that we've been deceived about our home. They're on the wrong side  Earth is demonstrably a level plane. No amount of words/pics will change that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DarrenPlymouth: Out canvassing and handed another flyer for a missing dog called Henry, disappeared in central park, yesterday (Friday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoriartyProfJ3 Still the extreme ones. On the streets too. In shops though it is still mask majority by a huge amount in south Devon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoriartyProfJ3 My friend  I went to a crystal shop earlier. The woman serving put her mask on in a panicky rush  said where's your masks. We said 'exempt', then got told her policy is only 1 unmasked in the shop at a time.  We left leaving words of truth. They've no faith in their stones ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock When you get the knock on the front door, go to prison.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Human rights activist Gurcharan Singh talking about what's happening in India.  https://t.co/FYrYKhJ02c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @noreward_norisk: There is a WAR going on that many cant see. Our children, freedoms, rights, elderly and infirm are ALL under attack.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock No thanks you psycho fooker. Keep your poison.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a  We live in a movie. https://t.co/TAir8bUeez]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Bodies in the street in India, is the new bodies in the street in Wuhan.  It is being used, as it was 14 months ago, to ter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmmaUK  some people are literally so moronic it is painful to witness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Those looked just like bubbles, in space? How can this be? Unlike the original ISS, I wonder if this time there will be video recordings in HD of its construction in 'space'? You'd think NASA would have video of the ISS being put together being such an engineering marvel but no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/XpTFslQA3R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Literally physical contact between them with no gloves  then to round off the pantomime show a little elbow bump at the end, for safety. What a farce!  These clowns think we're all stupid. Well @MattHancock  JVT, that was probably just a saline shot. You guys are psycho liars!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: The average person doesn't know what Event 201 is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenHarkness21: Do any of my lovely twitter friends have reliable info on how long the jibbed up shed for once they've had their trial]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NASAEarth The physics of water demonstrates that you cannot have convexity on its surface  it cannot cling to the exterior of spinning objects. It needs to be contained as well. The ocean floors have 50% flat areas called the Abyssal plains. Water lays flat, Earth is 71% water = No globe!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[store bans the VACCINATED https://t.co/Gz8TKhzpLX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nurses are scared to speak out, but this is an exception. https://t.co/h9jxwtJWQM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whatever your thoughts, just listen to what she is saying. This is getting serious! https://t.co/jsFcgSwW58]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews I wonder if the morons still wearing masks (that do zero to protect you) not omitting as much CO (as they're breathing in their own waste) is effecting the atmosphere? Plants/trees convert CO into O so there must be a cause  effect going on  Watch cv19 become climate change]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tompeck He is such a nobhead!   Politics is even more of a pantomime show to entertain the masses. What a farce this country  world have become.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neiltyson @thedaveygshow You're a clown Neil. Speak to Eric  let's settle this once  for all.  You won't because he will destroy you  the official lie narrative.  You're nothing but an actor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neiltyson Two actors in the photo. Mike didn't go anywhere but RIP  Look at the press conference upon their 'return from the moon'. They all act/look like they've done something heinous, which they did. They lied to the world.  Watch this for the truth. NASA lie!  https://t.co/gaiq3FK9ZX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @karma44921039: Msm caught lying again https://t.co/lwJv43aPiA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Sounds like a depopulation agenda is being carried out   If you've never heard of the Georgia Guidestones then look them up. Literally carved in stone - Maintain humanity at a population of 500,000,000 in harmony with nature ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wakethesheepnow: A Mothers cry  Part 1 https://t.co/dw16rORDOu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're waiting for permission to live freely then you were never free in the 1st place    https://t.co/spvcNFY24z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews They need to clash over this tyrannical/fascist state we now find ourselves in. It'll get worse unless we say no!  Oh wait, they won't b/c it's all a charade. The WEF's Great Reset rolls on whilst these idiots argue about the decoration of a property.  This country is finished!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Keir_Starmer A reminder for you-  1. Go to the nearest mirror. 2. Repeat the above statements. 3. Absorb what you just said to yourself  act upon it.  You/Labour are a useless opposition  are just acting out in this pantomime of a shit show government we have in the UK.  Resist this tyranny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sdaws5MUFC: Whoops https://t.co/B43Wda2miy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ryzoncity @NASA @Space_Station @Astro_illini I'll let you into a not so secret. The ISS is BS. NASA are deceiving humanity. Look up the Antarctic treaty. All nations work together on that and 'space', yet go to war for us. It's all for show.  That treaty  NASA were formed in the late 50s. To hide our true world. Look it up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DarrenPlymouth Wow! I've also seen they're using stock images from a chemical leak accident that happened sometime ago  passing it off as now.  This psychological manipulation needs exposing. The media is the main driver behind this so called 'pandemic'   Criminal behaviour.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DarrenPlymouth: Listen to this lady about India.  People aren't dying, they are just all locked down, a bit like the UK for the last 13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenHarkness21  What a loser!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KwameA007 Dunno which prick is this biggest outta all of this malarkey I see before my eyes!   The jab needle, the needle for the ink or perhaps the recipient? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Hmmmm pushing the ol' experimental jab quite aggressively ain't ya? What have 'they' offered you in return?  When the elite cabal have finished with you they will toss you aside, so less brown nosing your superiors ya twisted psycho ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: All the world's a stage. https://t.co/wd9CvuXEAp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Why 42 yr olds in particular Matt?  I bet you are standing right next to your phone ya creepy mofo.  Your vial will be one of the 'special saline ones' I bet, although you're such a psycho you'll probably want to take part in this experiment on humanity.  May god help us all ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NegDupree It's insane ain't it?! The world is indeed a stage.  You could show this blatant deception to many people  yet they would still believe the official narrative.  Their brainwashing/mind control is strong   Slowly more people are waking up though, so we have that going for us ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NegDupree: It is just a constant barrage of complete and utter bullshit. This is the kind of thing we have been trying to raise awarene]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock @drharshvardhan Matt, they have a population of almost 1.4 billion people. 2.5k deaths is literally a 0.0002% fatality rate.  Comparing them to the UK is asinine.  You're being deceived people. There is no medical pandemic. The WEF's Great Reset is what is happening under the guise of a virus ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Wonderful.  https://t.co/s68dWHVPiu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shiiiiiiiiit, six people!   It's outta control like a plague  Shutdown everything  people go back into your houses  don't go outside or we're all gonna die!   People sadly die every day. Get over it bedwetters  https://t.co/NZoIxVYmKN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neiltyson More fantasy drivel from Neil. Pointless 'science' referring to a Hollywood movie   How about you address some real science Neil? You're evading this topic because you know that you will be humiliated and the truth regarding our world will be exposed!  https://t.co/3KkIR5OSEq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['They' treat people who watch TV as non-thinking fools. 'They' usually get away with it. Great catch from a person who can see their deceptions.  Critically think  https://t.co/zE3o0X0au7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday  Earth is not a spinning globe   Lying for the Globe https://t.co/plyYKb07xL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DickPower369: What did he just say..? He's correct but... ... https://t.co/gJCWcu6VfV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sueperkins You're an idiot Sue. You really need to stop watching so much TV, especially the news ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pritipatel I wish a speedy trial date for you  your other criminal cabal in No.10  I saw the footage. The police were the instigators. They are nothing but violent thugs.  A peaceful protest until your goons went in for their photo ops for the media/propaganda  You're a vile human being]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenHarkness21 Wow! Yet people will still line up to receive the jab! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@voice_stolen Wow! Yet people still want to be jabbed? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Sky news - The fire had covid  spread it to all the inhabitants who burnt to death.  Conclusion = Covid causes fires which lead to death.  Coroner's report = Everyone died of covid.  Sky news = Government propaganda  fear spreader ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/w1rlYzG8Wc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HelenHarkness21: Our corrupt MSM are not reporting the anti lockdown march from yesterday, I never imagined any had the backbone to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chunkymark It's all about distraction  propaganda! Adult comics aka newspapers are there to bolster the brainwashing people receive via the TV.  You still haven't realised this yet?  Not even a mention of the mass protest yesterday for our freedoms  This pandemic is planned. Event 201 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HedleyLamarr20 @Reptoid_Hunter According to a BBC 'reporter' it was 5 - 10K people at best.   Okay!  BBC news is fake news ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Nurses protest with the people.  They tell us they are too afraid to speak up. #londonprotest #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mwendling You're BBC, therefore irrelevant  misreported disinformation, end of statement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews You guys reported similar BS last year regarding Mexico remember? .....Black smoke billows from the crematorium all day  all night as they struggle to cope....  Well that turned out to be absolute lies! We see how your propaganda works. Repeat a lie often enough until believed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke:  https://t.co/kkoJir14pS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anti Lockdown Protest - London https://t.co/VD25DRwDg4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Civic duty. Remove the propaganda  https://t.co/jmscV6797q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Better  https://t.co/newS3KsJ8M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/3k7U1nPek1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As crazy it is may sound, I think he is right   Don't be easily deceived when the time comes. Look up project Bluebeam  you'll see the tech exists   Get ready for project Bluebeam - fake Alien Invasion https://t.co/gttPR1hjMG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonahmiller_42 @AstroJordy @SpaceX @Space_Station I didn't say anything funny. This is the end of our interaction.   You're suffering with cognitive dissonance. I reacted the same when I 1st discovered the earth is not a spinning globe flying through space.  Research it  if honest with yourself you'll see.  Have a nice life! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/FdmA2nPeD4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonahmiller_42 @AstroJordy @SpaceX @Space_Station To hide our true reality  that we live on a created level plane.  There could well be more land/people in 'outer space', as in laterally in the outer land beyond Antarctica that is the shoreline the encircles us, containing the ocean(s).   Watch this   https://t.co/B4wU6fQ0Rt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonahmiller_42 @AstroJordy @SpaceX @Space_Station Nobody is a passenger. They fly empty  even if they did occasionally do fly people onboard then the speeds they claim they travel are ridiculous. Mach 23 = 17,000 mph! Okay!  No human could withstand 1/4 of that!  Critically think about it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonahmiller_42 @AstroJordy @SpaceX @Space_Station Sure, it's basically a fancy missile that does exist  does take off, but then it arcs across the sky until it goes out of view (due to how our eyes work)  then it drops down into an area of ocean that is out of view. If there's a witness they disappear. Bermuda triangle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpaceX @Space_Station Have an open mind  watch this, then you will soon see their deceptions.  I faithfully believed what I was taught without critically thinking  investigating their claims.  When you do look into their claims you soon see they're unfounded  https://t.co/fxTVFuremF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LEVEL (2021) - (PG VERSION) https://t.co/N7ouQiwYAD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpaceX @Space_Station Let's see HD video of them docking together from multiple perspectives. Or even better, get the Hubble telescope to photograph the occasion.  You won't because you can't. Liars always get caught out.  Critically think people! They are lying to us. This is the biggest lie of all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AstroJordy @SpaceX @Space_Station Could easily be photographed/filmed in a hangar anywhere. Probably a model  CGI.  Critically think and you will see their lies. NASA  Space X ( all space agencies) are deceiving you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpaceX @Space_Station Cool model and/or CGI   We know you deceive the masses   Wernher Von Braun, Psalms 19:1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Unlocked_UK_: Dr John Lee Unlocked  Covid is the cure worse than the disease? Coming Saturday 1st May https://t.co/josAI5s1nI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @humanvibration: The only movement is in our minds.   https://t.co/wh8NDy8pso]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: Dr. Bhakdi on #masking children: Were going to take people to court. A crime against humanity... https://t.co/QyCdBhNTuX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: Mike Yeadon is absolutely correct here. And shame on those (especially those getting paid handsomely to attack legitimate criti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: HUGE: 'Request for Investigation' of the UK Government and its advisers, for genocide, crimes against humanity and breache]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealCarlVernon Adults everywhere who condone this should be totally ashamed of themselves.  Something very sinister seems to be happening. It's happened before. Look up 'orphan trains' around the late 1800s. Masses of children appear with few adults. CV seems to effect old  sick, no kids ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DaveHil17430215 @SkyNews The sun is shining  people are slowly waking up. Joke all you want, the earth is a level plane  there is a not so secret cabal trying to enslave humanity  turn us into commodities. Whether you can comprehend that is our true reality or not doesn't bother me. I know the truth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews  your fear propaganda no longer works, give it up!  The masses are waking up to the deceptions being played on us.  Yesterday 'scientists' reckoned there were 55 cases of this 'Indian variant'. What a load of hogwash!  CV19 is seasonal like the flu, which has vanished ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neiltyson Typical Neil Tyson garbage as per usual   Fantastical numbers  unfathomable distances to distant 'planets'  'stars'.  These numbers are intended to make a person seem dumb  unable to comprehend.  Neil's an actor  spreads false info claiming earth is a globe. He dodges facts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews What risk of spreading CONVID in bars?  Isn't it true that there's no correlation between the spread  hospitality venues?  So what's this rubbish about robot bar tenders?   You're a terrible news broadcasting organisation. Propaganda  misinformation are your specialities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nurse Warns - Stay Away from Vaxxed People https://t.co/CeDHrYvodc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenHarkness21 Signed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Resist now or forever regret not speaking out!   Contact your local MPs. Tell them you do not want these changes.   Your silence is tacit consent.  Time to use your god given voice  brain  https://t.co/3auqM5wziI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Who listens to a war criminal?   Especially one that is rocking a mullet. Oi, Anthony, the barbers are open for haircuts ya twat!  Go  crawl back under the rock you deserve to be squashed beneath. You're a criminal.  There is no risk to covid to 99% of us. You're lying again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: A recent interview with Dr Mike Yeadon. Please make sure you listen to a variety of voices and opinions on new and old media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flight PERTH to Los Angeles over ALASKA? Only on a F.L.A.T - E.A.R.T.H   Earth is a level plane. Just look for yourself  think.  https://t.co/hBpUZGrhhx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic You mean on the plane right?   You really should chat to David Weiss at DITRH about our true reality. You're a good guy. Implying we live on a planet is making you be disingenuous  you're smarter than that  you deserve the truth.   What are your thoughts @thefepodcast ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/kAS8wBPSFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chunkymark  You're clueless to what is really going on. That pub landlord speaks for millions of us.   Labour are finished. They're so useless  embarrassing.  Brilliant review.......of nothing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomhfh Tom, do you have a eyes that can see  a functioning brain? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaL16: https://t.co/ILykXAsgYF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ When the cash goes so does our will to pay bills.  will automatically be taken from your account with no way to stop it.   A slippery slope into a social credit system like in China  https://t.co/eCjWDv6zgB]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>