<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[I had my first two orders the other day! #smallbusinessowner https://t.co/6LBDa3vxI0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! This is your reminder to take time to relax and reflect when you can ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had a great day painting in store at @Hobbycraft_CRO to raise money for Together For Short Lives!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hobbycraft_CRO: Almost there! #hobbycraft #tfsl #Croydon https://t.co/fkETedsPUv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I made my first two sales today!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[** New Arrivals: The 'Possibility' Collection ** https://t.co/v9qF09Nrsl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Love the spoons analogy! Hope you feel better soon!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LauraPAuthor Yes! 24.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update: I forgot to check if my work trousers fit me anymore and I've had to rearrange my organs to get these bad boys to zip up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How am I supposed to sleep knowing I have to get up for work at 5am?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@officialhambly How is everything you make so beautiful?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A sneak peak! https://t.co/lvJC4ET80q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GUYS! A package I ordered that was supposed to come on Monday just arrived! I'm so excited to show you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@banabbie Right!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have so many IDEAS! And not enough time to do them!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you need a sign to be confident in your ideas... this is it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A #commission that I'm working on! Very much a #workinprogress but you can see the vision! https://t.co/1bqQS2Y2K0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same https://t.co/BozFqFYIep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FOWfilms: If you have 12 bad cops and 1300 good cops, but those 1300 good cops dont turn in the 12 bad cops, you have 1312 bad cops]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me: God I'm so stressed Also me: *plays Under Pressure and sips on my third coffee while staring out the window* ALSO me: Why do I not feel better]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@calm_scents My family does hellofresh and its deffo worth it! They give you everything you need, and you end up having more variety in what you eat. Plus we almost always manage to find a discount code!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@banabbie I did this EXACT thing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cilusse: We landed on MARS! Again!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RachelKiki_: BC stands for Before Coronavirus now. Sorry Jesus take a hike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My #ValentinesDay cake! https://t.co/qJqSElF4aQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I ran out of ~normal~ places to stick the balloons and I guarantee nobody in my house is gonna find this funnier than I do https://t.co/SPMIwV6pjQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My FYP on tiktok has taken a swift nose dive into cleantok and I'm not even mad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secretly blowing up balloons for my grandads birthday (gonna hang them up once he goes to bed) https://t.co/7hwzRUQJkx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena That's such a cute idea! Glad you're making again!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've just started listening to @matthaig1 's 'The Midnight Library' on Audible and I'm already absolutely hooked!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spent all day working on my website and I'm so excited to eventually show you guys!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@akirarmsarms Congratulations! Just gonna drop my friends GoFundMe here incase anyone is able to help! https://t.co/FLlHiCNBdB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its snowing!! I love the snow ... the whole world just seems quieter doesnt it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impulsively shaved some of my hair off and I am here for it https://t.co/Kp4PUrhKth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've made a little new years resolution to read at least one book a month, this was my first one! Definitely worth a read!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This book had the AUDACITY to break my heart like 5 times in a row https://t.co/psyjdHJpV3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Yaaay!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My therapist: "I searched high and low for the belief system that would guide my work. I read all the greats, I researched them ALL ... but then, yknow who really said it best? Thor."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My third tiktok ever has over 600 views and over 200 likes OUT OF NOWHERE  I know numbers aren't everything but DAMN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cilusse Yeah  that's the point]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cilusse I've just tried this, which has helped a little, now it's only the blue parts which are blue ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do the pictures I've taken look great on my phone and laptop but look SO BLUE on my computer and why cant I seem to fix it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm submitting one of my paintings to a competition today  keep your fingers and toes crossed for me ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its snowing!  https://t.co/S0kvHsFiOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I will be painting all day  and still might not finish it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Okay so, I've been trying to get this painting ready for a competition entry and it's due tomorrow and I'm not finished  Someone send help]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's cool I think I've fixed it and it's gonna be great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've been struggling with this painting for a couple of weeks now and I've just realised that I am the source of all my problems]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Being in a lockdown in the winter is sucking so much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JVNCRO: To own a piece of art from your favorite artist WHILE theyre still breathing is really an opportunity you shouldnt miss out on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someones left some kind of pretzels shaped dough in the bathroom cupboard?  am I being pranked https://t.co/ty3vWfM03E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alice_Wilder: a lot of teenagers on tiktok are noting that congresspeople, after fearing for their lives and sheltering in place, now k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lunarlana_ 3 over here ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi! I started doing TikTok! If you're interested at all ... #TikTok https://t.co/dOcFusBeEj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last night I added in lots of the darker blues and purples to this painting! Still a massive #WIP ... https://t.co/UCPcfTaYWp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy frickin new years to every single one of you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena It really is, but I'd wager that they didn't read it ... hope you're doing alright Jess ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena It's pure narcissism fuelled by theories about the instagram algorithm, and shameless copy and pasting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Omg its SO EMBARRASSING that people dont even CARE what they're commenting on, selfish, arrogant and self absorbed nobodies so hell bent on getting some sweet sweet attention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[il-Milied it-tajjeb and Merry Christmas to you all ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Looks gorgeous!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Merry christmas! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kinda glad the shops are shut because I cannot go and buy everyone one extra panic present on christmas eve this year, but also I CAN'T go out and buy everyone one extra panic present on christmas eve this year ... yknow?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me every Christmas: IM GOING TO MAKE/CUSTOMISE MOST OF THE PRESENTS THIS YEAR Also me: WHY IS THIS TAKING SO LONG Also me: HAVE I BOUGHT ENOUGH GIFTS Also me: THESE TWO PEOPLE HAVE DIFFERENT AMOUNTS OF CUSTOMS OMG ARE THEY GONNA THINK I HATE THEM Also me: MOREEEEEEE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@banabbie  looks great Abbie!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreezyCreates Me and five other people wrote a collection of short stories that was published on Amazon on Monday  Still can't quite believe we WROTE A BOOK OMG!!  https://t.co/b3xkZk4GLK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's here! Raccoons Are Hard To Come By is now available on Amazon! https://t.co/jpNNJxkutx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's so nearly here! https://t.co/CZMkF1ff9m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've been working on this since March with @pindrop_pro , and it's been overwhelming and emotional and I've LOVED every minute of it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IT'S HAPPENING! ON MONDAY!  https://t.co/s0noEYjtwJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena I'm so sorry jess ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Say what you want about 2020 but this year has made me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was getting ready for my first ever zoom meeting for my new art job  feeling SO nervous. Finally sat down for the call, clicked the link, and realised that the meeting is next week :) :) not this week :) :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WORK IN PROGRESS! https://t.co/kaE1r6KJIj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My favourite hobby is reading poorly translated instructions really seriously]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A finished floral piece! https://t.co/xj7Fox68o3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I WAS TODAY YEARS OLD WHEN I LEARNED THAT COLOURING PAGES ARE NOT IN FACT COLOUR IN PAGES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Be kind to yourself today  https://t.co/T6Rwa5nuAR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woke up to the first flare up of my eczema I've had in three years  I am U N C O M F O R T A B L E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Supporting local and independent businesses during hard times makes the treats taste better, just saying ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had a nice little walk with my grandma and stopped off at a cute little Italian place for a takeaway hot chocolate and a cannoli ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going outside for the first time in 3 weeks ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mcapriglioneart: how to make an artist happy: https://t.co/3Fe2uW87FZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chilling with my painting  https://t.co/zU7hccM11Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Honestly? Magical.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lazerpussy @MeagMonroe Omg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feeling all mushy  love my life ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We wrote a BOOK! It's been in the works since April and I'm so excited I can finally talk about it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pindrop_pro: Our Raccoons have come to life!  In the form of 9 short stories and poems, in this new book... soon to be available on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BIG news coming soon! https://t.co/0h4ikBTiz1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @purelysage: PSA: Twitter is killing engagement for small businesses and that really sucks! Your guys support means more than ever to us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good afternoon! It's an admin kind of day today! https://t.co/Z9FcLssTOE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My household is isolating because one of us has tested postivite for covid and grandad just said "it's dress down fortnight" ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good evening! How's everyone doing today? https://t.co/s6qmGtcMXx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm absolutely buzzing today and I don't know why  I'm not complaining I swear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pindrop_pro I do! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@inVINCEable_NT I have a list on post it's that goes from my desk almost to my ceiling of ideas  I'm slowly crossing them off!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have so many ideas for projects etc that it's almost impossible to make them all happen! Hmmmph]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@byjessicaelena Aww, I hope your doctor can help you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @weiapparel: it costs $0 to retweet an artist https://t.co/xvrNDH1QUe]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>