<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@hazelma33259388 @_GeoffBadger_ ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Train beers for a Bank Holiday..... https://t.co/O6VGPsZwGx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_GeoffBadger_ Interesting sauce arrangement... https://t.co/eNAQ4ievNQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0_politics2 Oh God,  any women?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0_politics2 Where do you live? Rotherham?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0_politics2 She was fucking mustard....which adds to the bad gf great shag argument]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Right, I have 16.20 credit, do I just get them ordered and downed or ask for other stuff https://t.co/UDrl2AllPZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bjas1720 Sharing my bonus penis... https://t.co/r5UCRLUAQg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you are sat outside the pub  and you hear some girl say she can't find a boyfriend. Then you hear her basically tell her best friend how her bf is the most perfect bf ever....spicy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SizzleStevie Hahaha I'm missing all this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boredofmyhouse Remembered....just in time too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0_politics2 Because you are female?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0_politics2 A top quality hoover will take care of that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@0_politics2 Got one, how's your proper beard coming along lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melindiscott A few pints for me and I'm happy with them having the rest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melindiscott I do a lot wrong so hopefully it makes up for some of it lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You get a bonus at work  ppl you love benefit, nothing better than that. Daughter has intensive driving course, youngest has a paddleboard  money for big shopping day. Wife has a special present 4 her 40th, this is stuff I'd never be able to afford normally. May birthdays ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@argentumandcoin We had an hour of showers but otherwise, so nice and warm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bang! https://t.co/XXmxGk0tQH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CynicLiterate Point still stands]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now Young Girl by Gary Puckett and the Union Gap... https://t.co/FmTVIZ7xkX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Karl_Downey Sure I've seen this one on PornHub....  "Ready for your second injection darling?"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hevans1111 Jesus Christ! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@butterfly_fee Following here rather than unfollowing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Trailer_Swift69: Put gays on lockdown. Since you're such a fan of them. Make them have HIV Status passports. See how far this shit can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahDixon18 110%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahDixon18 I agree with the roaring 20s comparison wholeheartedly...seeing that nightclub in Liverpool on Friday, it just made me think people will relish having these freedoms back and will make the most of them. I also think this means they'll never let them go again without a fight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the culture war between the risk averse COVID Puritans and the Free Spirited who just want to sing, dance, drink and live life to the full.....because it's coming....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back to normal they said..... https://t.co/5Tj5erG9n6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mckeon_siobhan She even said she prefers it with me so it must be bad because I cram 8 pints into 2 hours lolol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The wife has gone on a Bottomless Brunch with a mate and the mate is drinking tea....not Long Island Iced Tea....PG Tips Tea! What a fucking waste! https://t.co/vPLkeNoaJG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @guardian I won't wear a mask but I'll put my fingers in my ears to stop this bullshit invading my head space...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonnachuO @KingstonXR If we all sat in a road all day, nothing would get done Ronan. I'm too busy earning the money that feeds my kids I'm afraid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trailer_Swift69 I wonder if Harry Cole is sitting somewhere now thinking "Admit it, you all thought I lost out when she left me..." https://t.co/WuyfQHjUmy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Maxaretunit Hahahaha.....I agree....it doesn't feel like my home city anymore...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doing overtime in my living room whilst sofa dancing to Boney M.....don't you dare say men can't multitask!  #DaddyCool https://t.co/9QVqWhxitn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gnash7 @heather_venter @melindiscott Oh come on, the Cybermen had a personality....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonnachuO @KingstonXR Intelligent and considerate people wouldn't sit in the road]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ....watching Number 2's of the 80's and Cliff Richards 'Daddy's Home' has come on..... https://t.co/ZTp7yREEQU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KulganofCrydee @dazdrewett @Iromg I agree...she'd make a better leader than the ponce currently in situ though....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sally64138643 That only buys you a boxroom in Chiswick lolol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IronWorks1990 How cold does he look....you are probably more likely to die of pneumonia* than COVID from a couple of pints in a beer garden lol  * - We'll mark it as COVID anyway]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna @GMB Never trust the advice of a middle aged man in skinny jeans and a roll neck https://t.co/uKgbAouqSp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet How awful that the murder of a black man by another black man is seen as normal and by many almost excused....I've always said,  you want true equality and justice, well it's a two way street.  Start holding your communities to the same standards you demand from the authorities]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Femi_Sorry They have a Space Program Femi. So watch out for an Indian rocket exploring the space between your ears some day soon.... https://t.co/Q2w1nWZZqq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SizzleStevie This is what made me laugh about the ESL, the product is getting worse  is less enjoyable because of their tinkering with rules and I actually think if fans weren't so tribal about their clubs, they'd bin it off. However, it's the billions of views in Asia they're worried about]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lisa Nandy would have been a better option for Labour leader.....I don't agree with a lot of what she says but she says it with conviction, no spin or bullshit  she could cut through better than a weak as piss, Islingtonian ponce wearing boxing gloves]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SizzleStevie I actually don't really enjoy football if it's not West Ham...I'm much more of a rugby person...if West Ham ceased to exist, I'd bin the whole sport off lolol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RitaPanahi: You dont have to be a white supremacist, you can be better.   Powerful message to the race-baiting Left who engage in th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Little_G2: Who wore them best ? https://t.co/1Imk0CHZmK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melindiscott Haha, very true....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melindiscott He looks as convincing here as he did on the punch bag.... https://t.co/hS2Bb1wRd2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews This will be interesting....we are about to witness the trans lobby devouring one of their own I reckon....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pub_politics: Who wins? Vs  RT for Patel   Like for Rayner https://t.co/VMqYZOB2Kb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cageyeff1 "Sorry, it was pints I ordered..."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesDelingpole @JamesMelville I hate snitch culture....but if those advocating it get hoist by their own petard....then I'll allow it on that occasion....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LORDGARY84 At least you know the sex is good....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonNantwich Reminds me of being a teenager....it was fucking everywhere lolol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidashleywall @YcmiYcmiu @KingstonXR "Of course everyone will be behind us....London is diverse, progressive and undoubtedly ready for a new green agenda!!"  Ten minutes later.... https://t.co/2zs0tAOMte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patsy_murrell @Holly_6000 I was under the impression that a lot of this went via DM as well which obviously can't be challenged. This isn't me being a pain in the arse so please don't take it the wrong way....I'm also fully aware that my perspective isn't going to be the same etc etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patsy_murrell @Holly_6000 Hey Patsy, can you find me an example of someone saying something that is going unchallenged?? Not being flippant here but I see a lot of football posts  to see a post which is outwardly racist is quite rare from my perspective  when it does happen, it generally gets jumped on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VictoryDay_Hope: According to Sky News, MORE than 9 in 10 people aged 45 and over have been jabbed. Lets run a poll here for a couple]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...and another one...  The Labour Party.... https://t.co/Yh6uUFRI8H https://t.co/wZty3xWL9x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YcmiYcmiu @KingstonXR They'll never target Canning Town again haha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingstonXR So....if the engines of the cars being held up are kept running whilst stationary....how do this help the environment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BurnsideNotTosh @Keir_Starmer @VulcanABC @Keithhunter50 @EmmaHardyMP @DianaJohnsonMP https://t.co/7Jivndzl6m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TomosBombadil @UKLabour ...and they keep on with the posts because they literally have nothing else....the NHS and Boris Home Furnishings....that's it....  They're fucked, they've lost the working classes and I truly hope one day they'll lose ethnic minorities too....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UKLabour How many years have you been parroting this nonsense and how often have you won elections.....that's without the fact that this is just a local election Can I suggest you come up with something other than this lazy bullshit. At least Magic Grandpa was offering broadband ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IronWorks1990 So many of the restrictions target alcohol it's hard not to be suspicious. NZ wants to cigarettes going forward for anyone born after 2004 as well....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1BJDJ @ToolstationUK It appears to be a station for tools alright...would he do that to a big bloke?  Would he fuck....the worst of humanity. "Most people I ask just apologise"....why don't you stop asking then you misogynistic prick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@daresh_j @lpoolcouncil @CIRCUSmusic @jenbruce1 You think? Weirdly enough there are risk averse twats across most demographics and a lot of the people I engage with on Twitter are probably what you would call 'Gammon' and they want all restrictions gone like yesterday.  But 10 points for getting Gammon into a tweet ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MerseyPolice #SnitchesGetStitches ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sash_or_Chicane @DPJHodges ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sash_or_Chicane @DPJHodges Just noticed your Twitter name haha https://t.co/Ay8dFcfNGV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sash_or_Chicane @DPJHodges The day I can walk up to an event like this, pay my money, dance all night, leave, grab a kebab, get a cab home the pass out, ALL WITHOUT MASKS, DISTANCING, TESTS OR PASSPORTS, is the day that I'll agree it's over. Confident of that by 21st June Dan?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NotreRene Just saw a clip of him indoors with more than six people...I think he just got himself into a pickle to go with his ham sandwich]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoffersWHU You say that but I've seen people 'outed' to their work for an opinion that whilst it might go against the grain, is completely reasonable. Surely the point of Twitter is free speech (not abuse of course). Cancel culture is as much of a problem as the trolls IMHO...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LozzaFox @Keir_Starmer He'll say it was a work meeting, guaranteed....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LozzaFox: It would seem that the mask has already slipped for @Keir_Starmer   Dont share widely. No one is perfect. https://t.co/1IO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is it with Chelmsford removing benches everywhere?!? Waiting for the other half to get her nails done and I'm sat on a very small wall, looking like a dosser lolol #BringBackBenches #YouBigDosser https://t.co/Em0gTvMH3G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BurnsideNotTosh To be fair, when I was younger,  you couldn't move for puffins...now I only see wankpuffins on Twitter https://t.co/3cs6TpjmQa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BurnsideNotTosh Barman is simply getting him back...."That will settle about the same time as your COVID restrictions....enjoy!"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@volvicviking ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenBarbaraSmi There you go....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope after a period of restrictions, when things open up fully and get back to normal (touch wood), I hope it ushers in a massive era of partying, clubbing and general debauchery and if any of the new Puritans try to get in the way of that, they get trampled and dealt with https://t.co/DpBBuHEPvz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't wait for summer festivals with dance tents.... https://t.co/kktcklzQJh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@volvicviking @Nigel_Farage https://t.co/nkJAW7dxVn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bahahaha https://t.co/1DSwDy4IoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Niki44 @twitt_twoo72 I mean, after being out last night, I was able to navigate to the toilet this morning without a headache, falling over or being sick. It's a different drinking experience when someone is checking the measures ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Niki44 @twitt_twoo72 Only problem will be you can't afford to drink as much as you do at home lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoffersWHU As long as people can remain anonymous on the people facing side, that shouldn't be an issue. Too many nasty people will trace you on here and go to your work etc if you disagree with them....that's why many are anonymous]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So, anyone missing those social media accounts that are blacked out?  Anyone think they have an inflated opinion of themselves and their importance?  Will it change anything? https://t.co/A8tAQV6yhN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/kGBz9LrxDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cheers! https://t.co/w0fARJt0kT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI I'd have more faith in the cunt if he could find his way to the barbers....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI The Tony Blair Institute aka The Cunt Farm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spruced up, ready to be out on the town...  #ProductInTheHairCountsRight https://t.co/yzwM22ot2O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trailer_Swift69 Well obvs lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trailer_Swift69 Tories sitting this one out I presume...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsForAlI: Liverpool right now! https://t.co/lkC4wLVQy0]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>