<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[I was going to say id love to see the reaction this bloke would get if he was in the local pub but then I remembered hes the biggest social reject ever and has never entered a pub in his life. https://t.co/Ub9V5jnb6a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Them conspiracy theorists at it again!!! https://t.co/IDgMijrfPP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whether we do though is a different matter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for that government but I think us grown adults know how to behave responsibly without you telling us to https://t.co/KhLdOJA0fT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seriously i dont care who you are, what your job is,  or what your circumstances are. If you have enjoyed a second of lockdown then id suggest looking at getting mental help or even better please stay indoors for the rest of time! https://t.co/cJ8aFW5loY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just say you have no mates to go down the pub with and move on Dom https://t.co/Sa0R3FVTJc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vulnerable are now protected, the NHS is no longer overwhelmed (even though I dont think it ever was), if you have the vaccine great and if you dont thats your choice   Open the pubs, dont wear a mask, dont social distance and enjoy a few pints]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the fuck is going on man? The pubs are opening with stricter rules than what they closed with ffs.   Has anyone ever stopped and thought hang on we have vaccinated over half the country its about time we can go to the pub without being treat like its a prison camp.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@REM831119 Already seen a pub in liverpool try and claim its the guidelines to wear masks outside]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI Check his blood pressure ASAP!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now Im all for getting back to the pubs we love and helping them out after the toughest year yet.  However you just know there will be some pubs probably enforcing masks outside, checking peoples phones for track  trace etc. If thats your pub then you deserve nothing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notadoomster Honestly I cant believe it. I felt bad going for the vaccine anyway because Im nowhere near vulnerable and nowhere near the age group needed but its due to work.   Every single nurse aswell not even 1 or 2, all of them double masked up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Second dose of the vaccine completed for me today!   On a bad note though, all nurses double masked up ffs. What on earth are we up against man and what chance do we ever stand??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The worst part it during all this Ive always felt Boris Johnson deep down knows this full thing is a bunch of power tripped scientists trying to stay relevant.   Sadly Boris Johnson hasnt grown a backbone throughout the full thing and still bows down to them! https://t.co/y745R8If08]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disgusting, how these bastards keep getting away with this is beyond me. https://t.co/hFyQlt5fCn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkyNews: "There is no evidence that general wearing of face masks by the public who are well stops the spread of COVID-19... what matte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive got a brother in secondary school, he said no one wears a mask anyway.   However it is annoying that we are told these things will be looked and reviewed however I havent seen one piece of evidence for masks working within school classrooms?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It might seem like its never going to happen but trust me one day very soon, this country will fight back against the lunatics in charge of it!   People have had enough and the majority are finally realising the lies within the roadmap. We will rise  #EnoughIsEnough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does Boris actually want these vaccine passports or do we just think its another idea from the social rejects advising Government?   Like the past year though, we all know whatever Sage and the Scientists want, they will get!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Freedom. https://t.co/P8pii1muaS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone from Wales on here or anyone who knows about what was going on in Cardiff etc last night? People finally taking to the streets to get that dinosaur out of power @fmwales ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just catching up on the news from last night. Vaccine passports look like they will be determined on Labour supporting or opposing them. God help us ffs!!! https://t.co/5YbwU5dlpD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seems like the vaccinated will be able to travel away this year. A kick in the bollocks to the younguns who have sacrificed an awful lot this year just to be told they cant enjoy a summer holiday because they wont have the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I often think about stuff like this but imagine March last year someone telling you that in 2021 the pub check list will consist of   Phone  Wallet  Keys  Vaccine passport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well well well.   Britain, the new North Korea. https://t.co/oasMCyzYNy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone make sure this blokes feeling ok https://t.co/B3JEGeH20p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FUCKING HELL!!!!!! This cant be true! The leader of the opposition acrually opposing something??? https://t.co/3niqCRUcPl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats my night of entertainment sorted then!   A bunch of French people sending the country up in flames all night. https://t.co/NH8JnYycXk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is AFTER the so called restrictions are going to be lifted on June 21st by the way https://t.co/6fQBr9TVun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crazy how this woman is now speaking for the majority of us in this country. Fair Play @GillianMcKeith https://t.co/tTHFp32qRg https://t.co/cOy2PlHQCO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sickening absolutely sickening. https://t.co/01UrS2dgMB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iCrowby @_Rick_Deckard_ Yep  Im glad you have put your point across, like a say you will be the same type of person who hasnt hugged a family member since last March and has Chris Whitty photos on his bedroom wall.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iCrowby @_Rick_Deckard_ If you read the thread, he called us a tin foil hat wearer to which I replied saying basically the same tin foil hat wearers that have been correct on every single thing thats happened. Vaccine passports for example.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iCrowby @_Rick_Deckard_ Wrong about what? Chris Whitty being a disgrace which is he?   Hes a scaremongering power tripped clown.   Bet youre the same people who havent hugged a family member since last March]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Them stupid tin foil hat wearers!!!! Imagine thinking youd need a passport to get in the local pub Lol you stupid conspiracy theorists!!! COVIDIOTS shame on you! https://t.co/L4An56ULyX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Rick_Deckard_ Ive got my tin hat firmly on as I have since March 2020, also still stand corrected on every single thing me and the other tin hat wearers have predicted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An expert in scaremongering https://t.co/B8SEUTuPfz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some people really upset at this in the comments https://t.co/OBjOiXbckw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/FAJHvLDZT8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chris Whitty knocks me sick.  Blokes on TV telling us it can still be dangerous for us to be walking in a park with someone and not socially distancing. Resign you utter clown.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[23 deaths in the whole UK today, never nice to think about or say but we are miles past the point where we have an acceptable level of deaths.   We have the same with flu etc so now its time to do the same with Covid. Also deaths are only going to get lower with the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Try give this a RT please everybody, be good to get a good understanding https://t.co/nw1WeyVLKB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine passports   Do you think you will need to show a passport type certificate to enter a pub this year?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not once, seen right through the full shitshow before it even came to Britain. https://t.co/ftiDYJd8IS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine if someone told you in July 2020 we would have half the nation vaccinated already! Youd of thought we were packing out pubs, stadiums, theatres etc months ago. Yet here we are.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lifes never going back to normal is it, its crazy how in June/July last year I was more optimistic about returning to normal life than I am now with over half the nation vaccinated ffs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That doesnt sound like the normal life we were promised!   Im fine about foreign travel stopping if there is actually a risk but dont make it sound like its a solution for giving us our simple freedoms back over the summer.Everything should be open domestically no matter what https://t.co/Z6vrqJ6D6B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whens the next protest? https://t.co/kH9gB52XrN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very well spoken again Adam   One thing however thats really frustrated me throughout this whole thing is the silence of so many. Why is down to a local landlord to speak up for so many people.   FIND YOUR FUCKING VOICE!!#EnoughIsEnough https://t.co/y4P45oZ1h3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine this time last year telling people in a years time you will need a certificate to have a few pints with your pals! Youd of probably been sectioned.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seeing a lot of people claiming pubs wont stick to the vaccine passport. Youll be suprised especially considering how many forced rules such as wearing a mask every time you went to the toilet etc etc. https://t.co/DqlUCri58q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last tweet took out of context slightly,   In short- you want to carry a card round saying youve had the vaccine then do it.   Should it be required to get entry into anywhere? Absolutely not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At this rate I Think I may have to change the name of the page to anti domestic vaccine passports!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cIRbaac4Aa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine my shock.   Like Ive said numerous times, if this country isnt at 100% normality by June 22nd then brace yourself in every single city and town for scenes that have never been seen before.  https://t.co/tqdBDmafae]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust me, this is the start of the end.   Id guess more people will agree than disagree with this however I find it quite disgusting. https://t.co/oL5kLtqLr5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrdanwalker fucking bottle job. How can these people constantly come on national TV to put these points across completely unchallenged??   Dr Nighat Arif, face coverings maybe part of your life and many others past covid but they wont be included in mine https://t.co/nXDahKckNg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: To mandate Masks past June,will be an utter disgrace. If people want to continue to wear them, please do.. If people want to c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yeah Mary Ramsey, hopefully you are the one who tries to tell someone on June 22nd that its compulsory to wear a mask still?   For the people who labelled everyone at the #londonprotest yesterday idiots, this is why we do it.   Wake up. https://t.co/myOcNSQJ06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember everyone, normality by June 21st! https://t.co/qBaOE0hjdV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats the overall mood in Wales at the minute? Seems like theyre being run by an absolute lunatic. If Boris Johnson came out and said this Id expect riots all over. https://t.co/3mjFebHDZL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Send these scientists to the fucking moon and let us live our lifes ffs.   Yes deaths are bad, yes old people being poorly is bad, but honestly if you think its worse than what is currently happening in our lifes then you are a lunatic. https://t.co/I7ljqD8AJW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following the science? Not one bit. I dont think one single study has shown the 10pm curfew had any effect at all.   Sturgeon should be made to come on national telly and tell the people of Scotland the reasoning for this and the data which shows why its being imposed. https://t.co/4OBu20lcU0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland.   WAKE UP FFS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its almost like people forgot other ways of dying existed during Covid! https://t.co/3laAUngbSl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If tonight has shown one thing its the police serve absolutely no one in this country. There will be a few resignations getting put in on Monday morning after the last few days.  This is an anti lockdown page but we can all agree.   FUCK THE POLICE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ACAB https://t.co/vcRZunYD1e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything this year has simply been a case of, if its not Covid then who cares.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Switch the news stories over from Meghan and Harry and get this on every front page, every news broadcaster. This is a disgrace and they should all be held accountable. https://t.co/YftBt9p9E6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Silly is one way of putting it but im sure people have many other words to use for it.   35 deaths projected weekly by April 11th ffs.  Whitty and co just swallow your pride and power trip pills and just allow a fast opening of the country! https://t.co/iHT1a30JpR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If only he knew someone who could do something about it.  Oh. https://t.co/Z9W9Sl0g2b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another one suitable for the firing squad I think!   Sounds like someone whos had the power to do what he likes for the first time in his life and he isnt holding back! https://t.co/qtN2oJEf24]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @newscientist Chris Whitty and the other muppets will be pissing the bed tonight at all the positive news coming today!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep  Just like the whole still hundreds of deaths expected in April  Ive said all along, these scientists have never been to a pub, footy match, gym, or any other social event EVER!   Theyre happy locked away and making everyone else as miserable as possible. https://t.co/5M7B81xvoJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im struggling to understand how the vaccine programme can be considered successful if everything results in a surge by late summer? https://t.co/cH3XjRnYow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FUCK CHRIS WHITTY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seen a few tweets today suggesting a few parents and even children were anxious about the return to school today. So a few things to say.  1- Get a grip   2- If your child is anxious over returning to school then you have failed them massively!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How can they even justify this anymore?   Crazy to think Scotland dont even move to LEVEL 3 until end of April either! Shambles https://t.co/cvOPZpoPqw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Captain obvious https://t.co/XQOI5daUP5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are going to be in lockdown due to a rise in common colds next arent we. https://t.co/P6HlU8VeE0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoMasksInClass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The worlds leading vaccine programme  The worlds strictest lockdown.   We are watching our European neighbours open up whilst we sit back and HOPE JUNE 21st is the end of this.   Wake up ffs!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notadoomster Without a doubt but the happy clappers will here everything back to normal by Christmas and carry on as normal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I honestly fear that a lot of people have became to comfortable with this type of life and have forgot just what normal life is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Either yougov are completely making this up or maybe the lockdown lovers are the majority now. Which one do we think it is? https://t.co/7HLoT4B3Bs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TJSM21 Without a doubt!   My opinion but I think they realised people were getting fed up quite quickly so this is the quick solution. Similar to like you say, the Christmas promise.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All over 50s should be vaccinated by the end of March. The end is virtually here.   What do we get? Matt Hancock on sky news telling us we arent done with this yet, the cases are going up in some areas and this varient which may resist the vaccines   Wake up ffs people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another reminder. https://t.co/taKNt1FTr1 https://t.co/rM0ZQeXevZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here we go https://t.co/MmNDBN8Dcf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The roadmap is doing a good job at keeping some people content but dont fall for it!  Stop falling for the same government tricks which they have tried on us for the past year.   #LondonRises #UniteForFreedom https://t.co/TJeoS6P4af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well Done Dublin #EnoughIsEnough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government- cases are rising in some areas  Also the government- please we urge everyone to get tested! Going to school, work, and college please get tested.   Sense-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No wonder noone watches this dribble anymore.   Sobering statistics they say as they show graphs which looked a world away this time month!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Van-Tam and Hancock have been a disgrace here.   Hancock just admitted that local restrctions could come back into place if cases rise in a specific area!   #EnoughIsEnough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scotgpd19 Are they? From what Ive seen it looks like the majority seem content with it which is insane but hopefully thats not the case]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Expecting huge protests to follow in Scotland after todays announcements.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just to clarify this isnt MY protest.   Kids returning to schools is great.   Staged plan to end lockdown? Where have we heard that one before? Oh yeah the last 2 lockdowns. https://t.co/80MTCETV37]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government had done a good job today, seems like this Covid restriction free date on June 21st is going to keep the majority complying for now.   Ill be very suprised if we make it to the may 17th dates without having the dates pushed back and further restrctions imposed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think its crucial people focus on the no earlier than that is getting repeated constsntly now in by Boris Johnson.   The full thing just stinks of a magical variant appearing just before certain points of the roadmap.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>