<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: If you haven't seen Michael Sheen's short film The Banker, you are in for a treat... https://t.co/qx9uA4uTY2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoeSimpsonArt happy birthday!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@icarus_drowned sunken cost fallacy innit. I'm proud of you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@achtungchio appropriate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PancakesETbooks it's hard I know]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@achtungchio bad dog!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PancakesETbooks you done the drinking loads of water thing? I have a diarolyte sachet as well sometimes but I am prone to dehydration]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@icarus_drowned you've finally seen the light! WOOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Right then, TV Choice awards: https://t.co/tQ26yoEbcu You can vote for the following Sheeny/DT things: Best new drama: Pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: A clip from Wales: Land of the Wild [Warning: toad sex] @michaelsheen did you enjoy narrating this series? It's incredibly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darylmine2 remember that we have many, many accents in Britain!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leolinders @rehza_rice it's fun to have a go isn't it. I once apparently did a perfect Austrian accent in front of my friend who is from there, she did this double take. It was a total fluke though I could never do it again... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darylmine2 I bet your accent is lovely]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darylmine2 I'm sure you could learn!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@icarus_drowned how very dare you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GISGuru yw. Going to try to do transcripts for as much as possible over on @TheSheendex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please follow @TheSheendex for Michael Sheen content, lots of stuff coming up. Not sure I'm going to be posting as much on this account]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: #SundaySerotonin Michael Sheen and David Tennant in WHAT HAS HAPPEN TO YOUR HAIR!? [transcript in thread] https://t.co/6Ay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Michael Sheen and David Tennant on Aziraphale and Crowley "you know they're gonna end up in each others arms..." [transcri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[M: Then what do you say? Do you say, well I just did it American? Or do you just go oh ok.. D: Ramp it up M: ...then do exactly the same thing again and hope that it's...? D: yeah...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[M: That's why you get self conscious! D: EXACTLY! M: I'm sorry, I'm sorry! D: Right there! M: I once did an audition for an American film, and I did it American, and at the end of it they said "and would you mind doing it American?" D: [laughs painfully]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[D: and I'm sort of going [in American accent] "can I get a cappucino please?" [in his own accent] "I'm so sorry, please don't mind me" M: I thought you said you did an American accent...? D: Awwwwww [dies inside] M: Oh see! See! D: See!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael: if I'm playing an American character in things I tend to keep that going David: do you, all the time? M: yeah because I find it harder D: yeah, I do it a bit and then I get a bit self conscious  M: yeah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael Sheen and David Tennant discuss doing accents [transcript in thread] https://t.co/a3NdA6XWDE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Eden_n_Tunnels @Malorkai @prodigalsonfox It's ok I sent overbearing ardour on behalf of the whole Sheendexing team]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Malorkai: Okay. I had a really bad, everyone hates me kinda of day (month/year) yesterday, but all of your lovely messages really che]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCTheOneShow Staged!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WCVACymru: WCVA President @michaelsheen wants you to join us in the fight against unemployment in Wales.  Find out how you can get fund]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @yavannauk: Oh, interesting... just had my first chance to look at availability for Under Milk Wood myself and there are two shows marke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@katy_cass Hm that's annoying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@katy_cass Do you have them turned on?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SheenTennantFan Very annoy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnderRaccoon it's just a backup for the sheendex gc incase twitter goes titsup again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnderRaccoon Ooh I have two! I feel speshul now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnderRaccoon Same. I only just started my own server thing though]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnderRaccoon I go on discord and sort of feel my way around but I reckon I'd have to dedicate some time to learning it all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EnderRaccoon ooh snazzy. I haven't actually worked out the notification settings in my discord yet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gemgem16554760 I did, I will do it again if it doesn't sort itself out soon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bunnyhuggerpro I hope mine does, it's very annoying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gemgem16554760 ikr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bananatiergod this is main tweets. *sigh*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are anyone else's notifications messed up? I'm currently the Michael Sheen fan account that doesn't get notifications when Michael Sheen tweets... https://t.co/3PvZm4iDf0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelsheen: It's important that everyone is protected against deadly diseases like COVID-19. There is no 'us' and 'them', only humani]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Michael Sheen speech at the NPTC Student Awards 2021 today. See the full event at https://t.co/Pqj8yPRVn4 [Transcript in t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PancakesETbooks ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PancakesETbooks Same. Never gets old]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MadGuida666 And hers!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@loveMSheenFFS The inspiration for my username!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrsKiraHardyWho @bananatiergod Yeah, he's brilliant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["What are you watching" "Well..." https://t.co/D55zEGRqnl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sheen365 Prodigal son, starring Michael Sheen, is about to be eaten by his wife]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NPTCGroup: Today is the day!   Tune in on Facebook and YouTube at 6pm to watch our 16th Annual Student Awards; featuring a very speci]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWales @bethanrhys @michaelsheen @BBCOne Hello, is there any chance of putting the full interview up? Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sheen365 He's home! I'm so glad!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBCWalesNews: Helping Welsh youngsters attend Oxford University, independence, the NHS and European Super League Hollywood star Michael]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBCWales: On tonights episode of #WalesLive, @Bethanrhys speaks to actor and activist, @Michaelsheen.  BBC Wales Live Tonight, 10:35pm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UniofOxford: We're pleased to see the creation of a brand new bursary scheme!  Developed in collaboration with the actor and activist,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @msheensource: Oxford bursary scheme named after Michael Sheen will support Welsh students https://t.co/C4sZajxeGs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @msheensource: @michaelsheen to attend "Who Speaks for Wales? Raymond Williams at 100" panel with Professor Daniel G. Williams and Leann]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@omensfromeden Ah OK thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@omensfromeden What's a W in this context?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Pandemica: Michael Sheen has taken part in voicing an animated series to raise awareness of the importance of getting the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelsheen what did you get David for his birthday?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twogeeksoup @neilhimself yes UK and Ireland I believe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@twogeeksoup @neilhimself American Gods, Anansi Boys, How the Marquis Got His Coat Back, Neverwhere, The Ocean at the End of the Lane, Stardust]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actually six. I just bought six @neilhimself books then... https://t.co/bHzEPtJq54]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Michael Sheen on Comic Relief 2021 https://t.co/zdnPtCEeeW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PatricProAuthor: Here's my interview with actor and activist Michael Sheen, who speaks about his career so far and how he has adapted t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oldvictheatre: We can all be like the Lorax    We asked some friends to help us share the Lorax's message of protecting our planet, wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Erm you probably won't be able to in a minute cuz I told them. Soz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FaneProductions Ah OK.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FaneProductions But people who haven't bought a ticket can watch it on the website right now. My friend in Wales is watching it...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FaneProductions hello, how come the Neil Gaiman event seems to be free to watch right now when it's also ticketed? Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seems you can watch this live right now without buying a ticket. That's not galling at all. #boughtaticket https://t.co/Rj54XRSeG4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm going to this in half an hour, it originally said Michael Sheen would be doing a reading but that was removed (after I bought the ticket of course ) but looking forward to it. https://t.co/GqdrKLTs5q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@achtungchio @bananatiergod NEVER!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bananatiergod @achtungchio But he's been around loads...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shitomens Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shitomens It's just a thing the author did because Michael and David are a top search term and it got his article to come up in searches for them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sheen365: Good morning!!! What are you in the mood for today...?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MondoShioren I can do but it will take a while!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Updated the @sheen365 page on the Sheendex with the most recently answered questions! https://t.co/yPthwW3pQL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone should listen to this, it's fascinating and moving and I cried https://t.co/Bq8eKBnlIo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: Updated the Passion of Port Talbot page with the new audio of Michael Sheen talking about his memories of the play, via Wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kit_catastrophe @omlsheen @TheSheendex I'd need more info lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MondoShioren @achtungchio no I haven't see it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bunnyhuggerpro @staged2020 Yeah they seem to be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBCWales: A love letter to the #NHS, written by @owensheers.  Featuring @michaelsheen, @TeamEveMyles, Martin Freeman, @CeliaImrie, @mis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've seen ppl talking about the 'new' extended versions of s2 of Staged which are 'exclusively' on Britbox. But the ones on Britbox are the same length as the extended ones on the DVD... @staged2020 are the extended parts different on Britbox than on the DVD?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RomanMollusc @AngelsTartanTie It's awesome we have so many people's versions of it though, like Michael said it's like lots of people's gospels of what happened]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sheen365 @master_crowley Beef curtains]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RomanMollusc @AngelsTartanTie The linedance? I didn't think that was in the film]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RomanMollusc @AngelsTartanTie oh I see. Well the movie is just one man's 'gospel' of what happened that weekend. ;)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RomanMollusc @AngelsTartanTie Here's the full version of The Teacher's story https://t.co/kQ5qylDfgw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bananatiergod I guess then you have to work on becoming a practice-tionist....?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bananatiergod that's my entire life]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @owensheers: 10 years ago today #ThePassionofPortTalbot had just come to a close. In this thread below a few photos from rehearsals  th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sheen365 I have a backlog of these to add to the website, but I haven't forgotten and it will be updated soon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @michaelsheen: Around this time 10 years ago on Easter Sunday the Passion came to an end at Aberavon Beach. I would love to hear from an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheSheendex: https://t.co/zn6tzhGTyA I've done a page about The Passion of Port Talbot, the play Michael Sheen did ten years ago in his]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>