<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @moxiee_xx: this  https://t.co/AOEIJXkyGG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets get this bread I guess  https://t.co/9ujEfBfdZe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreadyBois: Lets get this bread.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tiye_tiy: Working 5 days and resting for 2.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @not_kristin92: Hot girl summer isnt being about skinny its about being confident, loving yourself, and having fun. Thank you for co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tolul_ope_: the stare before the kiss&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me to my sisters kids when they ask what Im gettin them for their Birthday https://t.co/bZrm0J43kj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Caught a terminal case of being down. Bad. Rip pray for me yall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pero56870578:  https://t.co/P79oz6PASb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/e7tVojCgJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So then imagine that the MC is trapped and is just begging their captor to let them go home and they are referencing their SO the entire time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To them because we do this together or not at all and the MC telling them you are home to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ok there is this concept that I really love that would be a such a good story. Ok imagine: the narrator explains that home is not always a place, but a feeling. Cut to the SO telling the MC that despite them moving frequently it doesnt really matter much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @itsbabypears: sailor moon doodle  https://t.co/5JgMcCgnT6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dialectuz: i can change him honey thats eren jaeger only mikasa ackerman can do that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HlNDRIX: Enjoy it!!! These are the best years of your life  These.... are the best?!? https://t.co/0zl2doHNUv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrewedBlackGirl: I knew she was gonna come with some heat https://t.co/GovBNULHkb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @glamdemon2004: Are you actually supposed to be awake for 16 hours at a time that seems a little dramatic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OsamuJas: cant believe i used to let basic ass girls call me ugly ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @moimoiland480:  https://t.co/a0bfpo3uhY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SailorMoonOoC: Me discovering my self-worth https://t.co/N0pI8UlGxN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vRgSTscQzn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @luvleemelodie: Chile... they done got Beyonc on the #SelenaTheSeries  https://t.co/9dqkwDvrQo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guzzlingguzma: WHAT IS THIS TAG  #anitwtmatingseason https://t.co/6N2ek2OqZn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iamshaxo: these scenarios in my head be wild af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Artbaesel: In case you dont hear it today, Im proud of you. https://t.co/p0k4GVsskw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NarutoVisual:        *.   *   *               *       *.                            *. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nilamadison: everyone: May the 4th be with you  my Catholic ass: and also with you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/shrzV1nCv6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vIpwVs8yr2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestofparker: spider-man: homecoming (2017) https://t.co/y2ICA8zH6e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sootpride: hey neurodivergents, name something that annoys you that neurotypicals won't understand.   neurotypicals retweet to spread.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ghiblipicture: I need this https://t.co/7gAiYiTZtE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uwuthottiie: https://t.co/ge8dbbIe6c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aniqrahman: Remembering the time when Tom Holland and Jacob Batalon had a lightsaber duel #MayThe4th  https://t.co/Hjwd1sNthb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ickyvikiii I love this for you. Im definitely saving up for mine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_ThePaleRider @ickyvikiii Brazilian Butt lift.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AW5pVH8PGr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FUCK. Yall ever vibed to a song so hard that the mood just carries you through the day? Like MAN. The serotonin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My knees just made the most ungodly noise. Im going to have to next day ship that life alert]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@angelamavalla How fucked is it that not only do I have PCOS, I also no longer have a thyroid so when my body wants to act up I dont have a thyroid to compensate for the changes so I end up having low tsh.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angelamavalla: Facial hair (hirsutism) is common in women living with PCOS.   Its important to note that women of colour are dispropor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nah Im Robbin him https://t.co/NfLpNMTOtZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rein_spice: Thinkin bout *this* specific kind of angst  https://t.co/yg9pYr34bj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theeashleyray: fyi if you're a celebrity and you want to hit on me, i won't say shit on tiktok or anywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@queenb_ley GIRLL YOU ARE SO KIND OH MY GOODNESS THANK YOU.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @evildildos: imma show up already full]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @E__WHYTE: Two things define you: Your patience when you have nothing, and your attitude when you have everything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8YM13oANfE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pinkbluemiku: Collecting these like infinity stones https://t.co/tGKD9q2HXF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreadyBois: Lets get this bread.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The face                 The personality.              (Im just goin by what my people tell me) https://t.co/vnV8e8aqQ8 https://t.co/3NDLgqJ1x2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @belllmonts: if villain bad then why he love his wife? https://t.co/qrm0ht09Bk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaealissa_: The universe is LOUD when it wants you to know that something is in alignment for you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WINGEDHEROH4WKS: ok i want his wings to come back but this new look is amazing for him https://t.co/78xDKbKxY7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@issamanga5 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MilkBoxArt Top quality bird man]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @correcthq: maybe I like haikyuu because it has everything that I don't friendships and sports skills]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My serotonin up and dipped and left me on read. Wack.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tinazhxng: finding your signature lipstick, lashes  perfume is my favorite part of growing older]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laura_stahl: Being kind is free]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FicWriStrugglin: You know what would be great? if i actually wrote something]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jessf_white God. Its me again.. I dont ask for much..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @itsu_izzu: Its embarrassing when they fight over me like this   #Haikyuu #coachukai #jeankirstein #aot https://t.co/cGoPZIlhRD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @natashasmygem: a visual representation of every marvel stan at the moment #MarvelStudios https://t.co/FZYI4pB0mF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LMAO I meannnn they arent wrong #BuckyBarnes https://t.co/BrKZnbcvPW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wintersoldct: remember when my girl shuri absolutely dragged bucky barnes with this one line? https://t.co/TXWyiapFl3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KoenigAdam: So happy for him  https://t.co/F9OFebzonp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LilNasX: my soulmate probably somewhere robbing a bank right now. u go baby! get that money. love you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @silverscult: lets talk about kittens. a thread]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MilkBoxArt GIRL dont even get me started. Ibe been poetic as shit about hawks all damn day, like PLEASE who do I need to fedex my credit card to make this happen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @qLxke_: Gothams versions all the characters will always be the superior versions https://t.co/lOccKjtoyr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AniTrendz: (5/3) Happy Birthday to Narumi Momose! https://t.co/yDpK9psEAR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The perfect dynamic really #given https://t.co/CCHy0B9yWX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wlwbrunnhilde: also while were discussing thor ragnarok ill never get over how loki and valkyrie had so much potential for an amazing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VanillaCherie: sailor moon bunny  https://t.co/bnBHCZa9SR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @m0therdumpster: did anyone else listen to "all the things she said" by tatu on repeat in middle school or were you normal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Haikyuu #hinatashoyo #kagehina #Kageyama https://t.co/nPGhM0zQFp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FTPLuvsU: Pretending like Im not depressed everyday is the most tiring thing I do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lindawg_: i love when southern girls become alt. you guys r so cool. ur Yallternative]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheJDMara: normalize writing things that make your friends go jesus christ, dude]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @spideygifs: The Amazing Spider-Man https://t.co/uyb6bEcJXW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @xr0sesx: May is mental health awareness month, remember to take time for yourself this month and remember you are loved, cared for, and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[!! https://t.co/LWp5Q3NXlM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MilkBoxArt @bunnychansenpai Gorgeous. Its so beautiful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @qLxke_: even if you dont like The Amazing Spider-Man duology, there is absolutely no denying that the movies gave us some of the absol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nxemireyes_: Yall be careful ladies these curbs jumping out like crazy these days I got hit twice this morning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[   https://t.co/yHggBemfFs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @D3m0n_L3m0n: My lower back hurts from carrying around all my unappreciated humor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MilkBoxArt @geekygal11011 It counts as Self care to leave him there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I stg if no one holds me like this at least once before i die Im coming back as a poltergeist and haunting All yall https://t.co/QFU1JuuDW2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @elanadrex: Can we take a hot minute to appreciate that fanfiction is FREE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LMFAOOO  @MilkBoxArt @geekygal11011 https://t.co/FvJBzHtm6r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellkay_ MCR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nekoooo512: 2 https://t.co/JbMet1mZtc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fictitiousIy: we as a society did not appreciate andrew garfield as peter parker enough https://t.co/S95bDIpxqe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShadzMangaOnly: MHA been popping.  Don't let twitter narratives fool you into thinking otherwise.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OMGGGG IM SO EXCITED FOR THISSSSSSSS https://t.co/beUSYJJHOI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anime @MilkBoxArt @00chevan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anime @geekygal11011 @ashensiren16]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>