<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Laurence Fox is creating a brand out of gaslighting NHS staff  I spend my life advocating for them  His twitter followi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ByDonkeys: So many scandals swishing around Johnson, but dont forget this one. He didnt target Covid at the borders, instead he targe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @spacethirteen: if you are a man, and your first thought at the noel clarke allegations is concern for your favourite tv show rather tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReclaimTS: PCSO Julia James' murder is heartbreaking - our thoughts are with her family, friends and colleagues.  She was just walking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: BREAKING Why are doctors in court again today against the government?  @EveryDoctorUK+@GoodLawProject have 4 legal case]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @clarisselou: Please enjoy Harrison Ford watching a magic trick  then reacting in the only way Harrison Ford reacts to anything https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SoVeryBritish Anything consumed on your birthday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: We are doctors, and were meeting with over 100 MPs tomorrow to explain the NHS privatisation which has been escalating f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good start to the (birth)day! New books by @neilhimself @terryandrob @LevParikian and @ElizabethKnoxNZ (The Colour of Magic to replace a copy I lent to....  and was never returned!). Where to start?!   https://t.co/0PS3PdAe2H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@taurusismagic ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im rewatching #scrubs and Id forgotten how soon Id have to deal with this heartbreak #BrendanFraser  https://t.co/20P9H9OYXl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Weve heard for months about the lies and cronyism and dodgy deals. We now know the sleaze occurring while NHS staff had]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Face masks are still really important.  RT if you have better things to protest about than perceived reduction of persona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrMichaelSpicer: the room next door - Boris Johnson and Bunny Hugging https://t.co/RgfWpZIT6q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read the thread. Know whats happening. Donate if you can  https://t.co/Tr2DfsmwbP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @womblesofficial: On #EarthDay we can all play our part. Caring for the planet can be fun and enjoyable - plant more, cycle, upcycle, me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Guys we have a LOT of public awareness to do ahead of our court cases against the government in 4 weeks. Please can you h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Nurses are turning to food banks, and meanwhile the government wastes 2.6million on a room full of flags.  Its a disgra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CalumMcSwiggan: Just a reminder that you should post whatever you want on social media. Its your account so post what makes you happy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BarristerSecret: Now *these* are sentencing remarks. More people on the internet need to be told this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joncoopertweets: I urge everyone to dispose of their used face masks properly and responsibly. Never discard them on the street. When p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vile  https://t.co/aK5AEPtK0s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @doctor_oxford: Here is how you imagine the 150k lives lost to Covid.  Its just taken me 10 mins to walk the half kilometre length of t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: A plea for help Hardly anyone understands NHS privatisation. @EveryDoctorUK have decided to bring info to everyone; pol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StatlerWaldorf: Twitter reminds us a lot of The Muppet Show. There are 280 characters, constant nonsense going on, and no matter how mu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FFigureFBust: https://t.co/j9l1QM5afU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im loving all the Brendan Fraser appreciation tweets today. Definitely the wholesome content I needed to see.  https://t.co/bqfEm3puMO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NintendoFionna: #BrendanFraser appreciation post! https://t.co/7Cfw6mTdRO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AuDeLaClaire: #BrendanFraser is an icon. We still love you. You deserve the best. https://t.co/O2VsqdRgOD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stevenspohn: Everybody is tweeting about how great Brendan Fraser was as "his most famous role" in The Mummy.  But did you ever see him]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarnellAnita: Weve won our lawsuit over Matt Hancocks 23m NHS data deal with Palantir | openDemocracy retweet the hell out of this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrMichaelSpicer: the 'no racism in the uk' report team meeting https://t.co/LZyglWuc5D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @womblesofficial: Over the last year, we have all realised the importance of our outdoor spaces. Please don't litter, even us Wombles ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: CHALLENGE! Last time we did this, you guys grew my following by &gt;20k followers in 48 hrs  Laurence Fox has launched his]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReclaimTS: RECLAIM THESE STREETS RESPONDS TO HMICFRS ENQUIRY https://t.co/EOpWY5y9eL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrMichaelSpicer: Shocking news about Creme Eggs because I always thought they were made of mashed kale, spring water, and the wholesome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Hi!Im Julia-I run @EveryDoctorUK  In Spring 2020,our tiny non-profit built a coalition of 104 MPs to fight for NHS staff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BethanyinCBR: Absolutely THIS!  https://t.co/R2dKixf1d0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: What Ive learned from the government in the past 7 days:  Flags are important Statues are important Weapons are impor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scottstemp Excellent choice of GIF!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kirby_pj: Votes for women were not achieved by letters to the Times.  Rosa Parks was no doubt very annoying to some white people on a b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReclaimTS: Yesterday, we were invited to meet with @SadiqKhan and later with @MetPoliceUK Commissioner Cressida Dick. These were our as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@foodallergyuk @charlieLfarley Its so confusing. They are back at school but parents arent back at work. Theyre not allowed to have play dates or birthday parties or visit granny. But they can go to school.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JujuliaGrace So its not just women, its children too? Thats......not better...!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley @foodallergyuk Mine had tummy ache for a couple of days last week. Admitted over the weekend that hed been worried and some of his friends were upset. But at the same time hes loving being back in class with friends and teacher. Confusing times!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanLaveryMP: How could any politician support a parliamentary Bill which will introduce harsher penalties on those who attack statues t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Know about this bill. Know what it means. https://t.co/L13HuWbx83]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theipaper: Sarah Everard case unleashed 'tidal wave' of women who won't accept male violence, organisers say https://t.co/aWglCJDg7G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TNeenan: This week began with International Womens Day and ends with Mothers Day. But dont worry, that spirit of celebrating women r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @itsjoelstweets: This country is insane. Monday - women are great! Tuesday - not that woman. Wednesday - missing woman found murdered, p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jesstud: For a week thats bookended by International Womens Day and Mothers Day, Id say overall its been rather a shit week for wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReclaimTS: Statement from Reclaim These Streets on tonights vigil in Clapham https://t.co/9EA20GWAi6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Barristerblog: It's very difficult for the police, but if ever there was a time to turn a blind eye to the letter of the law this was i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SarahEverard #ReclaimTheStreets #ReclaimTheNight https://t.co/cFJUt2MeVf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Joannechocolat: They're coming for women. Right now. This is what it looks like. And for those of you watching from a distance, just be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidschneider: If a protest is noisy enough to have impact on a single person in the vicinity, the police can impose restrictions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Joannechocolat: Here's a little mini-thread, to test your imagination.  1. Imagine your child has been bitten by a rabid dog.  2. Imagi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theipaper: Peer calls for 6pm curfew on men to 'make women much safer' after Sarah Eeverard disappearance https://t.co/ItchmLsXbQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidLammy: Men, not women, need to change their behaviour. https://t.co/kbUdxNqxNE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarrietEJohnson: Every woman you know has taken a longer route.  Has doubled back on herself.  Has pretended to dawdle by a shop window]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley This sounds amazing!! Definitely want photos when youre done! Good luck ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kittyharmless: @caitlinmoran Tomorrow night, let's put candles outside our homes for Sarah Everard and all the women killed by men in t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fayesos: If you havent...  - text a mate Im home - crossed a road to avoid someone - called  said chat to me for 5 - noted a cab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SianySianySiany: We change our routes home, we cross the road to avoid being catcalled, we change our clothes, we hold our keys in our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: We could afford 7000 a day to pay Test and Trace consultants.   But we cant afford a pay rise above 1% for NHS staff, w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmmaKennedy: This is what a responsible presenter looks like. Well done @alexberesfordTV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @findingnature: How does the type of nature conservation action relate to a closer relationship with nature? Our latest research: https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: Ok, Laurence Fox has 235k followers and campaigns on a platform of hatred. I have 81k followers and campaign on a platfor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MakeSpaceforGi1: On teenage girls, swings and the right to lurk, which is important.  Our new blog post today. https://t.co/qjitPL3NYx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@taurusismagic Very accurate! https://t.co/88NwhNDNX6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StatlerWaldorf: Anyone who says they "can't complain" when you ask them how things are is certainly no friend of ours! If you can't fig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnEdwards33: This..  https://t.co/EmQjJTIsRf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley @ad_rogers Ive got my 5yo into Gummi Bears, Chip n Dale Rescue Rangers and The Muppet Show  he wasnt so impressed by duck tales though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cononeilluk: Well....quite https://t.co/K7PuUNOsqW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMuppets @KermitTheFrog @disneyplus Present. With one 5yo being introduced to the cast ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My thoughts exactly. Pass the chocolate  https://t.co/s7uegBJgHy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karlbooton Ive had it. More that once. Its terrible. Find a comfy position - I found propped up better than laying flat - and drink plenty of fluids. Other than that theres not a lot to do. Sorry. You have my sympathies!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soapachu: *sigh* https://t.co/VlnmNEVH0K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is just brilliant! If youre a fan of #JACKIEWEAVER then please watch this - its brightened my day! https://t.co/GWoV8Ya2Um via @YouTube ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KathyBurke: .@IAMKEVBISH just sent me this. Not as good as the Scottish one but itll do!  R https://t.co/ftTfL3EqKD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Accurate. Unsurprising. Disappointing.  https://t.co/Mgmin17H5h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Having been to many Parish Council meetings, the behaviour is commonplace. Its called bullying. It needs to stop. #TeamJackieWeaver https://t.co/LQX6J24FKh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley OMG  Im laughing because Ive just done the ironing purely to avoid the other people in my house.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: New rewilding project teaches tour guides to offer fresh look at travel https://t.co/CIB4w9cJ9u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley Do it. No down sides!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Here's the full poem from Amanda Gorman, who is the youngest poet to ever read at an inauguration.  "Somehow we've weathe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hollyoaks:  #DontFilterFeelings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley Massive mugs of tea are already in progress! I have a half hour yoga zoom session at lunchtime which is about the only thing Im looking forward to (other than bed time!) ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley I woke at 3:30am. Didnt go back to sleep. Today I have: Childcare/homeschool 8-12, work 12-6, webinar 6-7. Its going to be a looooong day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley It cant possibly make things worse! Cheers ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley Eek I dont even want to try!! Ill stay with year 1 maths  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley You havent opened the wine already??? I spent my morning muttering why have they made maths harder? They are 5. Why do they need to divide numbers into parts? WTAF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Something to brighten your Monday morning. https://t.co/l2WFDHuymJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrRanj: Face-coverings are extremely important. There are people who genuinely cannot wear them for medical  psychological reasons.  I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ByDonkeys: The 'back to school' scandal. Millions of kids mixed unnecessarily for one day while the virus raged. Boris Johnsons incomp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SoVeryBritish: Today's weather: Grey, wet, warm and cold, with snow for some, alongside dry spells and lashings of disappointment, worr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley Its very good. I watched it the other day and it surprised me!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlieLfarley Have you watched Morning Glory?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinSLewis @curryspcworld This whole thread is wonderful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidTylerPozz: The urge to add a "y" to the last line is why I'll never be a proper grown-up https://t.co/MFO6CrPcc2]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>