<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Children do not require any artificial immunity from Sars-CoV-2.  Statistics, graphs, studies, risk assessments - all tot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nightingale_31: Breakfast is included? Yes breakfast is included now sit down enjoy it and stop acting like this isnt normal! Not gett]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Protestlockdown: Please go out and protest on May 15th   No social distancing  No masks  Hug people if you can   I will be in London th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ImperatorTruth: I refuse to take the Covid-19 Vaccine. If you refuse as well please retweet. Lets see how many of us just say no.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bret_Sears: Retweet if you're not afraid of the coronavirus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After the march on Sat we stopped at a pub in Cov Garden  ordered 3 pints on the door, They came out in what looked like Mcdonalds cartons, we tried to pay with cash but they only accepted cards bcause of covid.  We plonked the beers on the tray and walked off. #LondonMarch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelbell1991 @ChocolateKay14 @davidkurten What was he doing in there in the first place? He was clearly told he wasn't welcome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carolina_moon1: R.I.P to my father in law. Murdered by our Government like 1000s of others after 1 jab of AZ They will be held accounta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: James Corbett sums it up in 2 minutes. https://t.co/nyIzXGja1Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: Until enough people refuse to muzzle themselves, refuse to test themselves and refuse to view their basic freedoms as con]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Hats off to @Roost_Coffee. Taking a stand against the illiberal and authoritarian vaccine passports. I will order my cof]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: It is a wee bit odd that a "pandemic" needs a marketing campaign.  #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeeHurstComic: You can feel the tension rising. Its going to kick off big style soon. Boris The Dictator needs to back off now as he w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: Some people seem to think Ive had the vaccine, I may as well get a vaccine passport. Thats like saying Ive got an or]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @battleaxeBrit1: Shame on the Government for not providing any level of  support to the teacher at Batley Grammar School!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: How long would this criminal event last if everyone stood up like this brave man? https://t.co/8HvKcQFFmk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Another conspiracy lie come true  Dont you think its time to start listening ? https://t.co/8v8K2W5Vtb https://t.co/7O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: If we all took part in this.....  how things might change. https://t.co/uxyL8K0Umv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattletiss7: Hey Government please dont send me or my family any covid tests as were not ill, (if we have any symptoms well stay hom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@solusnan1 You psychopath]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SomeToby @BreesAnna You cant stop the spread of flu you fucking imbecile]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Benjani1104 @danwootton Off you go Benjani back to your piss soaked mattress and we'll live our lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Ive been fighting this criminal Covid agenda for over 12 months now.   Ive had police at my door  helicopters over m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SimonPearson961: If people actually thought there was a deadly virus that was really life threatening and had a similar death rate to p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Had a  number helicopters over my house for 4 hours yesterday.  They dont scare me. https://t.co/i54Gk6QpTw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddersbloom: Because it is not about health Something journalists still don't get. Including you Peter. https://t.co/W5tmnxmZRV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulepearson @JuliaHB1 Paul just pissoff back to your piss sodden mattress.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @9thfloor: Great scenes across the country today of hundreds of thousands of Britons ignoring what they know is a lie. Now we need to do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Big pro govt propaganda campaign seems underway today to convince us that there is widespread support for Vaccine Passport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Tony Blairs Vaccines are your route to liberty"  is the 21 centurys equivalent of the Nazi concentration camp slogan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Supermarket workers come into contact with 1000s of people weekly. All of them would be in contact with a multiple carr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Steve_Laws_: Day in, day out, I watch illegals get ferried in by the Border Force and then every now and then Priti puts out a statemen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: There are only two Groups of people that still follow mask  vaccine because this is a pandemic narrative:  Group 1 -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeeHurstComic: Watch Britains celebrities segue seamlessly from supporting all Covid lockdowns to campaigning for cancer victims cause]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Reliable sources such as the BBC  #fakenews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Any surprise here folks?  BREAKING - Hancock, Vallance and Whitty all heavily invested in Vaccine Industry..  https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: The clearest most honest appraisal of the Covid situation to date.   Retweets are better than likes.   https://t.co/NnN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Even though its impossible for a ship to get into this position by accident, it could be unloaded in under 12 hours  f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peoplenotrobot1: @BlackersNot https://t.co/WXJi9f0Uiw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@3_resurection @JamesDelingpole @MoriartyProfJ3 #boycottpimlicoplumbers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisWickNews Knew it was a scam from the off.  So no not in the slightest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Many people have now contacted me about bad, prolonged, experiences post Oxford/AstraZeneca vaccine - yet we hardly se]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carolina_moon1: Please share as far as you can. My father in law in Sept healthy. Gave him AstraZeneca 19th Jan, Took to his bed ill ne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AmyMek: "I do not broadcast the [Muhammad] cartoons to provoke; I do it because we have to show that we stand for freedom of speech and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: This guy is truth. https://t.co/tG9PFfz5DJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @freenationtoday: BRADFORD TOMORROW 1PM  NO VAX PASS NEEDED TO ATTEND   In walking distance of 2 train stations and next door to the bus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: 3,964 DEAD 162,610 Injuries: European Database of Adverse Drug Reactions for COVID-19 Vaccines  Remove the underscore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LPerrins Time and time again we have supported radical muslims.  They will never support us.  When will people understand this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SayeedaWarsi This is about decades of trying to change our culture  And im not having it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamuelJJack2 @JamesDelingpole Also in the 80's if a teacher was spouting shit we'd pull them up on it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VanessaGray158 @JamesDelingpole They can not force anyone to take it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eleonorasfalcon @PeakePolly @WessTam77 @JamesDelingpole My immune system will do perfectly well on its own.  Why help weaken it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NuCosmicDimming @Tara500 @faystarot Unfortunately no as 99% of them died from un-related covid deaths.  Prove me wrong.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmma85 @ProKlausSchwab #boycottpimlicoplumbers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suemitch2017 @PeakePolly @battleaxeBrit1 None here,   Is there a problem not wanting an experimental concoction injected into one's self?  I'd love to hear your take.  Go ahead please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolPrestonArt @PeakePolly @battleaxeBrit1 Automated texts?  Yeah that's some timewasting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Stocky339 @PeakePolly @viesvies1 Is that an order Dave?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suemitch2017 @PeakePolly @battleaxeBrit1 She is leaving it so what is your problem?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ferdinand641 @PeakePolly @MadyWaterer Ferdinand just have yours and leave the rest of us alone.  Deal?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeakePolly @JamesDelingpole Same here, I've had 5 texts 1 letter so far.  Their desperation stinks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@talkRADIO @prwhittle @JuliaHB1 Pandering to them as ever giving them air-time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PatriotActive66 Dont even give these scum air-time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LozzaFox It shouldn't even be debated in this country,  Ever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UsforThemUK: One week today children will have broken up for the Easter holidays.   They must not return for the summer term in masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke Boycott #pimlicoplumbers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cityintel1:  UK protest alert   Anti mask protest in UK superstores   For more information email cityintel2@gmail.com #cityintel #pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @patcondell: My new video on YouTube. Im expecting them to remove it, so if you want to watch it there youd better hurry up. https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Can I point something out....  Our immune system is 100, 000 years in the making. We are designed to cope to with virus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simon_reeve This hack has been blackmailed otherwise he'll lose his job.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterRagg: Boris Johnson must go now. Please retweet if you agree. Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrimleyJack: @YorkusMarcus @JamesDelingpole   Worth watching: https://t.co/4zsdLOizF8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@talkRADIO @mrmarkdolan @simon_reeve @simon-reeve another lefty arsehole]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Please RT and discuss... don't let them give our country away without a struggle. https://t.co/hFqo13CNxW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arwenstar: All parents must unite against this monstrosity.  https://t.co/zbBQhoptng]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Childrens risk of Covid death by CDC figs is below 0.00001%  Childrens risk of vaccine death by CDC figures is 0.048%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDelingpole: Anyone who allows their child to be injected with experimental treatment for a disease that isn't going to hurt them i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GMB @ITV Cos she's a greedy fucker]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Do one you Evil Cunt!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @docuterror: #Europes Elite want their citizens to believe #OpenBorders  #Migration from #Islamic Countries will solve their need for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: This is by far the BIGGEST UK protest I have seen. They will not be able to police these crowds.   #RightToProtest #londonpr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ElaineW60: TAKE IT DOWN - RETWEET https://t.co/dpLj55xz0l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jonnyhodl: A couple of hundred protestors. Amirite, @BBCNews @SkyNews ?  https://t.co/2vp7aQJR2U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SkyNews @SkyEnda Fake News]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NancyLeeGrahn Very classy falling over another 2 times]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Steve_Laws_: Demo day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimDOfficial: David Lammy and Lenny Henry think Africa doesn't need any white saviours this #RedNoseDay... So Give it to us instead and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JBainsworthy: TAKE IT DOWN - RETWEET  Women in the UK need to feel safe to walk the streets but are confronted by the face of an abuser]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: I am asking ALL of my followers to RETWEET this:   For obvious mental health reasons, @JoeBiden has declined a public dis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Michael54325847: My business closed for most of the past 12 months. My savings nearly gone. Medics, politicians  public service still]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage Who cares now Fuck Off!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlackersNot: This should be sent to every MP in the country. An unwillingness to even consider the evidence which contradicts governmen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertJenrick: Were always proud to fly the Union Flag at @mhclg Its a symbol of liberty and freedom that binds the whole country tog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDelingpole: This traitor is TOTALLY unsuited to be our King https://t.co/ZENnptWaSz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: I will be off twitter for a while. At least till after the demonstrations coming up in which I will be attending and pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreedomIsrael_: #Israel is now officially an #Apartheid state.  The sign on the table says Seating for those with the Green Label  We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Friends let me say what you all know.  The only way to change anything is civil disobedience.  You have to get on the s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @crimlawuk: Emergency powers to deal with COVID must not be allowed to remain in place once the emergency is over.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: You really can't watch or listen to mainstream media anymore, it's constant propaganda and social engineering. I monit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LPerrins: We will witness a cranking up of the hate against the non vaccinated in the following weeks, by @BorisJohnson and his cronies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @prwhittle: A serious political party does not put out a tweet like this.   However , one that systematically ignored the mass rape of y]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>