<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[ENTRIES ARE OPEN for 2 COSPLAY CONTESTS for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! Which ONE are you? CONTEST RULES are now posted on our website. ENTRIES CLOSE May 7, 11:59pm! https://t.co/824a0l190e **CASH PRIZES! ENTRY FEE $25**  online May 21-23, 2021 #cosplay #cosplaysunday https://t.co/eHptam0xdg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WILL YOU COME TO PLAY? DUNGEONS  DRAGONS tickets are now open for FIVE DIFFERENT GAMES at FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! $30 entry. Check out details at https://t.co/QP2a07wVzxonline May 21-23  #comics #comiccon  #DUNGEONSANDDRAGONS #DUNGEONMASTER https://t.co/BSdNUuRbvr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LDUV2wK6vf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ENTRY OPENS TODAY at 5PM EST for 2 COSPLAY CONTESTS for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! CONTEST RULES are now posted on our website. ENTRIES OPEN MAY 2! https://t.co/824a0l190e **CASH PRIZES! ENTRY FEE $25**  FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23 #cosplay https://t.co/9v6ZACbwo1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lpPaQ90iZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Announcing DUNGEONS  DRAGONS tickets are now open for FIVE DIFFERENT GAMES at FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! $30 entry. Check out details at https://t.co/QP2a07wVzx  Online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC #Fanfaire  #comics #comiccon #DUNGEONSANDDRAGONS #DUNGEONMASTER https://t.co/SKT7cvCRHu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MASQUERADE COSPLAY ENTRY OPENS TODAY at 5PM EST for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! CONTEST RULES are now posted on our website. ENTRIES OPEN MAY 2! https://t.co/824a0l190e **1st PRIZE $150! ENTRY FEE $25** FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #cosplay https://t.co/G6nLGLavpC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TECHNICAL COSPLAY ENTRY OPENS TODAY at 5PM EST for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! CONTEST RULES are posted on our website. ENTRIES OPEN MAY 2! https://t.co/824a0l190e **1st PRIZE $200! ENTRY FEE $25**Special $15 fee for HSAD Students #cosplay #cosplaysunday https://t.co/oVw4wyav2b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[brisk spring days, you need a new layer! FanfaireNYC MERCH in colors and sizes you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  and raise money for High School of Art  Design*REGISTER https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23 #comiccon  #hoodie https://t.co/Qlo1JWeoCD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/g0VBJwpshp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WE LOVE WEB COMICS at FANFAIRENYC! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet J. L. Westover , Cartoonist and Author *REGISTER at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  J. L. Westover is the creator of the worlds sweatiest comic, Mr. Lovenstein  #cartoonist  #webcomics #mrlovenstein https://t.co/JxSDPnKcJT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WAKEY WAKEY with a cuppa! Merch in colors and sizes you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  HELP US raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. REGISTER AT: https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE to attend FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #comics #comiccon https://t.co/4pl31QBPjE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/akTXWehdij]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANIMATION RULES! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet J.J. Sedelmaier, Artist/Animator *REGISTER at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  J. J. is an illustrator, designer, author, and film director/producer, co-creator of "Saturday TV Funhouse". #comiccon #animator #animation https://t.co/azWhyF1P6l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANIMATION RULES! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Scott Christian Sava, Animator/Director  *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  Scott Christian Sava is an animator, illustrator, director, writer, and producer #animator #animation  #animalcrackersfilm https://t.co/Expc1Ez70q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BabAQBorFO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANIMATION RULES! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Rachel Gitlevich, Animator *REGISTER at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE   Rachel Gitlevich is a 2D character animator and designer working in New York City.  #comics #comiccon #comicart  #artist #animation #animator https://t.co/sG33gQDaHe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#boss Merch in colors and sizes you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  HELP raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. REGISTER NOW: https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE to attend FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23  #FanfaireNYC  #comiccon #charlizetheron https://t.co/TjJlQRj4x3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GUS APPROVES of FanfaireNYC MERCH! in colors and sizes you will LOVE too https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  HELP US raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. REGISTER NOW: https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE to attend FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23 #comics #gus https://t.co/SBFWWVX0Aj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[is that Cedric or Edward repping FanfaireNYC? Merch in colors you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  HELP US raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. REGISTER: https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23 #twilight #harrypotter https://t.co/vLPB395akw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oJB8tOwZQz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GRAPHIC DESIGN love at FANFAIRENYC! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Elizabeth Daggar, Graphic Designer  *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  Elizabeth Daggar is the Design Director for NYC  Company, the tourism marketing organization for New York City. https://t.co/RBd0k0Uptf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yzD88xMAHf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please donate to Art Design PTA . Shout out to our FASHION students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously: https://t.co/hFRHybU6N5   #GivingTuesday https://t.co/GFYOXS6pGr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FANFAIRENYC builds up your dreams with ARCHITECT guests! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Koray Duman, Architect *REGISTER  at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE   Koray Duman is the principal of B-KD (Bro Koray Duman), a research-driven architecture studio. https://t.co/iRCf8sgCct]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please donate to Art Design PTA . Shout out to our PHOTOGRAPHY students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously: https://t.co/hFRHybU6N5. #GivingTuesday https://t.co/647En46Lgi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FANFAIRENYC builds up your dreams with ARCHITECT guests!  Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet @taewookcha Landscape Architect *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  Taewook is a founder of Supermass Studio with clients including LaGuardias New Terminal B. https://t.co/trzCYoUM8W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/N6p8cQZEUs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#oscarsafterparty Merch in colors and sizes you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  HELP US raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. Please REGISTER NOW: https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE to attend FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #comics #comiccon https://t.co/Vds3eUiBP0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FANFAIRENYC but make it FASHION! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Lisa Di Napoli, Fashion Designer *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  Lisa Di Napoli has led teams at Tommy Hilfiger, Gap Kids, Best  Co., and H.M. . https://t.co/TogiinFmMl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FANFAIRENYC but make it FASHION! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Rachel Hall Danes, Fashion Entrepreneur *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE   Rachel founded The Danes collection a key luxury source for women. https://t.co/9hK4tSBLyj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FANFAIRENYC but make it FASHION!  Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Hisham Oumlil, Fashion Designer *REGISTER at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  OUMLILis a label founded upon a belief that we are here to celebrate life and that we often seek renewal, which empowers us. https://t.co/8otwhEbRMk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FANFAIRENYC but make it FASHION! Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Deanna Kei, Fashion Illustrator and Designer *REGISTER at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  Deanna has worked with high-profile clients including Tommy Hilfiger, Betsey Johnson and Karl Lagerfeld Paris. https://t.co/KlMeOkrh0x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eoUG2LsvNB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KOfitnessny: Cant wait!!! https://t.co/6bimtmaCBP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TODAY'S THE DAY to buy for FanfaireNYC swag if you want to have it for the event! Merch in colors and sizes you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwsbik HELP US raise money for High School of Art  Design. REGISTER NOW: https://t.co/iA9T84xdbc  FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace 5/21-23 https://t.co/M9Ea5Z39IB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet @simonfraser Comics Artist and Writer *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84xdbc . His credits include drawing Judge Dredd, Kingsman and Doctor Who. https://t.co/WIc3f7a3ER]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/or33VMfhWO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet @GilbertFord, Illustrator/Author  *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE . Gilbert has illustrated many New York Times Best Selling middle grade novels and award winning picture books.#artist #childrensbooks #author https://t.co/GErxO4EFx6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet our SPECIAL GUEST Stphane Roux, Comic Book Artist known for his amazing cover art for Marvel, DC and Semic comics.*REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE  #comics #comiccon #comicart #comicsartist #artstudents #artsinschools https://t.co/gAdPe0LOKK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/heFpdw4fsq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Guests Join Fanfaire NYC - May 21-23  - https://t.co/enf79NrEMW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SHOW YOUR LOVE for FanfaireNYC!  Merch in colors and sizes you will LOVE https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU  HELP US raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. REGISTER NOW: https://t.co/iA9T84fCjE to attend FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #comiccon https://t.co/im8GRc4d2z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bWtuKl8gqJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ORDER before Sunday if you want to wear your FanfaireNYC t-shirt for the event! SHOP NOW HERE: https://t.co/2LPIPwJMGU to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for High School of Art  Design. FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #Fanfaire #comics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1ap6Q7iFzv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GQWA2lYdmv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WORK IT! We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design https://t.co/R34PU502fk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please donate to Art Design PTA .   Shout out to our ILLUSTRATION students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. . Please give generously: https://t.co/QWpAvMzFnP https://t.co/LyizJRQlEi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shout out to our ANIMATION students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously to support their dreams. Donate at: https://t.co/QWpAvMzFnP #GivingTuesday https://t.co/VF9NLcIP4b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanaSchwartzzz: Q-Tips: do not insert swabs into ear canal https://t.co/jMDQqo1quT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gabriele_Corno: Whales in the garden - Canada - https://t.co/vpnIk1Tg0Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVER YOUR MOUTH, BUT MAKE IT FANFAIRENYC!  We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0NeyawMKeS for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design https://t.co/3YOPF1ci3x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANNOUNCING 2 COSPLAY CONTESTS for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! CONTEST RULES are now posted on our website. ENTRIES OPEN MAY 2! https://t.co/IjZ5XMt9ZS  **PRIZES WILL BE GREAT! ENTRY FEES WILL BE WORTH IT. More info to come**   Save the Date online May 21-23, 2021 https://t.co/438KgogQGr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @KOfitnessny at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/D0GJp6zRqE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @JamelShabazz  at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/Ia7FvbJ1SI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Kofitnessnycosplay, Cosplayer and MASQUERADE COSPLAY CONEST JUDGE! *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/Joviwt135K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Jamel Shabazz, Photographer *REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/5pix0MZpVe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @AnneFizzard    at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/WRKiQ2vfhn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Anne  Fizzard, Cartoonist  REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/PkGWnRHS88]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @LucyKnisley  at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/AsWYnMBtpl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @mimizchao at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/OPS1o6Ghnl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @LockettDown  at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/YN9V9UZ52r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We can't wait to have @artbymoga at FanfaireNYC  REGISTER at https://t.co/qe6kd4ho0P https://t.co/FUS8TFl7l0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't wait to have Cecilia Arana at FanfaireNYC   @nyckidsproject  REGISTER at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/SKqlkno9Ix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Regine L. Sawyer, Writer/Publisher REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/jBmnKGUlIL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Hlne Alexander, Fashion Designer and Arts Educator and TECHNICAL COSPLAY CONTEST JUDGE!! REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/lMut9Gzrc3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Mimi Chao,  Illustrator  REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/7TamSef2ES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Meg Adams, Comics and Story Artist  **REGISTER NOW at https://t.co/DbC2U9FLOX https://t.co/wg1VKgzoDe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shout out to our ARCHITECTURE students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously to support their dreams. Donate at https://t.co/QWpAvMzFnP  #GivingTuesday https://t.co/0ExuBILD49]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shout out to our ILLUSTRATION students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously to support their dreams. Donate at https://t.co/qHKiY1iGkW #GivingTuesday https://t.co/OCKlVjRIq8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YOUR DOG NEEDS THIS. YOU KNOW THEY DO.  We are thrilled to announce new FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for High School of Art  Design. Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace  May 21-23, 2021 https://t.co/uBKxJFJMkV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANNOUNCING 2 COSPLAY CONTESTS for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! CONTEST RULES are now posted: ENTRIES OPEN MAY 2! https://t.co/CepNv5fj15 . **PRIZES WILL BE GREAT! ENTRY FEES WILL BE WORTH IT. More info to come** Save the Date online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC #cosplay https://t.co/NZcL2mBb1b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who can resist a tie-dye t-shirt? already planning to wear it to shop for MORE comic books  We have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk  Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 https://t.co/d1saY6CbaW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Sam Lisenco, Production Designer .  .  .  .  .  Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/8lBKdPJuCL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Cecilia Arana, Artistic Director . . . . . Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/nPsWlpr9Tf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Lucy Knisley, Cartoonist  .  .  .  .  .  Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/h2WmK295Zt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Laura Freeman, Coretta Scott King Honor Illustrator  .  .  .  .  .  Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/S2wH2L9LXm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Mickey Torres, Art Director/Cosplayer, MASQUERADE COSPLAY CONTEST JUDGE!!  .  .  .  .  .  Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/LcY8BIWmjw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThatEricAlper: pre and after lockdown https://t.co/5AYM0eGDlO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Judy Stephens, Producer/Cosplayer, TECHNICAL COSPLAY CONTEST JUDGE!! . . . . .  Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/NWqCfpfdUU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FanfaireNYC  Cosplay Contests! Merch! New Guests Announced! - https://t.co/IagOMpx2UU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Opal Lines: An illustrator, filmmaker, and grad from the School of Visual Arts NYC. She directed and created her short film 'Check Yes!' which was selected for the NY Latino Film Festival, NFFTY  NY Dominican Film Festival. https://t.co/0m0E4BEAvv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Snoopy: Grow from every challenge life throws at you. https://t.co/nLHa6ke8vW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Ray Alma, Animator:  Ray is a contributor to Mad magazine, one of "The Usual Gang of Idiots". Ray has ventured into the world of animation and storyboarding on Showtime's "Our Cartoon President" Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/ah6JNyUlXh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come to FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace and meet Chrissy Fellmeth, Animator: I'm an artist and animator based out of Queens NY. I have been a storyboard artist for Our Cartoon President for Showtime Network and T.O.T.S. for Disney Jr.  Stay tuned for #FanfaireNYC news https://t.co/w71NTZ2iqp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HOODIE! HOOODIEEEEE! HOOOOODDIIEEEEEE! ! We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk  show you love  FanfaireNYC and raise money for High School of Art  Design. . . . . Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace May 21-23, 2021 https://t.co/2tBG49fdKu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANNOUNCING 2 COSPLAY CONTESTS for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!! CONTEST RULES are now posted: ENTRIES OPEN MAY 2! https://t.co/IjZ5XMKLos . **PRIZES WILL BE GREAT! ENTRY FEES WILL BE WORTH IT. More info to come** Save the Date online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC #cosplay https://t.co/PssWZwYAGK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We need your help: Please subscribe to the FanfaireNYC YouTube channel so we can do a live feed as part of FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace!    https://t.co/r2gHDNfYKb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We  our comic stores #comiccon #fanfairenyc https://t.co/ehlkyu0vyy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BAG IT IN STYLE! We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design. Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 https://t.co/6fOTA531dv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design.  . Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC https://t.co/AaQaOhSTXK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[G'morning! TIME FOR COFFEE!! We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design.  . . . . Be there online May 21-23, 2021 https://t.co/nWNIgZb7me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shout out to our FILM students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously to support their dreams. Donate at https://t.co/qHKiY1iGkW #GivingTuesday https://t.co/0SzrnawXcA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[buy some FanfaireNYC merchandise to show your fandom and support of High School of Art  Design Fanfaire NYC 2021 Gus T-Shirt on @Bonfire https://t.co/k3QhIZYiCA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design.  . Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design.  . Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC https://t.co/nudUssyJAq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce we have FanfaireNYC merchandise https://t.co/0Neyawv9nk for you to show your love of FanfaireNYC and raise money for our beloved High School of Art  Design.   Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC https://t.co/s6eHfOJpb1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shout out to our ILLUSTRATION students! The mission of the High School of Art  Design is to inspire, educate, and fully prepare our gifted students to become exceptional artists. Please give generously to support their dreams. Donate at https://t.co/qHKiY1iGkW #GivingTuesday https://t.co/wLjK66PMhk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WE  COSPLAY AT FANFAIRENYC! Please STAY TUNED FOR OUR VIRTUAL COSPLAY CONTEST CALL FOR ENTRIES. Save the Date for FanfaireNYC Launch Into Cyberspace online May 21-23, 2021 #FanfaireNYC #Fanfaire #FanfaireLaunchIntoCyberspace #comics #comiccon #fanfairenyc2021 #comicart https://t.co/2q2LQ2u7dL]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>