<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Darasim41102047 Ok so send me $45 rn on Venmo cash app or PayPal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_wildmilk: lmaooo this was a legitimate email my sister sent to a college professor when she forgot to submit a paper whilst drunk at a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Darasim41102047 No youll just ask for my bank account info]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goodwillcowboy I dont watch Harry Potter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I been trying to manifest something for two days now why tf isnt it working]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@glickzac Ok no offense but I thought I switched the age]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why would i ever want someone to see my Twitter account. Yes I downloaded it https://t.co/KlIwJAIuw7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So who am I gonna call on when I ain't got them boys with me And the situation gets a little sticky I'ma dial 911 like a motherfuckin' punk, fuck that, bla bla I'mma call that rude boy from Detroit, Trick Trick Quick come pick me up, bring them guns Come to the club, meet me out https://t.co/eMiHzVgN3L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gddog93 @StPaulSaints LOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sxttre There are some ethical boundaries that wouldnt allow me too (out of benefit for you and I) and I also dont work in an outpatient setting so Im not available to schedule individual sessions with people, but I can always help refer you if need be!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4th day of may. May it be with you or whatever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StPaulSaints Hello gentlemen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cheat code 69420: say out loud and the universe will destroy your landlord https://t.co/NgX8pGzKQi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itsmeheythere Omfg Anyone can learn all of the theories, modalities, and interventions there are but at the end of the day there is a personality and awareness factor that a lot of therapists dont have. My patients are definitely much smarter than me about their experiences]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyways https://t.co/lhh7dXOfCj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpenSpenBurt It 8:30 a.m. rn (CDT)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As a therapist I find like 90% of therapists annoying and dumb. I am also annoying and dumb but hopefully not in a clinical setting https://t.co/BO9oMtRUy1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday! I already ate my lunch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pebbut @JellieBeanes My precious kid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BraveWilderness Make it bite you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Twins @AKirilloff19 Apparently hes not nvm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Twins @AKirilloff19 Im single]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gameOFshane I dont either i think its dumb that 460k people did]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KylePlantEmoji @jazz_inmypants I love when my two bitches are together in one place]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KylePlantEmoji Is this u @jazz_inmypants]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pebbut @JellieBeanes My precious kids]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pebbut @JellieBeanes Omg is this ur gf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@taylornotffound Used to get stressed out by my flaws then I realized]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drewblockchainz What the fuck else is there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charleszinn1111 @kaylaszabo_ Ur still going wtf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpacemanVinny Sounds like ur kind of a piece of work too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charleszinn1111 @kaylaszabo_ Ok what am I missing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ihavenousefora1 It didnt help]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tertleproof This is aggressive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EarnWithBrenda Invest in deez nuts brenda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to go through the annoying replies under my viral tweets and be a bitch for fun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gameOFshane Can you just not have fun and laugh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoganPaul I been on the low I been taking my time. I feel like Im outta my mind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kennedyjavelin @FINALLEVEL ya it fuckin is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This should be illegal and is witchcraft. Burn him https://t.co/CYlFUYuLmt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BOpKx9C2tL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most recent celebrity in your camera roll is who marries bill gates next https://t.co/X8LNe5MOHr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Maybe if he was cuter she would have stayed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pic of me Taking a show er https://t.co/4EisHgXCmr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Me too.... https://t.co/bOjobFwqHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ValterSkarsgard You gotta check this out then https://t.co/OgELiaNK6b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No way https://t.co/ZdUo7PneJy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lilymancini01 Its huge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dms open bill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why that literally so dumb you have so much money why are you unhappy https://t.co/qtWGVMmwiK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dover_29 Fake fan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ben1Smart1 Idk Ive never seen it sorry to 30 rock if I stole this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this guy has DMd me on ig a few times regarding my viral tweets but he doesnt actually follow me on here. Yea Im talking about you Austin smh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackWilliamRtF May 29th I stg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[imagine if fianc was pronounced like Beyonc lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[for my birthday this year I would like to be given one free, no penalty hipaa violation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KaceyMusgraves keep up the good work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Target I would like to buy some things]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL I think this was cool https://t.co/h0tYRMeL82]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@parmesangirl Vegas lounge ugh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbfan911: On my morning walk  https://t.co/bT5sGzUTX1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL We would call that.......... self absorbed...... yep. Cole hard fact]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LAST TIME I WENT THERE A REALLY DRUNK GUY CAME UP TO ME WITH HIS EYES CLOSED AND SAID I WAS CUTE THEN PUKED UNDER A TABLE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants have you ever thrown a fistful of glitter in the air]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NO ACTUALLY WE DONT I DO NOT WANT TO IF YOU WANT TO GO DM ME SO I CAN PSYCHOLOGICALLY EVALUATE YOU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WE JUST REALLY WANT TO GO TO COWBOY JACKS OK https://t.co/FDjKRzcktW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thank you everyone, good night  https://t.co/u471k0ofb8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sprousecharlie_ I know, I dont. I like how I look. But I hope you find a better way to treat people :) words can really hurt others even if its from a stranger on the internet. You deserve to have positive interactions with others instead of saying mean things]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sprousecharlie_ That was mean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KylePlantEmoji That is the goal of life my good sir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KylePlantEmoji Waiter: how would you like your steak cooked sir?  Me: *slams fist* BOILED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey real quick before I go here just like in case youre mad sorry for everything Ive ever done whether it was good or bad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@umm_sheawhat Oh ok maybe I was wrong. My masters degree is worthless]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[did you know the further you get into higher eduaction the bigger the diploma is. Thats the only advantage of grad school]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants Kk talk to u at 7am my time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants I dont remember that no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS How can I get rid of the pores on my nose theyre so big]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants Ive seen like 3 pics of u tops]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants Tonight I hope ur sleep paralysis is central time zone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants ITS 9:42PM WHAT DO YOU THINK IM DOING? NOT BEINF IN TWITTER?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants Stfu this is exactly what you would have said]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants Didnt deserve it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Thenastyboys615 Thats just how they are :) ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jimscov732 Oh yea confirmed you are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jimscov732 R u obsessed with me or something]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jimscov732 @StjohnMatthew14 What are you trying to say Jim scoville Im listening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Propaganda. Italians are not this nice https://t.co/QcsYmxTHTs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wa hacked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I don't have that #swag :( Do you???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey guys me again! . Please follow me https://t.co/NMZadjljDc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingJames Best Buy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IdiotRyanKahl: oh really https://t.co/cTpHFdNQ3z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matchu_chutrain Please dont joke about our breakup like this on a public platform?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow seems like a lot of you have actually experienced this! To those of you who have, I have some advice: maybe dont suck and you wont get dumped!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jbfan911: Imagine ur reading  a breakup text on ur Apple Watch lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[going on a missions trip with a group of people but purposefully trying to convert the people to a different religion than the others youre with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On my morning walk  https://t.co/bT5sGzUTX1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants Cringe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jazz_inmypants I just used u for this u know I hate u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont have to imagine it anymore https://t.co/ai2vrlunie]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>