<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoojeeBear I thought Sweden... until a friend who has Swedish family reported that even though they didn't have a government imposed lockdown the people did it voluntarily!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LewisTa45225561 Same here, it's a tricky one.   Maybe its not so much the place, more so finding a community to sustain one another and live freely...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Question time -   What country would you consider moving to, in order to try and avoided this tyrannical world?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: Remember when the corrupt WHO posted this? Why did they change their minds I wonder... https://t.co/byMOU2WyGb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClarkeMicah: I always ask for details of what happened beforehand when I see such films, but walloping a seated man, from behind, seems]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any business in Wales taking part in the #TheGreatReopening please let us know so we can share!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hayley_2021: I have not worked hard for 8 years to build up my business to have it destroyed by a scam. I'm ready to fight for my busin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BritainFree: Weve heard thousands upon thousands of you say enough is enough in recent weeks.  To all those struggling businesses wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maevey: @AntiLockdownW can we get #TheGreatReopening trending all week? It's time that shops and businesses open up Saturday 30th Janua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @donkamion78: Government admit they put covid-19 on every death certificate https://t.co/FS5sJDEvVz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SGJackson: What Pfizer isnt telling you! https://t.co/p9QkTPpQSE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaisyAdeleleo: Bars, restaurants opening up in France, Italy and the Netherlands next weekend . Theyve had enough! It is catching on i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexbruesewitz @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris They got chocolate chip cookies though... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A time when the British people had pride and respected that freedom has to be fought for.   It's disgraceful to see what the British government, police and public majority has become. The millions that died at war have been let down. https://t.co/IYAKwAdv59]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The police have caught onto 'THE GREAT OPENING' and are sweeping through social media with propaganda.  It's a boring repetitive narrative. https://t.co/mh7D7PgHqU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pavlovsdog86: @DHSCgovuk Let's play emotional blackmail. https://t.co/Lz1UciOkbt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ghost_wales: Meanwhile under a Welsh Labour government of 22 years  200,000 children still live in poverty but not to worry theres lot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CameronOEdwards: Would you pay someone over 100,000 a year to make your life worse? No, so why do people still support the Welsh Assem]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's all one big joke https://t.co/1EHlIXy4DB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DefundBBC: It seems the BBC is still unclear about what the British public think of its output and the live TV tax that funds it, and s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Richardski_UK: We @AbolishAssembly have stated for more than 6 months, that @SeneddWales elections will more than likely be delayed, us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: 4,500,000 people in the UK are now on an NHS waiting list after cancelled treatments and screenings, and 70,000 UK househol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @greatorex: Welsh hospitality is on its knees because of the restrictions that we have all adhered to. Seemingly the rules dont apply i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brdlnrs: Well, the Italian's have just confirmed it! This madness only ends when the masses resist https://t.co/WlUxo5R92f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emmakennytv Has been a source of light, kindness and truth during these unlawful lockdowns, please follow her platforms https://t.co/nlNOuXVVF4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: The field equivalent of a face mask! https://t.co/Gc0K3E80bP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kateandtheboys: Well, eldest boy was just made to leave Sainsburys for not wearing a mask, despite saying he was exempt, because he di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFreePeopleA1: Can we grow some balls in the UK?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beautiful https://t.co/wBP2Q2KjO5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disgusting. https://t.co/brCfJMo3g2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UK_UNIFICATION: Trudeau's Coronavirus tyranny. https://t.co/hIhOYNIYL9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: The lockdown police dont like to be policed.  https://t.co/2z4YpAAZxz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: This is outrageous. I am going to be posting a video on the erosion of our civil liberties at 6pm tonight. https://t.co/k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Beyno22: Wales    We have been in tier 4 for ever  The children finish school early  Restrictions came in for Christmas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are we surprised...? https://t.co/c0yLG7L2PH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Are you, or do you know anyone, between 16-30 and against lockdown?   DM us to join a 'Youthers' network    Meet like-minded young people  Fight social isolation   Explore the truth free from fear or derision   Please RT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Probably the most important 2 minute video I've ever put together for UK citizens - I'll have to do this for other countrie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rob_miller12345: New Normal policing in action. A 92 year-old arrested for being present at a demonstration. https://t.co/epzW5hmoNf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Apparently 25% of the over 80s have already been vaccinated. So when the elderly and vulnerable have been vaccinated, sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PrisonerOfWar5: @Lyndonx 23 died OF covid in North Wales, 8 in South Wales in 2020....deadly pandemic  https://t.co/6QBQhhAzDl https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eastantrimmp: Thousands of businesses closed.   Hundreds of thousands of jobs lost.  Childrens development and education damaged.  Loc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @heritagepartyuk: A third lockdown in the UK is the wrong course of action for a virus that has not increased mortality above a normal w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IsabelOakeshott: Look at these Guardian headlines! Every winter, the NHS is at breaking point ...! https://t.co/yhfMJVFApx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emmakennytv: I know many of you feel alone...youre wrong because behind the scenes a group of scientists and clinicians are coming tog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCarlVernon: I've often wondered how, under dictatorships, such atrocities have happened in history.  I wonder no more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeremyClarkson: Dear the newspapers. I didnt battle Covid. I lay on my bed reading a book till it went away]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rhonda52807071: Sadly my father in law died of cancer yesterday (90). To our shock they blatantly told us they have to put Covid-19 as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: Close to 100 doctors, nurses and orderlies have a message for the world: they are having the time of their lives  and they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeangMikey: @DanStevens1103 @AntiLockdownW Lockdown measures will not work, they only put more lives, the economy, social, physical and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @photopro28: @Davidwenningto1 @JuliaHB1 We don't have 50,000 people testing positive per day, we only have the government telling us tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikeylusmusic: @simondolan This is the video https://t.co/dBnf9WqHKq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanStevens1103: 1918 Spanish Flu  vs  2020 COVID HOAX https://t.co/xEhlgbPQYZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/842PYwoUTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wales is becoming a joke  stop consenting to the idiots that run our country! https://t.co/WCZslziZxN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sc0ttay2h0ttay @MinistryDissent That's disgusting behavior.  This plandemic has pulled out the finest of society fighting for its cause.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same thing happened when I didn't wear a mask on the train and a young lad took his off.  Influence is powerful. https://t.co/RWbCXbgCgK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over the last 30 years, 2020 sits 14th in highest death rates, bang on average.   THIS IS NOT ABOUT A 'VIRUS' https://t.co/ZXGEP4gGK0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StandUpX2: THESE PROTESTS ARE BECOMING MORE SERIOUS. A few coaches arriving to London today stopped by the police - video footage to be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinDaubney: Here we go again. Why do the Met #TakeTheKnee to #BlackLivesMatter  soft-soap #ExtinctionRebellion  yet send in the bo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: More than 60 anti-lockdown protesters have been arrested in London today.   If they had been Black Lives Matter instead,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the direction the world is going in https://t.co/rRIZM9KAOf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meandmecash: Wow this gets more corrupt by the minute.   https://t.co/rDfydezNgw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChalecosAmarill: En #Francia AHORA el pueblo en la Bastilla se defiende de los ataques de los FASCISTAS, FUERA EL ESTADO POLICIAL!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[POLICE ARE MOVING WITH PANIC https://t.co/aRzPgc2Zue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ LIVE STREAM WATCH NOW   Protest in Paris  People are STANDING UP WITH FORCE!   https://t.co/nOGvymy8Wu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE STREAM - WATCH NOW   Anti Lockdown Protest - London https://t.co/cPEdSanzxs via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmmaSGarrett: My dad died today in a nursing home.   He was tested for Covid 3 times over the last 3 weeks.   He was negative every tim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS MUST END  @BorisJohnson look at what you're doing! https://t.co/ej0ALYqO6q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carlheneghan: Here's what happened when I posted our latest  @spectator article to Facebook - I'm aware this is happening to others - w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ltNOyqZyVx https://t.co/5qobJOfXJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charliekirk11: If you're okay with a government powerful enough to keep you locked in your home between 10 PM  5 AM for no reason what]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emmakennytv: I  realise that I have felt afraid to speak out. Im vocal, but Ive still not explicitly told my truth Ive seen my Mum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: 1 in 7 companies is on the verge of going out of business and we are heading for a double dip recession. Lockdown is doin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindaL16: Do your thing twitter   They are about to assault school children. Welsh Health Quack is @vaughangething (him who who was ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's some the the UK's new kids cruising over to spend your tax money on flat screen TV's  champers, whilst bopping to rap music.   So nice to see them thriving when fleeing from war and famine...    https://t.co/h6SlSiUo06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeahButlerSmith Blimey!! Can that be circulated?  As so many people still don't believe these things when we simply tell them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep. https://t.co/13UiJMouwS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeahButlerSmith Is there evidence of this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: I see that my tweets are upsetting left wing journalists again. I must be doing something right.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Millions is being spent on an absolute con...   https://t.co/Qc4esO8xeR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's frightening that people actually vote for compulsory vaccines https://t.co/IYzz1lpalC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK civilian death toll of WWII was 450,700 or more... You're VERY wrong.    The worldwide WWII civilian death toll was 45 million or more... COVID is supposedly 1.29 million.  THEY DO NOT COMPARE IN ANY WAY. STOP SPREADING FEAR THROUGH LIES.     https://t.co/ZbmjPW9kHM https://t.co/hMyVAVzt7H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EighteeN_O_FivE @EndUKLockdown1 The UK civilian death toll of WWII was 450,700 or more... You're VERY wrong.    The worldwide WWII civilian death toll was 45 million or more... COVID is supposedly 1.29 million.  THEY DO NOT COMPARE IN ANY WAY. STOP SPREADING FEAR THROUGH LIES.     https://t.co/ZbmjPW9kHM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EndUKLockdown1 @_mirelllla Some further educational info for you:  https://t.co/0uWN9E6Vw8 British Medical Journal https://t.co/yNhX2Sgrdc Medical professionals -Harvard, Oxford, Cambridge ect https://t.co/FsQTZNtqfs 1000+medical professionals worldwide https://t.co/vnSTWjCShE Psychology professionals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DBentleyMiller Plimsolls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NiallBoylanShow Is there a link or file with the ' White Paper' so it can be read  shared?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeeHurstComic: This virus is *so* deadly it takes holidays off. I am genuinely impressed each day by how many dumb people inhabit this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HarryHaller__ @SeibtNaomi MANY professionals stand against this: https://t.co/0uWN9E6Vw8 British Medical Journal https://t.co/yNhX2Sgrdc Medical professionals from Harvard, Oxford, Cambridge, ect https://t.co/FsQTZNtqfs 1000+medical professionals worldwide https://t.co/vnSTWjCShE Psychology professionals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Glenntwts @MinistryDissent Pardon?   We all have jobs here, thank you for your concern.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WEF founder Klaus Schwab A child of Nazi Germany. Wants to redefine human beings not as citizens, free individuals, or members of communities, but as secondary participants in a massive commercial enterprise. His 'reset' world means we all become non-human https://t.co/8eB9Z0a9UO https://t.co/LReYN7eb6Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Welshwarrior_ @MinistryDissent https://t.co/0uWN9E6Vw8 BMJ...Bonkers? https://t.co/sMuQyaYiNg Medical professionals from Harvard, Oxford, Cambridge, ect...Bonkers? https://t.co/FsQTZNtqfs 1000+medical professionals worldwide...Bonkers? https://t.co/vnSTWjCShE Psychology professionals...Bonkers?  We could go on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even the MSM is moving it's position  on COVID...     https://t.co/bojH1Wo8LQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thewibblemovem1 https://t.co/qy5Dvtx0RX  https://t.co/3XG4yRESbK  https://t.co/FsQTZNtqfs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Matthews_angst https://t.co/v443niixE7  Because they're a scam!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nigel_Farage: This is nuts. What is he hiding from?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @spencermorgan93: A lot of people these days are good at being politically correct and virtue signalling... but not at being nice to act]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thewibblemovem1 https://t.co/f9cyaZg7l3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read  https://t.co/97s67E4OXt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes it does make you mad.  It's hard to sleep at night with thoughts about the tyranny and destruction of ours and our children's futures.  It's hard not to scream at every mask wearing sheep mindlessly roaming around. But we must keep fighting to WAKE UP others. https://t.co/9vF4ud6QDc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Piss off https://t.co/4607WV009E]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>