<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Good day my Friends!  Its rainy, raw  cold here in Massachusetts  Wishing you a great day Peace  Joy  Love  https://t.co/gIKHmZanuO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A stop in Kelheim on a #Danube cruise I took a few years ago. There was a beer fest going on but I chose to roam over the magnificent hills with views of the winding river below. https://t.co/NUWjlPgFlU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These pretty Cardinals keep chasing away a small bird.  Cardinals are the official bird of my home state, Kentucky  https://t.co/0kdsN4du96]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love the sound of the chimes  https://t.co/wj8K1cqRtY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out my stepsons website; https://t.co/K8uJ3hCdqf  Today he was working on a video for patient pop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These photos I took are Aquinnah https://t.co/iLkba21CsH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is the exciting Kentucky Derby, which Ive been to many times in my hometown, Louisville, KY. But it is a sad time for me because my older sister Mary died in a car accident on Derby day when she was 40 yrs old.  (not her fault) https://t.co/k7hW5bHIsv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Father  son (Ron)  Ron makes videos  commercials for companies like Nike. Hes always in demand, even through the pandemic. https://t.co/ywbIg7ALyp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The dogs love Ron, my stepson visiting from Santa Monica, CA  https://t.co/nBmm8i4elC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beau likes watching all the action in the fields  https://t.co/AndWMEcqvr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lots of dandelions  In front of the tractor are water tanks were moving up to the top field from the lower ones  https://t.co/E5qk49X9P5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a day! Gorgeous weather after crazy turbulence yesterday with strong gusty winds leaving power outages  many trees down throughout Massachusetts.  Mother Nature!  https://t.co/cOrwFYIj2k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Santa Monica sunsets  I cant wait to get back there! My stepson, who is visiting now, is from there  https://t.co/FZJGP5k7UK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beautiful Aquinnah on Marthas Vineyard  The lighthouse  the famous clay cliffs https://t.co/A7kUeoUNOs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: @JuliaGrantham2 HiJuliaBeautiful photo of you with Max  Lilly Enjoy your time with your stepsonIt's the most]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My stepson is visiting from California  We havent seen him for over a year so we are thrilled to have him  Ill be less engaged here for a few weeks. Stay safe, be healthy  Peace  Joy  Love  To All   https://t.co/oxlyEmEWmE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we please go for a run? Bored Maxx  https://t.co/0No8gnu7sK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sounds of early morning on a farm: dogs barking, birds singing  #smallbusinessowner   Have a fantastic day my Friends!  https://t.co/fN8F2j8AVW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lining up for breakfast. Notice the order, Lilly first  Beau is last  https://t.co/asZ6WkexpQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it dinner time?  Lilly the #rescuedog   https://t.co/RkZzCZAguM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jack again. He no longer has to wear his mask in school. He  his brother have been in school in Texas full time since last September https://t.co/v9ffzb5Tiy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My grandson Jack in his fancy new Nikes  https://t.co/suKjgkvSIE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Silly Maxx   https://t.co/jbaGY0UH4d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Playful dogs having fun today on a beautiful spring day   https://t.co/y1nOC5RTlo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This picture always moves me: the woman was so touched by the shelter dog who jumped onto her lap  fell asleep that she rescued him  took him home with her, his forever home  https://t.co/sD1LQgibsA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marthas Vineyard with the charming Oak Bluffs cottages behind me  https://t.co/TtPFlyDxAW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On fabulous Elbow Beach, with its stunning pink sand, in #Bermuda  I long to travel again!  https://t.co/6suiv2CP7J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LesleyJ96294501 Thats wonderful Lesley! My uncle was in the Korean War too. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LesleyJ96294501: @JuliaGrantham2 God bless them all for their service.  You are in a blessed family. I've learned that my ancestor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LesleyJ96294501 Hi Lesley, TY for your support of Vets. My husband was an Army Ranger with a Bronze Star for Valor  3 Purple Hearts  my family have been Vets back to the Revolution ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning!  Happy Day to All  https://t.co/nNZwoxrK2a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pretty Lilly  https://t.co/gDp5PK5o81]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beau just got groomed  https://t.co/nvXGbMmu1u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: U.S. health officials say fully vaccinated Americans don't need to wear masks outdoors anymore unless they are in a big c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two male turkeys fanning out their tails to impress the lady  establish their territory.  This blustery stance, advance then retreat, is driving my dogs crazy  https://t.co/V1lnrKwF4A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a stunning sunrise!  Gorgeous day with birds singing  https://t.co/V2V6DvqPLB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodnight my wonderful Friends  Thank you for your kind comments, likes, follows  retweets  I appreciate you!  Wishing you a lovely week  Peace  Joy Love to All  https://t.co/F60UI0rVJr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: I spent the night in this magnificent medieval French fortified city of Carcassonne. Magical! https://t.co/aDqHKOs0XG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: The famous bridge in Giverny, France near Paris where the artist Monet lived  painted. https://t.co/eMTSyBqr07]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: Guess whos sitting with me? Beau!  Happy, inspiring new week my wonderful Friends   https://t.co/iWFpsN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Restaurants struggle with short staffing as more people return to dining. https://t.co/TEUJMG6P4V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Listen to that loud bird!  The dogs want to go to the large field but right now the turkeys are there  they are clumsy getting themselves out of the field. Not that the dogs harm them but the turkeys get rattled  seem to forget that they can fly quite easily https://t.co/hTTo5xo5vw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poor Maxx is sick again with allergies. Im waiting for a vet appointment  #Vizsla https://t.co/2bpTU42DL2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whiteteddybear5 Good day dear Isa! Wishing you a beautiful new week  Bisous et un norme clin ma belle   #friendsacrosstheocean https://t.co/HUbxwbXUbx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: @JuliaGrantham2 HelloJuliaBeautiful video in a very nice place Thanks for sharingWishing you a lovely Monda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Studyleaks Hi Audrey! Our household is always up at 5 am, 3 dogs included.  As an attorney, when I was working for a global company, I was at work at 5 am like all the other executives ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5:30 am and the full moon is still out, low on the horizon. Birds are singing, welcoming in a beautiful sunny, warm day   https://t.co/Lob36JOoaP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love the sound of birds trilling  chirping, the magnificent sounds of life  nature.  Winter silence is so stark without these glorious sounds of joy  https://t.co/pYtSqq5q0g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have many deer  they eat the tulips. But these planted close to the house have a chance of surviving  https://t.co/uwqBX0fsYL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The tulips are blooming  https://t.co/yttY03oDWK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2:  Happy Sunday  https://t.co/sRKEOJdHlE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: My photo of the Massif des Calanques, a rugged terrain stretching from Marseille to the east towards Cassis https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: My daughter  her son Jack a few years ago. I miss them  I miss Texas. https://t.co/RsHno7gwTe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: This is fantastic! So uplifting, I love it!  I miss being at live events, symphony, opera, theater; the energy, the en]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did someone say dinner?  Beau loves to eat  https://t.co/jZwHCdRUft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: @JuliaGrantham2 Hello Julia  So cute  Max likes to relax.. And have fun with his balls  Wishing you a wonderful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: @whiteteddybear5 Now thats a relaxed dog, Dear Isa, like Max  Bonne nuit chre Isa  je tenvoie toute ma tendresse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: Thank you twitterworld     for your Rts, follows and likes    good night and sweet dreams   Take care]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: Thank you twitterworld  for your Rts, follows and likes    good night and sweet dreams     Take care]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DisneyParks Beautiful  amazing! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol, in fact I will turn my back on you  Silly Lilly #rescuedog https://t.co/4UJvP91crR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lilly: I know you are there but Im going to ignore you, if you leave  https://t.co/iGGqw0JdGy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On my evening stroll I often end up here, the end of the road where I can see distant mountains. It is  so serene  https://t.co/vhm7hytHMa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chasfenwick Oh my goodness, I would not have expected that. 3s company or 3s a crowd  double your trouble with 2.  I once dated a man who was one of triplets. Did the other two stay friendly?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Out for an evening stroll  it is so lovely to have sunlight at 7 pm  This is our rock garden from stones found on the farm  Goodnight my wonderful Friends  Wishing you peace  joy throughout the weekend   https://t.co/dj2RiA8HRn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im with my good friends, twin brothers, celebrating their birthday. I always thought it must be fantastic to have a twin sister  https://t.co/VF1obm2Bdw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maxs 1st winter  just discovering what fun a tennis ball can be  #Vizsla https://t.co/3yISs13B9p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 years ago on Marthas Vineyard when Maxx was smaller than Lilly  He turns 4 in August  Time flies! https://t.co/MQYPWeYpwW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: What can I say?  Crazy Maxx  Hes full of personality  https://t.co/kdbYlEYWJm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: @JuliaGrantham2 Hello  Julia  Beautiful pic, I love it TYSM for your wishes and friendship  Wishing you too a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Walking around the neighborhood, admiring the beautiful, fluffy cumula nimbus clouds   https://t.co/oAj4ZDQTmw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Craig_A_Spencer Indentations of the goggles touched my heart. My son-in-law, a dr who had covid patients, would call at night to help me, in another state, navigate health issues  it was those indentationsthat made his sacrifices so clear.  God bless you doctors]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Silly Maxx  His idea of making the bed: mess it up, throw pillows off, give orders  Maxx, the Alpha Male Vizsla https://t.co/F31tR2bxBT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maxx likes wearing his red bandana  #Vizsla https://t.co/P0uk3hUHrv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spring flowers still blooming   Happy day to All! https://t.co/OHfQmjyh1e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good Morning Friends!   Look what made me smile this morning  My friends grandson, born a month ago   https://t.co/UovLPGUf5q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: @whiteteddybear5 Goodnight dear Isa  Wishing you a beautiful new week  Je tenvoie tout ma tendresse ma belle  Many]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whiteteddybear5 Goodnight dear Isa  Wishing you a beautiful new week  Je tenvoie tout ma tendresse ma belle  Many blessings  Bisous et un norme clin  #friendsacrosstheocean  My pic of a lovely sunset on the farm  https://t.co/iHJHGLcFhW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whiteteddybear5: Thank you twitterworld     for your Rts, follows and likes    good night and sweet dreams   Take care]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Amber02150 Congratulations Heather! I had my vaccine too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Patriots Day to my Friends in Massachusetts! It is a holiday here when we usually have the Boston Marathon, but this year it will be in the fall.  So I took a long walk in this beautiful park  https://t.co/tao8MrZUDy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeidiStea Fantastic Heidi! Im so happy for you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Amber02150 I havent been into Boston for a while. Your pictures are enticing spring in Boston is so lovely ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Amber02150: A great PatriotsDay to american people living in Massachusetts   by me  Harvard Campus in Cambridge  and Newbury Street]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess whos sitting with me? Beau!  Happy, inspiring new week my wonderful Friends   https://t.co/iWFpsNYPbz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were out getting the fields ready to plant  Maxx is a big help, as you can see  https://t.co/UN7CJUIODD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TapardeaA Thank you! I miss seeing them but they live in Texas  Im in Massachusetts ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WendyPositively Sadly, That was years ago. I havent traveled or seen them since Xmas a year ago. With my cancer, lymphoma, I couldnt see anyone from March to august last year ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 3 of Snow is melting fast in todays sunshine.  Lilly is ready to go out  play  https://t.co/OpATfuS0RD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LoriShemek: @JuliaGrantham2 Thank you sweet you! So kind! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: @LoriShemek Great book Lori! I gave it 5 stars ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoriShemek @perseveralways I tried it  there was no after taste or bitterness like others. But I dont use sugar much, never drank sodas etc Sweets  chocolate are my downfall ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaGrantham2: Southern France a few yrs ago  Wont it be wonderful to travel again?  https://t.co/SbFeFVWw8p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is fantastic! So uplifting, I love it!  I miss being at live events, symphony, opera, theater; the energy, the enthusiasm is contagious. Im sure most of us miss any human connection. I havent seen my family for I over a year. https://t.co/SJsRketZEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Miami with Cameron  Jack a few years ago.  Lucky us, Our hotel was on the gorgeous beach  #Miami #travel https://t.co/gdIl0MWzJm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arizdare1 You are so kind Mark. What a sweet thing to say. That embroidery is beautiful, looks terrific on the  jacket. Im sure she loved it. And Im sure she  other angels are watching over you.  Many blessings to you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arizdare1 Im sorry for your loss Mark  My mother died a long time ago, 8 days after my father. I love the colors in your art, the composition   the yellow flower is lovely, a color of happiness ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im back painting  suddenly 5 hours flew by.  Some of my brushes  oil paints were my mothers.  #Art #oilpainting https://t.co/jl9wDm2VOT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LuC4zNytMare Ive only been once  would love to return. My close friend is Hawaiian- we met in college  friends ever since. As a Hyatt exec, shes lived all over]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What can I say?  Crazy Maxx  Hes full of personality  https://t.co/kdbYlEYWJm]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>