<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA["Following consultation with clubs, it was agreed matches would not be open to away supporters due to varying operational challenges across the League and the need to deliver a consistent approach, while maximising the opportunity for home-fan attendance"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier League confirm the final two rounds of matches this season will be limited to home fans.  Was hope that 500 away fans could be allowed but PL have, this morning, said only home fans permitted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on Josh King: "In the last few weeks he had a small problem on his back.  He was back today after two days off."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on possible James contract extension: "We didn't talk about the extension.  I am not involved in this.  His contract is quite clear."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on investing: "We didn't talk for the next season but we are going to talk in the next few weeks to try and improve the squad.  Until now we have improved a lot compared to last season."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton have fully fit squad apart from Doucoure and Gbamin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good news from Finch Farm this morning  https://t.co/YLPZDNWDzi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LivEchoEFC: Liverpool ECHO is proud to stand in solidarity with everyone who faces hate and discrimination online. Our sports social me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're underway https://t.co/I7cVlK9HGX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delete as appropriate  A comical goal / A beautiful goal  A rubbish performance / A winning performance  My verdict from the Emirates  https://t.co/xrrO4tsusn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seamus Coleman screams at full-time: "F*****g get in there".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yerry Mina to come on next]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom Davies coming on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VAR check - goal stands]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOAL 1-0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delph on, Gomes off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delph coming on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huge appeals for handball from the Everton bench]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Offside.  No penalty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Penalty Arsenal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sigurdsson denied at the near pot by Holding's challenge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CROSSBAR Sigurdsson free-kick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Rodriguez looking frustrated that Everton haven't forced more errors from Arsenal with their pressing. https://t.co/tr6rw8Sd2v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Davide Ancelotti already off the bench and talking to his father about what he's seeing https://t.co/tr6rw8Sd2v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4-4-1-1?  https://t.co/tr6rw8Sd2v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Farhad Moshiri at the Emirates tonight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton use "hidden route" to avoid delays in getting into the ground  https://t.co/38pydLjU93]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No Michael Keane in the squad.  Hamstring issue means he's missed training this week]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Andre Gomes and Seamus Coleman start.  DCL back in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nathan Broadhead with the Everton squad again tonight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fabian Delph is with the Everton squad tonight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Jones94: Time for #EFC and the other Premier League clubs to have their say on 'appropriate action'  And, for Everton fans, there']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thousands of Arsenal fans protesting outside the Emirates Stadium ahead of the game with Everton https://t.co/6A41iUbefa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal's chief exec Vinai Venkatesham says he has apologised to Everton and the other 13 clubs about the European Super League farce https://t.co/laNDF9cN2p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on immediate reaction to Super League plans: "They are joking.  This is a joke."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti; "The way we are working now is the right way.  We have improved the team, we improved the knowledge of the players.  We have to improve other things to play the Super Leag...oh sorry!"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Jones94: On Brands: "It's a good sign for the stability of the club. We are in the right way and I hope that we can grow quickly h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I think the way they proposed the Super League, is impossible.  But in 2024 there will be a new format of the Champions League and there we can have a discussion..."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on punishment for six clubs: "I am not the right person to judge and say if they have to be punished.  There are rules that have to be respected.  Everyone can make mistakes but I cannot say if they have to be punished or not."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["They were wrong.  Full stop.  They are back now.  Everyone of us wants the Champions League more competitive. "]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The most important part, they wanted to build up a competition without sporting merit,"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on the European Super League: "For every supporter of football it was a strange day, a surprise.  We heard about the Super League in the past few moths but I was sure it was not going to happen.  What can I say?  They were wrong."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti confirms DCL, Mina, Gomes, Delph and Bernard are all fit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti: "I think we are ready [for the run-in].  It is true we didn't have a good moment in the last month but we are much better and have more players available.  We are ready to fight for this final part of the season."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's Carlo https://t.co/VuNgSuft5X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ConnorOn95: Carlo Ancelotti is due to speak to the media very shortly ahead of Everton's game with Arsenal tomorrow.    Follow LIVE upd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Adam_Jones94: A bit of info here on #EFC's latest application at Bramley-Moore Dock  https://t.co/nSwwbtJI7h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carlo Ancelotti has laid it out for the players.  This is what it will now take to secure European qualification  https://t.co/WY8fvy4jd6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LivEchoEFC Moshiri gave his 'blessing' and new contract talks didn't take long after that   https://t.co/3TOZBTLqfV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LivEchoEFC https://t.co/xHPUVFLlgs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton confirm Marcel Brands has been handed a new three-year deal as director of football.  Details and quotes from Brands and Bill Kenwright @LivEchoEFC  #EFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Rodriguez speaking sense about the European Super League   https://t.co/gonuITz6H9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If anyone writes a book about this sorry affair one day, then they could do worse than look to Everton's statement, from this morning, for a title.  'Preposterous Arrogance: the story of the failed European Super League']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The European Super League is collapsing before our very eyes.  But the shameless six cannot go unpunished  https://t.co/dLJ0yGtgdg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PreeceObserver: "For me, it's a non-starter. Perhaps owners are not liking West Ham  Leicester being in the CL places at the moment. O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBeesleyEcho: Evertons fantastic response to European Super League proposals and what the rebel clubs abhorrent scheming could mean f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton's FA Youth Cup quarter-final v West Brom has been confirmed for Tuesday, April 27, 7pm at the Hawthorns]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can have your say on the European Super League plans here https://t.co/dPVNaciRAd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No holding back from Everton in their official statement this morning  And no holding back from Farhad Moshiri on the radio either  https://t.co/bszhGNHeVU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Farhad Moshiri tells talkSPORT: "I think the Premier League should deduct points from these clubs."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well played Everton.  The first, as far as we can tell, of the other 14 PL clubs to speak out publicly on this.  And not for one sentence did they hold back.  They've torn a mighty strip off the ESL mob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Highlights include the use of:   "preposterous arrogance"  "betraying the majority of football supporters across our country and beyond"  "The backlash is understandable and deserved"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Put that in your European Super League pipe and smoke it https://t.co/1LX2jniEfQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton have issued a fiercely worded statement this morning in response to the European Super League plans.  Lots of strong language used.  Full statement @LivEchoEFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seamus Coleman in a future coaching role at Everton?  Sounds perfect  https://t.co/g0AUd8UYYG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carlo Ancelotti sounds dead set on getting this deal done in the summer  https://t.co/NOrDqj7WNh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Andrade didnt really want to hear it when @bigdaddybunce told him Liam Williams is tough.  Shouldve listened.  Great fight this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[King denied and then Richarlison blazes the rebound over the bar https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Davies off, King on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[King coming on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coleman really not happy with something Rodon has said or done there https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What an effing goal!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOAL 2-1 Sigurdsson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iwobi coming off it seems.  Coleman coming on https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spurs hit the post https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Half-time Everton 1-1 Spurs.  Strong finish to the half from the Blues who should, probably, be heading ahead.  James, Allan and Sigurdsson the key players https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Allan has, quietly, had a pretty good half here https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richarlison meets Sigurdsson's corner with a header but it's straight at Lloris https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Almost 2-1 but James denied by Lloris.  Fine move involving Allan and Sigurdsson https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rodriguez doing a fair amount of work off the ball tonight.   https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hits the wall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti just shouted across to Rodriguez to leave the free-kick for Sigurdsson.... https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOAL 1-1 https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sigurdsson to take....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PENALTY Everton https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It does look like he lost his footing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't work out from the replays what happened to Holgate there.  If he was stood up he surely heads it clear?  Strange.  Did he slip? https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Has Ancelotti told Lucas Digne to bin off the long throw-ins into the box? Can't remember the last time we saw one.  Digne was in the perfect position to launch one just then but threw it short https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton have started with a good tempo and intensity but some of the passing so far been really poor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huge game at Goodison tonight.  Join @Adam_Jones94 and I for updates https://t.co/PYEKYoOfzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gareth Bale joins the long list of his former players this season who have interrupted their walk to the dugout to stop, hug and chat with Carlo Ancelotti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton decided not to include Andre Gomes in the squad tonight as a precaution.  Declared fit by Ancelotti yesterday but player didn't feel 100% so decision taken to leave him out tonight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IN: Jordan Pickford Allan  Alex Iwobi  Full team news @LivEchoEFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isaac Price and Reece Welch with the Everton squad tonight again   #EVETOT   @LivEchoEFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Godfrey on pre-match media duties so a clear indication that he starts tonight v Spurs   #EVETOT   @LivEchoEFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LivEchoEFC: Everton confirm appointment of US figure to boost international plans.  Full story from @philkecho https://t.co/oaltgjzQwE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SamCarroll0: Every player excellent. But Zan-Luk Leban very good in goal again. Lewis Warrington the warrior in midfield. And Sean McAl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti: "[Gbamin] is a strong character.  His character is so strong and he will be stronger after this unlucky situation and it will help him for his career."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ancelotti on form: "There were games where we were not good enough.  It's a difficult period for us which came now with a lot of injuries.  But we have to continue to fight."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pickford, Allan, King and Gomes are fit for Spurs  DCL, Mina, Delph and Bernard back next week]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>