<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone else spend the last year wanderlusting over @airbnb from all over the world? Just me?I curated my very own wishlist in partnership with them and hope I can share the magic of these spaces with my kids some day soon. https://t.co/CVq8Uwhm8D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My feet are always cold. Good warm socks for sleeping recs? If not I will just buy a pair from Amazon by a clothing brand named like Panykoty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billie Eilish looks so hot but also Cillian Murphy is Billie Eilishs dad! https://t.co/OqO7Ey6Ba0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JocelynLeavitt: @mindykaling We are not technically GenX. We are part of a micro generation born btwn 78-83. Dubbed Xennials / the O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Like I skateboard to Ben Stillers house and we listen to Nirvana]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cant believe Im technically Gen X. Like my aesthetic is the movie Singles and Ethan Hawke and Jennifer Jason Leigh are my contemporaries]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Continuing to share resources to support the Covid crisis in India. Everything helps. Donations go directly to healthcare physical infrastructure, medical equipment, and vaccine support and mobilization. @GiveIndia https://t.co/Kka7AYluOc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Youre welcome btw for me not posting anything for international dance day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jason_blum Wonderful news!! Congrats!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy one year @neverhaveiever-versary!! Cant wait to be back in July on @netflix! https://t.co/gSlzus9BuQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maskless feasting at Jon  Vinnys Brentwood. Pictured: White Lightning pizza, spicy fusilli, grilled chicken. Not pictured: eggplant parm, little gem salad and my unbuttoned jeans. Chefs kiss. https://t.co/zDXjoOqomt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid-19 cases are rising in India. If you have the means, please consider donating to organizations like @AIDINDIA to help support relief efforts  https://t.co/v6hVtdFsrU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonathanalevine Whoa it looks so cool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wyntermitchell: As a woman who starts convos with Look, Frances is our patron saint. https://t.co/SWmqP23VfF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peakaboo sternum is the fashion trend eh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Regina King is so outrageously gorgeous it is hard to understand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fortunefunny I would love to see you both in something]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeeveswilliams: @mindykaling i always knew pineapple belonged on pizza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel like Guy Pearce did it. He cant just be the visiting writer to Easttown with a bob haircut who romances Mare. This isnt a spoiler its just speculation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@magracie EXACTLY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ok Guy Pearce is majorly sus in Mare of Easttown. A new writer who just moved to town who hit on Mare mercilessly, a huge grouch in a button down corduroy shirt. Doesnt add up memento guy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArielDumas The exclamation point]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thumbelulu: "You cannot stop the waves, but you can learn to surf." This feels like the key difference between now and ten years ago, b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love everything about this https://t.co/r9WQmI4CG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JocelynLeavitt @smittenkitchen Garbanzo beans?!? Must investigate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@janiobi @alait Amy Im worried I offended you by complaining about my WiFi somehow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[someone make me that feta tomato tik tok pasta pls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love tinned fish and I especially love @fishwife. Here is their rad recipe page, Im making these all this weekend !! https://t.co/fkboggMqyS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It does https://t.co/Xt0E9iZdoV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im a successful woman, I work hard, and yet it is impossible to have consistent dependable WiFi in my home and thats my cross to bear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/kGTdlApEdm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meenaharris: Rest in power, George Floyd.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congrats - and the fish is fabulous  https://t.co/A4D2Xkdm5a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My favorite white mans face (via @MyThrpstSays) https://t.co/MTJHYdzDK5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaxxd waxd and ready to pay my tax https://t.co/nXx815oPNB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[do they think we just forgot about Succession and Barry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidstassen What is it, like ice cream? Sorbet? I dont get it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shes the best ever! Happy birthday Katie!! https://t.co/Pg5FR4Vw4I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is watching #Nobody?! I am shook]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing saw this on @reghuds feed, its so good.  https://t.co/mVjWi9zPho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Everytown: THREAD: Americas gun violence crisis has been on full display in the past week; weve seen countless horrific acts of gun v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShoeboxProjects @jessicamulroney https://t.co/19FBGQhWsX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeffselph4 @asianamgirlclub Beautiful!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itsgabrielleu @DwyaneWade WOW!!! this is so awesome! Congrats!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billyeichner @colton Billy this is incredible]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[meme girl summer https://t.co/LSfHy8Qr5k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrisvandusen @netflix Huge congrats Chris!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrotiGupta But she can talk about Mean Girls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrotiGupta QA after with amanda seyfried and NO MANK TALK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Okay Adaptation is in, the best friend has spoken https://t.co/xjB63fMbaz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve all been on bad dates to the Arclight where youre watching a Greta Gerwig movie  the guy doesnt like it bc he knows Greta is more talented than him and also would never date him and you had the realization you cant date this kind of guy anymore, so SAVE THE ARCLIGHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adaptation is too high brow to be part of it, Susan Orlean! https://t.co/ZL0KPFpbN5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im gonna take over the arclight lease and use it to only show movies I like and then all you snobs are fucked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RIP Arclight chicken apple sausage baguette with watermelon bbq sauce. You sounded disgusting but tasted kind of okay. Will miss you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@keIseylr Fox books!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am cynical. I feel like the arclights not really gone and some corporation has already bought it and this is part of a strategy to cause mourning and then they swoop in and save it and we love them and forget theyre a corporation. I mean, thats how I would do it and Im evil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is so hard to make change. I hate it and so does my three year old. I love reading about people who do it successfully. Thanks for writing this @naanking, I loved it  was inspired https://t.co/39DrojvlOt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatieGreenthal You can! Pls document]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*my actual desk is covered in spiderwebs* https://t.co/CFFNKllyee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LAPublicLibrary: Raise your hand if you were inspired to read by @levarburton. #NationalLibraryWeek https://t.co/89K9FISS06]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@inkookang @LAPressClub Awesome! Congrats Inkoo!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spring sprang https://t.co/k2Fu9l9tzV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love this conversation!  https://t.co/ZXXMwLBokc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CatherineP725 @tgordon22 @PhilRosenthal Oh the Phil show is OG - hes the best!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My friends theory is that Stanley Tucci stays in Italian hotels with really good gyms and works out for two hours every morning, eats protein and salad off-camera, then then goes HAM onscreen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Stanley Tucci show the best thing ever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ziwe: famously on showtime may 9th https://t.co/YudlNHvMHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrotiGupta Brilliant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caitlincarrickm Very true my friend]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After surviving this last year, the very least Tom Hanks and Meg Ryan could do for us is star in my sequel to Youve Got Mail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caitlincarrickm Gotta disagree with you in this one. Tom Hanks is the platonic ideal movie man in YGM (confident, witty, ruthless tycoon with a great apartment), but Billy C is equally great as mildly tortured adorable overthinking Jewish boyfriend]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHMS has the one-liners, the incredible observations, the Washington Square, the Bruno Kirby... but Youve Got Mail has: I wanted it to be you. I wanted it to be you so badly. https://t.co/RNwq4QX9ea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jaywillis @jduffyrice I really appreciate the invitation but I cant take the heat from Rufus Peckham fans if I divulge my true feelings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jduffyrice Just looked up Hugo Black, yikes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@meenaharris haha I said I like raisins in my samosas the pain that rained down on me omfg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so moved! Thank you @KTLA!! https://t.co/11nEig8K6G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@naanking I did and i did]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KristenRose03 I just looked it up and the stairs seemed a little challenging!! Psyched theres a trail that avoids it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi LA based friends, can you please recommend the best hike in Baldwin Hills tor beginners and toddlers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I read this in one sitting. Please read this magical book, it will sit with you forever. Congrats Sanjena! https://t.co/YaIK7VQewo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BenMulroney @jessicamulroney Ben, I died! Shes so talented! I wish you both could visit every time she styles me for an event]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @casteIIahiris: @mindykaling so cristin milioti best chris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If theres cumberbitches Im a milidiot (Cristin Milioti fan)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gonna need extensions if I want to include my sons name. S P E N C E R https://t.co/wBVNIxv5Jk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks @people for considering this messy athleisure-weard mom a Beautiful person. I dont deserve it but Ill take it! https://t.co/QnLljIxICO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So excited to be working with Sanjena to adapt this special book!   https://t.co/kO0kchHPuy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DewaynePerkins Omg its so hard tho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Omg Winter Soldier has mucho problemos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hey I never want these memes to end https://t.co/KaTzNyY1Ui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thejdevereaux @inkookang Hahahahha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/hz5qnDoeBx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MikeMyatt_ Thank you! Somehow I thought it might have been more magical]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jduffyrice @meenaharris Phenomenally Preg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leeunkrich Lee you have no idea. Was it just Bonnies address or also a message from him to Andy. Did Andy think it was his mom or Woody, did Andy visit Woody ever again, etc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @itsgabrielleu: This makes me so emotional. @PoseOnFX is so much more than a great, culture shifting show. Pose is LIFE!! I cant thank y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes I assume Bonnies address was part of it but was there anything else? Like, did Andy think it was from woody?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just watched Toy Story 3 with my toddler, we both loved it (I had seen it before of course). She kept screaming at the screen GUYS GUYS you have to stick together!. Question: what does the note say that Woody writes and leaves on the box for Andy?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarayublue Congrats, that is huge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Passover  Happy Holi! I love what these two holidays symbolize; freedom and the triumph of good over evil. Im giving to @ThePadProject1 and Harmony House India, two organizations whose missions exemplify the holidays (to me)! How are you celebrating?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@violadavis @FallonTonight WHAT?!? THIS LOOK!!!!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>