<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Live NOW! | FashionTV Bikini and Lingerie brands - fashion tv watch now! https://t.co/Aop758dgYW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch this new collection of St. Patrick Bridal which is a tribute to the timeless beauty of Audrey Hepburn in the film Breakfast at Tiffanys. #weddingdress #fashiontv #ftv https://t.co/KfUNQL5HFI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember this Red Dress  When bellahadid walked down the red Carpet in stunning @roberto_cavalli Gown   Bvlgari Jewellery  #FashionTV #CannesFilmFestival2019 #BestOfCannes #FTV #BellaHadid https://t.co/rPl6hx2I9T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kate.xeeva this girl is on fire Join fashiontv sexy hand wash challenge and win the prize Create your video and upload to instagram with tag @fashiontv and hashtag #ftvsexyhandwash https://t.co/R5F4Lorjx8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SafeHandsChallenge from @naomi  FTV nominates you to post your Safe Hands Challenge and tag @FashionTV #FTV https://t.co/UjzmicoMA9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MBFWR MERCEDES-BENZ FASHION WEEK RUSSIA IS CANCELLING ALL IN-PERSON EVENTS FOR THIS SEASON DUE TO THE CORONAVIRUS PANDEMIC Russian Fashion Council, in cooperation with partners and participating fashion designers of https://t.co/iAruKJSxcV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LdlA610YjQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best nominated UWILL AWARD  Give your vote to beautiful  Natalia Kapchuk https://t.co/S61cObxNjf via @choicelyapp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To All Powerful Womens Happy International Womens Day 8 March   #8March #8 https://t.co/KD7aNaIqO4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 Remembering Best Moments from Paris Haute Couture  laetitiacasta few words about  LAST SHOW OF @jpgaultier  And what friedns and starts are here to say about last #jeanpaulgaultier show in Paris  #pfw https://t.co/r8DlFU5P7K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fashion Show   for @chopard x yasyaminochkina x  ritzcarltonvienna   Make Up  Styling  mud_makeupdesignory_vienna @ The Ritz-Carlton, Vienna https://t.co/W8KSgiRwwa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fashion Show for  @chopard x yasyaminochkina x  ritzcarltonvienna  MUA mud_makeupdesignory_vienna @ The Ritz-Carlton, Vienna https://t.co/9euMfJlqyy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RAHA  rahaxfatemi  Shines brighter than Diamonds  in yasyaminochkina   for @chopard x @fashiontv x yasyaminochkina x  ritzcarltonvienna   MUA mud_makeupdesignory_vienna  Make Up kamillastyle @ The Ritz-Carlton, Vienna https://t.co/8dwCApwQgL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SOPHIE  sophie.biedermann  for @chopard x yasyaminochkina x  ritzcarltonvienna  MUA mud_makeupdesignory_vienna  Make Up a.j.makeupart @ The Ritz-Carlton, Vienna https://t.co/4VpgpYF9xm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TATIYANA  tatiyanapolli  for @chopard x yasyaminochkina x @fashiontv  ritzcarltonvienna  #FashionTV #ChopardVienna #yasyaminochkina  MUA a.j.makeupart  Make Up mud_makeupdesignory_vienna @ The Ritz-Carlton, Vienna https://t.co/xda03y0ZiQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YULIA   STUNNING  yuliagermann  for @chopard x yasyaminochkina @fashiontv  #yasyaminochkina  location ritzcarltonvienna  MUA mud_makeupdesignory_vienna  Make Up a.j.makeupart @ The Ritz-Carlton, Vienna https://t.co/4wqi9W00VQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ZUZANA for @chopard x yasyaminochkina   MUA a.j.makeupart  Studio mud_makeupdesignory_vienna  Model zuzanakavulicova  Location ritzcarltonvienna  #chopard #fashiontv #yasyaminochkina #ritzcarltonvienna @ The https://t.co/rEixDgfgv7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FTVbackstage  Beautiful yuliagermann getting ready for the show tonight yasyaminochkina @chopard  Make Up a.j.makeupart  MUA studio mud_makeupdesignory_vienna  #FashionTV  #Chopard  #YasyaMinochkina https://t.co/hsJqCSQBKJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[kimberlybudinsky taking over FashionTV instagram for the @chopard  x yasyaminochkina Follow our instastories   Today Shooting for #Chopard ritzcarltonvienna #chopardvienna #kimberlybudinsky  MUA https://t.co/73bgPUoxIA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sarah Burton was dreaming about stark northern landscapes, windblown terrain, and the earths minerals for this collection, which was filled with sharp tailoring, dramatic embellishment and prints hand-drawn in the https://t.co/F9dcpL521l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FashionTV  interview with our favorite top model @gigihadid #FTVbackstage #topmodels #gigihadid  full interview  Youtube | fashiontv link in bio https://t.co/q9M6GOAURJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JOURDAN DUNN interview for @fashiontv @isabelmarant Fall Winter 2020 #pfw2020 #pfw jourdandunn   repost @fashiontomax @fashion2max https://t.co/jLun6kA8dm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DANGEROUS BRIDE bellahadid    @followwestwood Fall/Winter 2020/2021   joshuajpdavidson  #westwood #viviennewestwood #fw2020 #fw2021 #aw2020 #PFW #PFW2020 #fashion #fashionlook #fashionillustration #fashionista https://t.co/dx7mj5bZZI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FashionTV Top Model talks  #gigihadid about her style and make up #backstage #FTVbackstage  @GiGiHadid @FashionTV https://t.co/217cB5chrw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FTVNews:  FashionTV President Michel Adam in Beirut for the launch of the 5th edition of "Designers  Brands" Fashion Week by L.I.P.S. Management.  https://t.co/cwZn9rYFra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@divo.fashion introduces Global Platform for fashion. Models, New Faces, Modeling Agencies, BRANDS, photographers - all in one place  #fashion #divoplatform #mobileapplication #modelingagencies #brands #advertiser #models https://t.co/Ab0FSLRRSm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have a look at our Global Tour 2019! Heres a little of what went on during our launch at G2E Asia 2019. Share and join the #glam #FTVGG #fashiontv #fashionlovers #fashion #fashiontvgg #instafashion #fashionlife #fashionlifestyle #lavish #igaming #onlinegaming #onlinegambling https://t.co/wV5xJl22dm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV Gaming gives you the opportunity to add GLAM to your product. FashionTV Gaming launched BIG during the South Africa Show  Check our products on https://t.co/NMOGuq5yOd   #fashiontv #fashiontvgg #instafashion #fashionlife  #igaming #onlinegaming #onlinegambling #sports https://t.co/hoS9HbfEV5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A snapshot of fashiontvgg global tour 2019. This is our launch at #africagamingshow . More launches to follow, stay tuned! https://t.co/9a74UHFrCt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A snapshot of fashiontvgg global tour 2019. This is our launch at #africagamingshow . More launches to follow, stay tuned! https://t.co/W6sxdgNBdw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV is officially available on ABS-2A satellite (75  E orbital position, transponder No. 1A, frequency 11 473 MHz)  All other sources of broadcasting are piracy and illegal https://t.co/dBEHjnFfo5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[do NOT miss the deadline to create your very own team for the cricket world cup! Create your fantasy team with style now at https://t.co/4WxfXi1Tv7 https://t.co/dMcj6xBVfP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Be a part of the action, create your fantasy team now on https://t.co/mXt0xNTvYH for the cricket world cup. New Zealand vs Pakistan, don't miss the deadline to join the game! https://t.co/4WxfXi1Tv7 https://t.co/vT92YsLkq3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#cricket fan? #fantasygame player? Build your fantasy cricket team for the world cup NOW! https://t.co/4WxfXi1Tv7 https://t.co/wl25DdJ0LD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Asia Fashion TV After Party to be held in KOI Bangkok concluding the premier NEXT BLOCK ASIA Conference (https://t.co/S1DhD6YOE6) by @KryptonEvents Date  Place: June 26, KOI, Bangkok, Thailand. https://t.co/kBaVnqaKKS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billionaire Gammarth TUNISIA presents FashionTV's owner and president Michel Adam's special and luxurious birthday party!  Featuring our favorite voice of FTV, ANIA J! https://t.co/xd3xutuQ7F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FTV Gaming Group invites players to a unique gaming lifestyle environment, where they can enjoy the exclusivity of the FashionTV world whilst enjoying industry-leading games. Go to https://t.co/XqXaZWQ9lf! https://t.co/666Y1NnVpJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Be a winner. Be a dreamer. Play like you've never played before. https://t.co/LSaJumEVHP #winning #fashiontvplay #ftvplay #play #winners #playtowin #fashiontv #ftv https://t.co/Y5FuBFAo5Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why wait to be a winner when you can be a FashionTV Winner right now? Play to win! For more go to https://t.co/XqXaZWQ9lf   #ftv #fashiontv #fashiontvplay #ftvplayers #fashion #gaming #games #playtowin https://t.co/wRl3IUZHb2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV Gaming Group hosts a successful networking event  at the hottest gaming summit in India, with a warm welcome by Indias leading gaming companies\market at SPiCE 2019. https://t.co/2ZywzY28O5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV presents @EzraTuba direct from Mercedez Benz Fashion Week Istanbul on March 21st with Stratejist, @Estetik_int, and OnH fashion and more. Who's ready for some high fashion? https://t.co/YOveG3HMRL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prepare for the most epic night of your lives celebrating President of FTV, Michel Adam! Stay tuned for whats to come in only a few weeks... https://t.co/lMHi2pbKOv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonight! Dont miss! Special FashionTV   Blockchain @EBIC2019_ party with LIVE music  Free entrance! We are waiting for you  #ebic #ebic2019 #party #afterparty #fashiontv https://t.co/VxavHsWxvn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess who will be a guest appearance at the Opening of the FashionTV House in Warsaw, Poland?  Check out @TommyHilfiger and his wife interviewed by Ania J FashionTV about Dee Ocleppo and more! https://t.co/bsO8tlkCYc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[F Studio and Wellness Center to be developed in Bangkok, Thailand! Exciting things are coming....stay tuned. https://t.co/NEsvciGV7U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[European Blockchain Investment Congress 2019 in the heart of Europe, Vienna. 21 days left! Buy your #ticket on time. @ebic2019 #european #blockchain #investment #congress #blockchaintechnology #technology #speakers #ticket #ebic2019 #business #financial #crypto #cryptocurrency https://t.co/GdXbUTAfqD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV Gaming Group presents a whole new world with FashionTV Play!  Go to https://t.co/G0rNeom5Xb to be a winner. #ftvplay #ftvgaminggroup #ftvwinners #fashiontvplay #fashiontvwinners #playtowin #onlinegames #fashion #fashiontv https://t.co/z25KU0QmjI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV International presents, Dubai FTV Ladies Day @ Zero Gravity Dubai https://t.co/lWzg4I03IL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The famous English bloggers, Anna and Bambi visited Estetik International and took their followers on a tour of the facilities...and a little extra! With the one and only Op.Dr.Blent Cihantimur Doctor B https://t.co/k7VjI7IdZq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV Gaming Group is giving you a chance to dream and win big! Get ready to play...www.fashiontvwinners.com https://t.co/8eFSgSw4zu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you ready to win big? Be confident. Be exceptional. Be a winner. FashionTV Gaming Group is coming! https://t.co/YI6rGvS143 https://t.co/ldCJ4dzetD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BE A WINNER!  visit us now https://t.co/YI6rGvS143 and discover a power you never thought you had. https://t.co/2CA7zwlTeN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brazilian Model Jennifer Pamplona is in the Estetik International Beauty Car! Who's ready for a ride?  https://t.co/O0BYaUCyFk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can enjoy now FashionTV while flying @emirates  Brilliant flight experience boosted by diamond fashion shows to make your day even better  #emirates #fashiontv #fashionshow #bestflightever #timetofly https://t.co/TnNcFxyhVW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV is the Official partner of @EBIC2019_ - European Blockchain Investment Congress. Don't miss the chance of a lifetime to hear from worldwide entrepreneurs, developers, industry leaders and investors by getting your ticket here! https://t.co/w7oaneQ6xl https://t.co/whas44cdkk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glamour, @FashionTV , luxury and so much more take a peek inside our glamorous world and find out more here...https://t.co/LsHfCLklqh https://t.co/0Tn8NoC5ti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VladislavReznik @surfexpo ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VladislavReznik @surfexpo Wow, looks really beautiful!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VladislavReznik @surfexpo Amazing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theirishayk leads the squad in @Dsquared2 spring 2019 ad campaign taking the spotlight in sporty and military inspired looks. https://t.co/74ZpFK1dvH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ladygaga  songwriters win @goldenglobes for Best Original Song for 'Shallow' from the breathtaking film, 'A Star Is Born'. #ladygaga #GoldenGlobes2019 #GoldenGlobes #AStarIsBorn #AStarIsBornMovie https://t.co/wmaSInj9aq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billionaire  Fashiontv present live from Dubai, Burj Khalifa district the Dubai FTV Model Awards ceremony  dinner TV report - we love fashiontv party  #FashionTV #party #ftvparty #bestparty #top #billionaire #ftvmodels #topmodels https://t.co/KUhqHenF4b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A night full of sparkles and pretty faces. After a successful launch last week, it's time for round 2 of the weekly hunt for FashionTV's next top model from 7pm onwards on the 26th of December at the Billionaire Mansion Dubai with special guest @TimatiOfficial ! https://t.co/0T3uBzLVHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celebrate New Years Eve 2019 in style at @theclubatkoi , The White Winter Ball in Bangkok with FashionTV!  https://t.co/wAl6rxqE8x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MargotRobbie is ready for resort season in the Winter Escape 2018 cover of @PORTERmagazine https://t.co/K5ORpAJy8L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[F Cafe and Chocolate Bar Thailand! Who's hungry for some delicious chocolate kebab?  #fashiontv #placetovisit https://t.co/6fVvaYzoY0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FashionTV Party By  NEXT BLOCK - one more reason to join us on December 12 in Tel Aviv!  Allure of @fashionbarTLV , refreshing drinks, fruitful networking - JOIN NOW as a part of the loudest final cryptoparty of 2018!  Everything at https://t.co/Cf2rLtZ4eO ! https://t.co/SbFG5w2Fwr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Newlyweds Priyanka Chopra  Nick Jonas put on a great show for Vogue Magazine! https://t.co/JLo6bnV0o3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[December 1, 2018 is the grand opening of the 8th Celebration of Silk, Thai silk road to the world 2018 held at Centara Grand, Bangkok, Thailand. Beauty queens, ambassadors, diplomats and even the prine minister of Thailand are present in this event. #thailand #celebrationofsilk https://t.co/x6UulF6eXK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In collaboration with @swarovski,  @Versace has created a tiara for the debutantes of the Vienna Opera Ball 2019, inspired by Wagner's 'The Ring of the Nibelung'. #vienna #versace #swarovski #viennaball #viennaball19 #viennaopera https://t.co/srzgJsmEkb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kourtneykardash LOOKS SMOKIN HOT IN @GQMexico ! https://t.co/dUk0FUmryo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fur Caravan creates exclusive collections for people who love expressing themselves through their clothing, enjoying exclusivity and comfort. https://t.co/PdwJiA78Up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coming soon  FALCONMAN  @JCVD @RixosSaadiyat  #falconman #jcvd #ftv #fashiontv #comingsoon #fashiontv https://t.co/fN1HZU1Rae]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miss Angola 2018, Ana Liliana Avio,    is in #love with FashionTV Cosmetics and is looking gorgeous while shopping in the FTV Cosmetics Angola  store in Luanda, Angola #missangola2018 #model #missuniversepageant2018 #fashionmodel #fashiontv https://t.co/Xk8vm61j1p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Play with FTV as you have a chance to vote for the top 10 fashion brands in the world! Who will have more followers next week? Vote in the comments below or on our Instagram story. https://t.co/UoR7XhCurg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Play with FTV and vote on your bets for next weeks top celebrities, models, singers, football players, designers and more! Who will make it to the top? https://t.co/MbAxlwsq2q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who can guess the top 10 designers for next weeks FTV game? Play today and win tomorrow! https://t.co/SAI3bKaBMj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The top 10 have been chosen out of all categories! Who did you bet on? FTV has you playing and its so much fun! https://t.co/sV9Ixs535I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FTV is starting its own rating platform and anyone can make a bet to predict the winner of the week! Model Monday is here! Cast your votes below Can you guess the top 10 for next week? https://t.co/auCXLxR0NU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet FashionTV team and Jean-Claude Van Damme at MIPCOM this year on October 15-18 in Cannes at BOOTH P-1.G74! https://t.co/alRCljAZV0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Listen to @Caradelevingne sing about London  for her new @Burberry campaign  #caradelevingne #burberry #london #fashion #fw18 #trends #vibes #ftv #fashiontv https://t.co/tYg0kbeWXX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FTVNews: @AdrianaLima  announced  as @PUMA Ambassador  congratulations  #puma #ambassador #adrianalima #fashionnews #ftv #fashiontv #news #bestofthefay https://t.co/9IkmA7piSY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DELTA Summit closing party brought to you by FashionTV and designers Charles  Ron! Make sure you get your tickets now and check out our FTV Coin @Delta_Summit  #deltasummit #ftvcoin #blockchain #afterparty #charlesandron #closingparty #party #fashion https://t.co/kR7eV0fE0a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our very own Natalya Menshikova will be speaking at the DELTA Summit on October 3rd! Make sure you get your tickets before they are sold out with this Promo Code NM50OFF.  https://t.co/1nWTvK6bl0 https://t.co/nF3uFmDBST]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eros International PLC, a leading global company in the Indian film entertainment industry, announced today that Eros Now, its cutting-edge digital over-the-top (OTT) South Asian entertainment platform, has entered into a partnership with FashionTV https://t.co/mWm7gTIjWe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Haircut, anyone?  @GiGiHadid https://t.co/cu3uAADEVf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joansmalls for FashionTV backstage before @FilaUK SS show  #ss19 #mfw #fashionweek https://t.co/4RemqQVet8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing @Kinglimaa for @FashionTV   at #MilanFashionWeek  @philipp_plein https://t.co/Pn39pGgRNa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No comments... just butterflies   @GiGiHadid @ITSJEREMYSCOTT @Moschino @cameramoda #mfw #ss19 #batterflies #gigihadid #moschino  #fashiontv #ftvrunway https://t.co/P9kz8hpQy3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The  #VSFashionShow is back in New York! @VictoriasSecret  https://t.co/qA3YuaJW2Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Prince Harry! FashionTV loves you and the royal family!  #HappyBirthday https://t.co/4FYKSZNLzV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let's talk Ariana Grande on FashionTV's Blog.https://t.co/Uf3PeoH2Sg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to all who organized and participated in the Miss FashionTV Awards at @RixosSungate ! Check out how our model contestants spent their time enjoying the sun and preparing for the big event!  https://t.co/Zfi0YaZuIL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FTVRunway: backstage fun at @annasui SS 2019  #nyfw @nyfw #ss19 #spring19 #fashion #trends #newyork #fashiontv https://t.co/pF1XC4kpBR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday KARL LAGERFELD! We love this man so much. A legend! To see the story of Karl go to https://t.co/slAEYwFve8 @KarlLagerfeld https://t.co/mhCVHtFVS2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @cocorocha ! A very special day for a very special Coco! For more Coco runway shows and photoshoots, go to https://t.co/slAEYwFve8 https://t.co/WPQIzKhuyR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FashionTV pays respects to Mac Miller  RIP https://t.co/2dZ2IhdOyN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jcvd  @enisonatfashiontv talk beauty at the Miss FashionTV Award at @RixosSungate  Who will Jean-Claude Van Damme choose? #jcvd #jeanclaudevandamme #missftv #missftvaward #missfashiontv #beautycontest #fashion #modelcontest #model #models #fashiontv https://t.co/NKHHXy8DPu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JCVD  @enisonatfashiontv talk beauty at the Miss FashionTV Award at @RixosSungate  Who will Jean-Claude Van Damme choose? #jcvd #jeanclaudevandamme #missftv #missftvaward #missfashiontv https://t.co/gjccHdzA1K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can you handle the heat?  Miss FashionTV Award at @RixosSungate contestants take fashion to an all new level.  #missftv https://t.co/iUTXHlxcZT]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>