<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NYCEMSwatch: So, how is Mayor de Blasio's #VisionZero doing? https://t.co/2fULEflh8Q The number of NYC pedestrian fatalities is up 65%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could pretend rebellion be allowed? Playing Star Wars? We'd all be happier. https://t.co/y3SDEAHkYa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch "9 ways to make your rabbit happy - Expert tips" on YouTube https://t.co/7TZIFhaU0X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMail: NASA captures eerie sounds from Venus during its closest EVER flyby of the planet https://t.co/IEg4I7O6hD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I never liked baseball so I can just walk away. https://t.co/573TlDb96l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi Teacup https://t.co/7rW9OmGA0b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobertKennedyJr: .@FoxNews commentator, @TuckerCarlson, told viewers even though President Biden said COVID vaccines wont be mandated,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NVICLoeDown: Evidence Reveals That Military Team Collaborated With Lab Where COVID-19 Pandemic Originated https://t.co/MIUffbK1t3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But we don't punish them for wearing them or rip them off. https://t.co/m92yHZ0s7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No way. get him out https://t.co/AA64JTDgnA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Belgian farmer was annoyed by the stone in his tractor's path. He moved it and the French border - CBS News https://t.co/SPBEIHEU8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HighImpactFlix: At this point they're NOT saying "once you get vaccinated, you'll be free," they're saying, "Only IF you KEEP GETTING v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is this yours @MattsBanjo ? https://t.co/zIAK9bk9Dk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyMail: No barrel of laughs! Boy, 2, has to be freed with power saw after getting stuck in antique wooden drum https://t.co/eINXgAMT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wherever they are matters not because all I want are those funds. Let them return the beast and send me a $$ gift. My bday this month. UI ends soon and Cuomo says I'm still nonessential. https://t.co/Dx3sZIn2HO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ValarVarda: Raccoons are out again in Astoria, NYC.  #VaccinateRaccoons Make this a priority. Remember Summer 2020 Rabies Alert which n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stillgray: Donald Trump has his own twitter feed on his website. Amazing. https://t.co/wnOHnKicPY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ValarVarda: Raccoons are out again in Astoria, NYC.  #VaccinateRaccoons Make this a priority. Remember Summer 2020 Rabies Alert which n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These folks might actually get something done. https://t.co/XcMbsZJdIf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nypost: Long Island lawmakers urge Cuomo to allow Memorial Day parades https://t.co/w8XW8XYdir https://t.co/wl0JR8ydAD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eh, baseball is way too long. Speed it up with a faster analogy. https://t.co/GTPj1LBkoB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[good night https://t.co/M4SL1NnJDp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[wow are you deluded https://t.co/ut4gC0Hy1r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Raccoons are out again in Astoria, NYC.  #VaccinateRaccoons Make this a priority. Remember Summer 2020 Rabies Alert which no one broadcast. Rabies has no cure.  @nyc311 @MayorsPEU @NYCMayor @NYCMayorsOffice @HealthNYGov @nycHealthy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Raccoons are out again in Astoria, NYC.  #VaccinateRaccoons Make this a priority. Remember Summer 2020 Rabies Alert which no one broadcast. Rabies has no cure.  @nyc311 @MayorsPEU @NYCMayor @NYCMayorsOffice @HealthNYGov https://t.co/ckMl9jQb6q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of a true vax is to unmask. https://t.co/GEyAHgnI3e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Private businesses can still require. Biden extended travel mask mandate til Sept 13th. https://t.co/GEyAHgnI3e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Private businesses can still require. Biden extended travel mask mandate til Sept 13th. https://t.co/GEyAHgFiUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Remnant Newspaper - ON THE ENLIGHTENMENT: Remnant Columnist, Jason Morgan, Speaks in Tokyo https://t.co/xt7YGLkJLj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I had dental work done. No chewing gum for me. https://t.co/PKBYQbETXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's a given. Just file. Read the instructions.  But none of the unemployment benefits should be taxed. https://t.co/HUKLgMzhSm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaylorRMarshall: Desecrations in California and Flames in France: Who does this? https://t.co/NmvdHpJ14C via @YouTube https://t.co/Powp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But I'd rather go to work and dress up. https://t.co/xPbGrtcOh8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[side effects include death  other symptoms https://t.co/cWUJCFtqI3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey, if they're made of glass they match my glass slippers. https://t.co/zajooBllWf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really? They don't want that to be legalized? Pot is. There was a protest for hemp legalization in NYC on Saturday. #NY doesn't need any drugs or vaccines, we need peace  quiet from govt  nosy neighbours. https://t.co/mx0JHcFzl9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 'vaccine' is to spread covid more rapidly to the unvaccinated and who have survived w/o masks. https://t.co/2OtlPJk4Hq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Breaking911: PRESIDENT BIDEN: "There's one fact I want every American to know: People who are not fully vaccinated can still die everyd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AnthonySabatini: Today I sent a letter to @GovRonDeSantis requesting an Executive Order suspending the power of School Boards to mask c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I kinda like them https://t.co/zQU7rEvPle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fun times at DW. https://t.co/k1oYds7TpX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[crime, litter, filth, unemployment, godless govt, etc etc Covid is not the problem. https://t.co/tdNNjIU1Qv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryMakow: Nevada womans first medical bill after JJ shot was $513,000 -  https://t.co/0Dh9hSgPgo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Return to God and apologize publicly for not giving Him the credit. And #BanAbortion To save NY, you need God. https://t.co/mdesQA8gES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stronger? Muscle power doesn't fight disease. https://t.co/mdesQA8gES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think vaccine passports should only be used for travel to  from highly contagious foreign countries. https://t.co/GO7WP4v4Y0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RAZ0RFIST: Petty reminder that media straight-up lied for like 3 straight months about Ruth Bader Ginsburg's health, on the off-chance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilHollowayEsq: This is disgusting. Discrimination and segregation based on vaccination status is wrong and immoral. https://t.co/1afL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccinated wear masks til they reach the table. What lunacy is that? So the unvaxed can do likewise. https://t.co/Jm77rAVlbJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take sips. Use a spoon. https://t.co/X265yo9lBA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But masking|distancing is still permitted. So where can you shop in peace if businesses can enforce these superstitions? https://t.co/V9dXdJ2OhU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @townhallcom: DeSantis continues to show the country what real leadership looks like.  https://t.co/vwK0gyrwKT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He'll be eating real meat. It's all a scam. https://t.co/Q2Li9JA7iI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[excellent writers https://t.co/S2t7FLkTkG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Stephen90182822: Good morning folks   https://t.co/sQ8n7qyvhQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They can have joint. https://t.co/GIepaiXrMM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Communists always benefit from their slaves. https://t.co/0aqa0aqtmr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I didn't wear the hat but I voted for Trump. Then he started the poison 'vaccine'. So, I signed out. I'm Catholic first and I know about the 'vaccine'. https://t.co/s7FdPhmxxq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump wants the vaccine. DeSantis didn't ban the vaccine. https://t.co/UUiiAUM9Ti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So no democrats, liberals, communists, marxists, socialists, independents, etc are refusing vaccine? Trump promoted the vaccine. https://t.co/IMNAi3akRI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden revellers claimed they didn't care if they got covid. Rioters|looters were given carte blanche. They outnumbered many gatherings. https://t.co/IMNAi3akRI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[God didn't send vaccines. I like the way God conveniently shows up now to poison us but not all year to go to church|synagogue. Governors were punishing worshippers. In the USA. We're not hesitant, we're certain. We're not all GOP. I'm Catholic. And medical knowledge is reqd. https://t.co/vxFU9A9hAs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's ok. Medical protocol isn't about politics.   At least put on a gas mask if it's airborne. I mean, the pile of bodies outdoors is astronomical.   When I see masked people I truly am concerned. How can they breathe, esp underground in enclosed subway car? I can't. https://t.co/cTnhCEIix0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep going about your lives - not long after - no one is permitted to protest against lockdown. Rioting? Sure, express yourself. No religious gatherings or leaders will be arrested  houses of worship permanently shut. No gathering in homes. Biden won? Have a good time crowding. https://t.co/ogpmTeluSR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UgonnaMario: Another church set ablaze in France.  Fire at the church of Wazemmes - Lille. Pray for France        Sainte Jean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @P8R1OT: How come nobody is talking about why the USPS is profiling us by spying on our social media posts?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo some grandmas might kill first: in March 2020 prior to NY April 17 mask mandate an older female about upper 60s|70 yrs old struck me hard in the neck demanding where is my mask? On #MTA bus. I told her she's not supposed to touch me. She even sat directly behind me. https://t.co/ZzoMo23lfp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May 17, covid disappears. He's got some crystal ball. https://t.co/UuTrHApPNI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It better improve. It's filthy, littered w/everything imaginable, crime ridden   farebeaters enjoy free rides. Meanwhile I pay $127/month. unwanted loud music, solicitors of every stripe #RestoreTokens #RestoreNYmaskBan victims|criminals can't be identified @MTA https://t.co/UuTrHApPNI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How about every home | building gets new pipes and real water not the medicated poison? https://t.co/0VFy3vq4zW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DclareDiane: Roman Warm Period was 2C warmer than today, new study shows https://t.co/LrgAHNACEG via @JWSpry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think he did that already. Sensible grandmas won't want you vaccinated against covid. https://t.co/OIwyygnNTG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The question is, what was the point of turning the Carters into shrinky dinks? https://t.co/8lSNKDCdXH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is it taking so long esp when there's proof of murder but it takes seconds to smack a NYer w/overcrowding in his own home during covid scam or being unmasked anywhere? https://t.co/91o42RvQqN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[freedom of religion  speech don't exist https://t.co/TKkXlOjnKR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[stupid Applauding this? Then it's a scam to destroy yourself not a safety measure. https://t.co/emFNOBUwIq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is. yikes https://t.co/Kuue94gHZV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Free one month's rent with vaccine. https://t.co/hgHG6JighV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's stupid. Not everyone drinks beer but it's not that pricey. Buy it yourself. Why get vaccine, good or bad, because of beer? What about those under the drinking age? https://t.co/ZwAq72IK9t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryMakow: Steven Fishman - Who Will Survive the Vaccine Holocaust?  Within 5 years, 80% or more of those who have been vaccinated, ei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: During the Spanish Flu pandemic, patients were brought outside to be exposed to sunlight. Guess why... https://t.co/4dlYk6Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They wanted to see the little black spot on it. https://t.co/y8enu0MPiE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WatremezPA: Incendie de lglise de Wazemmes - Lille https://t.co/arAyhKWI4X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: They lied about OxyContin. They lied about Lipobay. They lied about Thalidomide.  They lied about opioid addictiveness. The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'd rather have less crime, cleaner city sans masks and covidiots. https://t.co/OCwrt3OesL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo https://t.co/3wcMLFAw7J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If my grandmas were still alive, they'd wallop you. They died ages ago. They survived the Asian  Hong Kong flus. https://t.co/ZzoMo23lfp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders came back. https://t.co/VGDlBGrBRD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Repeat this in NY @WillABarclay @NMalliotakis @SenatorOrtt @RepStefanik et al https://t.co/JGdYlmhw3O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why did you marry him in the first place? If you're not married to him then you are free. https://t.co/hJqOQtquwZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[huh? Quit the fear tactics  bullying.  God is in charge. The time on earth is temporary. Heaven is eternal. We dont need your #covidsuperstition https://t.co/oWSccGb9FQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thevivafrei: Poll: Were you aware that the term the big lie being used by MSM and politicians to demonized those who question the 202]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fatherz: Canons of St. Peters forbidden to enter Basilica for the May Rosary https://t.co/EJIPfkiXPF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch "Priest rails against pandemic of fear in powerful homily" on YouTube https://t.co/rdRZVp7Q30]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want cookies.  Chicken nuggets? That's McDs! https://t.co/3z6Ea0Fx16]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: Trump should not run in 2024  DeSantis should]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It will. Temporarily. Then God will eliminate it. It was predicted in 1917. https://t.co/3ln5Rjt6Jy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They supposedly took the vax. https://t.co/BoaZ9kgv2C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hit Ernie on the head with the book, Bert. https://t.co/AHCOrlYjqU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[lol and someone claimed we 'looked up to them' during pandemic|re covid... https://t.co/JqFK1BrfsM]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>