<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@willjrichards very unexpected scenes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[spoiler alert: i love this album. https://t.co/cwiHoONK1R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Hello Darling... St. Vincent (@st_vincent) covers our April 2021 issue!  Also featuring Wolf Alice (@wolfalicemusic), gir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New issue alert!  Very very happy with our first mag of 2021!! https://t.co/ygACIzmP0a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Four covers. Four bold voices. Tomorrow. 2pm. https://t.co/OwQIvqpeGn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emmaswannphoto usually the commercial flight industry is just used to plug gaps but as the demand for cargo is so high right now, most airlines are solely running routes to do that. i have an aviation-obsessed cousin who tells me this stuff ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emmaswannphoto *imports, even!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emmaswannphoto i believe most, if not all, commercial flights also carry imported cargo. throughout the pandemic, i was told a lot of passenger flights still ran without passengers to allow for important to still happen. not all, of course but a lot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[at least email me to explain what the fault investigation came up with before just sending them back to me no explanation? thats really inadequate customer service, off the back of the fact a fault has developed with my shoes after just two months.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp i got in touch with you via email a few weeks back about a fault issue with my nike shoes. i sent them back via a return you created, and have not heard a word since. the shoes have now just been re-delivered to me with no communication or paperwork. not cool?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Our first Hello 2021 show is kicking off on @state51's YouTube now! https://t.co/kcitPOMlEy https://t.co/dwrwi5I6JU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i really, really hate this year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[also, can we just give the most massive of fucking shout outs to all the women who make such incredible music, and overcome the shit thrown at them daily to do so?! fuck yes 2020 - us finally celebrating this is maybe the best thing to come out of this  of a year. https://t.co/IHBFW97t4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[have obv been a massive clich by naming @yelyahwilliams solo album my favourite record of 2020 (and wut) but i am consistently confounded and comforted by her capacity for openness, even in the darkest of times. thanks for keeping me company over these turbulent few months. https://t.co/bffktfaKnR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Thomas Headon (@thomasheadon) is the first artist to takeover the new-look @SpotifyUK Our Generation playlist, and to mark]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: .@SpotifyUK has announced a whole new look for its Our Generation playlist, and they've invited three incredible acts to t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[big tick off the bucket list with this one! https://t.co/MfphZLN0XD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: All hail Queen Bea! Beabadoobee covers our October 2020 issue  Also featuring Arlo Parks, Royal Blood, Matt Berninger, Wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EatYourOwnEars: Morning with @diymagazine   @sarahjamieson__ catches up with @CHVRCHESs @laurenevemay to talk quarantining on the othe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Kicked off our week of 100th issue celebrations at @SignatureBrew with an exclusive opening party with cover stars @idlesb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thepreshaah: Up Next #HoxtonLive @sarahjamieson__ @diymagazine joining us for a chat @hoxtonradio https://t.co/KYXpJC3sgF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[here it is! this one is a super special issue for all of us, especially after everything this year. huge shout out as per to team @diymagazine for just being the best lot in the biz. weeeee did it!  https://t.co/UxWN5ijAOr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thetrainline hey, a friend booked a coach via your site and now needs to exchange the ticket, due to a covid-related situation, however the option on your app to change the date/time isnt loading. can you help? he doesnt have twitter so has asked me to contact on his behalf.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[just had the rather terrifying realisation that ive worked on 97 of these 100 issues... but anyway, some actual real life (and v safe and responsible) gigs yaaaaay! https://t.co/Q2dLUwxLB1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sainsburys hi there, my delivery was due between 6 and 7pm but no sign yet. am now on hold on the phone but not getting through - any way you can help? thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Angel Olsen covers our August 2020 issue!  Also featuring Declan McKenna, Tkay Maidza, The Killers, Bright Eyes, The Mag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: AUGUST COVER IN ONE HOUR  https://t.co/Lr2p9m8mni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@easyJet hi, my partners flight was cancelled back in april and he requested a refund over 90 days ago now (on 23rd April) and hes still waiting for his money back. hes just spent 62 minutes on hold to customer service phone line but no answer - can you help at all?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesParrish i just took a week off and despite, at first, thinking god, what a waste if im not going anywhere, or doing x, i realised its less about what you do and its more about giving myself a bit of time away from the constant bizarre cycle of life right now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesParrish 100% worth taking some time off. if this were an alternate universe, and things were relatively normal, you wouldnt think twice about having a day or two away from emails every couple of weeks - i think its important to remember that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_rfalexander fuuuuuuucking hell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Phoebe Bridgers covers our June 2020 issue! Also featuring Run The Jewels, Nadine Shah, Jehnny Beth, 100 gecs, Orlando Wee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @phoebe_bridgers: Tomorrow (June 4) all profits from the merch store (including album pre-orders) will go to @bailproject. This livestre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[lols]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@livycoare i use glossiers milky jelly cleanser which has the grossest name but is really lovely on the skin. id also just say to be careful if you go down the ordinary route - know a couple people whos sensitive skin has literally been burned by it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[never have i needed a new series of @QueerEye in my life more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: In our latest issue, we chat to Sports Team (@SportsTeam_), IDLES (@idlesband), Car Seat Headrest (@carseatheadrest), PVRI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeliverooHelp hello! ordered from kricket in brixton this evening. order arrived on time but wed been sent the wrong main dish and have reported via the app but honestly, it seems crazy we have to wait up to 2 days to get some sort of refund / credit - can you help sooner pls?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[shout out to @yelyahwilliams for releasing one of the most raw, honest and liberating records of 2020 so far. five  for you, HW, five for you! https://t.co/ufJrSDL8hp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HannahLawtherr ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Please note! Because of social distancing measures, once again, we'll be sharing our issue digitally but won't be printing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: New mag alert! The Streets' Mike Skinner is the cover star of our May 2020 issue, which also features IDLES, Sports Team,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fredds_flowers hello! i received my first box yesterday and love my flowers but the foliage ive been sent just doesnt really work in the arrangement - it kinda takes over the entire thing rather than enhances! any idea how to style it separately, perhaps? https://t.co/hhshNqktJU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we finally made me a t-shirt  https://t.co/S4I2uhRgab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@El_Hunt_ @diymagazine sadly twas not me behind it, but i very very much endorse it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[support music magazines! https://t.co/qNIt5OYWFV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ we were genuinely so chuffed that this could happen - thank you to anyone who got themselves a copy! https://t.co/RrhA5FEfZs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: If you're enjoying our DIYsolation Festival, please head over to @HelpMusiciansUK and donate!  https://t.co/ho4GrfBLqv h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hello! our DIYsolation festival is in full swing over on our instagram page and itd be bloody lovely if you fancied tuning in (or even donating a lil bit of  to help musicians!) - go go go!! https://t.co/SYKpvl65W9 https://t.co/iFjhIHa6na]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_DanielleWarren best recipe ever: https://t.co/ahm419C1MU i always do half amounts though and it makes plenty. also swap the walnuts for white or milk chocolate ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_DanielleWarren @LouiseRamsay_ ive never used cocoa powder!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[on a more serious note: were throwing the DIYsolation Festival to both entertain our lovely readers while were all at home, and to try and raise some money for @HelpMusiciansUK. if you can donate, please do! https://t.co/vWCDesCZkM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[get on the bank holiday bevs and join in our virtual fest  https://t.co/0vwHYTkB36]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[none of this really went how we had originally planned four(?) weeks ago but i feel v lucky to have had this lot by my side during this weird time. big thanks to @lisaannewright @emmaswannphoto @ellywatson @sawn_off @coecoechanel @DIYmusicLTD ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HELLO! were all facing our own uphill struggles right now, but it feels incredibly good to have finally released our new issue. the past few weeks have been more challenging than any of my time at DIY so i wanna give a huuuge shout out to the team whove worked so hard on this! https://t.co/SpuB5xBaSz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: A message about our April 2020 issue, which features Biffy Clyro (@BiffyClyro), Perfume Genius (@perfumegenius) and more ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelloFreshUK hi, can you reply to my DM please? appreciate youre v busy right now but ive still not had any tangible contact about my missing ingredients / refund.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelloFreshUK hey there, just received my HelloFresh box and has discovered i also havent been sent any chicken for the two chicken-based recipes i ordered. cant get through on the phone so can you help please? i also had a few (less essential) items missing last week ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp @Hermesparcels hey, i ordered last thursday using my next day delivery, received confirmation Hermes had my order at the local depot on friday but its been delayed since then. yesterday at 1pm the tracker said itd be on the move in 24 hours but still no news?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my hero https://t.co/0sK7R1qxRW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i know its incredibly hard to stay positive right now and a lot of people (myself included) are struggling, so i wanted to share this article that helped to give me a bit of perspective in this very confusing time. https://t.co/W5p7cgNaCj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[if youre at home today and fancy getting a live music fix, were live-streaming sets from both porridge radio and king nun this afternoon! go go go watch now! https://t.co/MJxoInv1Xe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LNER hello, aware theres a lot going on right now but ive not received any contact from yourselves about my seat guarantee claim, which was filed on 23/2/20. were now a few days past the 14 working day response time, so i wanted to check in. thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[just a friendly reminder that the WHO hasnt changed its stance on international travel at all over the past week. in fact, its currently actively advising AGAINST travel restrictions ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[truly gutted for the whole sxsw team, the artists who were heading there and anyone and everyone whos put so much work into this over the last year. we must not let fear win and have even more events cancelled this year - it could be devastating on a much wider scale. https://t.co/mzptRJ2Mfx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[just did a lovely hour-long round trip from paddington to paddington ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lexcanroar: you're allowed to be shocked  sad that Caroline Flack is dead *and* take the abuse allegations seriously *and* think that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LNER thanks - seat reservations are still appearing on the screens and there hasnt been any sort of announcement (so im not personally convinced they have been lifted), but its all a bit confusing for anyone new who boards.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LNER when people are politely asking others to leave their reserved seats (ourselves included), theres a lot of confusion / aggression being thrown around. if any announcements can be made, that would help to clarify things.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LNER im travelling on the delayed 9.24 from kings x to durham. theres been a LOT of bother with seat reservations. people from the cancelled 8.30 train saying they get priority over people with reservations on the 9.24/ seat res have been lifted but no announcements to clarify]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dominos_UK hi, i made an order online last night and an item was missing. i contacted the store to notify them and asked for it to be sent out, but it never was. how do i get a refund if i paid online?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[heeeeeeeres kevin! https://t.co/9ZBKdTm8A9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/YLtjdAJbd4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/lBfwHUtZ03]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GhostWhaleLDN: After 5 days of renovation, we are now BACK OPEN IN BRIXTON!!! We have replaced most of the shelves with more fridges so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp hey, earlier, i attempted to buy an item and it then said there was an issue and to try again later. i waited, now it says that item is out of stock. have now decided on a new item and gone to check out, but its not offering my premier delivery, which is active?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[on the train home, no one sat next to me. bags all in the luggage rack with no trouble. the dream is alive and well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ginandconnick oh my god no way]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[and helping to save the NHS is just one tiny part of the reason that we must get rid of the conservatives today. this is no longer about lies and squabbles; this is about our families, and our futures. #ForTheManyNotTheFew]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[without the NHS i would not have the life i lead now - hell, i might not have had a life at all - and so every time i visit the RVI now i am filled with gratitude at what these people did for me, for free.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[when i first started to understand my condition as i got older, i remember asking my mam what couldve happened if they hadnt caught and treated my juvenile rheumatoid arthritis when they did. id have definitely gone blind, if not worse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[every time i walk into the eye department at the RVI in newcastle, i see people i recognise, people ive been seeing for over 20 years. my optometrist - the incredible mr garvey - has seen me grow from a 5 year old getting to grips with my cataract removal to a fully grown woman.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[if someone were to ask me to write a piece about my experience with the NHS, i could probably write a book. for the majority of my life, i have been in and out of hospitals, i have been supported by doctors and nurses, and even to this day, i still attend at least twice a year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @slowthai: VOTE LABOUR ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[bon appetite! heres our lovely class of 2020! https://t.co/lOcqJ1hNbX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iaskedforlove and gremlins.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this, this, this, this, this. https://t.co/bkquEDo0EK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DebraFox_ can you throw a milkshake at him pls?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[class of 2020 klaxon!!  https://t.co/oTkMHd7gtY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ginandconnick :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[re-fuckin-tweet  https://t.co/Zra9UvB4Dr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this week, my chemical romance reunited () and maybe my favourite issue of 2019 hit the streets. nooooot too shabby when you think about. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/dAYxrdYXKP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LottieHunt oddbox is all surplus veg and fruit i believe? theyve also got a few discount codes on the go!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WestMidRailway okay great, thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WestMidRailway hey there, ive got a ticket from london euston to birmingham new street at 14.15 and national rail is listing it as cancelled - what can i do? are tickets being accepted on virgin services?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[been suffering with severe pain in my feet for a year now, no ones able to diagnose it. then tear a bit of my ligament and suddenly everyone knows whats up  thanks guys.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the man, the myth, the legend himself!  https://t.co/3VKgVapgwE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JNewellPhotos i had never really done it til recently but a girl on the counter that did my make up was like oh i always give out samples because people should get to try stuff before they commit which was so nice to hear haha.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JNewellPhotos bit delayed here but also, if you dont wanna spend too much , go to counters and ask for samples. MAC are good at giving out lil foundation and primer pots and might give you a few options to build on without being out of pocket!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>