<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@JRehling 90% of the time the jobs are along the line of, "Hey can you translate this?" as it's easier to have someone on staff who speaks the language fluently than spend money teaching someone a new language]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marmel in short, no one wants to risk their life for $7.25]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MistrelofHorror Lilo  Stitch hits differently now that you said all that... https://t.co/f2lHnkiN1D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lcshorten Oh it follows one of the little sisters rescued from the first game returning to Rapture to see if it's still there only to discover it's still fully functioning (that's if fans can ignore the Bioshock 2 story for the sake of this scenario)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kieloneil A Pague's Tale: Innocence Lost Ember Siren Mark Of Kri https://t.co/SvdkenMH1O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nathanmhurst Hot Take: the pokemon card thing is the youtuber equivilant to lighting a cigar with a $100 dollar bill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@APlagueTale Giving him a hood, in the end, was the best decision.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OhMyMithrandir WAIT, WHAT?! https://t.co/DbNoqitkGa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @GameStop exclusive (Glow-in-the-dark) Skeletor Jumbo Pop! Not fee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @HotTopic exclusive Cherry Coca-Cola Can Pop! #Funko #Funkpop #Che]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt Where's my Dicky!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rmayemsinger ABNER! ABNER! There are all these people outside look at this!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveHofstetter if SHE used a condom she wouldn't have had to wait till the last minute to get her GED to run for congress.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Playing #FarCry 3 for the first time in a while and was quickly reminded why I hate the "Good Guys" and rooted for Vass. #gaming #writerslife https://t.co/iEmVVLcCI7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: Happy #FunkoVirtualWondrousCon! RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Diamond Collection Jolteon Pop! #F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HorrorPixi https://t.co/JO13IInPoc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tonyq666 @terrorca I think you can find them on Ebay and Amazon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@terrorca forgot to mention, leading up to the film's release McFarlain toys released her action figure and said the movie was called "The Tooth Fairy" this was all before the script change that also changed the name of the movie. https://t.co/xoMuBcE5wB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@terrorca Script changes were made to make her appear more. I guess in the original her big reveal was towards the end. She was also to be played by Doug Jones. https://t.co/4HyjtLofin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@terrorca hot take: the original concept of the tooth fairy's design was way better than the one used in the film.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(Insert obligatory selfie of me with a band-aide on arm showing I got the first does of #COVID19Vaccine here)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: This is fine . RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN the This is Fine Dog Pop! Also available for pre-order]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LewnaticLive?! https://t.co/yRkrH2oD1F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance TO WIN this Galactus with Silver Surfer (PREVIEWS Exclusive) Jumbo Pop! #Funko]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Coffeemate I love the Italian Espresso flavor! I like to have espresso in my coffee to boost the flavor but the drawback is having really bad jitters later on. This gives me the taste with no added caffeine!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skream_kween When will people learn loud/obnoxious does not equal funny?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zammit_marc Keep Myself OR @HorrorFuel_com up to date on this project!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @BoxLunchGifts exclusive Winnie the Pooh Pop! #Funko #Funkogivea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elle_hunt @utherlives WHY DID YOU ASK IF YOU ALREADY HAD THIS REHERSED OPINION READY TO BACKFIRE ON YOU?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@humble added 12 new #videogames to its lineup for #charity. proceeds go to @StopAAPIHate. #StopAsianHate #GamersDoingGood https://t.co/AyIbUenQN3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Target exclusive blacklight Rogue Pop! #Funko #FunkoPop #Giveaway]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caytlyn_brooke Lower Left]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: It's Deadpool's 30th Anniversary! RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Funko exclusive Nerd Deadpool Po]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gloombugg don't you mean, "Which horror movie should I watch first?"?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to win this Marvel Zombies Doctor Doom Pop! Not feeling lucky? Add this Pop! t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#StopAsianHate #StopAsianHateCrimes  That's the tweet as I'm too Pissed to say more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#RIP Yaphet Kotto, one of the only people in the #Alien franchise to go hand-to-hand with a Xenomorph. #RIPYaphetKotto https://t.co/eJt5AhShq6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lifesafeast Starship Troopers...because it's nothing like the book!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance TO WIN this @HotTopic exclusive Scarlet Witch Pop! #WandaVision #ScarletWitch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[have not been on here due to weeks worth of #Depression and #anxiety attacks, not only affecting my #mentalhealth but working on any of my #writings. The following pic was me just wrapped in one of the comfy blankets I wear during such attacks. #FacesOfDepression https://t.co/0fG4l094G8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaredPushner he's wearing assault tactical gloves that have plastic/Kevlar knuckles AKA Cheating.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Spring Convention exclusive Yoda Pop! #FunkoVirtualCon #FunkoECCC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lcshorten the key is putting the pineapples on before you bake it so they caramelize a little bit and become chewy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Spring Convention exclusive (glow-in-the-dark) Treasure Skeleton P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter: *#Xenomorph Trends on #Gaming* ME: "*gasps* A new Alien game?!" *Clicks* Twitter: It's a #Fornite Thing ME: https://t.co/K5BFwB2khb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmikillzombie interesting fact, Boglins are a breed of dog, I know cause I have one ^_^]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Spider-Man 2099 Spring Convention exclusive! #Funko #Funkogiveaway]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Should @Twitch allow "Sleep Streams"?  #twitch #gaming #livestreams #streamers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my #horror #shortstory written in only 666 words. https://t.co/P4SwCvKKOH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrrousselet Limelite]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lcshorten A visually stunning film, and that Bear Creature... *Chef's kiss*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RhysChryspies Dubbed Or Subbed?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MistrelofHorror there were two others but the behind the scenes special feature showed as they were making up the morgue (which was real) one of the corpses was moved quite easily by a crew member (literally lifted with one hand).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MistrelofHorror the hot button topic about this film, was a real corpse REALLY used in the film like the tagline claimed? Personally, after seeing it, I call BS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Sunday, try to put forth the effort of saying "Happy Valentines Day", because saying "Happy VD" will send the WRONG message. #ValentinesDay #valentinesday2021 https://t.co/45s5jdowbP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The perfect example of "Oh I heard you're kind of a big deal now...LET'S BE FRIENDS!" https://t.co/F0vByHv4pf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you were born the year of the OX and found out the #LunarNewYear  this year is the Ox. #ProudOx https://t.co/5I9B3BkOXH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TheLastofUsPartII #TheLastOfUs #Gaming #Horror   ME: *Minding my own business*  BRAIN: Is Abby now infected after orally coming into contact with Ellie's blood after biting off her fingers?  ME: https://t.co/H60TlzCfeG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Snape_ https://t.co/aqMdNOO5Ul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrjafri are you sure he was not shrinking?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveHofstetter didn't she also wait to get her GED only when she decided to run for congress?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL The big question is...which one are you going to watch first?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@erikaishii @BeastyChicks @yoshisquared Yellow Ranger was Bae for me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NinjaTheory https://t.co/ti6JmNS8V7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[in other news, CAPCOM says Lady Dimitrescu is 9'6ft #LadyDimitrescu #gamingnews #ResidentEvilVillage https://t.co/3itTSjvUQm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think @JaboodyShow should team up with @MiltonTPike1  on the Purge Minecraftoperate Server and opperate the courthouse together. Really blow the minds of the YouTubers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FakeHotelFacts the sheets are clean https://t.co/byxuOID1E5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've suffered from Clinical #Depression and #Anxiety since I was 14, if anyone can tell you if this bracelet truly works, it's myself or someone like me. I challenge @Apollo_Neuro to let me try this to see if it really works or not. #mentalhealth #MentalHealthAwareness https://t.co/BpS5X4854R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmikillzombie I guess it won't be a found footage but it will follow the events of the first movie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In #Gaming/PR news: I swear everything and everyone is trying to piss me off today... #findmyhappyplace #writerslife #youhaveonejob https://t.co/Sb3XGtXEu2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would be asking WHY THE F**K IS EDGAR ALLEN POE COSPLAYING AS A COWBOY IN MY BEDROOM AT 3AM?! #writerslife #writing https://t.co/2xGbcBEUb3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[America just woke up from its nightmare with @TheAmandaGorman as the alarm clock. #Inauguration]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeanLuk @TonyTodd54 @MSNBC install the lights, power them with solar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jenjburt https://t.co/CY8Sw1uG2c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DevonESawa this isn't some trick to get us to raise our hands so you can cut them off right?...RIGHT?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@terminalsio is the site still updating?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BaghdadBrian @riseagainst If she's getting into music that has a lot of social commentaries pretty much any band on the "Rock against Bush" albums. With Female fronts: The Soviettes, and Sleater-Kinney]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WerewolfVGAME @CyanideStudio Can't wait https://t.co/GoLj6nLKXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ReginaKimWrites Short answer: Yes  Long Answer: YEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEES!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @amazon exclusive Battle at Echo Base: Chewbacca Pop! Deluxe! http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We need to bring back honor and integrity to the Presidential #MedalOfFreedom, #EugeneGoodman deserves it as well as Brian Sicknick (Posthumously) and Howard Liebengood (Posthumously).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HorrorGeekMel Me, a New Yorker with no snow https://t.co/xrGbGLTraL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NOFSpodcast Scale 1-5 for both:  The 1959 film: 5  The 1999 Film: 0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nathanmhurst actually inspired me to write a prose titled "White Animals"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @BoxLunchGifts exclusive glow-in-the-dark Baymax with Mochi CHASE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OddNMacabre remember?! Dude I have a couple of them still!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@juda1313 Hands down, Nosferatu (1922), for a silent film it still sends chills down my spine. https://t.co/XuZjRfbPGm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @OfficialTLC CHASE Pop! prize pack! #Funko #Funkogiveaway https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LADYDARKFICTION I felt the "twist" in the first movie was spoiled at the beginning which kind of ruined watching the rest of it, the second film I think was trying to make up for the lack of supernatural elements missing from the first with and Ralph Ineson's talent being wasted scarier.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While in the middle of writing a #horror story and looking at my research notes then looking at my search history and thinking "I'm on a watchlist now..." #writerslife #writerproblems #amwriting https://t.co/QCMVx7tXtn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@freematik Dude, Kurosawa films, no other way to describe them except with this gif https://t.co/A1GrXC7WBs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BatEveryHour Looks like it wants to shake hands! https://t.co/pBmM5ubsoV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @EntEarth exclusive FLOCKED @RealGrumpyCat Pop! https://t.co/luU1o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Target exclusive Terror Claws Skeletor Pop! #Funkogiveaway #giveaw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is officially my last Tweet of 2020:  Farts are Tubas with a lisp.  #HappyNewYearsEve  #HAPPYNEWYEAR2021 #GoodBye2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I reviewed a lot of #Videogames this year, here's my 10 worst to best #horror games I reviewed! https://t.co/ZI5gNOIH6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got the Bluray of The Terror: Infamy, I'm no psychic but I see an all-day binge in the near future. @TheTerrorAMC https://t.co/TggHNA0n3o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@erikaishii WAIT WHAT?!?!?! https://t.co/5RY4KauRvs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this Funko exclusive 10" (Glow-in-the-Dark) Oogie Boogie Pop! #Funko #F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OriginalFunko: RT  follow @OriginalFunko for the chance to WIN this @Target exclusive Black Light Iron Man Pop! #Funko #Funkogiveaway]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>