<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#911onFOX 4x09 is the stuff of my nightmares, gah.  Makes me remember how lucky I was when I crashed my car... if I lived in that world, I would've ended up going the other way off the "cliff" (I don't think it's high enough to classify) and into the sea....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@malamalware @qikipedia @tomality Connotation? (If it's not, sorry and obviously my brain has already gone to sleep and it's time to put the phone down... )]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And the award for World's Fastest Childbirth goes to... Lucy! I know they're never realistic, but wow #NotGoingOut #ChristmasShopping]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welp, season 8 finale made me cry.  And it was only a prolonged daydream :D Or can we pretend that's what really happened? #Scrubs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @playingwithdust: Just remembered this - Mike Collins was great. https://t.co/XnjT46ESAG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @qikipedia: The editors for the first Oxford English Dictionary thought they would finish it in a decade; after five years they were onl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I agree with the Janitor.  There is way too much change going on towards the end of season 8. Ahhhh #Scrubs  (I haven't seen either part of the finale yet, no spoilers! Though I already know about season 9, so all these changes actually make sense...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Season 6 finale was awesome!   Pleeeease tell me season 7 doesn't bite. (Pun fully intended.  Ha.) Final seasons so often do... aaaahhh...  #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone bought me a set of wooden #crossstitch bookmarks! Cute!  I expected them to come with instructions, but no... I know how to find designs and sew them, but does anyone have any tips? Especially on how to make the back nice?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reached my first goal, and my second, now onto my third!  As much as I thrive on the ridiculousness of November's 50k, I love the flexibility of Camp even more &lt;3 #CampNanoWriMo2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's Something About Movies is the only show I can think of that my mum really enjoys.  Please make it forever :D #TSAM  She doesn't mind Would I Lie To You? and she'll sit through Pointless, but they come nowhere close...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Done with season 1 of #CallMeKat ! Hopefully the first of many? :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's a shame 13 was written before the cancellation :p (At least, I assume he's fine by the end?). They could've tweaked it so that the series literally couldn't continue... #MacGyver]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally finished Kula World! It only took 20 years and 9 months...   (The 20 years was the time it took between playing it at a friend's house and me actually getting a PS3 and the chance to play it myself. Though without a walkthrough, it actually might have taken that long...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(But yes, I realize that it would have made it too easy for her to escape in Normal Again, as proven by how Tara saves them) #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So the "Willow not using magic ever again" thing is actually going to stick, huh? I was hoping something would happen and she'd start again.  I liked her being magic.  Boo. #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did NCIS: Los Angeles become NCIS: Russia when I wasn't looking? I swear every other episode is something to do with either the country or the Russian characters they've introduced.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnFinnemore Listening to Uskerty for the 200th time, I suddenly have a question - why is Carolyn in such a bad mood at the start? It's hilarious, of course, but... she should be thrilled about her prank.  Is she annoyed that they're making her go and collect it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching #FawltyTowers always reminds me of how it took me WAY too long to make the fawlty/faulty connection...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not that I would *want* more scenes like THAT one in episode 1, but the rest of the season seems fairly tame in comparison? So far.  Famous last words? :p)  Why go that far if that's not going to be the tone?   More importantly, are there ever going to be any guests?  #BatesMotel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One of the brilliant things about working from home is being able to listen to #CabinPressure.  Currently listening to Rotterdam and wondering if the two Martins ever actually get that bitter? :P  @JohnFinnemore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ooh.  Does this mean Desi's going away?? Openings like that on shows like this nearly always lead to endings like that...  #MacGyver]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TV advertisement credits Jane as Lane.  Either I missed something or someone's finger slipped... :D #ZoeysPlaylist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My usual show isn't on tonight, so it looks like I'm finally watching RIPD! It's only 7 years old... oops...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching #BatesMotel for at least as long as it takes me to find that it's too scary for me :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just randomly caught the start of a Simpsons episode (I never watch The Simpsons) and it happened to be the Game of Thrones-like one :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vissersixxx: https://t.co/tOnBDUSLNP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellaluciewrites Just watch the premieres, the finales and the beginning and/or end of each episode? :D   I only caught the last ten minutes of one the other day and it was plenty to get the gist of what was going on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellaluciewrites I think I mostly just watch it for the episodes that end with a cool reveal.  The way they tease things out is usually pretty clever.  (It's probably relevant that I'm rubbish at guessing twists)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellaluciewrites Not at all.  I've somehow made it to the most recent season (5?) and I really don't know how I'm still watching when I go into every episode thinking "ugh" :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[911 and Lone Star are like entry level horror for people who don't like horror.  Don't go in there! Don't touch that! Nonononono Ewwwww .... really???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're supposed to believe that Nate can land in the middle of a field, look around and know exactly what country AND year he's in?? Historians must be magic. #LegendsofTomorrow #Shogun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I like the #Hollyoaks theme, but it really feels like it needs to be slightly longer so the same tune isn't repeated quite so many times...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does anyone know where I can find the 2015 Christmas Special? Everywhere that has all the other episodes doesn't have that one... it's almost like it doesn't actually exist... :p #NotGoingOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why does season 7 only have 11 episodes??  #Scrubs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lorettamilan: Its a #palindromeday! Enjoy the satisfying beauty of todays date. Read it front to back, back to front and upside down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mark_omeara89 I saw it! (Well, I actually saw this tweet first so I was probably looking for it, but still!) :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Awww, the wedding was sweet.  Though it felt like a very short engagement after watching the previous episode yesterday :P #NotGoingOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally time to start season 2! &lt;3 #ZoeysPlaylist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[... is Hugh Dennis the voice of the captain? :D #NotGoingOut #Plane]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@real_sara_scott We're accidentally watching the same episode at the same time! Wahey! Hi! :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Has anyone confirmed which #Walker is the most accurate? Are they all martial arts experts, or was the original actually just made to showcase Chuck Norris' skills? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giles can't leave! He's one of the best things about the show! #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why did they stop the Scrubs marathon? :( I was watching that! #Scrubs #E4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is anyone else with a Samsung Galaxy being annoyed by Offline Finding notifications? I can't figure out how to turn them off :/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it an unpopular or a common opinion to think it should have been Dawn that died at the end of season 5? (I'm late to the party, I know.)  I know why they did what they did, and I enjoyed it (read: cried), but...  #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finished season 5! My procrastination on watching The Body made it take far longer than it should have... :D #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The entire point of All For Love is about being accurate.  So sure, why shouldn't she be booked on a flight at the end when she said earlier that she doesn't have a passport? :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctor Who time! The fact that it's just finishing for most people and I haven't seen any tweets is worrying... :p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After two weeks, I finally stopped procrastinating and watched The Body.  Poor Buffy! Poor Dawn! Poor everyone! :(  As predicted, I immediately needed to go watch a comedy after :D   #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is the music in the galloping scene in the last episode? I'll know it when you tell me, but I can't place it... #Miranda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you, whoever it was I follow that made me aware of the John Finnemore episode of My Teenage Diary.  Brilliant! :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The kid that plays Jack is so adorable! &lt;3 (In season 5.  I assume the actor changes.) #Scrubs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RocketMinx Of course not! (Or if it is, then we're both childish :D)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why did Jack have to leave? :( Old friend is the only way a character like that can work, so they can't introduce a replacement, and Desi is just so... competent.  I miss the comic relief. #MacGyverCBS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MicroSFF: "Put it on my account." "We don't-" the junior bookseller said. "We do," the senior cut in. "Of course." The customer took th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was just starting to think "this is a weirdly light episode" and then... that ending... :o (I know about The Body, but I thought I had another couple of episodes before I got there!)  #BTVS #IWasMadeToLoveYou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What?? Elliott can't leave! What will poor Janitor do without his Blonde Doctor? #Scrubs #MyChangingWays]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was looking forward to You Might Also Like, but it's not what I was expecting :(   But then, I've only really enjoyed about half the episodes (over both seasons), so maybe the issue is with me and not the show :P   #TheTwilightZone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not saying I have a short attention span... but my favourite cop show is #BrooklynNineNine my favourite doctor show is #Scrubs and my favourite 'nothing' show is #Mom ... :p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've seen Groundhog Day so many times and I never really thought about it being creepy from Rita's point of view.  Thanks, #TwilightZone #TryTry :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IainRossi @andydalessio21 @IMDb Shh, spoilers.  (Kidding, it's old and I'm not a spoilerphobe, but I'm also trying not to learn too much).  I have heard that the final season is pretty generally hated though... a shame.  Quite often great shows don't know when to stop and let themselves down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andydalessio21 @IMDb It is amazing! I can't believe it's taken me until now to watch it! I always thought I had seen it before, but I don't seem to remember anything and there's no way I would have forgotten it :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IMDb Well, I'm halfway through #Scrubs and it'd be nice if it never had to end... :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not sure I ever watched #Scrubs properly before.  I'm on season 4 now, recognizing nothing, and it's my new favourite!  (Yes, I am the same person who is watching Buffy the Vampire Slayer for the first time.  They're called "oldies but goodies" for a reason!)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I *could* still win... but I don't think I'm going to put myself through the stress of 18k in 2 days. (I've won lots of times, it's fine.)  Instead, in honour of having had my 32nd birthday on the 16th, I shall set 32k as my goal! That's only 900 words away!  #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also a fan of how the end credits show scenes from the film.  It's like a mini recap.  More films should do that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally saw Last Christmas! Which I believe ironically came out just before last Christmas? :P   Very good, despite the lack of explanation... made me cry, because of course it did...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I rarely have the patience to write on my phone.  But every time I do, I'm always reminded of the thing I can't figure out... how does one indent paragraphs? :P #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please tell me Tom Ellis doesn't really leave at the end of season 1.  He's the main reason I've watched this far :D #Miranda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[25k! Finally! Very behind, but I have to stop for the night... my wordcount is both at 25k and a palindrome... :P  #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heeey, Miranda episode 2 has unexpected @JohnFinnemore ! Brilliant!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You know you're not a big fan of a show when you decide to write while watching it :D (I'm 10k behind, I have to!) #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Tis a dark and stormy night... and I'm wasting the ambience by watching a film instead of writing.  Oh well.  #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kittybliss I don't know them well, but I think I've seen Kerry on various panel shows? And Marcus' name in a different radio series?   Clare in the Community was one I was considering.  Now I have so much extra time, maybe I should be using it to try all the 'maybe's... :P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kittybliss Ooh! I don't usually get an answer :D I have not heard of it, I shall look it up! Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still on the lookout for a show I can love as much as #CabinPressure and #BleakExpectations .  Suggestions??   #BBC #Radio4 #comedy #radio #sitcom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10k! (It's still behind par, but who cares, it's a nice number :P)  #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TowerCopy Haha!  Yep, same... the "this is the year I'll finish and edit it into something halfway decent" lie.  Nooope.  Ah, I see we also share a tendency to get stuck on one story :D 10 years though! I hope this is the year it works out!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TowerCopy Do I take it I'm ahead of you? :p  2011 is great too! Do you actually finish and edit them, or are you more like me... most years just hit 50k and immediately stop? :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TowerCopy Hey! I've had lots of time to write, but I'm really good at procrastinating... so I'm only at 8k. We can do it!  I have! I think my first one was in 2005...  a lack of social life means I've won pretty easily almost every year :P  Good luck!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DevPitches I have no idea how they do it.  I think my personal best is 10k in a day... so far this year I've done 6k in 7 days :D  Good luck!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DevPitches 1am on November 30.  There are people capable of writing 50k in 24 hours... I am not one of them :o :p  (Though I'm not sure you can still validate your novel for a win that late.  So maybe not...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meant to hit 5k yesterday but failed.  Hit it today.  Acceptable! Only halfway from where I should be...  #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TowerCopy They call me a content writer, but I believe the jobs are similar :D Hi!   I managed to hit 4k today, how are you doing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ren_kofumi I really hope you mean the letters/punctuation kind of characters.... :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1807! Very unusual for me to start on Day 1.  Even more so to exceed the daily goal.  Probably can't keep it up for 29 more days :P Also, probably relevant that it's a Sunday... #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I realize saying #Sonic is too fast is like saying Mario is too super, but #SonicRush seemed a bit ridiculous? (I enjoyed it, but feel bad that there was barely a chance to appreciate the design...)   Maybe it's just this one? It has Sonic + Rush right there in the title...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy #NaNoWriMo! Anyone else in my time zone?    I never start writing at midnight, but I'm always still awake, so... good luck everyone!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NaNoWriMo What, like Stranger Than Fiction but you're in control? Good film.  I should watch that again instead of planning.  Thanks!  :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shouldn't the jump in the opening sequence technically have sent him splatting into the wall? :P #JamesBond #GoldenEye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 days?? But I'm not ready!  ... oh wait.  I'm a pantser.  I'm never ready.  Okay, carry on.     #NaNoWriMo20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AvifaunaLux It really doesn't! (Aside from the "oooh, computers" stuff in the early seasons.)   The problem though is that more than once I've looked up something about one of the actors and been rudely reminded that they're 20+ years older... :p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AvifaunaLux You mean I'm not the last person in the world to watch it? Yay! :D   Who cares if we're a couple of decades late? It's still great! Vampire shows are still cool! We win - we don't have to wait for new episodes/seasons!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AvifaunaLux That's true.  I suppose I also eat chips when I'm bored and trying to keep myself awake :p From what I've heard happens later in this season (I'm new to Buffy), lightness is needed where we can get it...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So... Buffy's the vampire slayer, and Spike is the slayer slayer (in love with the slayer?) :p  I know Xander and Willow eating chips on patrol was for comedy, but... surely they've patrolled before? Why are they suddenly being idiots and making fun? :/  #BTVS #FoolForLove]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Inspectors round didn't make sense? The answers weren't their inspector names and Richard didn't even say who they played :/ I don't like when I don't understand the question :p #pointless]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back in September, I decided I was going to have a go at being a planner this year.... it is now October 8 and I got nothing.  #pantser4ever #NaNoWriMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aha! I finally reached the episode where the infamous Dawn appears! #BTVS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally done with #AlexRider after missing the airing of the finale last week (I know! Bad planning on my part!).  Are we getting a season 2? I hope so!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>