<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ben_rosen: fox news is right, i received $1400 once and decided to never work again. why? to ruin the economy of course]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrotiGupta: every month I like to describe my period to my friends as "this weird thing that only happens to me"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaboukie: literally what does the lgbtq community have to do with this...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @filthymeeks: Its gotta be this https://t.co/FhbXRahquA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @raffysoanti: this the WORST typo ive ever fucking seen on this app https://t.co/4TTPBdtGwq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really good point]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @billyeichner: HAS THIS HAPPENED TO ANYONE ELSE??? https://t.co/j1MsAD8sSr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Sennott I think it works!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @liamgareau: hes a fucking star https://t.co/6NXWVbfIP5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saggiesplinters That works!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@milkglutton_ Hiiii]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @georgeciveris: .@Ziwe you were an iconic guest.   https://t.co/Z2PzwnC3OA https://t.co/gh8qDnL20y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caithuls: Me when the every color bot posts a pretty purple https://t.co/jfqXMzVell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @everycolorbot: 0x73009a https://t.co/KNQFTfagMY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ayah421: @angelamavalla PCOS fucking sucks, its not just the hair but also acne, weight gain, insulin resistance... the list is so lon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angelamavalla: Facial hair (hirsutism) is common in women living with PCOS.   Its important to note that women of colour are dispropor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @saggiesplinters: G I R L B O S S  https://t.co/g4Y0lSWVA4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saggiesplinters Please be cool about if I re-retweet this every time I see it ok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jamieloftusHELP: the only relatable thing bill gates has ever done is cancel his own podcast and get a divorce. fuck these billionaires]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jamieloftusHELP: do you ever patent a desperately needed vaccine while continuing to posture as a philanthropic grandpa with a shitty p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikaLomazzo Love that! Exactly how it should be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EASTMARKIE: https://t.co/fLL8k8hq4v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jdistef93 I really appreciate yall being vocal about this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AudreyPorne: So happy for her https://t.co/837IfG1eZC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And Im not saying it is or isnt bad just like some people that hold the same progressive politics and values as you do live in the red states as well]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @curlycomedy: Thank you to all the people who gave their lives figuring out which mushrooms we can and cant eat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I had to add location to my profile because when Id mention something SC specific, my mentions would be like aw I hope you arent in that horrible place for long and Id have to be like yeah I was born here and I live here now again!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@allisonoconor Every time I start writing sincerely some of the words just start autocorrecting to quarter inch piece of plastic :(]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @writtenbyahmad: https://t.co/yvcMRRbwKu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And before anyones like why do you know/ talk to people you know are republicans.. I live in South Carolina]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nothing scarier than a republican woman who looovves The Handmaids Tale]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caithuls: Ok this one is good https://t.co/ElzBTHbE3w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I made this up and I already forgot my thought process but I think it involves my ego!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A lot of people are saying I should be @twitter verified despite not having a job or any credits. Im inclined to agree!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @poptartdavid: Well this is gonna be awkward  https://t.co/NiEm6NFocR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @doubletrucks: me after it rains and my porch gets covered in slugs https://t.co/cw3pzjn8eJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mfbenji: POV: my best friend sent me a TikTok I saw 3 weeks ago https://t.co/aogsNxv8F8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrilllKnight: i do not identify as a boy or girl, i identify as a nuisance. an irritant. a fool and a problem]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bejohnce: Gently revisiting my #official @voguemagazine 73 Questions vid today. FULL VID HERE: https://t.co/UUYCs86F74 https://t.co/QvA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Buffalojilll Happy birthday!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jzux: i promise you, nobody notices that flaw you hate about yourself. theyre too busy noticing all the other flaws you arent even aw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HarperRoseD: Hi yall Im headlining PHX Beer Co Tap Room May 27th and am searching for someone to film my set! If you or someone you k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shanaz8201: jeff bezos and bill gates both realized marriage is a union and left expeditiously]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ellomelissa: only reason Billie eilishs shoot is controversial is bc she has big boobs if the girl had little bitty titties it would j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sahana_srini YES!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theeashleyray: fyi if you're a celebrity and you want to hit on me, i won't say shit on tiktok or anywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mark_DiStefano: If you follow someone who sexually harasses your friends, you are an enabler. By continuing to follow them, you enable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mark_DiStefano Happy birthday!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rajat_suresh: every time i take a shower 100% of the water coming out of theshower head goes directly into my mouth. i want to clean m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BringDaNoyz Thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thyholygemini So sorry and sending you love!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SydneyBattle: my friend makes fun of me because i nod  say "hello sir/madame" when i pass dogs on the street but it's called having a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @therealalisonw: no one has career advice like a person who has absolutely no understanding of what it is you do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danlicatasucks: it is Teacher Appreciation week, so i would just like to say that i appreciate it when teachers mind there own FUCKING]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @heykyleharris: Im always amazed by what my hands can create, nothing beats that smile when my client sees their new hair in the mirror]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brocklesnitch: The caption is drunk me thought she could do a backflip and it kills me https://t.co/81UABBJC5e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sleepingbonnet: a few portraits :)) https://t.co/coKHdqmFQm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joshgondelman: I think my dog melted? https://t.co/XJLjBVXaaG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apparently you can just post your own art and say Reminder. Really makes you think..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder https://t.co/aOOqDMOfgT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ANNOUNCEMENT: Stop being so fucking weird yall. Its bumming me out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sn0ozefest: https://t.co/niKdkdxu7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @notthedinosaur: the new doritos marketing is genius https://t.co/VDHVQhCRxF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thenatewolf: Life is like soccer because my mom signed me up for it and expects me to try my best even though I hate fucking soccer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abbycohenwl: Welcome to America https://t.co/itfe0ky7XI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caithuls: [me doing body positivity] I love my skin prison]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vinn_ayy: Shocking that I cant report replies for being a little off or energetically damp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deirge3 Hahah nah I had to mute that tweet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GraceGFreud: This is getting a lot of attention to day for some reason. Im guessing because its the best sketch of all time but could]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @codinghater: seems wrong that i can't hang out with my mom as a job]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@megstalter @bumble Bumble Sending Meg Stalter An iPad WHEN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megstalter: Yeah I dont really see what Im doing wrong hun https://t.co/9RKGwm6Arp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarahclazarus: I had a vaxxed friend over for the first time and her dog immediately snatched a tampon out of the trash and had to be w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RachelMComedy: Instagram is for narcissists, Twitter is for narcissists with body dysmorphia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @verymimi: muting the phrase why is no one talking about for my own peace of mind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SydneyBattle: when i make a tweet for two people and then it goes viral https://t.co/hyVBTkCaXw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Saucepan_Dan: This looks like u can buy it at autozone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarciaBelsky: In public trying to act like I havent just spent a year processing everything thats ever happened to me https://t.co/97]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ok I gotta mute. Yall have fun you freaks!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Flora__Flora: Do not bother trying to hook up w me if ur not wearing a long striped nightgown w a matching hat + holding a little plate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @memetazaa: https://t.co/Kb4Tceiiru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PallaviGunalan: men be like i cant commit and then stay friends with the worst people their whole lives]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PallaviGunalan: middle siblings have more de-escalation training than cops do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @caithuls: I have a phone interview today and someone told me to just be myself so Im not going to answer the call]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol the crop said KIND CUNT only]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi I love @PallaviGunalan and you should too!!! https://t.co/SjUv3SKKtH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaimaFerdows: going to save myself so much time with this https://t.co/aV633IQcPp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @heyjaredhey: Yesterday a man told me Japan is his second favorite country. I didnt ask! Happy AAPI Heritage Month!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Someone said yes its a historical artifact so why are you holding it like that ........ I just found a plastic plate and posted man I didnt know yall would eat this shit up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Im tweeting shit I need to hear myself: https://t.co/o9cOevouTZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZachBroussard No!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charles270: I can hear this plate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katie_schulze1: My grandmother had the Meg one and that's why I'm bi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoMoSenpai Which one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @notyourwaif: https://t.co/IRh9pHzcsQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vinn_ayy: I have been kicked out of the Kentucky Derby https://t.co/aLbCQ7Jo0j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My work is so important]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sandyhonig: https://t.co/o8iTktLgzh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im graciously allowing current followers to stay (unless you have bad vibes) and some celebrities to newly follow so as to maintain balance or some shit. But not TOO many celebrities! Im serious!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@khneori Ok fair enough]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>