<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Metronomy's Joe Mount chats us, track by track, through his memories of the bands game-changing 2011 release, 'The Englis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lifebanduk @6MusicStudio Absolutely smashing it x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @6MusicStudio pop day for reminding me that the most perfect possible bank holiday vibe prep is Lizzo b2b Gaga b2b Ru Paul ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: 'Chemtrails Over the Country Club' finds @LanaDelRey in an elegiac mood: "it's an introverted release that feels more like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ultrasubversive Noted and changed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ryanjamesjarman You cant dangle carrots like these when the worlds on fire, serve up the goods eh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Zara Larsson (@zaralarsson) covers our March 2021 issue!  Also featuring Celeste (@celeste), Julien Baker (@julienrbaker)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pals! Wonderful organisation @_WithCompassion need some extra pairs of hands. They make 1000 meals a day for those in need. Dm for info xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BLACKHONEYUK @jnessr AMEN TO THAT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Four covers. Four bold voices. Our February 2021 issue with Goat Girl, @palewaves, @Rico_nastyy and @slowthai is out now!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOVE LOVE LOVE this album - hyped to have them on the cover  https://t.co/ntMXTEQCM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thegallowboob: never seen a more perfect cake https://t.co/RAXbntKwHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheForty_Five: Tuesday 26th. 8pm. Instagram Live  We interview music journalist, DJ and Features Editor at @diymagazine, @lisaannewrig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lostlibertine done!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jnessr ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecribs: Christmas (All Year Long) is officially OUT NOW! Spread the word and Christmas cheer. Merry Cribsmas everyone! xxx  https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tentacles and tits on the new issue (plus loads of properly brilliant new artists). WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT EH. https://t.co/EEZKdbLrZz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read all abaaaaht it  https://t.co/s5bzEdPwHg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did a big chat with all time number one hun Damon and honestly, I think maybe I love 2020 now. Out tomorrow! https://t.co/eiguwBPiI0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vornietom: Me, a villager, outside of Dracula's castle after he has stolen my third wife for his harem https://t.co/Gj2XzNzZ1y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New mag alert!  https://t.co/fLWeJemDJK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pandamoanimum: Beyonc dancing to the original Grange Hill theme tune. https://t.co/A6r8fJPYzP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: In short, it is fucking dire so, of course, it has arrived in our desperate, joy-deprived laps now just to rub salt in th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jnessr Hmm, it's actually missing a couple of paras. But thank you! Getting sorted now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Always a pleasure to interview Joe @idlesband, especially when it's for @diymagazine's big 1-0-0. Champions, one and all. Read all about it&gt;&gt; https://t.co/FjjBB0Aap8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: The Cribs (@thecribs) are back, baby!! https://t.co/qP8h1SIQXE https://t.co/eBFh8otmeU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @matthewmaltese: an interview I did with my favourite  @lisaannewright https://t.co/2eeSyWFfdT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@matthewmaltese @diymagazine ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10/10 https://t.co/BGfxtFnjrI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@niall_mdoherty Good luck pal, I expect great things x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come hither children and let us teach you the ways... https://t.co/pvjiKaSAOR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two cover stars for twice the fun  https://t.co/3ERgMIz5aR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YnnsPhilippakis: Imagine the music industry in the UK being wiped out. No shows, no festivals, no venues. Call on the government for ur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LookHewittIs @EmilyRoseMackay Woop woop! Big congrats to you both! x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecribs: Got the old band back together for a fashionably late isolation video, our first live performance in almost 2 years! Feel l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@idlesband @lifebanduk You guys... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MissAHaddow: Jeez its sweltering today. What I wouldnt give to be Prince Andrew]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BISH BASH BOSH. @idlesband are back and we had a lovely chat about it  https://t.co/l2crAzWfc5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Happynessmusic ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Always loved how LQ's covers go from the biggest stars to the newest curveballs. Such a great ethos. Support if you can x https://t.co/gxpFMUPw7i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A TRULY EXCELLENT GAFF https://t.co/V8tugJmFku]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also #timstwitterlisteningparties tonight with Supergrass and The Coral just fully amplifying the feeling that in lockdown I have turned back into a nerdy teenager wigging out about records in my bedroom. Into it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I remember getting very very into Black Wire as a teen and being v sad I never saw them. Then in 2013 (so long!) I got to put on their reunion gig (so good!). Now they've finally released their long-sat-on second LP. WHAT A TREAT https://t.co/mKbec5PjNm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecribs: Back when we were touring The New Fellas, our frequent tour mates were Leeds legends Black Wire. They were one of the best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ellywatson: Super overwhelmed by the lovely response to our @diymagazine DIYsolation Festival this weekend  Big love to @HelpMusicians]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This weekend @diymagazine  https://t.co/NRQLnIDXHm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarahjamieson__ @emmaswannphoto @ellywatson @sawn_off @coecoechanel @DIYmusicLTD Team work, it does indeed make the dream work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @liamgallagher: Heres another one you might know. Its called SOAPERSONIC. If you know the words wash along LG x https://t.co/pG4ZHjH5VL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine:  INDIE STORES/VENUES SEND US YOUR CROWDFUNDERS/KICKSTARTERS/EVERYTHING SO WE CAN SHOUT ABOUT YOU ONLINE! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nomadicrevery: You cannot, *cannot*, FUCKING **CANNOT** tell people to avoid pubs, theatres and restaurants without giving those instit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[By not forcing the closure of venues, pubs etc, thus securing insurance payouts, @GOVUK @BorisJohnson is sounding the death knell for so many creative places. Yes, we shouldnt go right now. But holy fuck dont make this last forever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Happynessmusic: Thanks @diymagazine and hun @lisaannewright xxx https://t.co/VU5R5Bkc0K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Charliegunn love u Gunno xxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[KP NUTS IN THE HOUSE https://t.co/PXanB2TXyC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Resurrecting @AntidotesLDN for a night of solid gold indie bangers and more!! @thelexington// Sat Feb 15th// come shake a leg https://t.co/IyD0wJJ3tb https://t.co/sMtPH1nFoK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhatsApp Hi can you follow me so I can dm? Account's been hacked and need some help. Ta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @leoniemaycooper: Nick Cave's reasoning for Kanye West being the world's greatest artist thanks to being so "committed to his own derang]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grimes x Sleigh Bells x Download festival x  @poppy https://t.co/ilCB9fyNrV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/4AI0GUCAiv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellen_cph @thestaves haha, they are very good (although I cannot say I care for The Staves, I am sorry)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SportsTeam_ Intrigued/ worried]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seen any good bands with xmas merch out this year? TELL ME PLEASE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: the campaign starts here, gang #harrystyles4diy https://t.co/Z1LcEPzYzY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@snkrwck @Truman_Black thanks pal!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emmaswannphoto: The November issue of @diymagazine is out now, and this one of @orlandoweeks is in it - he tells @lisaannewright all ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellywatson @Truman_Black stop it im blushing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spoke to @Truman_Black in two different bits of the world and he told me LOADS OF GOSS about the new record. CLICK 4 GOSS&gt;&gt; https://t.co/QZzwLTo3U7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@transgressiveHQ IT'S ALL TRUE xxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The glorious ppl @transgressiveHQ are endlessly wonderful and inspiring and just generally ridiculous legends, and if you want to work in music you should be more like this&gt;&gt; https://t.co/ueN7Z39RqH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: POP WORLD! Iggy Pop (@IggyPop) covers our October 2019 Issue, featuring @teganandsara, @keleokereke, @DIIV, @kingnunband a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thobbsjourno @diymagazine @metronomy thanks!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bleep bleep bloop its the new issue of @diymagazine out fri! I wrote the cover! Its @metronomy! https://t.co/kr8bPCPvRX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lifebanduk did not expect to agree so much with basically everything they stand for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would thoroughly recommend Hail Satan? doc. Some pretty fucking sensible points. Interesting read on it here&gt;&gt; https://t.co/GnubILbbau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Literally pulling into Oxford station, listening to this monster like  @foals https://t.co/fDOEp1pDpz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[York people! Wanna review a show for DIY??? (please share and RT etc) https://t.co/q9xq0w8vrE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Journalists! Who wants this nice time? https://t.co/ISadTs3jXm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have inadvertently developed a horrible laugh like a low rent Jimmy Carr and my penance is having to listen back to it on interview transcripts daily. Sorry to anyone I have laughed around/ near/ at/ with.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dancad @ellywatson @wonderlandmag @diymagazine don't be scared, Dan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very proud of this issue. Loads of great shit and the one, the only Indie Dreamboat of the Universe on the cover. Praise be. https://t.co/jhKKQtbGGz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got these shit hot bands playing for our takeover of the Jagerhaus at @allpointseastuk today. Come have a shot and a bop. I will be attempting to not get bottled off the decks by Bring Me fans  https://t.co/5cKPT1N5q2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lindsaymelbo @emmaswannphoto @potteryband @thegreatescape Im nothing if not consistent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I watched @potteryband twice in 24 hours at TGE and Im gonna watch them again on Thursday cos theyre THAT GOOD. https://t.co/yJUYIpJ5OY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrTobyL The absolute greatest of pleasures. What a day to be alive! X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@willjrichards dislike]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love u @superfoodjunk https://t.co/r30Qmm9Wfs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: OUT NOW! Pick up your copy of the April issue of DIY, ft @Hayden_Thorpe, @stelladonnelly, @whitneytheband, @puptheband, @s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New DIY out Friday, featuring a beautiful, wildly verbose, often ridiculous (aka the best kind) comeback chat with Hayden by @willjrichards  https://t.co/ARcZoClrqD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you live in London? Have you or any of your pals made a big effort to reduce your carbon footprint (only walking/ cycling everywhere perhaps)? I would like to talk to you! Also anyone else London based being super extra green!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StuartBluman I think theyve put the wrong byline on this - wasnt mine Im afraid!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BMGsyncUK: Sweet @KarenO and @DangerMouseJuke interview by @lisaannewright in @diymagazine #LuxPrima https://t.co/agGs9pRWvH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YnnsPhilippakis: Big ol chat in this months @diymagazine   https://t.co/zMygPgQ3D8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got down deep with the Best Band In Britain (don't even try and fucking argue with me) @foals for this month's @diymagazine cover. NOW THAT'S WHAT I CALL MUSIC. https://t.co/LRoAC5dgrh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: The March issue of DIY, ft @foals, @Japanesehouse, @fontainesdublin, @KarenO  @DangerMouseJuke and loads more is OUT NOW!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@willjrichards thanks bbz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ @foals on the new cover alert - out fri. Get it in yer. https://t.co/G1UQoRDQtF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is fucking fantastic. Lizzo is the queen. https://t.co/bgimChMoil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @diymagazine: Read the DIY cover feature with @sundarakarma online in full. https://t.co/IfeXC39FJP   @lisaannewright  @Hannahdiamond]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019: AND WE'RE OFF! https://t.co/VENKVTYmDS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @willjrichards: Me, @lisaannewright and @rachelmichaella wrote about a bunch of the most exciting new records we're expecting this year.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>