<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[3 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IamMzilikazi @AfricaStoryLive True. But the reality: Selfish, money loving politicians. Selfish, money loving Celebs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IamMzilikazi: Africa needs back its economy, its politics, its culture, its languages and all its patriotic writers. ~ Ngugi wa Thion]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bindyb123 Too many are blinded! As written, in the BIBLE! Sadly!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bindyb123: #BlueLivesPrayers God Bless and Heal America Heartbreak #EnoughIsEnough https://t.co/VpdTE5iNw9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Steve_Sailer @LABeachGal1 DISGUSTING!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's just DISGUSTING! https://t.co/Li2TJoK7OZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise @LABeachGal1 By purpose!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteveScalise: What I saw at the border was even worse than I thought.  Make no mistake: This is a major crisis.  WATCH  https://t.co/R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise @LABeachGal1 What Covid?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteveScalise: You can't operate your restaurant at 100% capacity.  But at the border, Biden is allowing his Donna migrant detention fac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AfricaStoryLive: In Botswana, two people have allegedly died from taking AstraZeneca COVID-19 vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GOP: Joe Biden  Kamala Harris are refusing to listen to the science on reopening schools,  its impacting working parents, ESPECIALLY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LifeNewsHQ: BREAKING: Arkansas Governor Asa Hutchinson signed a bill today to protect doctors, nurses and other medical professional fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LikeTheMountain Nope.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LikeTheMountain: Were you ever actually worried about getting the Covid?  Be honest ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrDamienBlack: Who else isnt getting a vaccine  ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMiniAOC: The only thing the CIA is missing is the H and the N.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: There once was a man who would walk out and give press conferences multiple times a week. Never forgot a name or needed n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: The crisis at the border is so bad that Biden is denying the press access.   Why is @AOCwho once staged a photoshoot to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @codeofvets: Check on your battle buddies. The weekends are hard.  Veterans. How are you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realneil3 @cynthiamckinney They never knew ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GhanaNet: @cynthiamckinney It's called East Germany 3.0 "Nobody has the intention to erect a WALL" East German Communist leader Walter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cynthiamckinney It's called East Germany 3.0 "Nobody has the intention to erect a WALL" East German Communist leader Walter Ulbricht - Jun 1961. / "Leave Britain"ILLEGALLY" and you pay a 5000 pounds fine!" Globalist puppet COMMUNIST leader @BorisJohnson March 2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cynthiamckinney: URGENT, URGENT: After four hours of debate yesterday in the House of Commons, the United Kingdom has approved an emerg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dats_right_ie: @Allycon3 Stopped watching  listening to every RTE platform months ago, even deleted the news app from my phone too. I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: We have a President who actually just fell "up" the stairs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DuckDuckGo: After months of stalling, Google finally revealed how much personal data they collect in Chrome and the Google app. No wond]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Make no mistake, the CCP just humiliated the US government in public on US soil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @codeofvets: No one can put a price tag on our freedoms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mliz77: Putin basically called Joe Biden an incompetent pussy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Joy_Villa: The US is now being challenged by North Korea, Russia and China. Where is that global respect the left was talking about?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @QrisMidnytrdr: Is it just me or is literally EVERYTHING racism?!? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @altadonna_trina: What does Biden gain by letting everyone illegally into the country through the southern border?I dont think its pop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cynthiamckinney: https://t.co/obiJyZk6hE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RightWingJewess: The democrats pulled off the biggest scam in history when they stole the election and got away with it. Now that they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StandUpX2 Cardiff 1pm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StandUpX2 Enough said...! https://t.co/iym4m5P2TQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StandUpX2: WORLD WIDE RALLIES EDINBURGH LOCATION ANNOUNCEMENT LETS DO THIS PLEASE SHARE. LONDON LOCATION WILL BE ANNOUNCED TOMORROW MOR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone in the UK! Get this POS out of office!  Matt Hancock: Matt Hancock Resign Immediately - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/ookg242y2C via @UKChange]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Everyone in the UK! Sign and SHARE, if you had enough of this Lockdown and LIE BS!!!!!  Boris Johnson: Covid Vaccine related Deaths within 28 days of receiving Vaccine - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/rryU9MHY1p via @UKChange]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSitcPa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cynthiamckinney: Stunningly Frank Observations on How Deep Is the Medical Swamp  https://t.co/bbD02Mhicg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thebradfordfile: The FBI framed a man for treason, got caught, and the only guy to be charged got probation.   You can't make this shit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/sT0DSibBXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden must be place into the BOUNDARIES of the CONSTITUTION! https://t.co/Ug4z6YtEgd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GhanaNet: Good Morning lovely PATRIOTS  https://t.co/cMDIIQ8zbk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @politstrip: GOODBYE @GOPChairwoman  GOODBYE @GOP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chuckwoolery: After All He Did for the Republican Party and Her, Chair Ronna McDaniel Wont Back a Trump Presidential Run in 2024 at Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: The Biden administration is a complete and utter disaster.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @codeofvets: Tomorrow I will be driving up to Nashville Funeral and Cremation at noon where Code of Vets will be presented a donation. I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@David11468542 @PresskayIeigh_ Fake!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jamaicaire @PresskayIeigh_ Not parody. FAKE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@magdishalash @PresskayIeigh_ Because you fall for fake accounts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Just4TheCause @PresskayIeigh_ @reaIPatriot Nope!  @kayleighmcenany is not suspended. !!!!  a FAKE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patricia_rattew @PresskayIeigh_ @paulk652517 Smart. Following a fake account.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Warheadrocket @PresskayIeigh_ @reaIPatriot Sure. You follow now a fake account! Really smart...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alisonouthwaite: @PresskayIeigh_ @reaIPatriot The real kayleigh is still her @kayleighmcenany https://t.co/OTYlGqJRTE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chaga500K @PresskayIeigh_ People are LAZY! (Don't want to use other words!)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BellaDJ4justice @PresskayIeigh_ @RealCathyOBrien Here is the REAL account! .   @kayleighmcenany is not suspended. !!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeeW0W @PresskayIeigh_ Simple! By checking FACTS! And Nope!  @kayleighmcenany is not suspended. !!!! It's a FAKE!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PresskayIeigh_ Nope!  @kayleighmcenany is not suspended. !!!! You are a just a FAKE! Disgusting!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nope!  @kayleighmcenany is not suspended. !!!! You are a FAKE! https://t.co/xChzhvHDoO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeWillBeFree82: This amazing epidemiologist has been smeared and sent death threats for simply voicing her scientific opinion. She has]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheEndisFar @ChuckCallesto TRUMP also said, vaccine is your choice, and he isn't having it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good Morning lovely PATRIOTS  https://t.co/aziUU7nkE7 https://t.co/cMDIIQ8zbk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ALMahmoodAM: @ChuckCallesto For the meantime  For sometime   Could be this what Trump and Kevin Mc Carthy had agreed on in the yesterda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Create a new party! NOW!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: REPORT: The RNC will not back former President Trump if he chooses to run for office again in 2024 and will instead rema]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Matthew_4_Trump: Millions can't even see that most of this has nothing to do with a virus.  That's a big problem.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ReaganWorld: Remember when Obama created all of those wonderful green jobs and then they all went bankrupt well Biden is going to try i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut Because that hardly works!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: The people are waking up that the system is rigged]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ErrolWebber: Gavin Newsom isn't the dumbest Governor in the US, however...  ...No, he is the dumbest.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Irish_DaisyGirl @BrianKirkland5 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LifeNewsHQ: BREAKING: South Carolina Senate Passes Bill Banning Abortions When Unborn Babys Heartbeat Begins   https://t.co/2Yf6hb5VEa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shammygrl1 @BrianKirkland5 I drink water ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: America..... are you waking up?  Our government is being run by a very old Muppet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whoever doesn't know: That "capturing" is a SHAM! Why: CO2 is needed for Soda, packaged meat, Food container vessels, and much more. The TRICK: Let all of us pay DOUBLE, TRIPLE for that "New Green Deal". Most people don't see trough that SMOKE SCREEN!  Bill Gates is also on it! https://t.co/PCyvrH9RMJ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>