<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[I have officially lost the last pound of my quarantine twenty. Now I just need to lose my pre-quarantine twenty.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is a bad headline. https://t.co/DGYm35Ebsd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melissadominic Atypical 80s: Midnight Summer Dream - The Stranglers Gentlemen Take Polaroids - Japan Getting Up - Pigbag  Electronic Parents: Girls - Walter Meego Joe Le Taxi - Hanayo Meine Welt - Siriusmo https://t.co/0DwLYoOXGl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melissadominic Bulbform!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 Ok, I take it back. Thats a dope ride.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 Everyday I try to better understand the world around me, but I dont think Ill ever understand Volvo Twitter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sometimes dinner is three slices of crispy bacon and a cup of coffee. And thats ok.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BGGRobert @gmtgames Ive never played the original, but I grabbed this because the playtime is shorter and the consensus seems to be that its better for 2 players. Also, I really like the ocean theme and art.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 You win this round...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smoke em if you got em. https://t.co/FcqyzFjdjQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big boy (and girl) game day with Dominant Species: Marine from @gmtgames. #boardgame #boardgames #tabletopgames #bgg #boardgamegeek #j2s #brettspiel #juegodemesa https://t.co/c5WTDM1aIp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What I Do For Love, Chapter 14: Painting Tiny Skulls. https://t.co/DQnfsYyfVm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 Oh, I should have mentioned, it doesnt really have anything to do with the ginkgo biloba tree. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 It's excellent. Plays quickly, not too many rules to remember, and some really interesting decisions to make. Importantly for us, it's good for two players and solo play. Here's an overview, if you're interested (game is explained in the first 15 mins.) https://t.co/CXs7ahWPpp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My sidekicks new game ritual. https://t.co/9BHbUSzEhS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont you just hate it when you have 300 board games and nothing you want to play?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Cover yourself in aluminum foil.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 I mean, I love naps but I also love eating. This has been a very confusing time for me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make that 72 hours.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The side effects from my second dose were 48 hours of fatigue and loss of appetite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Split Enz is a perfect soundtrack for a sunny Saturday afternoon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Nature is healing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RaquelStecher https://t.co/n32C4FwOQy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im not even sick today. What a rip-off.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, its come to this. I got Pfizer and she got Modena. We were up all night talking through it and we decided to try and make it work. True love conquers all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just picked up some more 3-D goodness from @KinoLorber. https://t.co/ZnrBpt4QRH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hootsuite has decided to jack up the cost of my account tenfold, so I'm experimenting with other methods of tweet scheduling. https://t.co/xdb2dEOIbn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmilyDensten I have that board game. https://t.co/Q7agZpv6F1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Last week I made tamales with ground pork rinds instead of corn meal. They smelled funky but tasted good.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Low carb life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Which hobby should I take up next, pickleball or disc golf?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7bj0X7t3Rt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now watching Steve Earle and Emmylou Harris live from Nashville. https://t.co/akZ80ID26V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[milk milk lemonade round the corner fudge is made childhood drollery  #haiku]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He figured out how to get it off within a day. Luckily, hes cool about letting me put it back on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just backed Long Shot: The Dice Game  on Kickstarter. https://t.co/j4Ug3RGcgT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think Ill be an early adopter of this. https://t.co/idO0A8k68i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carolineavenue I woke up at 2 am with this song stuck in my head. So... youre welcome?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wish I loved anything as much as my cats love puking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift I don't have the heart.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Hes not loving it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cone Cat. https://t.co/6yCpnNYdtu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HollywoodComet @thebasementtan #wetboysummer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe after this Ill try to break him of his need to be outside. Again. Wish me luck. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would love to keep him inside all the time, but we took him in as a stray and he gets disruptive if he cant go out a few times a day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grady had to go to the vet this morning with a head wound. Cat fight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookishbelle The one that got away.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carolineavenue Best I could do. https://t.co/12AwImxIJ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just backed Fjords on Kickstarter. https://t.co/BSetJ8In9h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@railoftomorrow Its a pun.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmilyDensten Also Grady creeping in the background.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmilyDensten Stripey. https://t.co/T44ptNK3Yn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This might be the happiest day of my life. https://t.co/XJDIK9srXu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tried my hand at making sushi for the first time tonight. Not disappointed. (Subbed riced cauliflower for sushi rice. Muy bien.) https://t.co/xp4wDVtGtP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The FU store called... https://t.co/CDKHuWtI1D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookishbelle *Divine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookishbelle American Movie The Kid Stays in the Picture I Am Devine The Cockettes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beforeyouplay_ @SenFoongLim @bamboozlebros Brain-burny fun.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im starting to think that middle-aged men who open trendy sex clubs are not primarily interested in creating a safe space for artistic expression.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebasementtan To be fair, I had extra time to workshop it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebasementtan We would have also accepted Chai Gang.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mharvey816 @MinskysPizza Same.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just found out I'm eligible for the vaccine as of yesterday. Now if I could only find an appointment somewhere...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They want me to start drinking oat milk now? I just got onto almond milk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ah, simpler times...   #boardgames #bgg https://t.co/tX9wP3CSkz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Youve got hail (if you live in Sacramento). https://t.co/fUh7seKPLu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Golden Tortoise Beetles (not my hand). https://t.co/XULoj1lqkM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellalovesbg I ordered it when I saw your first tweet about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Unfortunately, its a very hard habit to break.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I did sock shoe, sock shoe this morning and have been feeling uneasy all day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 @OldSchoolLab Cool.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just want to quietly drink a cup of coffee in a big room full of strangers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quarantine impulse purchase #237: Electric milk frother. https://t.co/zjDF8qz9yL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just another game Im not allowed to play. #MiniExpress #bgg @moaideas https://t.co/lLTbCQ8iBN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looks like I wont be getting the vaccine for a while. https://t.co/QzwdJKfX1n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Sweet drop-leaf table in the corner.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The main thing Ive learned from this whole COVID situation is just how often I have funky coffee breath.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im live streaming from my home right now! https://t.co/cRjy9WQyXA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimmiechem2 *The story, all names, characters, and incidents portrayed in this tweet are fictitious. No identification with actual persons (living or deceased), places, buildings, and products is intended or should be inferred.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Midday cheese biscuits ready for the oven. https://t.co/aaorBrKjNr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My least favorite kind of tweet is a photo of a page of a book.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Birdwatching. #wingspan #boardgames #bgg https://t.co/DXTCcxbypf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just joined old guy twitter. Gooble-gobble.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting to think that blood thinners were invented to keep the band-aid industry afloat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Doesn't everyone? https://t.co/CnTfar8LJi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@J__Swift Its just on my shelf to impress visitors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hmm, which cat should I read today? https://t.co/tBFyGrqp5r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tamales are in the steamer. Im beat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you download it and need help with the rules, or want to play against a human, let me know. (I am a human)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The card game Lost Cities is free on the iOS App Store today. It's a great two-player game and I highly recommend it. https://t.co/FtxIoh8oxc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NotDBordwell Turns out winning that game is easier than negotiating the grocery store safely. Who would have guessed?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beforeyouplay_ @stonemaiergames @jameystegmaier @UrielChael @Pierce_Brown Excellent video. You two are!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The toenails, on the other hand, never grow at all." https://t.co/zjH5hzSt2W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hot tip: When there's "nothing to do" at home, you can always reorganize your board game shelves. https://t.co/QIOTXVs4x3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I call tonights pizza A Thousand Burning Suns. https://t.co/hrQ39oB6k8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thebasementtan I mean, I have a lot of romantic deep cuts. No movie recommendations, though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our baby magnolia tree is blooming. In February!  https://t.co/HHHmI68Ihg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just backed Bandada: A Quick Playing Game for 1-2 Players. https://t.co/7wh2BUkdRP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I found textured paper tamale wrappers to substitute for the corn husks. My kitchen will once again be a no-sneeze zone. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beforeyouplay_ My Favorite Shapes by Julio Torres (HBO Max). https://t.co/oDIAzDvMFD]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>