<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Link to study re: Furey article  https://t.co/QzZomqHfnc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: A new study out from a Simon Fraser University professor breaks down both the ineffectiveness and the harms of lockdowns]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Holding Canadians hostage is it? https://t.co/u3bEr4Pym7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep this guide handy, you never know when you might need it https://t.co/kigrcCID3o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rubiconcapital_ @fordnation #FireTheOntarioScienceTable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rubiconcapital_: I will post this chart regularly. To show that unscientific lockdowns, for all their extraordinary harm, *do nothing*,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you look? Well? Did you? If you didn't, then the shame is all yours  Read this thread. https://t.co/l17PEE8W2c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These don't look like the words of a group that's engaging in science, but rather, they look like the words of a group that is a lobby that is engaging in politics. https://t.co/byXTTsG7fq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hello Police? I'd like to report a chart crime https://t.co/F3N9cpu8xW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ColinDMello If those were measures specifically recommended by the Science Table, then that isn't a science table, it's a politics table.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The funny thing about Friday's announcements are that those who advocated for lockdowns crowd can't understand how they directly contributed to this.  Don't worry, we won't let you forget that it's your fault.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LDBildy @erdocAA Good for all if those same lawyers remember that to scrutinize all decisions, not just this one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrP_MD: We need to start reporting the vaccination status of people with Covid in ICU https://t.co/0xkgBa8Dos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've been asking you and your colleagues that question for months https://t.co/5zWrl1PPEV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntiLockdownONT: How to treat @fordnation next lockdown announcement:  Don't listen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hard to see how lockdowners don't live to regret these days.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See pinned tweet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isn't mask compliance close to 100%?  But don't worry, we know media won't challenge @SylviaJonesMPP  on this claim https://t.co/4BlC5Qr1g6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adx599 @anthonyfurey Show us the exact science that shows irrefutable evidence that this occurs in a meaningful way, and we'll believe you. No assumptions, no anecdotes. Actual data and science that somebody has put together based on suitable sample size in real life occurrence.  We'll wait]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: Gyms should have never have been shut down in Ontario. A silly move. https://t.co/apWj83aHZo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Comment not necessary https://t.co/RbiaAS0Irc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Thank You to thousands who tuned into @OnCall4ON COD Covid-19 Summit!  Thank you to Profs @MartinKulldorff, @SunetraGupta  B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MikkoPackalen: Ontario's school closure again lacks any assessment of the harm this will cause to children's health and life expectancy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It didn't take very long for fact-checking to turn into a weapon for propaganda and control, did it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CHogarthPC yawn  "We are lifting all covid restrictions" would be excellent news.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most fascinating part about just how bad "economics" of the zero covid pledge is the evidence presented is entirely anecdotal and not a single person did any real work on it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tune in, it'll be good for your frame of mind and thinking https://t.co/cizGdKFOMv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmberHaveyou That's what we were referring to. Our guess is the people that made those plans worked for months on end crafting it using decades of data. Maybe it was longer?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: OPEN THE PATIOS DOUG!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Things people react negatively to:  1. Feeling of being lied to or misled 2. Feeling of being coerced into doing something  The first has been happening for a year, the second is happening right now.  Why are health experts and government confused over the lack of vaccine demand?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CHogarthPC Please advise what "freedoms" you are talking about that we have today, April 9, 2021?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rpoconnor: No one should ever tell you that your livelihood isn't essential. It is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cTQbh9JzrE https://t.co/39Qz9iuABr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No Shirt, No Shoes, No Service? https://t.co/GMrK45aRJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Milhouse_Van_Ho: Ontarians nearing a breaking point under lockdown:  "...the number of Ontarians hovering close to financial insolvency]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Milhouse_Van_Ho: Ontario should move alongside Michigan. https://t.co/6LGyLIWUcc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Title misleading, it was humans deciding on lockdowns that did this, not the virus, which could have been dealt with another way. But informative nonetheless https://t.co/W1yHzbNlbv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eugenefds3: @AntiLockdownONT Just did a podcast with David Redman about this!   https://t.co/EssRkozqSv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine having a comprehensive emergency plan that was worked on for months, but then changing your mind last minute and deciding to enact lockdowns instead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation @celliottability @SylviaJonesMPP Good news! We're already ignoring you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you are cheering on heavier lockdowns and restrictions again today, expect nothing from anyone when we come out. The world will leave you and your ilk behind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @strauss_matt: I will be on @sauga960AM in 25 minutes if anyone wants to hang out. https://t.co/Vx6FWMOivE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Asys1991 Agreed, but it's a start.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many signatures here, add yours  https://t.co/FdIVRYCfVO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario instituting measures that didn't work in Manitoba is priceless]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A short story about just one the costs of lockdowns:  https://t.co/0j5poyXJVq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we close the Toronto Star too? https://t.co/AwnnQFHFyT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Play stupid lockdown games, win stupid lockdown prizes https://t.co/5V6dyVxMKS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Must be just a coincidence https://t.co/iMraUICIR5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone else noticing that focused protection is now being suggested by the same people who chastised it 7-8 months ago?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine being so bad at your job that you're still searching for "how to get it right" over a year into this thing. https://t.co/5er0n0aEuT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@freedom_fanny @digitaltincan @Milhouse_Van_Ho Some have. We wish it were more prevalent. But it's not non-existent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katewand: LIVE NOW: Tragedy  Crisis in Ontario https://t.co/IWjbXzleDM   #COVID19Ontario #onpoli #ontariolockdown https://t.co/X96mad3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The big picture people are missing part 4  Also, keep an eye on what's contained in this month's federal budget announcement https://t.co/eqoT9d4b4d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The big picture that people are missing part 3 https://t.co/caUx5X4yPv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The big picture people are missing part 2 https://t.co/L70PSE3MIJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The big picture that too many people are missing https://t.co/9LkNSpZ59O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make no mistake, Canada's economy is in absolute ruin and Ontario is leading the way. This reality is being hidden under the guise of "government supports".]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MikkoPackalen: 1/ Our coronavirus response is beset by populism and fundamentalism. There is a fervent belief in our means to control t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SomeGuy_Tor78 You're never allowed to look at the bigger picture because it's disinformation if you do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomato_tim Amazing, isn't it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't quite put a finger on it https://t.co/GzyBT8PV5Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sounds like a tsunami of death is coming. Where have we heard that before? https://t.co/cpQB1ePQYr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fair question https://t.co/12vTIkAv1t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fact check: True!  Industrial revolutions created the economic prosperity necessary to give rise to good health and health care systems https://t.co/ngIu45Sil6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fact check: False https://t.co/I0qCSlRsRt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation Fact check: False]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Great Barrington suggested to focus protection on these groups, and LTC/elderly, what was your response then? https://t.co/Dof0omXXW7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you want to return to normal? do you want your career or your business to flourish and prosper? Travel again without hassle?  Sign this petition, and you have a chance at that. https://t.co/pGCaRraDvD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@velopajaro @fordnation "Friends" became even more cringeworthy, but still voted accordingly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New pinned tweet for all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fitness in particular, the most impacted industry by business capacity loss in the entire group, hosed again. https://t.co/VLvu1vEtyJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine saying that lockdowns suck when lockdowns are risk free to you.  The entitlement of the pro-lockdowners just rages on https://t.co/eyy6Hm9DuL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur Dude, stop, you love lockdowns. You love them because you refuse to consider or suggest a single other alternative, they're your favourite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada is, quite officially, an Authoritarian Communist country https://t.co/hB9rx0Yome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our favourite thing: asking real questions of real data.  Have not seen the Ontario "biostatisticians" or social media MDs do a single shred of this kind of analysis in their work. https://t.co/Mm2X23lgcb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ColinDMello Got any incontrovertible proof that last sentence is true?  We haven't seen any]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobAdam74497148 good point, tweet needs to be re-written]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoMoreLockdowns #No3rdLockdown We do not consent to you locking us down  @fordnation @CHogarthPC   #IStandWithRoman https://t.co/QSRkSz3Ygj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CityNews LOL. There's going to be nothing left of Ontario once this guy's done with it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to treat @fordnation next lockdown announcement:  Don't listen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey, you, fear mongering lockdown crowd: How many times will public health mislead, or outright lie to you, before you wake up? https://t.co/vIhYbsUzbo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bk1022 Indeed, just speaking the same silly language that ridiculous crowd uses so they understand the message]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/4p8LD8cpLr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's a big difference in language. Too big  Wild that anyone would still listen at that point https://t.co/i58uqORMIk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Furthermore, do you think the people owe you to be jabbed after destroying their businesses and bank accounts? Given what is said in the first tweet?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Milhouse_Van_Ho: Rushed approvals for covid vaccines for children isn't a way to protect kids.  Kids aren't super spreaders and aren't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did any of you lockdown loving maniacs think to yourself that maybe the reason vaccine demand has fallen off a cliff in Ontario is because nobody trusts a anything you have to say, don't trust vaccine data, or you are not openly guaranteeing a return to normal once vaccinated?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let this resonate with the all: Take matters into your own hands and stop looking for government to do it for you, because they're not only going to screw it up, but also control your life all the same without letting go. https://t.co/N61JlrfcF8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Barking_Digits: @AntiLockdownONT @Milhouse_Van_Ho Texas, Florida, Sweden are proof the lockdowns are unecessary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ontario Pseudoscience Table, the local and provincial Medical Officers of Health, and the local and provincial governments have had 13 months to come up with an alternative to lockdowns. Time for smarter people to do the job.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur Why would you want to wish for them to believe in shoddy work and being wrong by several orders of magnitude?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nursecaro13: @IrfanDhalla https://t.co/IOZBKjpGVK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If he ever actually does (we suspect he won't), @bruce_arthur will be the last human in Canada to concede that lockdowns had very little impact and destroyed everything https://t.co/dntEfhizTX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur Sorry to hear you need government to protect your health and can't do it yourself. Sad really]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exhibit A: Bruce would prefer we ignore absolutely everything else and only focus on lockdowns and COVID. https://t.co/uhiOyyusz1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Anti-science government"  My word, @bruce_arthur is the least intelligent human in all of Canadian media. https://t.co/yEmQ1rOTLG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also, someone doesn't know that most of Ontario is still very much locked down. Should ask him what day of the week it is just to make sure he's alert today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When there's nothing left of small business and the middle class but a pile of rubble, the spin will be to blame anything but lockdowns, even though lockdowns are the ONLY reason.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See hospital administration below looking to lock you down on yet another consecutive day because he thinks they work, doesn't care about you, and wants to take the easiest, stress-free path to making &gt;$300k of your tax dollars. https://t.co/KjskBCHrGi]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>