<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Primark: Tonight is a night for new Primark pyjamas, fluffy socks  manifesting a good four-day week  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away this adorable Paul  Joe cat-themed sparkling eyeshadow and lipstick on Twitter. To enter, follow @davelack]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away this YSL Collector Face Highlighter Duo Stuck that illuminates and highlights your complexion. Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Waited a whole year to finally get a week off work  just my luck #weather https://t.co/wrjGokwUHJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love Dior? I'm giving away Dior Addict Stellar Halo Shine in shades "hope star" and "happy star" on Twitter. To enter, RT ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One more week then @Primark I am coming for you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away this beautiful Rare Beauty by Selena Gomez Eye Palette on Twitter. It's shade "Confident Energy" with rich]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loves #SaturdayNightTakeaway tonight! Childhood memories #chums @antanddec you are legends ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FragranceDirect: FOLLOW, LIKE  RT TO WIN!   Today we're giving away a fantastic bundle of Skin Generics products worth over 60 featu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away Givenchy's gorgeous Prisme Powder Blush Duo in shade "02 Love". Givenchy makes some of the best powders on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She is just so elegant and flawless  https://t.co/L2pbAiquoz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Thrilled to be giving away Dior Lip Glow in shade 'rosewood' + Rouge Dior in Nude Look Matte on Twitter. To enter, RT  fol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: My next luxe beauty Twitter giveaway is one of my all-time favourites: YSL Touche Eclat in shade 02. It's a collector editi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@antanddec I leave with a 6 year old who instead on doing the end of the show show ever single night ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away this Guerlain collector Rouge G duo on Twitter. It's a luxe matte lipstick in shade No. 40 + a co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's prestige makeup Twitter giveaway is Clarins' SOS Primer in shade 'amber pearls'. It highlights your complexion with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away Dior Addict Stellar Halo Shine Lipstick in shade "treasure star". It promises shimmering colour,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away Dior's Backstage Buffing Brush that helps create a professional airbrushed finish. To enter, follow @davela]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty giveaway is Dior Backstage Buffing Brush - ideal for working with Dior Air Flash foundation. To enter,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FragranceDirect: FOLLOW, LIKE  RT TO WIN!  VIKTORROLF FLOWERBOMB DEW GIVEAWAY   Embrace a new floral lightness with Flowerbomb De]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have to say I dont think I appreciate how brilliant sex and the city was! Just rewatch all 6 seasons and I love it more the first time  need to go shoe shopping now ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away YSL Vinyl Cream Lip Stain in shade beige progressif - a great neutral hue. To enter, follow @davelackie  R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away this Diorshow Colour  Contour Eyeshadow and Liner Duo in brown/peach. To enter, follow @davelack]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just what one day where I am not stressed or worried! Just one day pleaseeee ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[COVID vaccine one done! Scared for side effects now https://t.co/Eap2V0tt9J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty giveaway is one of the best mascara's on the planet: Lancome Hypnose Volume Mascara in Noir Hypnotic. T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newlook ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newlook: COMPETITION: Your Monday just got better  WIN this dress on us by, following us (we check!), RT this post and reply with a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itvnews So are you telling if you got an sos call from your parents you would go!!!!!! I dont think it matters who you are you would go!! Give her a break!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe makeup giveaway is a multitasker. It's Nudestix Intense Matte lip + Cheek Pencil  Gel Colour Lip + Cheek Balm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's prestige skincare Twitter giveaway is Kiehl's Midnight Recovery Concentrate, a replenishing elixir of pure essentia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away this pair of purple-hued OPI nail lacquers on Twitter. Shades "Galleria Vittoria Violet" and "OPI Nails the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really want to hibernate until this weather goes away  I hate travelling in this weather! Life as a keyworker just gets harder ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's skincare Twitter giveaway is philosophy's ultimate miracle worker facial serum roller to help uplift and firm skin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love the scent of orange flower  mandarin? I'm giving away Dolce  Gabbana's Orange fragrance with notes of Sicilian orang]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe fragrance Twitter giveaway is Dolce  Gabbana's uplifting Orange fragrance. It blends notes of Sicilian orange]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @riverisland: The most underrated style inspiration  https://t.co/i2RWzK52o0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Good morning. Today's luxe beauty giveaway is Guerlain Meteorites CC Glow Colour Correcting Highlighter in "apricot". To en]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally catching up on all the Christmas telly I recorded! That my Sunday sorted ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe skincare giveaway is Korres' Foaming Cream Cleanser with Probiotics. To enter, RT  follow @davelackie https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I miss normal life ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away Dior Addict Stellar Halo Shine that delivers shimmering colour with incredible hydrating care. It really ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel massive letdown by the Government ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty giveaway is Dior Addict Stellar Halo Shine in shade Passion Star. It gives a wash of great colour with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe fragrance giveaway is very clever. It's L'Eau d'Issey, a light aquatic floral for her. The cap pops off and it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fortnums: Perfectly poached eggs, on fresh-toasted crumpets topped with lashings of butter and #Marmite...   Because some mornings, a s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its definitely Martine McCutcheon https://t.co/vHh6HqQ43V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away Nudestix Magnetic Nude Glimmer in 24K Goddess + Magnetic Nude Lip Plush Paint in St Tropez. To enter, RT ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe makeup giveaway is Givenchy's Gloss Interdit Vinyl Lip Gloss in Solar Orange. To enter, follow @davelackie  R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Clarins recently reworked its eyeshadow palettes and I really like this "Jade Gradation" shade. I'm giving it away on Twitt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@10DowningStreet Please close nurseries or at least explain the rationale behind them staying open! Its a very scary time for everyone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away Dior Addict Stellar Gloss in shade "zodiaddict" - it nourishes, protects and creates a plumping shine effec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Start the New Year off with an amazing balm lip gloss that promises plumping shine. I'm giving away Dior Addict Stellar Glo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zzFa5VcFFA and it only 1st Jan! Year started off splendidly! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty giveaway is this exquisite scented candle by perfumer Francis Kurkdjian. It gently scents the room with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love YSL? I'm giving away the beautiful YSL Mon Paris Parfum Floral fragrance for her with notes of citrus, white rose, jas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe fragrance Twitter giveaway is YSL Mon Paris Parfum Floral, a fruity-floral scent for her with notes of peach,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away Giorgio Armani's Si Passione Intense eau de parfum on Twitter. It's a rich floriental fragrance f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My favourite Christmas gift - from my nieces and nephew  https://t.co/NGvzuei8zY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love Lancome? I'm giving away the amazing Le Chromatique for lips, eyes and cheeks - in shades "mademoiselle" and "s'il vou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love YSL? I'm giving away this pair of Dessin Des Levres - The Lip Styler in shades "L'Or" and "Fuchsia Rouge". To enter, R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would give anything to be sitting right there with a good book!! https://t.co/5y9GG231o6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away YSL's fab The Lip Styler in shades L'Or  Fuchsia Rouge. It's a lip base, a contour  styler. To enter, fol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away this cute too faced Cinnamon Bear Makeup Kit on Twitter. It features 8 eyeshadows, pink blush, liquid lipst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KSI: Ive been trying so hard to stay strong this whole year, but if Im being honest, its really starting to take a toll now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away MAC Strobe Cream in shade "silverlite" on Twitter. To enter, RT  follow @davelackie https://t.co/38EcEMCFTP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BorisJohnson_MP you expect me to look after other people childrens as a nursery manager but I cant even see my own mother on Christmas days! I cant tell how devastated I am! I havent seen my own mum in a year and you do this 6 day before Christmas! Honestly I have no words.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's fragrance giveaway is the brand NEW Versace pour femme Dylan Turquoise 10 ml purse spray. It's a fresh floral-woody]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away the NEW Versace Dylan Turquoise (at Hudson's Bay) - a light floral-woody-musk scent for her with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hate my life ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away this Clarins Gold Mascara Top Coat on Twitter. To enter, follow @davelackie and @NinaWestbury  R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away this incredible Dior Double Rouge matte lipstick in shade "Candy Cane". To enter, follow @davelackie  RT h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Surprise "Thank You, Followers" Twitter Giveaway: Lancome La Vie Est Belle Intensment. It's a beautiful floriental scent f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love Dior? I'm giving away this amazing collector Double Rouge matte lipstick in shade "Candy Cane" - beautiful pink hues!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching military wives, such a brilliant movie ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Excited to be giving away these collector YSL The Slim matte lipsticks. I'm giving away shades 21 Rouge Paradoxe  8 Contra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's skincare giveaway is Clinique Fresh Pressed Daily Booster Pure vitamin C 10% It helps boost radiance  even skin to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty giveaway is Christian Louboutin Khol Les Yeux Noirs Lash Amplifying Lacquer. It promises definition, cu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love Dior? I'm giving away Dior Addict Stellar Gloss in shades 643 EverDior  092 Stellar. These balm lip glosses promise p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love MAC? I'm giving away this beautiful LipGlass in "Heart Heist" + clear LipGlass Lip Gloss! To enter, RT  follow @davel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There goes my early night for the next 3 week #ImACeleb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol Donald tramps hairdresser lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love the Tesco advent lol #nonaughtylist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So freaking happy #imacelebrity ! So need this ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FragranceDirect: LIKE  RETWEET TO WIN!  Gift him the thrilling freshness and intense woody vibration of Match Point, the new aftersha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away shu uemura x One Piece Rouge Unlimited Lipstick in Red Gatling  Nudy Romeo on Twitter. To enter, follow @d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: I'm giving away YSL's NEW luxe mascara called "Mascara Volume Effet Faux Cils Radical" that promises bold volume and deep b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love Marc Jacobs? I'm giving away the NEW Perfect eau de parfum for her with notes of daffodil, almond milk, rhubarb  ceda]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are people the way they are? Sometimes I dont understand peoples minds ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newlook: Sunday morning routine:  - Coffee - Skincare - Coffee - Check horoscope - Instagram Scroll - TikTok Scroll - Shop for Christma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Love MAC? I'm giving away MAC Powder Kiss Lipstick in "Mull It Over"  the Brow Set Gel! Great products! To enter, RT  fol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty giveaway is this pair of Clarins Velvet Lip Perfector - a creamy, ultra-light texture with velvety text]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: This just may be the perfect winter lip colour. I'm giving away Givenchy Le Rouge Deep Velvet in shade 26 framboise velours]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@op_pjj Hey, no this is the first time I have ordered! I think the delivery takes 6 weeks! I will let you know ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davelackie: Today's luxe beauty Twitter giveaway is YSL Dessin Des Levres Lip Styler in shades L'Or  L'Argent. To enter, RT  follow @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive just discovered #saramartapp I am obsessed! Made two ordered already, so hope they come!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Christmas shopping Christmas shopping Christmas shopping  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialPLT: Christmas in New York would be a DREAM  https://t.co/zotcUZtxfj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loved the new @NetflixUK movie #Holidate ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Payday tomorrow, @primark here I come ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>