<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: @elonmusk The right is now a larger tent. The truth is the left has moved far left and the right has moved toward the ce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @elonmusk: The left is losing the middle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SMART https://t.co/LaaHoMB8jW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dawn_Kopecki @jasminejhkim @NYGovCuomo @higginsdunn This isnt normal. Completely at odds why NYC dwellers are out of their minds. Why? What changes when you live in a rat infested shit hole that makes you go full 1984?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dawn_Kopecki @jasminejhkim @NYGovCuomo @higginsdunn You are a threat. This is insanity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dawn_Kopecki @jasminejhkim @higginsdunn #GlassHouses https://t.co/FbcZ3N1v0B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasminejhkim Where did Bill Gates go to medical school?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasminejhkim Will you report on Cuomos decision to intern COVID patients with nursing home patients?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasminejhkim Anthony Fauci has actively politicized a virus and scuttled the world economy over shutdowns that havent slowed the spread. Hes not a victim. Stop making him out to be over people getting pissed about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Timcast: Why does Twitter, Facebook, and Youtube have a medical advice policy?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LaraLeaTrump: Must have missed all of the medical degrees held by the fact checkers in Silicon Valley.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fbnewsroom @andymstone @nick_clegg @business Why is the left so outraged over speech? Hate speech is purely a cover for speech we dont like.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andymstone Facebook is a massive Orwellian propaganda and censorship machine.   Reevaluate your motivations.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WhiteCoatSummit #COVID19 https://t.co/U4QrQ5iTIH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: This press conference of doctors had 14 million views on Facebook today. FB took it down shortly after a NYTimes reporte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robbystarbuck: Fighting censorship is critical to the survival of freedom in America. Either we have a country where bad ideas are beat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lalalandlover51 @Amy_Siskind @Jocelyn39791771 You are Squealer from Animal Farm. Read it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lalalandlover51 @Amy_Siskind @Jocelyn39791771 Why are they attacking the federal building?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FauciFraud There is a CURE for #COVID19  https://t.co/MClSt9fChG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo https://t.co/mkAM2ahuRv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gimleteyeLA @Amy_Siskind Trumps base roots for law and order. Your gal pal here is enjoying the carnage and anarchy. Great for ratings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind @Jocelyn39791771 Tomorrow they should stop attempting to burn the federal building to the ground.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind NO SYMPATHY FOR ANARCHISTS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Trump lives in your head and he doesnt even know you exist. Rough life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind You know there was a time we hung traitors... She got off easy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@treat_wanter @wylde_buc @WhitmanHarlan @Amy_Siskind So why was she out in the street? What are they actually protesting?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stillgray He has the dead eyes of a shark. He was ready for trouble.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Man approaches your car with an AK...darn right Im not asking questions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Is that where #RomanPolanski fucked off to?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost RUNNNN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@teslaownersSV Nope. That merges Teslas great tech and poor design.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fleccas 2+2=5. SAY IT!! #1984 #jerrynadler]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MonstaLetMeLive @nypost Cant wait to see the wamen jump in the ring for this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JenRoss4Scot @nypost Live and let live. I get it. The cover of a fitness and sports cover is getting co-opted by political games. She is morbidly obese...she needs medical intervention, not praise for being wrapped in a bikini.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jc_1303 You need more? More what? You are a spoiled little shit...terrorizing people driving. You should be arrested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jc_1303 GET OUT OF THE FUCKING STREET YOU LITTLE MAGGOT.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jc_1303 Julia. Go home. Stop being a fucking asshole.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Portland will seal the second term for @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/Pa85Cvc8Ff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sooze555 @jameshohmann @wildwillow65 @CleveWootson @isaacstanbecker @lori_rozsa @jdawsey1 Go apologize to something Snow Mexico Sooz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jameshohmann @CleveWootson @isaacstanbecker @lori_rozsa @jdawsey1 Relax Jimbo. For a state full of retirees the numbers are minor compared to NY.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @realDonaldTrump Suppression of a medication for political purposes necessitates a malpractice lawsuit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLeoTerrell @drawandstrike @realDonaldTrump Glad to see you come around. I used to watch your segments before you took the red pill...happy youve come to be a part of the right side of history.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/eTNFbKriT5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dbongino @CitizenFreePres is the new conservative version of what the Drudge Report used to be.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mchansley @ChillOnTheRocks @espn @nyliberty @seattlestorm The anthem isnt tearing people apart...leftists are tearing at the fabric of society. You cant be this dense.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mchansley @espn @nyliberty @seattlestorm How about you fuck off to China.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@espn @nyliberty @seattlestorm And not a soul was watching.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ARmastrangelo CARDBOARD CUTOUTS.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marycole121 @nypost Youre an idiot. This is what happens when liberals dont get their way. They act like children. Run along kids.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost And no one even noticed...@nyliberty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dbongino I have a second home in the finger lakes Im selling if anyones serious about getting out. Dm me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StephenMarth Napoleon the pig...telling the rest of the farm what they can eat. #AnimalFarm  @NYGovCuomo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost NYC can burn. Its full of 30-40 somethings with Peter Pan syndrome. Twats.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @elonmusk: Another government stimulus package is not in the best interests of the people imo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how you get through #Walmart without a #mask. https://t.co/4aFA3iH07B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrandonTBanks Youre too stupid to realize what youre even saying.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArtValley818 Little commie bitches]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@steppenwalrus @DontTreadOnJake @DanCrenshawTX Moron...you dont destroy your history.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Youre a cute little baby rhino Dan. Never to be trusted. https://t.co/kzyD1DXRFF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adultswim Depraved shit programming aimed at pedo deviants.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarrahh011 @sooner_okc @nypost Punk? Remind me what he did that was out of line?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@espn Perfect!! Now while youre down there, SMD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Sweet! I love crime shows.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT 53 comments. Not one supports your racist liberal agenda.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT https://t.co/S05criz9tB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jamieob256 @parscale @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump You really are a moron.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jamieob256 Tell me...how many more dead Chicago residents is acceptable to you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo https://t.co/mG93UbWW0E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo https://t.co/xBnTPX3vjG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ABC He should have used bleach bit and rubbed the server with a cloth. #HillaryClinton  @HillaryClinton]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Urban warfare? Who started attacking whom?#PortlandProtests https://t.co/zuGlJ9UJVb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: Raise your hand if you agree with Rand Paul that Cuomo should be impeached for his awful coronavirus response. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@khamenei_ir Go fuck yourself]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 https://t.co/99nToC5DoR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NancyPelosi https://t.co/ch5Ht7HlHC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kayce_johnson85 @nypost Lazy human. Zero guts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Shes not wrong:)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brendalawrence is a fraud. #BrendaLawrence https://t.co/iXWht9Aasn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Thats not a doctor. Thats a murse.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EpochTimes Marxism denounces Christianity. Shes on to something.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT So long @NBA! Woke politics ruin EVERYTHING they touch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Any chance youll be cancelling @chrissyteigen anytime soon? Asking for friends. https://t.co/zHQECqRxBS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Variety Dont worry Dave...will now be homeschooling my kids and shielding them from left wing propaganda.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CitizenFreePres Would consider it a move...not a cave. No mandate from him, kills the argument hes putting people at risk.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CitizenFreePres Sean has a habit of coasting. He will repeat his tirades daily, have the same guests spout the same talking points and tell the same stories over and over. Watched for years...cant do it anymore. Sean, time to get some new material.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CitizenFreePres I cant listen to @seanhannity on Patriot nor watch his show. This shows his total lack of understanding of the gutting of small business across the country. Sure Jeff can make a buck...but what about business forced to close their doors while hes allowed to cont deliveries?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fred2700 @Lynne__Andrea @nypost She knows NOTHING. Your support for her shows your total lack of judgment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fred2700 @ClaytonWKenned1 @Lynne__Andrea @nypost Yeah...better to put them on welfare and sit at home. My bad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton @Liz_Cheney John...go slither back into your hole. Well get Deblaz to pull you out for spring.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChloeSalsameda Thank fucking god. https://t.co/MDLlIVLZM0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fred2700 @ClaytonWKenned1 @Lynne__Andrea @nypost What about all the jobs she killed through her stance on Amazon? No biggie.  Shes a bartender with a social media presence. 13k votes in NYC does not make one a legal scholar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fred2700 @ClaytonWKenned1 @Lynne__Andrea @nypost GREEN NEW DEAL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Fred2700 @Lynne__Andrea @nypost By threat...what do you mean exactly?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justwinph @Lynne__Andrea @nypost Wrong. Shes a blatant Marxist. Dont lie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lynne__Andrea @nypost Because of her buffoonery social presence, shit politics and cancer to society.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Shoe fits]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ericowensdc @nypost And you have a blue check. Incredible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Crime good! Orange man baaad!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DC_Draino https://t.co/do7qyZggnE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nypost Laughable.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>