<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@atasiding8 Yes people are that dumb. Get a free beer and donut after taking vaccine then die. https://t.co/JvmqNB6llH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarcusTriton Wow, that is alarming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez https://t.co/bNZMaRYJEm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roo_mint ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atasiding8 The only news links I see is when I scroll through YouTube and there is always a line of covid news. I never click and only sometimes will read the heading.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atasiding8 I havent been on since 31st January. I dont read online news anymore nor watch or listen to any news. Ive stated what I believe about convid plenty of times and I dont wish to interact with but rather ignore the psychological operation that is covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont take the clot shot https://t.co/i7QBhK8V5E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@youknowchard @PabloOk47 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez And those who refuse the chip??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SulleyTruman Trash worthy ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still the only proven method https://t.co/dxPMoIq3pG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Josef1601 You tried. Sad to hear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davenewworld_2 Basically he knows covid is a big lie and people that still@havent caught on yet are just dumb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople The guy filming him to the side but not helping him ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TonyGreyMan: @SandraWeeden https://t.co/tDqdztEPIx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccine injured her son yet she still wants the vaccine herself . . Covid brainwashed https://t.co/KlMfLU1h2V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come on @ScottMorrisonMP you need to not bring this trouble to Australia https://t.co/QOIKSNuAGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Correction to the lies, she is in hospital because the covid vaccine damaged her https://t.co/KDNdd6MbAL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bharri45: Its 2031, been on the run for 9 years now, getting harder to connect with fellow humans as over 90% of the remaining populat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@simsy1977 And if you fail this IQ test you die https://t.co/6P8k13TMHv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @simsy1977: Anyone else feel like this whole Vaccine situation currently is like the biggest IQ test in the history of the world ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople Sickening. And just what they did with teaching evolution to school children and climate change]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ridingwithc Never watched a super bowl ever. Its just an opportunity for the elites Illuminati etc to predictive program their next moves. Oh its all so old and tiring already]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottMorrisonMP more deaths from the real killer and that is the vivid vax https://t.co/t0BTCbLBov https://t.co/cABmCNYHWC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WatchtowerRome @ScottMorrisonMP They wont answer that simple question]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WatchtowerRome: Why would you vaccinate an entire population based upon a 99.7% survival rate? @ScottMorrisonMP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulBateman3 @ScottMorrisonMP https://t.co/9QZINnkFJb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@t_blacswan https://t.co/6nZ8bG9Ols]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulBateman3 @ScottMorrisonMP You cant travel between states after the covid vaccine is administered because you will be dead]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@t_blacswan 5 years after first covid shot . . . I am dead and shouldnt be typing this https://t.co/yiUL1Pz2vk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottMorrisonMP how many dead people will it take for you to unsubscribes Australia from the covid vaccination kill shot? If one case of the fake covid shuts down a city then one dead person from the covid vaccine should easily shut down the vaccination rollout https://t.co/8UY9FtcAnI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez @ScottMorrisonMP Heaps. Not just mockers but people who have been deceived by the hoax that is covid. Also those who will take the kill shot just to travel, but you cant travel very far if youre dead, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez @ScottMorrisonMP All the mockers will be in line for the covid kill shot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BritIndian2: https://t.co/60T97dM8HH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez People dont want the covid vax because they know its killing people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottMorrisonMP dont bring the killer vaccine to Australia. Kill it off and kill of youre friendship with Bill Gates https://t.co/rgx7vg2yy3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cmon @ScottMorrisonMP how many injured and dead people will it take before you stop the madness pushed on the Australian people? https://t.co/zf3gF1omZs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraWeeden No surprises here  . . Covid vax administered  . . . Bad reactions , uncontrollable shaking, death etc. People should all know by now to avoid the covid vaccine like the plague]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LekkaMercedez: Bullshit!  This article is trying to stop ppl questioning. You know ppl don't have to be forced, coerced, bribed, or thr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@germ_nation14 Nothing has changed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont watch this garbage https://t.co/neI2o3Xhd0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The vaccine is good even if it kills . . That is how insane these people are https://t.co/4BWlmkLZlc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The purpose of the Covid vax is to sterilise the world. https://t.co/UVt8lJe9tN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople https://t.co/nUkrFy3dho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He experienced communism and his experience was that everything his family owned was stripped from them, sound familiar??? You will own nothing and be happy, the be happy bit is just a slap in the face or a kick in the guts when youre down. https://t.co/Ao0IOsk4oe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TBG9270584 C.O.V.I.D . . . Certificate Of Vaccination Identification. Certificate only good for 5 years https://t.co/p8CVYW9d18]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople All this damage done because of this hoax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraWeeden The detail they left out probably would be that the covid vax was rolled out before hand]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@monica_2978 Masks can increase the chance if contracting bacterial pneumonia and nobody wants that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DThurisaz @Adenoughofit https://t.co/bfNrRdCPuG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gorgonzola_68 @Adenoughofit Nothing is beyond what they could do right now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ds13_manon Just treat them like the JWs, give them 80 cent and take a Watch Tower and Wake and never read it. Just dont let them stick their foot in youre door.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople They want more people dead]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TBG9270584 But @ScottMorrisonMP is still living in a government  media conjured up imagination called a pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cmon @ScottMorrisonMP call off the killer vaccine https://t.co/GIg8pVXvJS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPotcner Thats alright, God will sort it out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@t_blacswan They are conditioned via predictive programming to believe that a vaccine having side effects is normal. What about the lady whos husband died from the covid kill shot. She said if he were still alive today he would have had the covid shot again. These people are sick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople They are dispensable to the elites]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople Theyre are getting the covid vax first right!? The elites have them in the firing line first possibly because of all this shoddy dancing upset the secret masters.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LekkaMercedez: If govs telling us no flu now coz mask wearing, why not tell us this all these yrs ago to avoid millions of flu deaths?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is why I refuse to wear a mask https://t.co/zaPI87iYDO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sherloc98788726 @LekkaMercedez https://t.co/bjP68ikxDX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Too true @ScottMorrisonMP Australians wouldnt know about a virus if you didnt tell us, reality disproves government and media all day Ling https://t.co/jBR6xEJ7Od]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mustangmez Covid is a lie and is a war on people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a joke https://t.co/0wX7LkGK1x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Michael_Liddle9 Did she take the covid kill shot?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timesuppeople Think about the proud person who mocks us as conspiracy theorists and then receives the covid vax and gets all types of problems because of it. The covid vax is the ultimate instant leveller. Then within 5 years theyre dead https://t.co/u8Kqg2gtjJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez There were no 800 deaths and we all know it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That covid vaccine killed him@. . . No doubt https://t.co/pkodvL1s0s https://t.co/HrEXgcUc1D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TBG9270584 More propaganda. Frontline nurses dont want the kill shot https://t.co/wDQoCO0Kr1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I went for a cycle and noticed a few massive warehouse type structures close to the ocean in the former industrial area. Are they renovating or renewing these structures to hold those who dont want the vaccine?Nothing crazy is off the table right now! https://t.co/w6z9EEibCu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ds13_manon The plan I believe is to herd all the unwilling participants into Quarantine camp outside the cities and urban spaces.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnonymousSage1 Yup https://t.co/W2XBimOXkF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Adenoughofit Wow. https://t.co/RaijOXP5sb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPotcner Yeah but what can you do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@germ_nation14 And look at the girl depicted . . Blue hair like a woke sjw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SandraWeeden Its all for tv and she would have to be dead by now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mjrowland68 @GregHuntMP Is that the vaccine thats killing people? My mistake. . . All covid-19 vaccines are killing people and doing untold damage]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stephaknee__ Nope and it is impossible to have covid because c.o.v.i.d stands for Certificate Of Vaccination Identification. Once you have that certificate of vaccination then you have officially got covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vax 2 https://t.co/lGOBtlxdfx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DebbeeHutchins1 No]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheCoronaCure_: Please wear your raincoat to keep others dry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hes right https://t.co/2vap00sycW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: BREAKING REPORT:  Wisconsin State Assembly approves resolution to THROW OUT GOVERNER'S EMERGENCY ORDER, which will then]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cmon @ScottMorrisonMP the Australian people know https://t.co/obXHPDyXUD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@James14782804 Death is a side effect. Be careful https://t.co/wjTsR2Vm4b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DannySchmidt211 @James14782804 Yup https://t.co/Witr9403FW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@James14782804 https://t.co/BR18b2bcW9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@James14782804 That is just mocking the people that died from the covid vaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Michael_Liddle9 The guy is an atheist yet sees the variety of Gods creation more so than most people and now hes telling us to take a killer vaccine? Hes a crazy man that also believes in depopulation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarcusTriton Just down with everything covid related]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The elites or secret masters put it out there . . . The vaccine kills. It was everywhere. Now they have warned and revealed what happens and then those that take it are responsible]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez @germ_nation14 Yup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LekkaMercedez @germ_nation14 Yes and he stuck a hair dryer down his throat trying to kill the non existent virus. If anyone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@germ_nation14 He would probably be telling them he never felt better in his life just like when Richard Wilkins had covid which was a false positive test.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPotcner Saving electricity?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MentlHelthMatrz See a lawyer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ParkHaJin12 @AlboMP @SueChapo Did you have any side effects?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlboMP And the killer vaccine# should never start here in Australia. It is totally unnecessary and is shown to kill people.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>