<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 Ok, fair. I will delete.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @LeaderMcConnell @cmclymer @thereidout Thank you for having me on. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cmclymer @JoyAnnReid Thank you for your advocacy and for standing up for the most vulnerable amongst us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thereidout: "I don't know how you teach about 1865 without acknowledging that 1619 was an important year."  @nhannahjones on Mitch McCo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im up next on @thereidout to talk #1619Project, but warning: Its late so Ive already had some wine. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thereidout: Tonight on #TheReidOut:  Biden updates vaccination goals, the fight for voting rights in Texas, and tonight's absolute wors]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cawmsworx @petersavodnik Critical Race Theory was coined by @sandylocks and began as a legal theory. My Lord.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kevlar80808 I can always tell whether anyone has ever read CRT by how they comment on it. CRT is a legal theory, not a way of teaching history...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CindyKGoPackers Cite relevant passages from CRT texts, since CRT looks at the law not individuals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@petersavodnik List the CRT texts you've read.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If a nation is so fragile as to collapse under the truth of its history, what type of nation is that? https://t.co/dIV2o0BCJ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[History is the fruit of power" and "the ultimate mark of power may be its invisibility; the ultimate challenge, the exposition of its roots," ,  Michel-Rolph Trouillot in Silencing the Past: Power and the Production of History."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Nations need to control national memory, because nations keep their shape by shaping their citizens understanding of the past," Joyce Appleby, Lynn Hunt, and Margaret Jacob.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why would we expect the nation's power structure even to acknowledge, much less come to terms with, such a dark and formative chapter in our collective family history? historian Pete H. Wood on slavery and denial.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley Also, I thought the word literally meant in a literal manner or exact. Please cite the critical race theory text that tells white children they're racist. Lastly, the 1619 Project is journalism, CRT is is a legal theory, which you probably didn't know since you haven't read.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley The First Amendment to the Constitution of the United States ensures freedom of speech and prohibits the government from restricting its free exercise. Pre-order #1619project books here: https://t.co/3BtWGk8nLm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley Could you list the critical race theory texts you've read?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse Heres a radical thought: The way to end slavery would have been to prohibit slavery, not count for apportionment people who were excluded from the political system and ensuring inordinate one-party power for enslavers in Congress.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TweetTonyHarris @otgenasis Ha!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mario_anchor My tweet was about wearing masks, not lockdowns.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patcaldwell Love the hair, btw.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndyMLinn I agree. I do think this is why the CDC keeps issuing the guidelines it does, because if lifting mask mandates for those who are vaccinated, there is no way to enforce against those who aren't. And I agree, they should just say that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mario_anchor What about my tweet contradicts any of that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScarinasVault Yes on all accounts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The arrogance of people who presume it's because people are being silly, or frail or anti-science. I know I am vaccinated, but no one else knows that and a whole lot of Americans are not vaccinated, so how does it harm me to put others at ease and keep others safe?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's a thought: Maybe vaccinated people are still wearing masks because none of us know who is and is not vaccinated and so it is an act of being unselfish to not force workers/others to determine who is putting them at risk and who isn't. WE'RE STILL IN A PANDEMIC.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kat__stafford: I love that this is the first job responsibility listed in this @MLK50Memphis job posting. Newsrooms take note: Frame n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Yamiche @washingtonweek Yes, Yamiche! I am so tremendously proud of you. Words cant even express.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vmramos: Indias official average of newly confirmed cases per day has soared from over 65,000 on April 1 to about 370,000, and deaths]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dijoni: Did you know that America had labor camps for black American kids and their family long after slavery ended. https://t.co/3cirR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @errollouis: Gun control in the U.S. is a joke, the note read. Thanks for making the process so easy. https://t.co/0rSNUZEK8P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GodisRivera Oh, Im so sorry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Admissions_DU: Welcome to the Avenue of the Oaks. We pulled out all of the stops for Dillard Decision Day. Faculty, Staff and Students]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IAmSophiaNelson ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@reneewauthor ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Asha_Hinda ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: I think they they see,  @nhannahjones. Its just not their kind of 1st Amend fight. Like racist voter suppression in southe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IAmSophiaNelson There will never be a time where I do not stand up to efforts to legislate against speech.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilLewisJr @nrookie Wow.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ACTdj18Fsi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Hh2OpJTbN7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevinLevin: I appreciate Abraham Mosley's attempt to focus the public on long-term change at Stone Mountain, but I wish we could move b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: I'm a critic of the 1619 project. But 1619 is an important moment. Lincoln, in the Second Inaugural: "...until all the wea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nrookie @LeaderMcConnell EXOTIC.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IBWellsSociety: Apply to be a summer investigative intern @AP. We're looking for juniors, seniors and recent grads, especially those fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJSlaby Yep.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are a lot of exotic notions about what are the most important points in American history. I simply disagree with the notion that The New York Times laid out there that the year 1619 was one of those years.  @LeaderMcConnell  https://t.co/IYrQma7raW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best news this YEAR! Few I respect more in this industry. Kevin is the type of editor that every journalist deserves to work for. Congrats @meridak https://t.co/sN98orneHu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CAIRNational: CAIR Condemns Legislative Effort to Ban Anti-#Racism Teaching in #Tennessee https://t.co/4N1DEpMoxP #CriticalRaceTheory #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seems a bit of contradiction to rail against the so-called First Amendment issues of a private estate choosing not to publish its own titles anymore but then applaud efforts by the state to legally prohibit the teaching of works it does not like.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was all prepared for this to be edited to make it seem like I was saying something I wasn't, but they actually just provided the transcript and let people see for themselves.Yes, efforts to ban American journalism frm being taught is a free speech issue. https://t.co/1wOqmRsZOs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeeves1942 @mimib_11 @MrsTaquana @kenramonet @logoff151 @DPMCanty All of these were cold and calculated business decisions, so I am not sure what point you think they are making?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeeves1942 @mimib_11 @MrsTaquana @kenramonet @logoff151 @DPMCanty It's because they depleted the soil with tobacco production and had to switch to less labor intensive crops, such as wheat. That left them with a surplus of enslaved people, which they then sold South for profit to feed growing cotton labor camps spreading across SE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: John Christopher Smith, who was enslaved at a South Carolina restaurant for years, should be awarded $546,000, an appel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TwightFinancial: @nhannahjones I found this article at the @ABA today, "Another important consideration is that many of our nations sy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @srobi719: On Monday, May 20 at 6 pm CST, dont miss @wttw IDA B. WELLS: A Behind-the-Scenes Preview  Discussion. @sylviaewing3, @srobi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CrystalpeteD @OneWorldLit Anywhere that books are sold!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@debreese @meredithdclark @yunpovi @msteGeorge @ndntea @jmmck9 Congratulations! But also, how shameful for them that this is the first.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NAACP_LDF: "Its about race, and every time we use another descriptor Democrat-run cities, urban areas, we draw attention away from]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Damn. https://t.co/eUbzo3cr9J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whoopthereitg0 I like how you keep pretending the state passing laws is parents choosing when these laws actually remove local choice. Im not interested. Have a good one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whoopthereitg0 This is state and federal law makers trying to *prohibit* the teaching of ideas they dont like. Imagine not knowing what the first amendment is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zyegor1 @OneWorldLit ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gibsoche Yes! And refusing to deify Lincoln. He calls him the white mans president.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@reneeygraham I called him Rick. Whoops. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NKinNewEng @cjm_bklyn Yes, but hes an historian.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cjm_bklyn https://t.co/aaXWPVa3d9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seriously, y'all. 1936 review of W.E.B. Du Bois's "Black Reconstruction" versus 2019 review of 1619 Project by a Princeton historian. https://t.co/GLibIF2P7H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I mean, even high schoolers in metro St. Louis get that: Students like me are sickened by the blatant constitutional infringement that MO HB 1141 presents,  I join more than 25 studs at Univ City High School in urging state officials and lawmakers to consider their position. https://t.co/iYkVwHKAPu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I do not understand how people, especially national journalists, do not see these anti-1619, anti-"Critical race theory," anti-anti-racism bills being introduced in states all across this country as blatantly anti-free speech. Local media certainly seems to get it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["and admit frankly that we are using a version of historic fact in order to influence  educate the new gen along the way we wish. It is propaganda like this that has led men in the past to insist that history is 'lies agreed upon'; to point out the danger in such misinformation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If "we are going to use history for our pleasure and amusement, for inflating our national ego, and giving us a false but pleasurable sense of accomplishment, then we must give up the idea of history either as a science or as an art using the results of science..."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["We have too often a deliberate attempt so to change the facts of history that the story will make pleasant reading for Americans...But are the reasons of courtesy and philanthropy sufficient for denying Truth?"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would implore those who are reporting on the anti-1619 Project bills as some politics-only story to read, especially, DuBois's final chapter in "Black Reconstruction" called "The Propaganda of History."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rlnave ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: The Asian-Americans I know are just angry, and theyre speaking up, the poet Cathy Park Hong said in an interview. Theres]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfMSinha Im so sorry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SorayaMcDonald: https://t.co/hhBM1munq7 https://t.co/dQ4GPDhRZc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnJHarwood: Biden Treasury Secretary answering GOP attacks on "job-killing tax hikes":  "The greatest threat to our economic prospect]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jdesmondharris: "In short, Howard students read the texts required at predominantly white institutions plus the Black stuff ... There i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sulliview: https://t.co/YfJWgZAHPY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @propublica: Many months after racial justice protests swept across New York City  videos showed police punching, kicking  trapping de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@essexie @Bri_Elyse1 @HourNinety Then there is history as in the field of history, what is recorded, what is studied, what is taught. Then there is history, which is our shared memory or understanding of the past. Both of these can be revised and are constantly revised. But, you know that. Have a good day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@essexie @Bri_Elyse1 @HourNinety Youre being intentionally obtuse in order to appear smart, and Im not sure why. The word history has multiple meanings. There is history, which is everything that has occurred in the past, most of which is unrecorded and that well never know.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrreedshistory @Bonafide557619 South Carolina: https://t.co/MWZeu369J2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrreedshistory @Bonafide557619 Where do you teach? https://t.co/qZmQc9DLwN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@essexie History is both what happened and what is said to have happened. Have a good one. https://t.co/moGK65TpCE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrbodyNobody @DohnJawes @TenPointPG My essay also never calls Lincoln a racist, though I did use his own quotes to say he did not believe in Black equality, which he didnt. This is the problem with people whove only read conservative talking points about the project instead of the actual project.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shannon_10Ten Nope. If you read the actual project instead of just conservative media, youd see all of the essays are unchanged, including mine, with the exception of me inserting the words some of in front of colonists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shannon_10Ten How many prominent historians wrote for and are writing for the project?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karlbykarlsmith @JamesSurowiecki @dskamper @EricLevitz What?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the problem with people accusing the 1619 Project of revisionist history. The history weve been taught, in school books, in museums, is revisionist. It seeks to hide the truth of the past because it was shameful. How can you get upset with a museum for being accurate?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Fsx5U3mmHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesSurowiecki @dskamper @EricLevitz ...why do we imagine that is?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The facts of American history have in the last half century been falsified because the nation was ashamed. W.E.B. Du Bois  The Propaganda of History https://t.co/acpoxyi9o3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: Really good: The politicians who tried to overturn an election  and the local news team that wont let anyone forget it -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrreedshistory @Bonafide557619 It might help if you actually read the secession documents.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarah__bartlett: We have an exciting job opening at @newmarkjschool  for a new person to lead our Arts and Culture concentration: https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoyceWhiteVance: One woman, there to look for her daughter, was pepper sprayed  was crying on the sidewalk because she couldnt see. S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @en_dash: Im in @CommonWealthMag with a combination essay and data visualization about inequalities as you cross town borders in Massac]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>