<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato, I was thinking, maybe it would help to realise not all diabetics are comfortable eating food labelled for diabetics  how condescending to diminish someone to merely being their illness. Stop speaking for people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Colin got goons  https://t.co/Hn7jZxmahS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WWE: The duo of @sanbenito  @ArcherOfInfamy is on  against @mikethemiz  @TheRealMorrison!  Stream #WrestleMania on @PeacockTV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MariahCarey Iconic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make sure you take a screenshot of your journey quotes with @Uber #UK they like to lie kmt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mysticmeg_xo @instagram Okay, had to Google said movie ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mysticmeg_xo @instagram Cardi/JLo one?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seriously @instagram hope feminists are enraged. Instagram saying women arent worth scamming  https://t.co/FdOpQek9GV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @epilepsyaction: "My chosen family help alleviate some of the stress of being a queer epileptic by providing me with a secure base to fe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arianna_Ajtar: Petition for over 25s nightclubs to be a thing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gabz_Louise_ Both gorgeous but short is just  youve honestly got the face to pull it off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YasminPinkk: Cancel culture is hilarious and the mental health campaign on here is hilarious you guys do love to pick and choose I must]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@coopuk Harrow Rd branch cash only. Why are your useless staff not saying anything and letting people waste their time queuing? Not one member of staff informed us! Open your mouth  #trash]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @latimes: The true crime series that may develop a "Tiger King" style following.  Here's what you need to know about Netflix's new, haun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BKChat: We are working towards a new season, however the new lock down doesnt help but we are working]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sharethfukinpie So rather than ask him if hes ok, you share it to social media? I hope this is your friend and some sick attempt at clout. You and everyone here commenting trying to be funny are honestly so fucking lame. Do better.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@karanjohar Bollywood Wives was phenomenal! Season 2 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cece_Alexandra: 3K Grant Giveaway from @_Money4YOU BAMER HUB - You Choose Who Wins https://t.co/QJerBp8X7T https://t.co/QJerBp8X7T  We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can confirm Gabz is a sweetheart Get those audition videos in  https://t.co/lzsKOJkx6s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone asking me how I got on the show, here you are! Shoot your shot  https://t.co/hbUfrxA0Za]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Showing my age, but @BustaRhymes #ELE2 is the hip hop I know. Story telling, meaningful lyricism. Mariah, Mary and ODB features? The children are not ready ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We need to stop these very public and very dangerous messages, that simply being a woman, equates to innocence. Its a slap in the face for domestic abuse victims irrespective of gender and a slap in the face for equality #JusticeForJohnnyDepp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ffs! Didnt even get to watch the video you did with Guh Deh  hope you can get your content back man https://t.co/3nItwLS3sp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reading all the comments, this is mad! Im so sorry youre all going/went through this. Keep pushing! https://t.co/QvqRGQEWJi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I had psoriasis before @KimKardashian made it cool #JustSaying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I fucking love Romain. Put that Davina bitch in her place #SellingSunset]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@netflix Actually it was very representative seeing as its a scene from the movie! You openly admit in YOUR OWN WORDS that the artwork is inappropriate, but continue to support this! #pedoflix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its so disturbing. Some scenes I couldnt even watch  https://t.co/9agYCtFuga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Came for two episodes of #SellingSunset stayed for six]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BFrank2020 @MariahCarey Lamb...or damn ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MissyElliott: All my prayer warriors who pray lets pray for our sister TamarBraxton for those who Believe in the Power of Prayer and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMichelleW: I am so sorry!!! Thinking of family and close friends of Naya Rivera!!! Was hoping for another outcome! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beautiful Naya  I prayed every night for God to give you back. But it wasnt His will. You brought joy to so many through your art. You sang Madonna under the table! Rest in perfect peace ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I live a poor bitch dreams, Coco Chanel me please  @YungMiami305]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This cover-art tho  https://t.co/0zX7OWhJHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pollen in this country is ACID! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShaySAL_ Doppelgnger for sure ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy b day @_CatherineNancy  https://t.co/DbIAi07MBZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exploitation of some of the most vulnerable in society. The UK government is truly living the American dream https://t.co/KcVuB8RZ9W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KimKardashian: Sunbeams https://t.co/XbLve6D109]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is old school. You need to understand where these words are coming from and get the emotion out  @LatriceRoyale the kids these days could never! #iconic ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am a diamond cause of pressure. The bigger the trial, bigger the blessing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IGGYAZALEA: One can only aspire to age like Cher.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shes sooo beautiful! https://t.co/BSP69OsSx5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jstlivinbbyy: Jst a reminder... https://t.co/W2tdpgTdrg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @XXL: #BREAKING: 6ix9ine could be released from prison "any day now" due to coronavirus https://t.co/aq2xIjq5jR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UpNorthFiddy: Kate McCann Has Urged People To Stay At Home ?, If Shed Done That, We Wouldnt Even Know Who She Is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Too white and middle class hun. Its only neglect/abuse when other people do it https://t.co/BnLqk8uCZk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chenqiushi404: Who's Chen Qiushi? Where's Chen Qiushi? When will we see him again?  Chen Qiushi has been out of contact for 51 days aft]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If youre not using some of this lockdown time for introspection, what are you doing. We learn the most in the hardest of times]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ComplexMusic: Biggie's posthumous second album stands the test of time as one of hip-hop's greatest, most idiosyncratic achievements ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@denzeldion I read this as death threats ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are you surprised? The Maccas and KFC in Bush have 24hr security guards  https://t.co/gySKtmfnb1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[27/3 https://t.co/UUTKqk0wAw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MsBanks: Imagine youre going for a walk and you see your friend with her child, now its 3 of you in public and feds are sliding by, i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please God, let her make it  https://t.co/VPW9czqEz1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The way she told the passport handler, Youuu, should be wearing gloves  #QUEEN https://t.co/Kvr5UkTJt9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She went to jail for scamming so she must know a scam when she sees one  https://t.co/NTyAMrigcu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DJ_ScarfZ: I think NHS staff working through this Coronavirus should have access to everything they need free. Free travel/cabs to work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you for reporting on Iran. Because theyre not white or European, western media doesnt even give them a mention! https://t.co/0q2pJwCSNX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arabnews: When do you think the Novel Coronavirus crisis will be over?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casinos closed...its getting real https://t.co/4ZI8bm6MV4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cece_Alexandra we got blocked by another bitch for telling the truth  if youre gonna try troll me, see it the fuck through! Talk and then block kmt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@llIlIIIlIllIlIl @sophfirmino Thats how I know youre an ignorant fuck. Im not even white. Yallah ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@llIlIIIlIllIlIl @sophfirmino They highlighted the fact that its harder to succeed as an ethnic minority because guess what, IT IS! Youre judged differently and thats the unfortunate truth. You interpreted it as them saying white people hate them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@llIlIIIlIllIlIl @sophfirmino Child abuse?! Youre talking on matters you clearly dont understand. And thats ok. But you need to stop now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sophfirmino @llIlIIIlIllIlIl Thank you @sophfirmino I remember as a teen, my friend was telling me his mum had the same conversation with him. And this was 20 years ago!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worse than your flu that made you feel ill for half a day as you wrote in the Daily Mail today? How the HELL are you a medical professional! https://t.co/BlOPNCsfgd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gina_VFL: Im 46 and have been on immunosuppressants for 15 years. These meds keep my body from fighting itself and enable me to functi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NorbertElekes People are being turned away from the London flagship right now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VeganLover28 @khaleejtimes The only inequality is people like you assuming women cant make their own decisions. Stop assuming based on a picture that none of these women chose for themselves to practice modesty/covering up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHO:  BREAKING   "We have therefore made the assessment that #COVID19 can be characterized as a pandemic"-@DrTedros #coronavirus http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The issue I have with the Sherry Pie story and others like it. Theres always the promise of fame and fortune. And as harsh as it sounds, had you gotten those things, you probably wouldnt be saying a thing #sherrypie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whoa... https://t.co/rsrJXOiUN4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theestallion: #SUGA OUT NOW https://t.co/mfyyCosmdu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BKChat: Reunion week! Guys purchase your tickets now!!   https://t.co/fUhEr00rQl https://t.co/bxda9dXUb4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theestallion: #FREEMEG #FREETHEESTALLION]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BKChat: Our platform was hacked and all our content was deleted on #Trendcentrl https://t.co/1zI6nAcoJW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Writings On The Wall reference whilst using Say My Name in the new #Candyman trailer is genius]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SylviaKay__ Petty. And I love it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So @CarolynSmith86 retweeted this but insulted my friend with epilepsy. Dont pretend to be an advocate for disability when you are judgmental yourself #hypocrite https://t.co/g56NgaBJuT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cece_Alexandra @CarolynSmith86 @zacharykorn @IEJGov @CarolynSmith86 youre a grade A twat. Who the f are you to grade ANYONES access needs! Ignorant af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @patriciaxesther: @BKChat Todays episode This was wild!! #bkchatldn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BKChat: Episode 15  Out now!! https://t.co/yWKaTxhHiq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KashARTworks: BKCHAT LDN: EPISODE 15 [TEASER] https://t.co/t9dEPtk2Dr via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pinkk make em wink and its all Good. See what I did there  @YasminPinkk and @Lani_Good7 new video up now  https://t.co/EwPkYjNUq6 https://t.co/m1C0vSTd6R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/yssUCgvnU0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ayeyehinkso Dont be silly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[About last night  #gucci https://t.co/oLtcKmZsQO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NaomiMbelu: @chickenthottage said hed  marry me cause Im intelligent https://t.co/kxhd9Un95f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissyElliott @dblanks Soon as I saw this, I remembered Missy saying she was so sick she couldnt hold a pen. Look how good God is ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Their algorithms are insane  https://t.co/lRiMgsS3aC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cece_Alexandra At least get your source right. Trying to be The Guardian but not even Daily Mail ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Luke Bieber better keep an eye out for his Selena  #loveisland]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CJINMYVA_GINA: YESSSS GWARNNNN NASSSS #LoveIsland]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@McGannJack Loool wow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Leanne ok? You didnt want him love, you made that very clear  #loveisland]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finley that shirt is a look  #loveisland]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I keep saying this!!! https://t.co/8e5Eod0OUp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MichelleS070 @bolsbols2 @LoveIsland @itv2 ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>