<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@arismainpov We're truly sorry to see that, Aislinn! When you can, please DM us with your order number, name, email, and phone number, so we can best assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lyssm96 We're truly sorry to hear this, Alyssa! When you can, please DM us with your order number, name, email, phone number, and the name of the missing item, so we can best assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itsnaomieden We're sorry to hear this, Naomi. Please send us a DM with the information you'd like to change, and we can further assist. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brooke_albano Hi Brooke, we're sorry to hear this! Please send us a DM with more info on your order, so we can assist further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bestallyever_ Hi Ally, we'd be happy to see if can assist! Please send us a DM with more details on the issue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@innalemy Oh no! Send us a DM with your order information, and we can assist! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whoamoose We're sorry to hear this! Send us a DM with your rewards information, and we can assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeansfanatic Mama knows best ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reminder #MothersDay2021 is just a week away ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats the best beauty advice your mom has given you? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lilyisacutiiie We never want your order to arrive this way! Please send us a DM with your full name, email, phone number, and order number, so we can assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bradleigh__ This isn't what we like to hear! Can you send us a DM with your full name, email, phone number, and more details so that we can look into this matter with you further?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dialaforartee Hi Artee, this is not what we want to hear and apologize that this was your experience. We'd like to connect further over your visit, please send us a DM with more info.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@krjax8 Hi Kennedy! We're very sorry to hear this. We'd like to connect and discuss this further with you. Please reach out to our Guest Services team at your earliest convenience either via a private DM, phone at 1-866-983-8582, or email at gethelp@ulta.com.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michelefiveoh Thanks for these additional details, Michele. Please see our response to your DM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@littlem3rma1d That's not what we want to see! We'd be happy to take a closer look if you could send us a DM with more info. Looking forward to hearing from you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@freexkey This is awesome! We appreciate you sharing this with us, and well be sure to pass that kudos along to our Charlottesville team!  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LowKiLux Oh no, we're sorry to hear this! Please send us a DM with your coupon code, so we can assist further and make sure you can get your products.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lore_em_in We can take a peek at the order, Lauren! Please send us a DM with your order info, so we can assist further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeatherVentures Thanks for letting us know. Well be sure to pass that along!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatyDelahunt Oh no! Send us a DM with your order information, and we can assist! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sunkyuties Oh no! This isn't what we like to see! Send us a DM with your full name, email, phone number, and order number so that we can take a look!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eribnsto Hi there, we are aware of an issue with this coupon and are currently looking into it! Thank you for your patience as we work to resolve the issue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FemmeFtle9 @femmeftle9 We will be happy to assist you! Please DM us with your full name, email address, and phone number!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoLTonelica Hi there, we can take a look at this for you! Please DM us with your typed out order number, name, email, and phone number, so we can best assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sugar_kitty1 @sugar_kitty1 We're so sorry! Please, DM with your full name, email address, and phone number followed by your order number.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AshleyAudet92 Hi Ashley, we're sorry to hear this! Please send us a DM with your full name, email address, and phone number.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElenaDeleon_98 We're sorry to hear this! Send us a DM with your login information, and we can assist! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RadioNikki Always happy to help! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sydneyandsports Hi there! We're sorry to hear this. Please send us a DM with your order number, full name, email, phone number, and shipping address, so we can take a closer look. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexisselfies This isn't what we want to hear! Please DM us with a few details so we can chat further about your experience.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lakerangel14 Of course! Our associates look forward to assisting you on your next visit ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lakerangel14 Hi Sarah! We're sorry to hear that you didn't love this purchase. If you purchased these items under your rewards account, you're welcome to return/exchange them. If not, you can also receive a merchandise card to pick out another favorite. Hope this helps! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@noturavegrl Oh no! WE're so sorry to hear this and want to look into this for you. Can you please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@a_fals Hi ashley, we're sorry to hear this! Please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number, so we can take a closer look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@washironfucketc Hi there! We have verified that these gifts were part of your order, so sorry that you did not receive them! Since they are while supplies last, we cannot reship free gifts, so we'd send a small gift card to replace these free gifts. Send us a DM if you need further assistance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sckswithsandals This doesn't sound right! Please DM us with your order number, name, email, and phone number, so we can take a closer look at this for you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlexiaJayGlam We want our stores to be a welcoming environment for every one of our guests and we recognize that was not your experience. We would like to connect with you, can you send us a DM with your full name, email, and phone number, and any more details you would like to share?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soyalejandrojc Hi there, we're sorry to hear the frustration! Were not able to accept orders placed from outside the US at this time, but we'll be sure to pass along your interest for the future! If you have any other questions or concerns, feel free to send us a DM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RaffyDrama Morphes announcement to end its business relationship with James Charles directly impacts products carried at Ulta Beauty. We are working with our partners at Morphe to wind down sales of the products, after which we will no longer carry the collaboration.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EccentricLeelee We apologize for any frustration! We'd be happy to look into this for you. Please send us a DM with your order number, and we can assist. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kerishiamarie We'd be happy to take a closer look at this for you, Kersha! When you can, DM us with your name, email, phone number, and a screenshot of the error you're seeing, so we can best assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@D00dette91 We're sorry to hear this! Please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number so we can take a closer look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RockyPerez95 Yikes, that's no good, Rocky! Please DM us with your order number, name, email, and phone number, as well as any pictures you have of the damage, so we can best assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissSoNasty Oh no! Send us a DM with your order information, and we can assist. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@money226156 Hi there, this isn't what we want to hear and we apologize that this was your experience! We'd like to connect further over your visit and invite you to DM us with the store location and any further details of your visit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CheriPegelow We'd like to look into this! Send us a DM with your rewards information, and we can assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chelseainspace Hi Chelsea, we'd be happy to take a look at the issue! Please send us a DM with your rewards info (name, email, and phone number), so we can assist further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@a_nnicka We're sorry to hear that you were disappointed by your visit with us. We would like to connect with your further. Please reach out to our Guest Services team either via Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, phone at 1-866-983-8582, or email at gethelp@ulta.com with more details.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michelefiveoh We apologize for any frustration with your points, we'd like to look into this! Send us a DM with more information, and we can assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Moodymelanin31 Hi there, we're sorry to hear this! We appreciate your feedback and invite you to DM us with any further details on your experience with us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpoffordLiana Thanks so much! We've shared this with our teams to look into.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpoffordLiana Hi there! Thanks for bringing this to our attention. Are you able to share the link to this ad as well?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@keyab2u Hi there! We're sorry to hear you're having trouble with your coupon. We'd be happy to take a look if you could send us a DM with your full name, email, phone number, and a screenshot of the error.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bbravobri We are sorry that the packaging you received was empty! We would recommend you return to the store to either receive a new item or a refund for the missing contents. If you have any further questions, please send us a DM!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@H3atherAl3xis Oh no! Send us a DM with your full name, email, phone number, and the order number so that we can take a look into this with you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_ohheyrenee Hi there! Of course! You can take it to your local Ulta store for a return. Make sure you take your order number or Invoice receipt with you when making this return!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maureenszturm Oh no! We're sorry to hear that you haven't received your order yet. Please send us a DM with your full name, email, phone number, and order number, so we can take a look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lolgurl_1 No problem! Send us a DM with the typed-out gift card numbers (no need for spaces or the pins) and a valid email so that we can merge those for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WonderDeity Hi there, this isn't what we like to hear! Please send us a DM with your Rewards info (name, email address, and phone number) and your order number, and we'll take a look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_kat11k Hi Kat, we can help out! Please send us a DM with your coupon code and your rewards info (name, email, and phone number).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MariahCleveland We can double check on your order for you! When you can, DM us with your order number, name, email, and phone number, so we can take a closer look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carly222 That's no good, Carly! Please DM us with your order number and any pictures you have of the damage, as well as your name, email, and phone number, so we can best assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@baileynh_94 That's not what we want to hear! When you can, please DM us with your order number, name, email, and phone number, so we can take a closer look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@__Selenaaaa_ Oh no! We're sorry to hear this. Send us a DM with more information, and we can assist! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurendanise We're so sorry to hear this Lauren! We want to help. Can you please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number typed out for us?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlyLindsay We're happy to look into this further for you. Please follow us so that we can message you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlyLindsay @blylindsay We're so sorry! Please, DM with your rewards info and details. We'd like to look into this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miss_mle85 We're sorry to see this! Please DM with your order number and details. We'd like to look into this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dlgb18 Hi there! We will be happy to look into this for you. Can you please DM us your full name, phone number, order number?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lakerangel14 Hi Sarah, we'd be happy to look into this for you and make sure the order went through! Please send us a DM with your name, email, and phone number, so we can assist further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@geckomother_ Hi there! Our associates will be happy to assist you in-store with a return of the items. As it is past 60 days of purchase, store credit will be the only refund option. If you have any further questions, please send us a DM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy #EarthDay Sending less to the landfill means good things for the planet, so we're shining a spotlight on the brands doing their part! Drop a  if you use these brands. #ultabeauty https://t.co/UGA4imRqXZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SDomynique We're sorry to hear this! Feel free to DM us with more information, and we'll look further into this. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@furbylovr Oh no! We want to look into this for you, can you please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and a screenshot of the error you are receiving?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maichidarling Hi there, thanks for reaching out. Please know it's against our policy to resell products for any reason. If you have additional details you'd like to share, please DM us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BXCCl Yikes! Please, DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number. We'd like to look into this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pokibelle We're so sorry Kendall, we want to help. Can you please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mayrlopez1234 We're so sorry to hear this Mariel! We want to look into this for you. Can you please send us a DM with our full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Krisnakaye_ We're sorry to hear that you were disappointed by your experience with us, Krisna. We're happy to help. Please send us a DM with further details as we'd like to learn more about your visit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cheekijen Oh No! This is not good at all, we want to help! Can you please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and order number so we can further assist?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YasminePea1 Yes, this offer is currently online only!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sasha_p_xo We're happy to help! Send us a DM with your purchase information, and we'll look into this for you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@erquarius We're happy to help! Send us a DM with more information, and we can assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@madeup_artist We'd like to look into this! Send us a DM with your order information, and we can assist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@allredke Hi Karen, thanks for reaching out. Not all products are sold with a seal; we recommend reaching out to Lancme to see if that's the case there! Otherwise, please know you're always welcome to return or exchange a product if you don't feel comfortable using it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_ohheyrenee That's no good! Please DM us with your order number, name, email, and phone number, as well as the name of the missing items, so we can best assist!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@audreythefrog ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HcxALfRRLs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@teriobrien Hi there, we'd be happy to take a look at the order for you! Please send us a DM with your order number and info, so we can assist further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NBalboaPhoto We're so sorry to hear this Nicole! We want to connect with your further. Can you please send us a DM with your full name, rewards email, phone number, and store location?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SharonAnne71 This isn't what we want to hear! Please send us a DM with your order number, so we can take a closer look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cindafuninrella Oh No! We're so sorry to hear this Ranae! We want to connect with your further. Can you please send us a dm with your full name, rewards email, phone number, store location, and full details of your experience?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justmeloli We always want our guests to be notified as soon as possible if their appointment time needs to be changed or canceled for any reason, so were truly sorry to hear this about your appointment. Send us a DM with the store location, and we'll set up a contact request for you. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rachelsaysLOVE We're sorry to disappoint you. Because we begin processing orders immediately after you confirm the information and select Place Order, we're unable to modify orders, as shared publicly in our online shipping policy. Feel free to send us a DM with any questions. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cmontalvo94 Hi Cecile, we'd be happy to see if we can help! Please send us a DM with more info on the issue you are having and your rewards info.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@missmarisol Hi! We're sorry to hear this. Please send us a DM, so we can further look into this for you. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mprescott77 Hi Michelle! We're sorry for any disappointment. We'd be happy to merge your gift cards here. Just send us a DM with your full name, email, and gift card numbers!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dosesofraye This isn't what we want to hear. We will always stand for equality, inclusivity and acceptance, and strive to provide a welcoming environment to all our guests. Wed like to talk more with you about this. Please send us a DM with further details regarding your experience.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrsBurger14 Oh no, this isn't what we want to see! We recommend returning to the store, so our associates can assist you with getting the right product. ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>