<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FunTimeFred1: DO NOT VOTE CONSERVATIVE   Thats the ONLY (admittedly slim) chance we have to make Boris reassess his dystopian directio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Every time we follow the money it leads us to Bill Gates... https://t.co/kS2mciBc1N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is pure evil. I am ashamed of the human race for being so pathetic as to not speak up for  protect children https://t.co/HzxXqoMMtD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TamShah1: @zoeharcombe @JaniceW78256134 Short clip explaining how the loss of freedoms will be achieved if we don't do anything and let]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TamShah1: Why pay companies millions if it seemingly a "temporary measure"  Tax was supposed to be temporary too... #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jimmy31922581 @zoeharcombe Really?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peterpalmer52: @zoeharcombe We now have to decide if our Gov't is incompetent, evil or just gullible. They heard "science"; got modelli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@peterpalmer52 @zoeharcombe They aren't incompetent. This is the start of period of depopulation, it's very deliberate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @allisonpearson: On @BBCNews massive pessimism about opening up. Then the embarrassing fact -1 Covid death!   The disconnect between the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKcitizen2021: We are delighted to be joining forces with other organisations, who are committed to the importance of truth, freedom an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @end_lockdowns: Shocking. The good people of Ireland must stand up for their own against this tyranny. It could be YOU next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Raab knows restrictions like masks will need to remain this summer, not on health grounds, but to keep this going until th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Enough is enough. We've got six weeks to show the government that if they don't give us our lives back we're just going]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toadmeister: SAGE cites evidence that it claims supports Government mask mandates, but follow the footnotes and what you find is a mess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking. The good people of Ireland must stand up for their own against this tyranny. It could be YOU next. https://t.co/jw4roMxVSA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DominicFrisby: "Boris Johnson is just a fat Tony Blair" splayed across the Houses of Parliament last night.  Buahahahaha! https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieSuB: @zero_to_here_oh I never ever would have believed that my Government ,of any hue ,would purposely become my enemy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timfprice: *If you thought Covid was bad, get a load of the Communistic coup that has swept the West]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DickDelingpole: Ultimately, the restrictions will kill the pubs which gold plate the rules. Regular drinkers are the least bed-wetty an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @petedjackson: Id suggest all hospitality print this off and place them around your business in preparation for opening up in June. htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BBC News - Lockdowns hurt child speech and language skills - report https://t.co/c2EiYUw8GD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: ON BBC NEWS: GOVT TESTING THE DEAD https://t.co/P2xzK643rj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarfsee: Would you believe it? The virus was coming out of your tv all along!  https://t.co/WYKoSGTSXA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/DLgW9PjsKD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: So the UK govts idea of a removal of restrictions on 21st June means people still having to wear masks in cinemas, thea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@janet_cutts @Barbara57595701 @goddeketal @angelogiorgian2 @FalzoneEnza @sketchnoteson @HowardSteen4 @Bobby_Network @gummibear737 @normanrr @joanned1 Trilateral Commission Starmer Parliament is theatre Democracy has been faux  Politicians are controlled opposition .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goddeketal: The dehumanization of humanity needs to stop. It's dignity and respect what sets us apart from the world's ruling elite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Dr. Peter McCullough, in a 32-minuteinterview with journalist Alex Newman, said if this were any other vaccine, it would have been pulled from the market by now for safety reasons." https://t.co/Mq2tabBG2R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billionaires regard us as human cattle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Govt is 100% about coercive control.  They are attacking us all, this is war. https://t.co/yiqf6TMFyb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kinstery: @AntiWokeBritain The light from their eyes has gone, unfortunately the government and MSM are  winning  https://t.co/Hd3TPzF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheCoronaCure_: @AntiWokeBritain @TimHowe73500437 Cut the Internet and have a food shortage.  That should wake people pretty quick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomBomb11490104: @AntiWokeBritain You dont readily reverse brainwashing. It has been demonstrated that, even if it can be proved to th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntiWokeBritain: How do you reverse the brainwashing of millions of people over 13 months?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These NHS adverts are EVIL. HUG YOUR MUM  NOT HUGGING KILLS https://t.co/OIY5RRoYPX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lensiseethrough: I'm disturbed we are talking about rolling out the vaccine to children - at what point did we reverse the idea that ad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Covid-19 has created record waiting lists and a logjam of care for heart disease, stroke and cancer patients with charit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: I was at the pub yesterday. 10 of us, but thats not the story. Out of the 10 we had 6 unjabbed including a nurse. I wou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1984cov: Do u guys think there is something on the Covid tests? I do but some people insist there is not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShuttleMrGeo: Is this why health insurers like #VHI and @Bupa won't cover you if you've had the vax? The depths of evil of our Governme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @end_lockdowns: What do YOU think the majority of teenagers think? Please retweet ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do YOU think the majority of teenagers think? Please retweet ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NHSuk Evil.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @end_lockdowns: @tony2015555 @FunTimeFred1 Govt(s), UN, WHO, Gates-funded science SAGE, media have DELIBERATELY tried to FULL ON twist y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: NJ school nurse suspended after saying masks are harming students https://t.co/Hm1iEZ1b7y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: So how do we stop the vaccination of healthy children?   Please share and come up with solutions below.. https://t.co/iNSLg5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tony2015555 @FunTimeFred1 Govt(s), UN, WHO, Gates-funded science SAGE, media have DELIBERATELY tried to FULL ON twist your Mellon a year #UntwistYourMellon  Hurry up Masks are political, psychological,  PCR cases are fraud Children in masks is wrong,  Face up to it CALL it OUT! #SackSAGE #BorisOut https://t.co/tOovNuzqR0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Try looking here instead. #BRAZILplease share   #EndLockdowns! #EndTheLockdowns https://t.co/h6R2bT1Vfw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DON'T LK chuffin here!  COMMUNISTS WALLPAPER  https://t.co/eC86QsnoWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lopi99474430: @Demo2020cracy @rv_parkes Sick of the propaganda from mass media]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AustinKBF: @Demo2020cracy @end_lockdowns The Brazilan variant, so deadly that it doesn't kill its host!  I wonder if the MSM will show]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kevind04: Though given his history in front of the camera I can see why so many people believed it https://t.co/PKRt0mlbgI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: GO BERLIN!!!!! YES!! #EndLockdowns https://t.co/0nvSVfdOt0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: I was around in 1976. Listen to the elders who remember. Share. https://t.co/a7M7KHGSTN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: Coronavirus cure: Scientists plan bizarre 'self-spreading vaccine' to fight pandemic  "informed by the scientists behind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: NOT ON BBC "NEWS" : TODAY IN BERLIN https://t.co/MahVlQhGBy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: How's this Brazilian VARIANT for you Boris?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamBrimson:  https://t.co/WNQihdoY5j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @burak_turna: Kresel medya inann Iidden ok daha ciddi bir terr rgt...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FLMIRONES: #MIRONEWS Decirle a un abuelo que si acepta voluntariamente inyectarse un experimento peligroso va a poder abrazar por fin a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/2USV6vDEHd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The land of the free.  https://t.co/LpgrJH6kov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danielmkovalik: Food for thought:  https://t.co/KlW3v3hI1N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laworfiction: Revealed IN COURT:  neither school nor govt conducted ANY assessment of the risk to children of harms of masks  unchall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am anti totalitarianism.  Retweet if you are?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GalGur_: This video has just been published, as part of an official campaign by the Israeli MOH - in the "vaccinated Israeli society th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GO NAPLES!  https://t.co/amf9DlQzue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For the love of God. Are people really that dense. https://t.co/UKTFNRrbQw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RadioSavana: Una volta la giovent si emozionava per la prima Comunione, oggi per la prima dose di Pfizer. Una sorta di eucarestia vacc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreedomIsrael_: #India Whatever they tell you, its bullshit https://t.co/zbKQnDlApf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gbdeclaration: Having concerns about the cost of lockdown does not make you a Covid-denier, I would never dream of labelling someone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Idonotconsent6: Keep speaking out the world needs people like this ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Life is getting more surreal  https://t.co/a8dGJ7e7O8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We need a man like this in our Parliament.  https://t.co/phV6PUPdua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[100% worth 10 min.  https://t.co/oSOVxXr3EJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ToniaBuxton: Why does the Government not care about children? Why are schools  not fighting for them. I feel despair that I send my chi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Almost 40 million people in England currently live in an area with almost no new Covid cases, according to Public Health]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Playing silly games when the country goes to the knackers yard.  Pillock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GERMANY KEEPS ANTI-LOCKDOWN GROUP UNDER "OBSERVATION" https://t.co/MsgfnCnsxm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InProportion2: This is the news from Germany: "lateral thinkers" who question the legitimacy of the state are to be put under surveilla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrTardigradeUK: This is people power. Parents in the UK, sending emails wont change anything. You need to go to the schools and force]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: The suffragettes were so sweet, so nice and lovely and nothing happened UNTIL they were no longer so sweet and nice....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/AJ1oYWEV7V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoriartyProfJ3: It is still crap but pushback is getting somewhere https://t.co/DJ5pEh0Y64]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @end_lockdowns: Wake up. They have taken us for fools. 2020 Global pandemic. Hmmm  https://t.co/W06tsL0SLW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@szarvas87 London was a good sign]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClarrisaWj Really does.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nova144000: My Daughter just rang me ..Her Friends relative who lives in Ukraine has told her Ukraine Media are saying Britain is stru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @GMB https://t.co/RKTAV0Q1VB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: We must stand up and say NO!!!!!!!!! #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EightBells4: @angelovalidiya @benmagelsen @FatEmperor @NassMeryl @RobsBottin80 @MichaelPSenger @end_lockdowns @JaniceW78256134 @NickHud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GO VAIL SCHOOL BOARD!! Come on UK parents. Wake the hell up! #binMasks #masksdontwork  #PoliticalMasks https://t.co/sudcaWaztZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@angelovalidiya @EightBells4 @benmagelsen @FatEmperor @NassMeryl @RobsBottin80 @MichaelPSenger @JaniceW78256134 @NickHudsonCT @naomirwolf Terrible. It's unbelievable what's happening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: This guy is a hero - he is an American Pathologist - watch his COVID lecture:  https://t.co/JR5POJiTqL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @justin_rowberry: @NHSuk Enough of this bullshit now!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pure evil.  The psychology used by this government, under the NHS name, is an absolute disgrace. https://t.co/Ns7UXiVd2d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NOT ON THE NEWS: MASK WEARING RUNNER COLLAPSES. I wonder what it will take for people to face up to what's happened to the world. Maybe this will  Terrible to watch, she brutally falls as she passes out. https://t.co/EcKnZq4y63]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccinated, still lockdown, can't go on holiday and then you get #covid19 https://t.co/PbfDFYc75f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GO FLORIDA!!! https://t.co/IDp4WXd6N6]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>