<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket @AdigunPolack I love it to the moon and back! And I am a big supporter of artists. If I can give phat tips, DAMN IT I WILL.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket I CRY EVERYTIME YOU SAY THAT LIKE IM IN DISBELIEF. THANK YOU HDJSDFHK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JiskeyJasket: a portrait pixelart comm for the extraordinary @LeafOpal  https://t.co/GD4ywYzDkX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket THANK YOU FOR DRAWING MEEE. I am inlove with this. AHH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chel_faust I like B. It def has some ethereal vibes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket I adore this!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia for real, i never was into brands, but one day, id like one gucci bag... just one T_T, maybe if i go for my nurse practicitioner...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@studioalluvio thank you ;w;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia i bet that bag was like 2-4 gs. I like the sneakers a lot but id like literally be afraid of scuffing them. I literally shop at tjmaxx and walmart for my style LMAO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Like I pull up the website and oggle at the sneakers ( which is 650, and maybe I can splurge on those if God is good and doesnt throw shit in my face). But damn. 2000 for a bag... and my coworkers drop a whole ass avocado on them bags bruh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NGL. I want like, Gucci sneakers or a handbag just to feel bougee as fuck. But I can NOT for the life of me, drop, 2,000 USD for a small bag that may not be able to fit even my wallet in it.  MY 25 USD target bag is literally everything I wanted tho.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia she radiates &gt;:3c vibes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lunaesii listen, soft serve vanilla icecream after a nice hot day around 3-4pm when the sun kind of lets off. yeeeAAA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[working on this ning thigh-high ahjkfhjsd https://t.co/kPedK2qbgd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia ONE CLUCKY BOI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlorTheStar ohhh that sounds SO FREAKIN GOOD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lilamitehcookie GOD YES. I LOVE IT ALL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yume7391 exactly! it's sweltering right now for spring!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chel_faust Chobani's key lime pie flavored yogurts have been my saving grace lool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chel_faust YESSS i love lemon flavored and lime flavored sweets.... keylime pie is going to be the death of me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yume7391 ommmg i want that now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's your favorite dessert?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kam2D Love this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@minsong1274 I love this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Franrekk In love!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Okay, gotta get out of bed and be productive...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[reupload] Chicken Griffin! ( now that I was taught the correct way to upload pixel art here haha) RT appreciated  #pixelart #pixels https://t.co/7HsuDFINk6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2Diamonded @JiskeyJasket This is amazing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ConarCross legit thought this was a photo omg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you for all the love on this piece hfjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tayl3r_t0t Thank you !!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adrienettem AHHH thank you ;w;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket shhhhsdhfsjk THANK YOUU, sounds like a case of pixel-ception because youuuu got me back into it hfjk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@illufinch sooo good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sylvia_FineArt @ReArtistron thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Thoof4 @ThePixelSword @Pixel_Dailies Love it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RhlPixels Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeranran thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chel_faust thank you! the lady bug is my fave part lol!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@faticorns Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chel_faust This is sooo pretty!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_lill0999 Thank you ;w;!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kianamosser I LOVE THIS AHDJKF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ohilin @ThePixelSword @JiskeyJasket so pretty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iyfias Thank you so much friend!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I reposted it! Yay!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia Thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lily of the Valley  RT appreciated!   #pixelart #pixel #art https://t.co/EczLlEO0Do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was trying to lay down and nap but instead i was just uncomfortably full ;;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@faewrites can i have advice on my life lmao]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elissinia my day has been dragging i want it to be monday already T_T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rhaeiny: [ RTs appreciated ]  opening faster style_ icon(?) chibi head (?) commissions   Price $15 USD   Open 10 slots Example and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer drink?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeafOpal: Diluc fan practice   #GenshinImpact  #diluc #fanart https://t.co/hlQ7zhMqdT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeafOpal: Face improvement, I did get lazy on Diluc's hair tho lolol https://t.co/fwJs6jNrow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeafOpal: Chill Tuesday ( Gonna try an post a video of painting this piece, too!) #art #artstudies https://t.co/IMzJW4oxdl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeafOpal: Please check out my timelapse of my painting study! https://t.co/3vK0ghoZaX  #art]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want y'all to know, even though I'm on vacation. I'm not  https://t.co/23QLN0Gd2F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia yes i got told that saturday are ded times. I'll reupload soon !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I deleted the pixel post to upload on a better time ;w;&lt;3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@qalomena AHHH im so glad? That was my goal ;w;. I wanted it to convey sense of secrecy and magic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia ahhh IF ONLY. I'd love to do really complex animations. Animation feels like math to me. Extreme confusing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@raspberrrrri Thank you friend, it means a lot!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Melon__Milky Thank you! I'm really proud of it lol!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia This is my first time LOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Johdaa_ I LOVE THIS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia totally agree. i thought id make a killer doing lil' kid portraits. it's taken me over 6 months to get through this kid's portrait. im literally fucking dying. i hate drawing little kids, i have found out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket Not sure if it's just me, but like you say that and here I am, in my own head about my own perceptions about my skill. I think that's what your thread is about,too. When you hear external opinions on it, it's so pleasantly surprising you're like " whhhatt!"?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket JKDHSYDFHSJ. Whenever you say that I'm always like lowkey like whaaat I'm an inspiration? fjsdhfjd Your pixel work is inspiring me to get back into pixelart. Seriously. I'm so excited to commission you! It's funny you say that because (1/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Art became something heavy to lean on this past year, so I feel as though it's become more personal. Opening for commissions is difficult, because I am seeking to gain a positive emotional outcome from my art.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A lot of my old work had an eldritch, old gorey feel to it. I'm trying to lean into more pretty gothic skeletony style. Right now I'm kind of in a fantasy fluff kind of style that's more cutesy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funny thing, I used to be a horror-themed gore artist. I wanted to be like junji ito! Now im like. I wanna draw flowers, lol.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charmrage your my favorite artist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket @eagersprout I like your encouragement. I've been down in the dumps, mostly from work, so art is a hard rock for me. I like it as a journal but I also like visibility. And I have no idea where I lie in art now XD.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@qalomena @duchessdynamic In love with your work. Memerized by how fast you whip up these babies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charmrage @GeekiestGeeker GOD THIS IS GOOD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GlorTheStar @01impai I love it!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JiskeyJasket jfhsjhdfj thank you! The goal is building up a visual reference in my head to draw creatively again loool I appreciate the kind words ;;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sk3ll2 love this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Franrekk in love]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Art practice. Practicing painting heads.  #RT is always welcome!  #art #ArtistOnTwitter https://t.co/VKxGcA6aLz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IDK BUT TWITCH KICKED ME OFF. WERE BACK ONLINE THO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rosenfrills Thank you ;w;!!! It means a lot, you're like sempai levels of artwork fhsdj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Prettyflowerdog tHANK YOU ;w;. That's the goal... hopefully haha! I used to make tons of OC work, I deleted my tumblr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@qalomena @orlais Your work is always gorgeous and inspiring!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurelings hjhfskjhfdskj THAT MEAANS A LOT! I want to get  back into pixels so badly lol. I just have been a blorb about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zeranran Thank you friend ;w;. It is most appreciated!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iyfias !!!! this is a game changer!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia Thank you ;w;! I love naunced expression, it makes me happy you think so!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossy_dahlia lmaooo NOOO it wasnt anyone, just a lot of work]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FarrenDustfur I JUST FEEL INDEBTED FROM ALL THOSE YEARS OF DEALING WITH LITTLE KID ME!! thank you ;w;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@necrotancer Dang this is good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissHalSimon1 Thank you ;w;. I would love to make some cottage and farmcore styled work!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iyfias I appreciate it! I miss painting. If only i had eight arms and two brains to draw.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iyfias ahhhh thank you. i love your work too!!! I knew the name was familair but I couldnt place it. I love pixel work and want to return to it, but the twitter resolution is discouraging haha.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol today was a confidence blow at work, I'm feeling crummy. Can y'all tell me what you like about my art and what you prefer to see from me? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@qarosyqarosy @Shinkushika_ @Nemukuma_ Wow this is, LOVELY, I love this and I hope more people see it and gives it the love it deserves!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FF_XIV_EN @Mrhappy1227 @spofiee @Larryzaur @AnonyMooseXIV WOAH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theposearchives: New poses! We took some more expressions the other day, weirdly enough I find these a little difficult to do, my rang]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeafOpal: Stolen from @qalomena  Give me some prompts dawg! https://t.co/QHKrRGxAcR]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>