<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@RonFilipkowski @RepNearman should step down now!  The @GOP never rallies to get rid of the disgraced members, they continue to be the enablers of bad behavior!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreeCandy4_4 @ThatKevinSmith @BrianCOHalloran I have the high ground!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeredthSalenger My hair wasnt long, it was BIG!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreeCandy4_4 @ThatKevinSmith @BrianCOHalloran The red one always falls the same.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreeCandy4_4 @ThatKevinSmith @BrianCOHalloran Boring conversation anyway. Luke! Were going to have company!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreeCandy4_4 @ThatKevinSmith @BrianCOHalloran He maybe small, but hes mighty! Thats Shakespeare, boys!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreeCandy4_4 @ThatKevinSmith @BrianCOHalloran Badges? We dont need no sticking badges!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreeCandy4_4 @ThatKevinSmith @BrianCOHalloran Fill your hands, you son of a bitch!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess who?  #QueensGambit https://t.co/dEf0HRWtCZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House Flippers are assholes!! There, I said it!! Stop with the house flipping!!  #HouseFlippers #HouseFlipping]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newbeverly I would still wear a Fn mask no matter what!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you. We had to put him down today. Hes been a constant member in our household for 15-years. Everything he loved had been a struggle in the last 2-months. He didnt even want to roll on the lawn. Im glad our kids were able to be with him in the last monuments. https://t.co/YX3QjIy03G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJDMaru I got my shots and Im still gunna wear my mask everywhere for a good long while!  Im going to wear my facial tan-lines like a badge of honor!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RexChapman: Have watched this at least 30-times in full. Its simply perfect...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady I stopped watching him when he said that fat shaming should be brought back.  Theres nothing liberal about being a bully.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stevefeather3 @RexChapman Its possible and after looking it up, it happened more than once!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RexChapman: How to deal with car jackers... https://t.co/qNHoB7THtw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Plaidstallions When my son was a toddler he mashed buttons on the wrong remote and it somehow lucked the TV.  It took months to find the right combination to unlock it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TitsMcG10613254 But they previous owners stiffed people out of their severance pay.  Cant reopen without paying them out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im not getting that many reads this month.  Come on, who doesnt want to read a comic about topless mermaids? #AdultComics #NudeTeens #CreepyUncleSebastian #picoftheday #Love #nudes #sexy #seduction #18andOver https://t.co/IV4vLBRqsC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Joepcro @annielkozak Its a little more $ than that and benefits (free lunch).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@annielkozak I had a very hard time getting a position filled during Covid. People are scared to get back to work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CousinBarnabas @TikiAmbassador Derek Smalls and the Dominoes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TikiAmbassador I missed the first airings, but found them on YouTube!  John Lithgow as Yoda?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My stupid dog, Jasper is dying of stupid cancer. https://t.co/rIgYXL98N9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@parentdaniel @ArchieComics @CW_Riverdale @sabrinanetflix I always thought that Jughead was the love child of Miss Grundy and Mr. Weatherbee! https://t.co/Xlfqqq7Wg1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@parentdaniel @ArchieComics @CW_Riverdale @sabrinanetflix I have been asked if I would do a comic about Covid. I said, what would be funny about that?! #CreepyUncleSebastian]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@parentdaniel @ArchieComics @CW_Riverdale @sabrinanetflix Thanks for the preview!  Looking forward to the full story!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItCameFromBlog I had this poster in my room in 1979!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TikiAmbassador Annie  Poltergeist (I actually saw that once)!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson The advertisers of @FoxNews need to demand that @TuckerCarlson stop his misinformation campaign about the basics of stopping the spread of #COVID19. Boycott @SwansonDinners @damondjones @ProcterGamble @AllState @Progressive   https://t.co/DTjNSC5U73]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I realize that I have too much stuff.  I have to watch an old episode of Hoarders to feel better about myself.  I can watch that and think, Im not THAT bad!  #Hoarders #collectibles]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson @foxnation Lean on the advertisers that fund @TuckerCarlson! #DefundFoxNews Were done with misinformation and irresponsible rants! Boycott @SwansonDinners @PetSmart @AskLiberty  @AllState @Progressive  @VerizonSupport @AbbottGlobal  @GM @Carvana @noom @Novartis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have to pressure the advertisers of @FoxNews to stop the irresponsible news thats coming from @TuckerCarlson! @damondjones @ProcterGamble @AmazonHelp @KraftHeinzCo @Pfizer @BestBuySupport @PetSmart @AskLiberty  @AllState @Progressive  @VerizonSupport https://t.co/YCYvvsDZGv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DLSinque @HamillHimself I get tested every week and sometimes Ill get a nurse that acts like shes cleaning the coffee machine while swabbing my nose!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@2Texasbears @CREWcrew @FoxNews @GOP All we can do is lean on the advertisers... and #DeportRupertMurdoch #DefundFoxNews https://t.co/IL3l9an5UD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The neighbors backyard party had to stop due to rain. What-a-shame.  They had at least 40-people there. #COVIDIOTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@terance2440 7 DIFFERENT SAWS IN 1!!  How do we get along without one?!  It slices, it dices, it writes underwater!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BackintheBronze The best time to read comics!  I could get 2-comics off the 7-11 spinner rack, grab a Abba-Zaba. Hand the clerk a dollar and get change back! Kids are really missing out today!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 #AdultComics #NudeTeens #CreepyUncleSebastian #picoftheday #Love #nudes #sexy #seduction #18andOver https://t.co/SFR1aYbnIV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 #AdultComics #NudeTeens #CreepyUncleSebastian #picoftheday #Love #nudes #sexy #seduction #18andOver https://t.co/2DpnvHjrYi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew What does @FoxNews say about VP Pence taking a ski trip during Covid-19 lockdown? It cost us $757,527!! @GOP only finds the faults of others, not their own! #DefundFoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BackintheBronze ...so, Disney released the movie on DVD.  It was recalled and people rushed to buy the remaining copies to re-sell them on EBay!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Plaidstallions: PlaidStallions turns 15 today and I wanted to share a few words: https://t.co/nChlNzkRC9 https://t.co/65IgQYCpdE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@terance2440 This moment is brought to you by Tylenol.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@travisakers @TuckerCarlson Let the advertisers of @FoxNews know you will boycott their products if they dont pull their funding of hate and bigotry! #DefundFoxNews @damondjones @ProcterGamble @AmazonHelp @KraftHeinzCo @Pfizer @BestBuySupport @PetSmart @AskLiberty  @AllState @Progressive  @VerizonSupport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 Please taken down this post that encourages people to steal my work! #Piracy #Amazon @AmazonHelp @TwitterSupport @Twitter https://t.co/gqQfcVIiHk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wendimclendonco: Here's a clip of my character "Monica Rappaccini" enjoying a fun fight with @pattonoswalt's MODOK! Coming to Hulu on M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RackSpinner I think its time for Ka-Zar to enter the MCU!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skylightbooks Sorry for your loss. He looks so young in this picture.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LornaMarieDavid Swap her shoes with his shoes.  That would driver her nuts!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mikehomeseller King Kong from Universal Studios (1991?). Old Banana Breath was destroyed in a fire that was set by a security guard. https://t.co/7ER8y8tMR8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 #WizardOfOz https://t.co/e0pqN24POk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ri0mL6uvue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Venmo #AdultComics #NudeTeens #CreepyUncleSebastian #picoftheday #Love #nudes #sexy #seduction https://t.co/SFR1aYbnIV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 #AdultComics #NudeTeens #CreepyUncleSebastian #picoftheday #Love #nudes #sexy #seduction  https://t.co/s5QtRgBkzP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 https://t.co/DpYl500mK4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 #AdultComics #NudeTeens #CreepyUncleSebastian #picoftheday #Love #nudes #sexy #seduction https://t.co/l66gNuQ2c8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 #AdultComics #NudeTeens https://t.co/S78bd21jl9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJDMaru Fox News doesnt inform their viewers of the reality of the situation. #DefundFoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 https://t.co/g0UOQWPfMv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 https://t.co/m9d5xSRelA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GFE_STARZ @STARZ https://t.co/E4rHlLnCj0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 youre still not taking down this post that encourages people to steal my comics! #Piracy #copyright https://t.co/QjoHa0OMlH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJDMaru It drives my daughter crazy when I say Insta-Chat.  Yeah, I know that its not a thing, but its funny! #InstaChat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ComicsintheGA The 1980s series was awesome! I was reading the reprints at the same time the bi-weekly series was running.  We got to be introduced to Valkyrie! Wow, a full-grown bad lady falls for a teenaged boy! And she had a whip!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJDMaru Save that for your Insta-Chat profile!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 you know what a copyright infringement is, right?! #Piracy #Amazon https://t.co/bsCP1XfWPZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 youre going to get a nasty Tweet daily until you take down the link and stop promoting the theft of my work! #Piracy #CopyrightLaw https://t.co/Sa31SlZ8hP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 Copyright infringement (at times referred to as piracy) is the use of works protected by copyright law without permission for a usage where such permission is required, thereby infringing certain exclusive rights granted to the copyright holder.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 remove the post promoting the illegal download of my comics! #Piracy #Theft #copyrightinfringement @AmazonHelp https://t.co/PCKwYhDxM9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 youre taking away sales from me! @AmazonHelp needs to pressure you to remove your post! I only make a fraction of a penny per page and youre stealing that! https://t.co/Hn05RXuDgu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronMeyers Saw them on the video rental shelves, but never watched them.  I know people who saw them and they were traumatized!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 @amazon @AmazonHelp this Twitter post is promoting people to download one of my Amazon comics for free, in PDF form!  Or to pay her and not me! They are stealing my #Amazon publication!  Please have @gatatata13 cease and desist!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AJDMaru Im gunna fo-up!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RichDent thank you for the re-tweet of my E-Comic!  https://t.co/E4rHlLnCj0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres a video that I made to advertise my fanzine, Monster Menagerie Magazine #1.  https://t.co/xa9gOrCou7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LastBlockDoc: Correct.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have a new comic book out on Amazon!  #CreepyUncleSebastian The Goth Mermaids!  #AdultComics #Teen #Nudity https://t.co/6OKKpXgyWK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatatata13 Youre helping people steal MY book!  Please remove this Tweet! I only get a fraction of a penny per page and youre stealing that!  #Piracy #Theft #CopywrightIssue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please remove this Tweet! Youre helping people steal MY book! #piracy #copywriting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One of my Creepy Uncle Sebastian E-books if in the top 100 best sellers in its category!  #31 in Erotica Graphic Novels (Kindle)  #48 in Erotica Graphic Novels (Books) #AdultComics #Teen #18andOver  https://t.co/m9d5xT8Pd8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DevonESawa: https://t.co/ELLPIDjAja]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronMeyers What?! Jack co-created Captain America with Joe Simon when Stan was only 19 years-old!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jessiemaltin I shutdown my site that used to be free on Yola. It started charging me $80 a year plus $20 domain fee!  I havent found good place to go. https://t.co/5skN0225TM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whats the matter with #Texas lawmakers?! Who funds these anti-trans bills?  #LGBTQ #StopTransHate  https://t.co/aNk0ssQvhK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABC7: Elizabeth Esteban, the daughter of Mexican immigrants who work in the agriculture fields, lives in a mobile home in the Coachella]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@romajis @annielkozak Who was the tester on this game, Wile E. Coyote?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BackintheBronze I bought the 1st issue of Micronauts without knowing it was based on toys! (Tik) https://t.co/owelh5sXrg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im working on uploading my new #CreepyUncleSebastian comic! https://t.co/eyHQpTxtgJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deanetts Three out of five of those comics were struggling! I only read Nova when there was a crossover story (once).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NakenTeens #AdultComics Because you wanna read something funny!  https://t.co/cUwBrGFkwD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mmfa This is where the advertisers of @FoxNews need to realize that they are funding division, hate  misinformation. #DefundFoxNews @KraftHeinzCo @Pfizer @BestBuySupport @PetSmart @AskLiberty  @AllState @Progressive  @VerizonSupport @AbbottGlobal  @GM @Carvana @noom @Novartis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @RandPaul Youre being an irresponsible Covidiot!  #DefundFoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NPRinskeep can you please address what these rags are saying about the co-founder of BLM?  https://t.co/7oBoy1UpSX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blaksheepno1 I was in a comic book store (pre-Covid) when a guy walked with a bag of these comics. All damaged with covers loose and missing. He thought he had a gold mine.  He was as disappointed to learn he had reader comics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EntennStudio: @MONSTERPALOOZA1 https://t.co/NiZ2RJeE2e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This comic is getting some reads and the pennies are just rolling in! #TeenComics #TeenNudes #AdultComics   https://t.co/cUwBrGFkwD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BWashington6575 I have it, without the cover!  Still sounds good and when I was a kid I liked to play only the sound effects in the beginning and when the spell is read.  The storm sounds is from Disneys Chilling, Thrilling Sounds of the Haunted House record!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jessiemaltin @RockinPins @leonardmaltin I see Koko and I got to the history of the character that I read in your fathers book!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>