<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[They didnt get that phone back  #catfish #pornhub https://t.co/ejfYpo9pe0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@h0lybananas Probably both]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel bad for him but what kind of loyalty was he really expecting from somebody he met on pornhub #pornhub  #catfish #catfishmtv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He dont want her  #catfish #pornhub #mtv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DOWNundaaa Facebook is the new porn hub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KamieCrawford let me find out you a #pornhub aficionado    #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope he knows hes not getting that phone back. Its in her purse  #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh hell no  #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NevSchulman I want a phone also. Yall need my addy  #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How shorty cant afford a decent phone, but she can travel FOH #catfish #pornhub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NevSchulman @CatfishMTV  @KamieCrawford yall sending phones now #catfish #pornhub https://t.co/tCHSQRNhmN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AliciaChantel__ Just get a Google voice number, and a fake email address youll be fine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That Part #catfish https://t.co/TmiGO9VLsw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This episode is teaching a valuable life lesson. Never catch feelings for anybody you meet on pornhub #catfish #pornhub https://t.co/nwFOxNTEPY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since he didnt have good luck on pornhub, maybe he should just try only fans #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just want to know if he ever found anybody to create content #pornhub  #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just because shes married doesnt mean she wasnt the one on pornhub #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nobody used their real name on pornhub #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She definitely a catfish. #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe I need to join porn hub #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh yeah. Anytime you meet somebody on porn hub This is going to be good #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ok lets go  #catfish https://t.co/iNL7AFU9aL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont understand how people still get catfished. But Im gonna be here for it #catfish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA @PABusTerminal I used to work at the port so Ive seen them before]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CFoxyFox5 Me either]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA Yeah they try next act like mta employees]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA Yeah they do that. And thats really entrapment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA The audience be hyping it up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA People still pay to get on the train. Cause I just walk through the gate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA @bigboutya1 I dont even go to McDonalds anymore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA Yeah I hated that corner]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StaceyWeikel @Cic_Austin @AETV They all probably caved. Grandma was the worst of them all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA Is that show real or is it scripted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA They do or they wanna sell you a swipe  to get money for a fix]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA @bigboutya1 The one on Fulton  Flatbush is the worst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cic_Austin @AETV True. I kinda figured he wasnt gonna make it. He needed his fix too bad #Intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA Yeah theres a clinic but the 6 train on 125. I hate going Over there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA @bigboutya1 Thats where they go for some reason]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 The parks in NYC you liable to see anything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Damn. He just couldnt get it together. #intervention https://t.co/hrPAdedZYn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well dam. #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least he accepted the help. Thats half the battle #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA I wanna go see Maury]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont see Mike making it  #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA It really is. I work in a office not too far from there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 @EMauraA Yeah they do it right there ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 Thats crazy. But people do it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just wanna know how these addicts dont know that theyre on intervention #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is all Mike cares about  #intervention https://t.co/jdlAy5C9m9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tell Colette stop lying. She love that druggie  #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 She did]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jenjihere Canada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hes really at her house throwing rocks Like Troy did Robin  #intervention https://t.co/0zgigdCOjS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bigboutya1: #intervention those track marks are making me sick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did he really just shoot up before they did the ultrasound #intervention https://t.co/DzfSwf5b0E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA She does. Cause aint no way]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA True ive never heard it called taking out the trash]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA Theres a special place in hell for whoever did that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigboutya1 I miss Brooklyn ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did he really make her leave the baby shower because he got mad #intervention https://t.co/DlhzX0DOVY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA I wouldnt be able to take that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did she just call Mike her husband #intervention https://t.co/b3JtPUoguP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did he just walk in the house, not shower and change his clothes? #intervention https://t.co/xPWgjHJzoW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA Lord I hope he doesnt try to sell the baby for a fix  #Intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just want to know what shes gonna do when the baby comes and he starts taking the diapers etc and selling them for drugs #intervention https://t.co/vWMmcDHT78]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would never sleep with anyone who uses drugs  #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[His first baby mama is smart. She took her keys and left #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So exactly how many kids does this man have #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA I hate taking the 4/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A junkie at 12  #intervention https://t.co/VWW8Y6zqDj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EMauraA Oh I know. They do it on 125/Lexington all the time ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So she got pregnant by a bum, who uses drugs, and steals #intervention https://t.co/yYK8M1DMJz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So hes a thief and a druggie #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is he really shooting up in the park? #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And we start off this episode with this guys girlfriend pregnant and hes a druggie #intervention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time for #intervention  #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Totally disappointed in him. #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@uncagedxlibratd AE but its about to go off and #intervention is coming on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The house is still cluttered  #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really hope code enforcement tears the house down. And I hope his wife get some help #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope he doesnt have an active license as a therapist  #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Beaglerado Exactly. Hes complaining way too much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Olympia205 Sad but true]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As soon as we found out he was a therapist we knew this whole episode wasnt going to be a good #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow she just said it . They dont respect women #Hoarders https://t.co/vLyen7SDRQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I feel so bad for his wife. She cant even have a voice  #Hoarders https://t.co/A8VlPDiIOC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That Part #Hoarders #Hoarding https://t.co/NQIGcSgOTz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow So now he doesnt want them in the main house #Hoarders https://t.co/6FTL2qntVw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tim is beyond help #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoProFartfinger Probably. But I dont think the neighbors are going over there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What kind of fake ass electric vehicle is that #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Melissa76751925 Plenty of it also]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why does Tim need tools? He can barely walk #Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@waywyrd Its easy to get a replacement title]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wonder if the cleanup crew ever sells scraps to make money on the side #hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh Nah Tim is too controlling. His wife cant have a say so #hoarders https://t.co/TVLsxY38q3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hybridlib It is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Was that a typewriter  #hoarders https://t.co/DJqTRcWaie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hes going to snap when they tell him that his stuff is junk #hoarders https://t.co/l01tn5swQY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hybridlib And hes a therapist]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>