<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@GGExtensions_ Grand rising!   Im Tamrah and i make self care items. Let me help you TAKE CARE OF YOU.  -Scented candles -Relaxing bath salts -moisturizing body butters  -Natural soaps and much more  https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI #BlackOwnedBusiness #Organicskincare #smallbusinessowner https://t.co/jr9cPHez5t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grand rising!   Im Tamrah and i make self care items. Let me help you TAKE CARE OF YOU.  -Scented candles -Relaxing bath salts -moisturizing body butters  -Natural soaps and much more  https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI #BlackOwnedBusiness #Organicskincare #smallbusinessowner https://t.co/QzQbCn2QKd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grand rising yall Let today be great]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: The Gold Besties by @kasiakaringold   Yes the Butterfly anklet comes in Rose Gold as well !   https://t.co/QH5IUF1Fcm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LEssentials_: ONLY THREE AVAILABLE   Amethyst Keychains! Brings you peace, healing and positive transformation into your life!  https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HUEGIRLSZ: Good morning HueGirlsz! As you know we are transferring over to Shopify! We will have all new products and some items are NO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EnvymeC1: New Product Alert!! Come shop with Envymecosmetics and buy yourself a cute new keychain!  All keychains come with one charm a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PudJewelry: To my late night shoppers, use code MOM to get 15% off your purchase and you better hurry up. Today is the last day of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @svacity: Get you a cute bag from our 15% off sale use code "Mom"   Handbags Lipstick  Watches  Bookbags + More  https://t.co/v6Sh6Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @livenbeauty_: Happy Teacher Appreciation Week to all my teachers. I am a 4th grade teacher so I understand the hard work and struggles]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brookewrite: I see a lot of people asking what to get the moms in their life for Mother's Day.  Here's an idea:   An investment  Why]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @livenbeauty_: Hey my name is Raven and I own workout brand named LiveNBeauty. My brand represents a unity, sisterhood, and letting wome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @glossyfinney: How Ill be living in a few years  https://t.co/3jgYdPAIL6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DaebreakStudio Im Tamrah and i make self care items. Let me help you TAKE CARE OF YOU.  -Scented candles -Relaxing bath salts -moisturizing body butters  -Natural soaps and much more  https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI https://t.co/12dULgUOyO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yourvirgocrush Vanilla Dream is a classic vanilla scent that fills the room One 8oz Candle and 3 wax melt packs left  Pink Sugar is the ultimate feminine scent. It really does smell so good youll want to eat it  One 8oz candle and 2 wax melt packs left   https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI https://t.co/SB04AtTSub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @promisekaylah: Have you been looking for a self defense keychain but havent been able to find one? Look no further I got you  go shop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @visualllee: It's Tuesday so I'm writing shit down and everything as always but I have a #quickquestion...  Do you keep track of ALL you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @visualllee: NEW #YOUTUBE   NOW LIVE !! #arttutorial #howtodraw #encouragingartists   Watch "HOW TO DRAW HANDS, well one for rn [ART TU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mdrbymichelle: I still have all these pieces left from my summer collection left !  go to https://t.co/hB9Ysv2vnI right now and grab t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PixieStrmDesign Welp, you sold that well lol. I just got some roses from you do you know if you will have more of the flower mix?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MuthaLuvin: Normalize self-care ANY day of the week.   Check out our website where we have scented candles, calming bath soaks + body s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @keepingupwitnea: Who doesnt love a cute tube dress  Check out my site today and save 30% with the code mom    https://t.co/j90v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lavishLayybaby: Soooo yall know I had to start the cases off right !! Our local rapper @shutupshy1 has became a Lanyarette  https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HerbalKirby: I loved making this order  I hope my customer enjoys their new products.   https://t.co/ztvuqJx9gp https://t.co/aCDMjaY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @keepingupwitnea: New luxe shorts set is now available in sizes Small-XLarge ladies!  In the colors pink and black! Use code mom t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themeltedco: Reviews, reviews   Oh how we love reviews! https://t.co/04ljEDZrWA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tionneskin: Who loves Whipped Body Scrubs?  Very Vanilla Scrub is made with Shea Butter and is vanilla scented.   Organic Sugar is used]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @beautyandblinks: The reviews just don't lie! The new scrub formula just can't be beat. Pickup your exfoliating scrub at https://t.co/sK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tionneskin: The turmeric scrub has so many benefits and can be used on all skin types!!  Your skin will soft, smooth and moisturized af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jahlato_ My boo @kasiakaringold has all the jewelry you need ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFeedeeLife @ceebeescases Im Tamrah and i make self care items. Let me help you TAKE CARE OF YOU.  -Scented candles -Relaxing bath salts -moisturizing body butters  -Natural soaps and much more  https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI https://t.co/JYFfXVWhHT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@famekeke @theboxforlovers Im Tamrah and i make self care items. Let me help you TAKE CARE OF YOU.  -Scented candles -Relaxing bath salts -moisturizing body butters  -Natural soaps and much more  https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI #BlackOwnedBusiness #Organicskincare #smallbusinessowner https://t.co/Zl1Lm5SMuy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bonitanishaa: No dry skin this summer  have soft glowing skin with our whipped coco butter   Made with cocoa butter  shea butter to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: No flash, all Kasia Karin Gold vibes   Ive had my anklets on for months, never take them off  and my ankles are still]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanilla Dream is a classic vanilla scent that fills the room One 8oz Candle and 3 wax melt packs left  Pink Sugar is the ultimate feminine scent. It really does smell so good youll want to eat it  One 8oz candle and 2 wax melt packs left   https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI https://t.co/O06TeE2AhI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tasami Natural Whipped Body Butter  Made with Shea butter, Cocoa butter, mango butter and host of skin nutrient carrier oils. -Available in Eczema therapy -Original (non-scented  -Many different fragrances 4oz, 8oz, 32oz https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI https://t.co/2LuS7sEtXM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey Im Tamrah  Start your week by checking out my shop Filled with self care items  You can end your week using them and feeling great -Body Butters -Body Scrubs -Bath Salts -Natural soaps  more  https://t.co/MY6yBBzVgI https://t.co/R6OAUkW1qr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @koatedndripbl: MOTHERS DAY SALE EXTENDED UNTIL MAY 9th at 11:59PM MAKE SURE YOU USE MOM AT CHECKOUT TO GET 20% OFF YOUR ENTIRE ORDER]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mdrbymichelle: orders have been sent out !  Every and I do mean E V E R Y package gets love  thanks again to those who shopped ! https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lexoticccc: I  Lashes  https://t.co/lCsA3BtjkP https://t.co/OgBRZlEjs1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lexoticccc: Very good portrait , wearing envy 3D mink  https://t.co/lCsA3BtjkP https://t.co/XEe3GBO4bK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: Just got out the shower and my anklet was just glistening so I had to take a video    All anklets are from @kasiakarin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_Komm1ssioner: Weve just added 3 new additional colors in our Brand New League Tee! They are now available for purchase on our web]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1euphoricbeauty: Lets hydrate together !  Keeping your lips hydrated is a very important practice. Keep your lips soft and moisturized]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mdrbymichelle: Im doing an inventory refresh soon so Im doing a 50% off code for you all may5 for 50% off orders on top of my piece]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GGExtensions_: hi my luvs  this weeks #TikTokTuesday is presented by your favorite, @tannesiavs  she said she wanted to show the girl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @justpeachyhair: Post office run  https://t.co/jgrVlEXqAn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sochosenapparel: The ladies asked and we delivered! Our Pink  White Crop Tops are NOW AVAILABLE!  https://t.co/bkGDoRaYBB https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HUEGIRLSZ: Our New Website will be dropping soon! Make sure to subscribe to be notified!   https://t.co/6xLZDx4IDh https://t.co/BEf1ykE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mrclutch2011: Still looking for that first sale of the day. Who wants to bless me and receive some  merch from a black owned business?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themeltedco: Dont forget to enter our giveaway! You have until May 15th @ 11:59PM EST to enter  Follow the 3 simple rules posted bel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alizzeeeeee: She said buy her stuff yall  https://t.co/TD2nnDmBM4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bonitanishaa: Still have 1 of each in stock until my restock   Beard wash helps keep your beard clean from dirt/dust  helps clear up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @svacity: Ask and you shall receive Now to 05/09 use code mom to get 15% off   Handbags Lipstick  Watches  Bookbags + More  https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kdgotsol: Got my first two orders for the day, only need two more to hit my goal! So lets see !   Baby yoda says Sol-Era today shop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @justpeachyhair: Whats some products yall would like to see in the future? https://t.co/q7RybWweSN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @glossedbyjani: Have you got glossed up by GLOSSY CEO yet?? If not. Get glossed up today!! Purchase our Champagne  Gloss pretty combin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @keilanadezignz: go check out the full video here:  https://t.co/voIxd524CB https://t.co/yMq3oAdxPl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@keilanadezignz ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All orders have been sent check email for tracking numbers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Honduran_Flower: I love her products. Her brand. Her small business not going to stay small forever. I know it @1euphoricbeauty http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rvictoria_: SIM SIMMA, Who let the luxe girls out this summer! Shop swimwear this season and next with Luxe Moi  All sizes and styles a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_Komm1ssioner: I received 1 order already for the day lets see if I can get 2 more for a total of 3!  #SupportSmallBusinesses #Black]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Skinflint_ I did and shes prettythank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lavishLayybaby: Did you know??  Did you know that it only takes 5 minutes to complete one phone case? How long did you think it took to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bonitanishaa: The teaser bundle makes the perfect way to treat yourself or a loved one    Best way to try all my current body  lip c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theboxforlovers: Our box might not be for everyone, but it could be a great Mothers Day gift, grad gift, or birthday gift for someone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @justpeachyhair: ITS TUESDAY HAIR TIPS!!!   Today were learning about how to maintain our during the summer  https://t.co/pO9DAaVxbP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BlackOwnedBusinesses #bathtime #luxurylifestyle #shopsmallbusiness https://t.co/JwuomPjXI9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alizzeeeeee Completely!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Skinflint_ Now i gotta watch that show lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @glossedbyjani: In need of a gift for Mothers Day? Shop @glossedbyjani  . We have everything for a Glossy Mom  use code: GLOSSYMOM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GGExtensions_: hi my luvs.  City Girls season is approaching so feel free to have your man swipe them visas at https://t.co/zUMFDLVoZX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lavishLayybaby: I be ready for yall but dang yall follow me too on tiktok @ thelanyardlab https://t.co/hXhg6PpyrO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kdgotsol: Twitter its going down tonight at 7 pm on Instagram Live Join me along side @Nevaeh_Michelle   Gems will be dropped as alway]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @promisekaylah: So excited to be apart of my first pop up shop on May 15th 12-5 pm. Hosted by @blueswickco the link to register is in he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sis is sick of everybody shit https://t.co/sV9RRnzZ2m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: I can wear my @kasiakaringold in the shower everyday, can you do that with your gold jewelry?   https://t.co/QH5IUF1Fc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@teiana__ 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LEssentials_ Of course! Ill be back ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LEssentials_ Youre welcome boo!!! I been waiting for this drop ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kiadasavage: shop https://t.co/JrvQhEfVNJ today  we have the hottest styles and more just in time for hot girl summer!  https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: I know I post @AllieKayss a lot but thats because I loveeee these products   Its the fact that she mined the crys]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JameeChanel: Help me reach 100 followers on my styling page and enter my giveaway   https://t.co/GGml68LEy4 https://t.co/VzLVGP8UZE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ManifestItSkin: We are on IG! Follow us https://t.co/fijUKNOvGN https://t.co/EvnIfSzrjZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alizzeeeeee: At this point I think I need to increase the size of Slippery YaYa  https://t.co/Me8t2yYZOd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_Komm1ssioner: FLASH SALE  Visit our website today and youll receive 40% OFF your entire order at checkout!   *40% discount code]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: Its the branding for me   Simplicity is   https://t.co/QH5IUF1Fcm https://t.co/yMiyb0pWjX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: Yall remember those glass golden looking rings they used to sell at the flea market in the late 90s- early 2000s?   I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kayofalltrades: Pandora is getting so boring and played out   Tell that man to get you some @kasiakaringold   Each piece was handpick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @regaliacandles: Its almost here!! All candles will be restocked TOMORROW 05/05 + (2) two new scents on deck do not disturb  All vi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lavishLayybaby: Turned an old bangle onto something new  https://t.co/KqAJmFrKMK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MuthaLuvin:  just like that, our "1993" + "nude" candles are back in stock!   I had so much fun creating these magical + beautiful so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @svacity: Our handbag collection knows no end check it out   Handbags Lipstick  Watches  Bookbags + More  https://t.co/v6Sh6YlD9j  #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Otw!! https://t.co/h7TMCuPwdl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @blueswickco: We are soo excited about our Virtual Pop Up! Come out and Support May 15,2021 12-5pm EST   We have some dope black woman-o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @justpeachyhair: Have you checked out our 2.0 collection? You wont be disappointed!!   https://t.co/drlvDGHswP https://t.co/5mIoEgZ3ir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mdrbymichelle: Day 4 of 31!  Trying to get my older inventory gone before my new beads get here  shop with a small business today! I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HerbalKirby: Heres an updated map of places weve shipped to shoutout to Utah for being added to the map   https://t.co/ztvuqJx9gp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PudJewelry: The Mothers Day sale ends tomorrow at midnight! Act fast and get 15% off your purchase like on one of the newest products,]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>