<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[ Hey @DellAustralia @AlienwareOz  Trying to give you money, but your salespeople have no ability to actually sell me a desktop without the bundled monitor, mouse and keyboard.  Why can you discount a bundle, but not the desktop with the same specs by itself?  #Dell #Alienware]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Do I?   11th Gen Intel  i9  (8-Core, 16MB Cache, 3.5GHz to 5.3GHZ)   Windows 10 Home  NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3090 24GB GDDR6X  64GB Dual Channel DDR4 XMP at 3200MHz  1TB M.2 PCIe NVMe SSD (Boot) + 2TB 7200RPM SATA 6Gb/s (Storage)  CPU Liquid Cooling  1000W Power Supply]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PressStartAU Gleam is evil. Be prepared to unsubscribe to a multitude of subscriptions and give permission for Gleam to access your data.   You really need to work out another way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Photo enlargement and enhancement work is fun. Original photo 1152 x 648, enhanced 6912 x 3888 or 600%.  #photography https://t.co/jVPJPCiqAf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Hey @thaRadBrad   Wish to say thankyou for what you do, being humble and being you throughout the past decade.   I started watching your channel in May 2011, 10 YEARS, Alan Wake,  have followed ever since.   Never stop gaming.   #TheRadBrad #gaming #gameplay #walkthrough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GameSpot Well what's the point of releasing a patch then?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I'll end up buying #IndianaJones on #4K Ultra HD Bluray when they are available separately.  Only want two of the four films.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I really need to get around to watching my #StarWars #4K Ultra HD Blurays.  Bought Episodes 4, 5, 6 and Rogue One.  The good ones.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I think more people are starting to realise the negative aspects of #Retirnal's game design without one save state being available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Sure those #PS5 #Nike sneakers look cool but supply won't meet demand.  Lot of scalpers.  Might need to wait for the knockoffs to appear.  Unless @AskPlayStation @PlayStationAU could secure me one, happy to pay now for them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Sometimes I just wear #headphones or #earbuds with nothing playing to give the impression I can't hear people around me.  And for them to not be able to talk to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IGN Bad move. This is why they should have had one save state.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PressStartAU: Target Melbourne Now Has 50% Off All Games/Consoles Bringing Some Ridiculous Bargains https://t.co/9WMNrcEqXu https://t.c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ The #WWENetwork is still available in Australia as we do not have Peacock.  If it shifts from its current distribution method to piggybacking on another I'll consider unsubscribing.  #WWE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ If you're looking to download #YouTube videos which have #HDR, the best file format I have used is webm.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Just created a Take Profit order for #dogecoin. $5,000 Aud per #doge holding.   Why? Because why not.  Retirement or nothing.  Always invest what you're prepared to lose.  Never sell for a measly taxable profit.  Beyond Diamond hands. Beyond the Moon, Mars and Pluto.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ BALAN WONDERWORLD PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/i1sQzeUGcc https://t.co/G456twcgHi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Pac-Man Championship Edition 2 - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/b22zBopyHp https://t.co/b77mbqtw6h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ CAPTAIN TSUBASA RISE OF NEW CHAMPIONS PS5 gameplay walkthrough 4K 60fps PlayStation 5   https://t.co/2Jet1X0WJM https://t.co/xpIhtHkLmh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ LUMO PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/XOLPqk0Lx3 https://t.co/NnNwvd6Z0s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Tricky Towers - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/XPrRpHH07p https://t.co/0i2C0awWvh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ DESPERADOS III PS5 gameplay walkthrough 4K 60fps PlayStation 5   https://t.co/154KX5bZwa https://t.co/kIIA4PgrtF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Rogue Aces - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/1gqx0XK8zq https://t.co/xTF5qr0VOY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale MISSION IMPOSSIBLE comparison 60fps   https://t.co/kgw7jxqfew https://t.co/JPoJVJZzDn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale DARIA comparison 60fps   https://t.co/bo4GZ0o91X https://t.co/1FmxXJZQBy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale TINY TOON ADVENTURES HOW I SPENT MY VACATION comparison 60fps   https://t.co/N5pkWLtrei https://t.co/FyEyQOiKgc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Vince Mcmahon needs to step down and retire from the #WWE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ The more I see of #Returnal, the more I'm happy to wait for the price drop, or even when it comes to PS Plus.  No hurry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I like Ni No Kuni II Revenant Kingdom but I just don't think I can be bothered continuing now with this gather citizens and upgrade your kingdom part.  It just has halted the game and my momentum completely.  Decisions decisions.  #NiNoKuni #NiNoKuniII]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ The sound in #Returnal is amazing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale WHERE IN THE WORLD IS CARMEN SANDIEGO Introduction 60fps   https://t.co/ItQTdS88Yz https://t.co/aWlBrG8GAo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ And Ni No Kuni II Revenant Kingdom was going so well.  Up to this level up your kingdom BS which has halted the momentum of the game completely.  What were they thinking?  #NiNoKuni #NiNoKuniII]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlayStationAU Downloading now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale BATTLE ANGEL ALITA Battle scene 2 60fps   https://t.co/GqGUjdbQ4s https://t.co/ZgHNQGrgqh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IGN What about Devil Dice remastered by @bluepointgames   *wink*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale BATTLE ANGEL ALITA Battle scene 1 60fps   https://t.co/OwWtIiuMVT https://t.co/SSz4jzZ91g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gajulasatwik3 Correct. But i'd rather leave the investment to rot or go to Nil, than sell without this goal reached.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ The truth is, I need #Dogecoin to get to $3,000 AU so I can retire.   In addition to this, it would be awesome to see it reach that amount for the hell of it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Who's a good boy? You are! Oh yes you are.  Good doggy!   #Dogecoin https://t.co/4kCULW3gCo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Did someone give #Dogecoin Viagra or something?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PressStartAU: Bargain Guide  Resident Evil Village https://t.co/ml2L7h3jUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JcsCommentary Death by golf ball in the back of the head.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale BATTLE ANGEL ALITA comparison 60fps   https://t.co/L9R5fJ2oCK https://t.co/TOSsMfzU98]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PressStartAU https://t.co/qw1lRJCiLA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@foxygames_uk I find it the same, even without a Gamepass like service, Australia doesn't have PlayStation Now, I'm gaming more on the PS5 than the Series X which is played on travel, visiting friends etc as it's easier to transport due to the form factor.  I only have Gamepass with the X.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @verge: Microsoft adds FPS Boost to 74 more games on Xbox Series X / S https://t.co/g4VOfgEETT https://t.co/Bv0670Gq8o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JcsCommentary I got into this crypto market a few weeks back. Invested in Dogecoin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Meh https://t.co/mx5BqEMNsN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Tools Up - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/TL68tk2da7 https://t.co/yM9Bqkb6fW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Flower - Part 1 - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/lhFE031p6P https://t.co/NvVl6GxQPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Bound - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/nXE8lCd4Bf https://t.co/9NIpLQ3XGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ STAWWHAL PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/5jsU6Hw8vJ https://t.co/YKJ2Zi8hZU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Q Bert Rebooted - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/fzsPmINZaB https://t.co/T0eWPQh8jz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Laser League - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/ds5VtnZtLa https://t.co/EQuIEaejvz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Apotheon - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/SSVlKGU4J9 https://t.co/ALaEeV9DeR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Horizon Chase Turbo - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/jQOJUWp69r https://t.co/JtW7ZnWSMc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ TETRIS EFFECT PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5) Part 1   https://t.co/hY4JljpLGT https://t.co/CZkkXs3pRF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ JUDGMENT PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5) Part 1   https://t.co/UAFLOSVBYv https://t.co/iukfnMdyLI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Now you see me, now you don't. https://t.co/wltukJaBMy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Six https://t.co/lyacGvEntf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #TheSimpsons went downhill after Season 6.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Apart from the opening sequence, Kano, and the Sub Zero V Scorpion fight, #MortalKombat (2021) was a let down.  Interested to see how they go with the sequel, but not hyped for it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Super Meat Boy - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/NRipoh8j9u https://t.co/JbX8G5QOnL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale SAMURAI PIZZA CATS Speedy's sword scene 60fps   https://t.co/69BdHeIcYY https://t.co/XYCkxXGzkU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @noclipvideo:  NEW DOC ALERT!   Explore the design and legacy of RollerCoaster Tycoon in the first episode of our brand new series: G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ That moment when you think the #movie you're watching is in HDR, but the TV does such a good job it's actually SDR.  Same with the occasion where you think 4K, but actually 1080p.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale SAMURAI PIZZA CATS Battle ready scene 60fps   https://t.co/5zRJCdQXpc https://t.co/wPFU5Xy9nH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #Speed on #4K Ultra HD BluRay will have a 4K DI.  Excellent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I loved the 1.33:1 aspect ratio for Zack Snyder's #JusticeLeagueSnyderCut and wish that all films which are released, or intended to be released in @IMAX, maintain this ratio for the home viewing experience.  Or at least switch to 16:9 if not possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I am making great progress with #NiNoKuni II Revenant Kingdom, but I feel I will have to hit the grind soon to level up.  Now at Chapter 6, 10 hours in.   Playing on #PS5 with stunning HDR.  Thankyou @BandaiNamcoAU @LEVEL5_IA https://t.co/OMeihBgDPa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale SAMURAI PIZZA CATS Introduction 60fps   https://t.co/9OyEnkSJoj https://t.co/INWZGFjOtj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale SAMURAI PIZZA CATS comparison 60fps   https://t.co/nOSHbekMWL https://t.co/n9pf69gnzo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES Introduction 60fps   https://t.co/tXBlvJhASW https://t.co/C9PffTTRpx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 4K upscale TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURLES comparison 60fps   https://t.co/iovh6PvPKy https://t.co/VZONGM9sTQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ 9 Monkeys of Shaolin - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/P8j9zCQtCO https://t.co/KFBxXImhlU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ NEX MACHINA PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5) Part 1   https://t.co/1vPg50doCj https://t.co/QmBO3QMEFS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ PURE POOL PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/IQrfYhfrdC https://t.co/sArSGyBCy7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Disc Jam - PS5 Gameplay Walkthrough 4K 60fps (PlayStation 5)   https://t.co/UXSQ5ARMuw https://t.co/FcyBBBjaBn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ As much as I wanted PlayStation VR 2 (#PSVR2) to be a complete wireless experience like Oculus Quest, for budget  specification efficiency it will leverage off the #PS5's hardware with a single cord.  I don't mind, the hardware will be a leap from the original.  No camera.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Don't be too fixed on acquiring a #PS5 or #XBox #SeriesX.  The #PS4 and #XBoxOneX have dropped in price (console  #games) which make for good entertainment and now a mass library of games.  Good deals still to be had.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LastStandMedia Absolutely onboard with these credentials.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlayStationAU Ni No Kuni II through the PS5.  Still clearing that PS4 backlog.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@The_CrapGamer This is all well and good, but the game needs to appeal to the mass audience also.  The technical aspects of a game is one thing, but to entertain your audience and leaving them wanting more is another.  Games dont need to be technical marvels on every occasion.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Having fun at the moment experimenting with #4K AI upscailing but wish I had a better computer to process the video faster.  There is something cool about taking a 30fps DVD video (or lower in resolution) and making it 4K 60fps.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Yes I bought #dogecoin  Yes I HODL Dogecoin  I'll only sell if it is enough for me to retire, which let's face it, is a rocket past the Moon, Mars and Pluto.  Otherwise happy to let the investment be at a loss or Nil valued.   Still, the #crypto and community is fun.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ It's been nice to #game without the need to record #gameplay  do editing for  #walkthrough #YouTube upload.   It's a more sense of calm, and not needing to feel like you need to impress.  I will keep doing #gaming videos, but may scale back to select games and not all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ So far we have had the following  #PS5 #games through #PSPlus  Oddworld Soulstorm Wreckfest Bugsnax Control Maneater Destruction AllStars Maquette  Not bad for a start.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #XboxSeriesS with #Xbox #Gamepass makes for a excellent #gaming package if you want a console for travelling or a holiday with.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ The landscape of purchasing individual #games, at launch or post, has changed dramatically with  #Xbox #Gamepass and #PlayStation #PSPlus.  I purchase games once a year now during the Boxing Day sales, the rest are through these subscriptions and my game backlog.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Those complaining about #PSPlus #games need to remember that you're paying, in Australia for example, $2.92 per game (24 games per year) at $69.95 annual subscription.  Even less when there is 25% off the cost of subscription, or when three games are available per month.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @digitalfoundry: Genshin Impact received a native PS5 update this week, and here's @cataferal to tell us all about it, along with PS4 Pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Hi @Housemarque  I get the #gameplay mechanic of #Returnal, wouldn't change it, but you need to introduce availability of one save state.  Make the game better for the player, give them the option.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Don't forget to add #OddworldSoulstorm to your #PSPlus library, and #Wreckfest next month, through the #PlayStation site even if you do not have a #PS5 yet.  By adding to the library it will become available for download when you do get a #PlayStation5.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlayStationAU Bit worried here. GTA V is in the three spot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IGN Hope so, season three just didn't feel like CastleVania.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IGN Yeh F that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@foxygames_uk I'm just so HDR right now for it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@foxygames_uk It Just Looks So Good  And this is early PS5 days]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlayStation Serious Adrift vibes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IGN Oscar winning performance]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>