<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@sjhogg Hello Stephen, thanks for getting in touch.  We really appreciate you thinking of us, but to minimise the risk of introducing new disease or pests, were unable to accept tree or plant donations. Thank you for your support.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmilyPrevCons Thanks so much for your kind donation, Emily.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Katied_25 ...We really appreciate your feedback and have passed this along to our membership team, thanks. (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Katied_25 Hi Katie, our Supporter Services team will be happy to help you with a replacement car sticker, if you give them a call on 0344 800 1895 or drop them an email to enquiries@nationaltrust.org.uk... (1/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ValePrendergast @TheTreeCouncil @lewishamledger @charityleather @LSFederation Very talented indeed, thanks so much for sharing for #BlossomWatch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carmelpilgrim Thanks so much for sharing, Johan.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fullynuking Wow, what a feast for the senses. We can almost smell them just thinking about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Georgina_Dot_ Wow, sounds like you had an action-packed weekend. It's great to hear you're making the most of your membership too - thanks for helping us care for these special places by being a member.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JGPhotography25 @peakdistrict @vpdd @PeakDistrictUK @OPOTY @OutdoorPhotoMag What a lovely, peaceful scene. Thanks for sharing with us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rumwellfarmshop What a treat to see, thanks for sharing for #BlossomWatch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@live4sights @journiesofalife @Maritelcostales @HarryWatson63 @napapattours @CharlesMcCool @twobytheworld @travelingmitch @carpediemeire @Giselleinmotion @suzytheexplorer @live4sights Thanks for the shout out, we never get tired of these sea views.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Posyfish Fantastic, we're so pleased you've felt the positive effects of nature too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lee36Simmons We're available any time to taste test for you of course...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bethiatld @WhiteHorseDC @activeoxon @OxfordshireMind @BBOWT @WildlifeTrusts @WildOxfordshire @CPREOxfordshire We're delighted to see you're making the most of the spring sunshine on your walks, Bethia. Lovely photos, thanks for sharing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GearingIan Beautiful, we hope the bluebells help to brighten your day too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tjp_tim You might like to find out more about the history of Powis Castle on our website here: https://t.co/m0z1rIAd00]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BhavneetaP @gbalmy We're so pleased to hear it. We hope the fresh sea air left you feeling invigorated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fredajg Looks like you have a brilliant day to enjoy them with, what an uplifting display.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BristolFreegle Stunning - we can almost smell it from here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AliceCPoole We can see why. Have you got a favourite place to enjoy bluebells in, Alice?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZGYoungZena Isn't it always the case - whenever you prepare for rain, the sun comes out.  We hope you have a great walk, Zena.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fullynuking Beautiful. Did they smell as lovely as they look?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulaAdey It is indeed, well spotted. Have you explored here many times before?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JenZead Always an uplifting sight we find.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShawnMarieH We've got some recipes you might enjoy in that case: https://t.co/adBgoLlc5R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrTimDunn We're glad you found it a peaceful place for a stroll, Tim. A bit of fresh air, open space and nature can be such a pick-me-up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kirstincalgary @Lougheedhouse Aw thanks, we're blushing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Georgina_Dot_ @UNESCO @EnglishHeritage Sounds like a cracking weekend, Georgina. What were some of your highlights?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JanBishopSocial @ntstourhead Good timing. What was the highlight of Stourhead for you, Jan?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GrahamClowes3 A flavour pairing made in heaven: https://t.co/hGLbFcMasS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SophiaBIR Why not have the best of both: https://t.co/2xxB4ox9Tu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Goochoid We don't suppose there's any leftover for us?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndrewarthaPat We bet it's delicious. The perfect accompaniment to these perhaps: https://t.co/hGLbFcMasS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jenxy5 Sounds like this recipe is for you: https://t.co/2xxB4ox9Tu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@song_title How about a rhubarb and orange cake? https://t.co/wZA47deUQI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julescoxphoto @OlympusUK @julescoxphoto Gorgeous photo, Jules, thanks for sharing. Nature never fails to amaze us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rhsgill Now that sounds yummy. You might also enjoy this tasty recipe from our team at Longshaw: https://t.co/wZA47deUQI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dazed1984 How about apple and rhubarb? https://t.co/2xxB4ox9Tu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lee36Simmons We probably shouldn't show you this recipe then: https://t.co/hGLbFcMasS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neil_hhb Home grown rhubarb always tastes the best. If you're ever looking for some recipes, perhaps we can help: https://t.co/hGLbFcMasS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@redhed108 Simply delicious. How about something a little different for your next rhubarb haul: https://t.co/hGLbFcMasS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jondalladay We've got just the recipe for you in that case: https://t.co/2xxB4ox9Tu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@phonetic_planet Absolutely! Sounds like we have some recipes you might enjoy: https://t.co/adBgoLlc5R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KrustyAIG Sounds scrummy, we'd gladly help with any that's leftover...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Posyfish A sight that never fails to amaze us each spring too. Did the bluebells help to brighten your day, James?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nige04060510 @wildeastdevon @Nige04060510 Lovely photo, Nige. We hope you found it a calming stroll in nature.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GuyPThomas22 @sgbart @GuyPThomas22  Hello Guy, we're sorry to hear this. We still have availability for Polesden Lacey, Hatchlands and Petworth this week, if you'd like to book a visit. We look forward to welcoming you back soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GuyPThomas22 @GuyPThomas22 Hello Guy, we're sorry to hear this. We still have availability for Polesden Lacey, Hatchlands and Petworth this week, if you'd like to book a visit. We look forward to welcoming you back soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kensturman Sounds like you know your stuff, it may well have been used for this too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlanEdwards43 No arguments here. Did you find it a relaxing stroll through the spring blooms, Alan?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackiHicks @NTTrelissick It is indeed, though we've had reports of wisteria blooming already at places like Ham House. Won't be long before we see the full display.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajjistralPark What a cheerful flower, thanks for sharing for #BlossomWatch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarahfhfinder Oh dear, we'll make sure to have words with those geese.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jaques132 @lakedistrictnpa @Ullswater_info @countrywalking @VisitEden We're so pleased you enjoy it here, Geoff. We find there's something a bit magical about a waterfall.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JanetV_Hooper Hello Janet, thanks for confirming. There should be a phone number on the sign that people can call to pay for parking. We hope this helps, thanks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@apd32 @CarenzaLewis @ntstourhead Ah very sensible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DamionTaylor @ormondroyd Hello Jon, were a non-political, independent charity which exists to look after places for everyone for ever. Find out more info here: https://t.co/dgqjw7t4Ah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maridvarela @ntstourhead That's great to hear, Mariana. Did you have a favourite part of Stourhead?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A sea of blue in the heart of ancient woodland is a sight that will make your heart sing. Once seen never forgotten. #EveryoneNeedsNature Photo: Andy Blackwell https://t.co/AElltDlyN9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whos already treated themselves to a double helping of rhubarb crumble this spring? https://t.co/rmZaWeTtGO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many of us have enjoyed a recent trim, but youd struggle to find such a beautiful item on a visit to the barbers. This intricate barbers bowl is cared for at Tatton Park in Cheshire. Large quantities of these bowls were shipped from China to Europe in the 18th century. https://t.co/iFEXJKe7zc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're getting little legs moving with our new baby  toddler partner, @HiPPOrganic.   Together, we'll plant trees and help you and your little ones get more from nature: https://t.co/matQPC9F15 https://t.co/6A83s7Pm7B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slowbones ...to visit within social distancing guidance and minimise disturbance to wildlife. Were currently in discussion with the local tour operators and are working together to find a solution. As soon as we have confirmed opening arrangements, we'll update our website. (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slowbones Hi Todd, thanks for getting in touch. Were really sorry to hear this. We look forward to welcoming visitors back to the Farne Islands this year and were working hard to reopen, exploring ways for people... (1/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scottaman80 Hi Scott, thanks for getting in touch. This shot is from Newark Park, in Gloucestershire.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paydaydesign We publish the pay of our Director General openly in our annual report: https://t.co/AV5wRfUyWe (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paydaydesign Hello, we follow charity sector best practice in benchmarking our senior salaries against the sectors within which we are involved and ensuring verification from an independent Senior Management Remuneration Committee. (1/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EJHarrison6 Hi, thanks for getting in touch. We release tickets every Friday for the following week, so the dates you're looking for may not be available yet. We hope this helps.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shandley10 @nationaItrust  social distancing, and frequent cleaning to maintain the safety of families using the equipment. Were unable to do this at many of our play areas, and so they remain closed. We'll open them as soon as soon as we can ensure that it is safe to do so. (3/3)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shandley10 @nationaItrust Many of our other play areas, including those with traditional play equipment and those indoors, remain closed. Our play areas are very popular, and to conform with government guidance, wed need to consider introducing booking systems to restrict numbers and maintain (2/3)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shandley10 @nationaItrust Hello,, many of our natural play areas, which are made from natural materials and are often in larger, open spaces, are now open, although we urge visitors to check property websites before visiting. (1/3)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@apd32 @CarenzaLewis @ntstourhead Uh oh. Are you planning to turn left next time or just bring wellies?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TriciaCaputo Bluebells can be quite invasive and spread if left alone. We'd allow them to flourish in some areas but try to dig them up where you really don't want them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@m13ldb Thanks very much.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndyHoldcroft @HidcoteNT Gorgeous photos, Andy. We do hope you enjoyed your visit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DebMarlowe @ntstourhead Mr Darth-y.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@m13ldb @NTmountstewart @NTRangerToby @NationalTrustNI @UlsterWildlife @RedSquirrelsUW @brsquirrel @NDRedMarten @ANDborough @NArdsChronicle Hello Lesley, thanks for sharing this great photo. We'd love to share it on our social media channels, this could include Facebook, Twitter and Instagram. Would you be happy for us to do this? We'll credit your first and last name, if youre happy for us to do so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PastorScooby @sheffieldparkNT The sound of birdsong, the calmness of the water, and blue skies. What more could you ask for?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadySG @sheffieldparkNT @southeastNT @BatemansNT @scotneycastleNT @SissinghurstNT @BodiamCastleNT Thanks so much for your support. We hope you're able to enjoy a slightly less damp visit soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DebMarlowe @ntstourhead Which character from the Star Wars universe would you like to take a walk around Stourhead with, Deb?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngelsInDisgize @ntstourhead Maybe we should come up with a big, walking robot and call it an NT-NT?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sector29 @godalmingnub We're glad to hear you enjoy your visits. Thanks for sharing your photos with us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SuziGuy We would. It's the leaf you want to avoid eating.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Parkesland That's a shame. Hundred Pound Bridge is a cracking place for a game of pooh sticks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peter4tax You're very welcome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLyddy We hope you enjoyed your visit, Mark. We're glad to see the spring colour on display.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@A_CuriousNature @BSBIbotany @wildflower_hour Our team @scotneycastleNT will be able to help you out.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CCcodes_x @SkyUK Congratulations, we hope you enjoy your prizes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrsKJCahill @LouiseMarley @ntstourhead What a coincidence. How was your visit?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dawni You certainly know your stuff and it sounds like you've been to see them for yourself?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Scarfie1 @ntstourhead Hello, thanks for your interest in becoming a member. Though we don't offer trial or six-month memberships, our pay monthly Direct Debit option might be of interest? Under 5s also get free entry to all of our places. Find out more here: https://t.co/7n7gMuqVfM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadySG @sheffieldparkNT @southeastNT Great choices. Is this somewhere you've been often?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CountryRanger1 Thanks Henry. The best control is to cover the plants with insect-proof mesh between March and April and then again in October and November when the insects are active. Don't grow alliums in the same place in subsequent years. We hope this helps.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's all the gardening tips we've got time for today. For more advice from our garden to yours, visit our website: https://t.co/zXuPwtPl5K https://t.co/HS4KecGoz3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ade https://t.co/qrLADmIf1s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UkuleleNige Absolutely not, there are only 235 days to go.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mivec1 Such a wealth of glorious colour. We hope you enjoyed your visit, Simon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peter4tax Thanks for your question, Peter. Try a loose mulch like bark chip which is easier to dislodge them from when they try to root. It makes it easier to hoe. We hope this helps.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@implausibleblog Look at the 'no dig method', that is about intensive cropping in a small space. You can see it in action in actions at places like Clumber Park and Wimpole Hall. (2/2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@implausibleblog A traditional allotment was said to feed a small family for 8 months a year. They were 300 sq yards or 250 m2. Gardening books from the 1940s and 50s really focus on self sufficiency and are worth a read. (1/2)]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>