<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#Happiness is a perfume you cannot pour on others without getting some on yourself ~ Emerson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Instead of seeing change as difficult, see it a path to becoming even better ~ #GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is not our abilities that truly define us - it is the choices we make ~ J K Rowling]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Resolve in advance to persist until you succeed, no matter what the difficulty ~ Brian Tracy #success]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Throughout the #Process of #Self #Discovery - I continued to look for ways to uncover and #Discover https://t.co/1TA1z7wbxX #GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U can only give away what you have ... If U have love, U can give it. If U don't have it, U don't have it to give ~ Leo Buscaglia LoveFest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TwitterTip Find someone who is using Twitter the way u would like 2  duplicate what they r doing #socialmedia https://t.co/3TfwQ0s225]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Learn every day: Repetitive Listening  drumming it in, will start to seep out of you https://t.co/JUGaFEZFT2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No matter wht sort of difficulties, how painful experience is, if we lose R hope, that's R real disaster ~Dalai Lama]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When the choice is to be right or to be kind, always make the choice that brings peace ~ Wayne Dyer https://t.co/KPyxrKlqBw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The biggest stars look at me w/ yr eyes.  as I luv U, the pines in the wind wants 2 sing yr name ~ Pablo Neruda #LoveFest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After every failure, we R obliged 2 strive again 4 success ~ Dean Koontz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It has been my experience that folks who have no vices have very few virtues ~ Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A man can #Succeed at almost anything for which he has unlimited #Enthusiasm ~ Charles Schwab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's those very things tht we are most afraid to do tht provide the greatest liberation  #growth for us ~Jack Canfield]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation  I AM Content https://t.co/xQ4yWZv7Jb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Need help to develop your Twitter Strategy? Get details https://t.co/3kFpznzK6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best way to #appreciate your job is to imagine yourself without one ~ Oscar Wilde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is a time to deliberate...  a time to act. Learn to recognize which is which,  act accordingly ~ Merrill Douglass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DO NOT TO SELL ANYTHING on Twitter until you have 2,000 Tweets  Followers https://t.co/BGbqclGM0Z #GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Failure will never overtake you if your #determination to succeed is strong enough ~ Og Mandino]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cherish your vision  your dreams as they are the children of your soul; the blueprints of your ultimate achievements ~ Napoleon Hill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The more successful U R, the more mistakes U will make. Ppl who don't do anything, don't make mistakes ~ Robert Anthony #success]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TwitterTip People you should follow are the ones who are retweeted https://t.co/jmG7bGQhbN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation BREAK some RULES  If I'd Observed All the Rules I'd Never Have Got Anywhere https://t.co/130OyXzupa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Create a #vision of who you want to be  then live into that picture as if it were already true ~ Arnold Schwarzenegger]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To attract Twitter followers, help your followers achieve their goals https://t.co/wi0JdZnHzG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Friendship is always a sweet responsibility, never an opportunity ~ Khalil Gibran]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thr R many fantasies that many wld of nevr thought wld of become reality, but in time they have - I don't judge those thoughts ~ #GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Never give up on a dream just b/c of the time it will take to accomplish it. The time will pass anyway ~ Earl Nightingale]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patience is a most necessary qualification 4 business; many a man would rather U hear his story than granted his request ~ Lord Chesterfield]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you want more get value, give more give value ~  Wallace D Wattles]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you learn from defeat, you haven't really lost ~ Zig Ziglar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation I AM Expecting Unexpected Money  Gifts https://t.co/37Lo6Sdr6e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 #Subconscious #Thoughts that run thru yr mind it's either: "Tell me more or so what" https://t.co/xMQ2fzQNeJ #GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Growth means change  change involves risk, stepping from the known to the unknown ~ Unknown]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember networking is relationship building, keep it fun, light  informal https://t.co/i5YID6FsIG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you let pride stop you, you will hate life ~ Tim Ferriss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big pay  little responsibility are circumstances seldom found together ~ Napoleon Hill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All things chg, nothing is extinguished. There's nothing in the whole world which is permanent. Everything flows onward ~Ovid #GoWithTheFlow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The hardest arithmetic to master is that which enables us to count our blessings ~ Eric Hoffer #Gratitude]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TwitterTip  Share Software Or App Reviews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation  I AM Driven to Change Lives for the Better https://t.co/O0HhPTUAmY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StevenJosephR: Star Wars: Some Lessons From the Franchise On How To Achieve Success https://t.co/wht60paqM5  #StarWarsDay  #MayThe4thBe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Goals are like magnets. They'll attract the things that make them come true ~ Tony Robbins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @latimesent: 17 years after this stunning performance by Prince, I finally had the chance to go in and re-edit it slightly... I got rid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happiness is when what you think, what you say,  what you do are in harmony ~ Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you were not born in a healthy family dynamics, what can you do https://t.co/pAIH6airma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The royal road to a man's heart is to talk to him about the things he treasures most ~ Dale Carnegie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If I cannot do great things, I can do small things in a great way ~ Martin Luther King,Jr #MLK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People need to hear your #Story in your voice https://t.co/QMd6g18XiA GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Laws control the lesser man... Right conduct controls the greater one ~ Mark Twain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is better to remain silent  be thought a fool than to open one's mouth  remove all doubt ~ Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#LoveFest was created 2 spread love  shift consciousness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SalesTip: Work towards the achievement of your #goals every day, even if it is a small step]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Learn when there is higher Engagement activity on Twitter https://t.co/ztrP7PeJ9a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best leaders have a high Consideration Factor. They really care about their people ~ @BrianTracy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A thought, even a possibility, can shatter and transform us ~ Nietzsche]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TwitterTip Do Not ask or beg to be followed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Relaxation means releasing all concern/tension  letting the natural order of life flow thru one's being ~ Donald Curtis #GoWithTheFlow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ctrl: Control your emotions, Alt: Alter your attitude, Del: Delete negative thoughts, Smile  Reboot ~ Unknown https://t.co/muzm0kcigZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time ~ Thomas Edison]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation ~ I Love Enjoying The Outer World]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are not what we know but what we are willing to learn ~ Mary Catherine Bateson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Twitter, let your authentic personality fly https://t.co/kPqQeUiBG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Life is a series of natural and spontaneous #Changes . Don't resist them - that only creates sorrow ~ Lao-Tzu #GoWithTheFlow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take the Road to Self Discovery https://t.co/g9ML63nufl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Once you master how your own #Consciousness operates, anything can be #Desired  #Achieved ~ Deepak Chopra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Only when we give joyfully, without hesitation or thought of gain, can we truly know what love means ~ Leo Buscaglia #LoveFest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The greatest thing you'll ever learn, is just to love and be loved in return ~ Eden Ahbez https://t.co/xwbi05mlQ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's not about the #goal. Its about growing to become the person that can accomplish that goal ~ Tony Robbins MindMastery]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You have power over your mind - not outside events. Realize this,  you will find strength ~ Marcus Aurelius #MindMastery]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A #business exists to create a customer ~ Peter F Drucker #BizStructures]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A man convinced against his will Is of the same opinion still ~ Dale Carnegie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Founder of @LinktoEXPERT presents @GaryLoper w Collaboration Champion Award https://t.co/gTd5n032Ku]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All progress is precarious,  the solution of one problem brings us face to face with another problem ~ #MLK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TwitterTip Share content from your favorite business leaders, authors  celebrities https://t.co/3TfwQ0s225]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the creator had a purpose in equipping us with a neck, he surely meant us to stick it out ~ Arthur Koestler]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The main task of the spirit is to free man from his #Ego ~ Albert Einstein #Spirituality]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plant your seeds in a solid foundation https://t.co/1FyD65SaqT #GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Speed and quality are allies in the pursuit of the customer's long-term benefit ~ Eric Ries]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You never know when one act or one word of encouragement can change a life forever ~ Zig Ziglar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suffering is not good for the soul, unless it teaches you how to stop suffering. That is its purpose ~ Jane Roberts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The old saying of getting your ducks in a row seems to fit  https://t.co/dn7RYSflEC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are always getting ready to live but never living ~ Emerson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JustForToday Affirmation #YOUMatter https://t.co/HuMiftmjVx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We achieve inner health only through forgiveness -  the forgiveness not only of others but also of ourselves  ~ Joshua Liebman]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation Keep A Level Head]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perfection does not exist -- you can always do better and you can always grow ~ Les Brown]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You never get people's fuller attention than when you're #listening to them ~ Robert Brault]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Entrepreneurial #wisdom: Build your security around something that can never be taken away from you ~GaryLoper]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You never know how impactful your message will be https://t.co/aW1vtdcDeh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TwitterTip Recommend people to Follow - everyone looks for quality Tweople]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Keys To Make A Great Leader https://t.co/y31FggGZfg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#JustForToday #Affirmation  I AM Allowing Myself to Receive Love https://t.co/rVBEvrV0Al]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All I have learned, I learned from books ~ Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In our daily lives, we must see that it is not #happiness that makes us grateful, but the gratefulness that makes us happy ~ Albert Clarke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is only one time to Awaken. That time is Now ~ Buddha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Material #success may result in the accumulation of possessions; but only spiritual #success will enable you to enjoy them ~ Nido Qubein]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The man of #wisdom is never of two minds; the man of benevolence never worries; the man of courage is never afraid ~ Confucius]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>