<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[goodnight https://t.co/h4GUmGqI2y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oocthementalist: https://t.co/MxbBWUarkC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oocthementalist: https://t.co/ewrB9IbNYq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @incorrectjisbon: Lisbon *very seriously*: you need to stop doing weird things to cope with the stress. going outside might help  Jane:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @incorrectjisbon: Rigsby: how are you feeling, boss?  Lisbon: good, except for this headache that comes and goes   Jane: *enters the roo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jisbongifs: https://t.co/IgsDbhAzIy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @archivelisbon: https://t.co/OBMdLfS3S6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @archivelisbon: https://t.co/lO1xhfO2xn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rt_YourFavBands: Muse "Supermassive Black Hole"  https://t.co/aGwUXEqk23]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[stalking matts ig and the fucker hasnt posted anything in almost a month  where is he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hold up a sec i just realised bing turns 10 this july,, i- time damn flies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i wonder is bing touched or ashamed by the fact matt wrote follow me for him]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sanriobong: my bratz dolls when i got home from school https://t.co/Qe3NfGdozA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EliseDuBois99 well fair enough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[jane writing letters to lisbon in 06x09 https://t.co/abQUaZiOgl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rennbaebae: me with a 14 hour screen time average https://t.co/gTL4Id5nqg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EliseDuBois99 have fun going through my 30,9k likes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rehza_rice: He really got into it Im  https://t.co/gT4HOYZ9tW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[once again thinking about this https://t.co/Y7Ngs43nak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tl dead? finally some silence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[do some people really go through someones likes on their profiles tho? well if anyone ever goes through my likes, good fucking luck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaartFart: look at their liked tweets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i dont know what was i expecting but that was a lovely surprise tbh https://t.co/o7X9SAXHwV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CeciATL: ppl splitting up after decades of marriage is so interesting to me. i always wonder what the last straw was lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[obviously? https://t.co/VshwnLNYIP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thinking about david tennant sort of cosplaying twelfth doctor https://t.co/gUFd1iYadc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[wow well this blew up and i wasnt expecting that at all but hope yalls day is/was better having seen this cute shit https://t.co/GuCDDcPKDZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lcvefear: this entire part is SO good https://t.co/mlUHlIou0d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i love how he replied this to ida saying that neo classics devil is the things that men do. ten said fuck mens rights, as he should. https://t.co/jKMT0JVGlz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScriptDoctorWho: If they get back in touch, if you talk to Rose, just tell her... Tell her I... Oh, she knows.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nevereatpears_: #DAVIDTENNANT: im an acting chameleon https://t.co/uyu2o4iTg0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[nobody retweet or like this tweet now https://t.co/HmVjr2Nil7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fancysnaake: my god https://t.co/HYGgjuNWTg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurensmuffin_ anytime :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@txrdisparrow i think stephenie meyer once said that she cited muse as her biggest inspiration to write and even thanked muse for the inspiration in the first book at least idk ive never read it tho, just heard things as muse fan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@boilingsulphur yep hes out of the box now  honestly same. i might not play with toys anymore but i sure do love collecting toys of stuff i like. like doctor who for example]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[of course it is. i hope youre okay tho  i love you so much https://t.co/vY88gHhHBH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigchiefrinoboy i know the feeling tho ive lost so many tiny detachable parts of my toys when i was a kid lmao]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tw // food , vomit mention   apples literally make me throw up, pears fucking suck, pineapples are shit, tomatoes can go to hell for all i care https://t.co/k9lZ7BLTp2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigchiefrinoboy ITS SO FUCKING TINY AND DETACHABLE IM AFRAID ILL LOSE IT ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hes been unboxed. HE :D https://t.co/7sGYdgQmXi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tinaennvnt: david tennant as alec hardy Overwhelmed https://t.co/VrUG5hEVSw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dttimetraveler: david tennant  looking extremely hot at premieres https://t.co/v3fy3s33JU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[quality content  https://t.co/8IGpNVCa1D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hands and arms full of bitey and scratchy marks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[that dog is getting on my fucking nerves. i can never be a dog owner on my own.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@oodoneout my thoughts exactly!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we love a self aware man https://t.co/eY6f65Z1Ep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/t5JeLrSPFp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oodoneout: The magnificent beard  https://t.co/xxXUwrKfRW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i prefer him clean shaven or with a stubble but he rocks that beard look tbh https://t.co/uE8f2KyzN0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SouthTexasPansy thats fair. so am i and i got tired of seeing it on my tl. i usually try to stay away from these kind of topics though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[20 + 40 = 60 8 + 7 = 15 60 + 15 = 75 https://t.co/CR1ld9rVRS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SouthTexasPansy im sorry i didnt mean to upset but its just tiring to see that so i decided to put my two cents in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[everyone else on tl laughing at a tweet that has been tweeted by an account that has you blocked really feels like youve been left out oh well]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how many times does it have to be said? bi/pan lesbians dont fucking exist. youre either a bi/pan or a lesbian. there is no way in hell you can be both. lesbians are NOT attracted to men whereas bis and pans are. is that so fucking hard to understand?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MayomKun: Had a dream where everything is the same except ten wear crocs instead of converse sneakers https://t.co/nV6jQPxH3T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my shitty teachers didnt know how to teach me mathematics in a way i could understand so i never learned it. of course i can do plus, minus, multiple and divide calculations but thats pretty much it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CONGRATS LEIGH-ANNE  https://t.co/L5m2WYPlBC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fyi ive been diagnosed with a learning difficulty in maths by a school psychologist so like me and numbers are arch enemies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 which means it was failed https://t.co/7DPFa4HWX4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[someone make a fancam of the midnight entity (or like sky and the doctor while being possessed)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[did i just see a fucking davros fancam i-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SHOWBllZ great minds ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@futurismaddnes i know right /j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[it gives me uk time tho which is a slight shame and i dont know if it can be changed but oh well its still pretty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @saikipluto: all im saying is if i were the captain of the titanic i wouldve just gone around the iceberg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[im a fully grown adult and here we are. no regrets https://t.co/6KhO5PpucH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@upon_a_girl true lmao]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[anyways im now a time lord in hiding https://t.co/3EOSLtPQaZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@upon_a_girl its so painful honestly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the fact that the writers of twilight and 50 shades of grey were apparently inspired by muse... the fact that muse has inspired twilight and 50 shades of grey... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ManMilk2: https://t.co/b7EDhMBzxp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[im gonna take a step back from my life and focus on my twitter account]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YALL GO VOTE https://t.co/m6j3XC2q0W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YOU FUCKING HAD ME FOR A SEC https://t.co/uhb7941KUD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MochaQuokka: Finding this way too funny right now. https://t.co/cBi4XO2hmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sapphicpond this is a great idea. i support it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[now i wish i wouldve gone to sleep after the courier woke me up at around 9 am. im so fucking tired]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @artichokehartz: https://t.co/O1XsrswH7X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dwohtreptour: thinking about this https://t.co/rVv2VpDrU5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[god shes so fucking hot im gay https://t.co/Doz8XhOadJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[L = Laing, R.D. G = Giacomo Casanova B = Barty Crouch Jr. T = Tenth Doctor   so true]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[they had a lookalike doll for that scene but david said in the dw confidential that he still ended up doing most of the steps lmao https://t.co/XnVhUzsReU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[cant stop thinking about how rtd full well knowing david had a back surgery still wrote the damn scene in the end of time pt 2 where the doctor is strapped to the trolley and gets rolled down the stairs kdjskd rtd, chaotic evil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[david quite literally just sacrificed his back for doctor who basically]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this is an excerpt from an audio commentary for the next doctor with rtd and julie gardner btw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thinking about rtd admitting that he broke dt lmao https://t.co/lCsaHJNIRz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aIextalktoem: Still this https://t.co/tJd0wCHqBJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[sometimes i just remember this madman does some of his own stunts https://t.co/M7DvJl15Zc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eviIrats: i love people who sexualize old ugly men. i will never understand you but i love watching you bend those ancient bones into s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[david tennant going on his hibernations here and there https://t.co/reGLc02Rxz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@oodoneout @boilingsulphur yeah maybe but i agree, thatd be weird]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[pls i cant be the only one who noticed that ass in this pic like boiiiiii  https://t.co/AoMCNAqqsx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i miss early 2018 when i was helplessly obsessed with the greatest showman]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1kqfqTYzrK holy fuck im listening to this after a long while of not listening to it and damn hughs voice is still like honey]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[girlboss                                        malewife https://t.co/INvEczmBMD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i have no memory of this episode and im so confused https://t.co/CInnN67lR0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[may the 4th be with you i guess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[bringing this back for funsies https://t.co/F9buWy1KLf]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>