<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tedcruz: Had a great dinner tonight with President Trump at Mar-a-Lago.   Hes in great spirits! We spent the evening talking about wor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So hes in custody but no name or description  of suspect?  Must not be a White Male.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 Asian women stabbed on San Francisco street, suspect arrested, police say https://t.co/m6u5gY4Gx7 #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeneEnglish @DanScavino @tedwheeler Agreed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Private school parents pressured to become BLM activists, NYC dad says https://t.co/3MyGYVWjDw #FoxNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SebGorka: Not soon enough.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stillgray: Tucker Carlson slams the embarrassing CIA recruitment video. https://t.co/14nfZZjsGp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackBrewerBSI: Can I get every Christian influencer in America to stand with me and demand the Word of God be established as truth in o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: If minimum wage is going to be  $15 an hour that is $2400.00 a month... So why is Social Security for the elderly far be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OohFa @justininglv One of the funniest parts is telling the cop he will never be White. WTF is that?Pretty sure that was never on his list of things to accomplish with his life.  She obviously feels very inadequate to White folks. Someone better tell her she will never be White either, or thin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeneEnglish @DanScavino @tedwheeler Wasnt Antifa trying to kick Wheelers door in a couple weeks ago?  Cant you just him hiding in his closet saying over  over There is no Antifa problem.  Liberal Beta Males are a sad bunch.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanScavino @DeneEnglish @tedwheeler  This illustrates that being a White liberal requires the ability to deny facts  reality no matter the circumstance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanScavino: Travel and tourism is on firein Portland... @tedwheeler https://t.co/c9WYBDE1JA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @conservativeADG @jessuppi It seems they can. This last peaceful protest had looters walking up  down the Target isles as if they were shopping. The frantic sense of urgency is gone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave  We have a on  off button but you will never find it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LadyRedWave: Hubby sent This To Me - So Im not a man hater - just think its funny - We NEED to laugh more! Have a great day my friend]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SebGorka: A man who wanted to save America.   Not destroy it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @conservativeADG @jessuppi Thats what I meant. But if I can only loot you a Turbo Carrera S you will take it? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobGerundo: BLM releases new list of demands, including permanently banning Trump from 'all digital media platforms' https://t.co/dhE9V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @conservativeADG @jessuppi Well the next riot/looting/ peaceful protest, youre getting that Cayman for sure. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @Richard4m The 2 people sitting down are so much smarter  coherent then @JoeBiden  Dr Tablecloth. Yes Im aware that is Jimmy Carter  I stand by my statement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Wheres Joes mask? Wheres the media screaming about CDC guidelines? Hes indoors with elderly people with health issu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @conservativeADG @jessuppi Thanks for the back up... again. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@annieka77 @Breaking911 True, even pathological liars have some idea they are lying, dont they? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobGerundo @WestJournalism Seriously, How in the hell do most liberal White women look the same? Are they freakin clones? Is there some Area 51 facility where they make crazy ass liberal White women?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RobGerundo: Dem Sec State Who's Fighting AZ Audit Once Vowed to Use Her Office to Help Dems Take Over via @WestJournalism https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ToscaAusten: The odd alliance of GOP leader McCarthy and Google lobbyist and political pollster Luntz tells us all we need to know. Dis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kevinbooker99: Kevin McCarthy doesnt look too happy this morning.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SocialismSucs: First we find out he lives with @FrankLuntz, now he's in bed with China too? Wow. Not a good look, @GOPLeader. Not a goo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GuidoFawkes1976: https://t.co/v9QsW8KaMz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @conservativeADG @jessuppi Oh let me guess, the low IQ tweeter is bashing me? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Do you think she believes all the drivel she spews daily?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Breaking911: WATCH: Jen Psaki says Biden deserves credit for "improvements" at the southern border after "four years of destruction and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conservativeADG @SocialismSucs @jessuppi Not sure its me making you look bad. Pretty sure your foul mouth  lack of any education past 6th grade is doing that for ya. I read your timeline. You yap a lot but no one responds to you  you have 64 followers in nearly 3 years. Im guessing bot or imbecile. #BotBlock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Washington DC says you cant dance at a wedding but Biden just authorized 62,500 refugees to enter the US before the year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeMari81 Love how the Donkey is laughing its ass off. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeMari81: Ive laughed so hard.  I cant quit watching this. I love boxers and this is too cute...he was gone. https://t.co/gvoHEZEB1r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @A13KF2: Joe Bidens little brothers company got a 1.5 billion dollar contract, while he was VP, to build housing in Iraq. Guess how ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lalovestrump Not at all,  I dont mean the bear, I think the John Cox campaign is DOA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goodblackdude How is that show still on? So im guessing its demographic is miserable, self loathing, racist, liberal White women ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goodblackdude: Where do Whoopi Goldberg and Joy Behar get off thinking anyone actually wants to be around either of those old hags? Id]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conservativeADG @SocialismSucs @jessuppi A bit much for who? You? Thats ok, you do you. Thats what makes America great.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HellOnHeels2020 The anger,  total self loathing are sure signs of mental illness. Its like to be liberal you have to submit to a life of misery. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheReal_Hurl Oh shit thats funny. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @jessuppi Yep, even better if the crime was somehow caught on security camera as shes being robbed by a non White, non Hispanic thug. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @jessuppi I hope shes getting robbed or carjacked someday, calls the cops  I hope they drag ass getting there. Yep i said it  I mean it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SocialismSucs: @jessuppi @californiapatr2 Here's a review from one of her students at Los Angeles Southwest College. Many, many more li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jessuppi @SoBeAmerican Lets make the ungrateful, racist, grifter, thug famous.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jessuppi: Kalunda-Rae Iwamizu a.k.a. Kalunda Jenkins a.k.a. Kali Iwamizu was previously fired from her last professorship and sued by h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@APEntertainment Anyone else wish this Kardashian wannabe would just stfu  go away?  She is the Colin Kaepernick of British Royalty, not real good at it, so threw out the race card  tried to burn it to the ground.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @ganne_v @BuzzPatterson @BillFOXLA America has a problem with racism but its increasingly racism by BLM supporters. #BLMIsARacistOrganization]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SocialismSucs: @ganne_v @BuzzPatterson @BillFOXLA True. She's a vile, disgusting opportunist looking to create situations that she can]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SocialismSucs: Well, now we know this disgusting, vile jerk's name and where she works.   Doubtful she'll be canceled for her abhorr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FD1000 By National Movement she means violent thug riots, arson, looting  assaults on innocent White people correct? ....Thought so. #BLMIsATerroristOrganization]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POdPatriot Agree . There is no common ground with folks who voted for a party that hates Christians, Jews, America  kids. #liberalsaretheenemywithin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POdPatriot: Yep!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IceIggy: https://t.co/wiMD2z7hJD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrritesgood @BillFOXLA @Popehat So did George Floyd have the behavior of violent criminal thugs  previous murders of cops to thank for his treatment?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @catturd2 @GOPLeader Says he is obviously a corrupt traitor, which is shocking to no one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facts  Truth.  https://t.co/4L3kLCLOh6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmeraldRobinson: THE BIG LIE is that @Liz_Cheney is one of the leaders of the GOP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Frank Luntz is the Big Lie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs Thug culture just hates cops, has nothing to do with fear. Actually thug culture hates any type of rules or laws in general. Chicago  Baltimore are perfect examples.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SocialismSucs: Huh. Go figure. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs Shocking that a career criminal would lie to us huh? #LiarInChief #BidenCrimeFamily #bidenisnotmypresident]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SocialismSucs: Just what we all need right after not having any income for over a year. Fecking fools. #LiberalismIsTheRealPandemic #Li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TamaraBender15 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TamaraBender15: Raise your hand if you walk around unvaccinated and unmasked ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikepompeo @Ella_OC1 A business man like Trump knew this. A career criminal politician puppet like @JoeBiden ...does not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/lZ0VGBfUtM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikepompeo: If you raise energy costs, burden companies that invest in America, and reduce the ability for small businesses to take ris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeneEnglish ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeneEnglish: That little "Ah" at the end...priceless ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Thomas1774Paine: CNN Turns To Disgraced FBI Official For Legal Analysis On Rudy Giuliani. https://t.co/cKKKqTSaje]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vanssurf: Back in Bali with Karina Rozunko and her high level footwork.   Jimmy Jazz https://t.co/zVBy0h8VGi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeneEnglish Im betting the pole climber VP would.,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thejimjams: Florida Governor Ron DeSantis Eliminates Local COVID Restrictions https://t.co/OEdGCrUIAA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DeneEnglish: @TheRightMelissa Exactly. https://t.co/SWRModK5uW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRightMelissa: Malcom X: The white liberal is the most dangerous thing to the negro in the Western Hemisphere  He saw right through]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TifanyRobb10 All true  quite possible.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @CRZYRedHead2018 The entire McCain family are traitorous stains on America.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WayneDupreeShow: "Cindy McCain is shaking in her commie boots over the AZ audit..." - Missy Crane    https://t.co/fcg76nphhs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brithume @ChelleStafford This gal has extremely high intellect  ability to reason. Why in the hell cant we get folks like her in office? Compare her to  for brains AOC.  There is no comparison.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brithume: This is worth a listen. &gt;  https://t.co/MEqsPJ5gn7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzPatterson: Melinda Gates isnt the only one that wants Bill Gates out of their lives.   Signed, Every American]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: The mainstream media promoting Bill Gates while admonishing Joe Rogan is the reason nobody trusts journalists anymore.  H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gwynie_disco ok that made me lol!  I didnt expect anything less from you. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ella_OC1 Your right but they would most certainly be liberal. Lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant even begin to speculate what brought down the Gates marriage but its probably safe to say Bill wasnt cheating. Ladies, even with his money...would you? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TABYTCHI @FD1000 Im actually shocked that it took her this long to be over the evil little nerd. Do you think his block out the sun plan was her last straw? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TABYTCHI: Wtf do Bill and Melinda Gates even argue about? Which African nation to sterilize next?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FD1000: 100%!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JediTimbob @haveaconcern Exactly! The fact that Twitter allows that tells you everything you need to know about the White Liberal social media industry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SocialismSucs @charliekirk11 Shes so thug that she lives in a apartment but thinks the cop is jealous of her 300 series baby Benz. Haha. I bet shes leasing it for $149 per mo. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@haveaconcern @noxa_nonne Just one more reason why White liberals are the enemy of our society.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @haveaconcern: I'm going to assume this doesn't break Twitter's rules? https://t.co/DyyGEm6jNV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lavern_spicer: Kamala Harris is the worst thing to happen to female leadership since Hillary Clinton.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @my2cent95070851: #TheBigLie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Wow, and this bigmouthed, racist,  bag is a teacher? Really not surprising. This country is doomed unless we take back our education system from radical liberals. #DefundTeachersUnions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charliekirk11: Watch how disgustingly this teacher treats an LAPD officer.  This is not the type of person that should be teaching ou]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>