<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@leehoward_art Makes sense to me... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #Artist friends! Im looking for a new photoshop brush set that has a more painterly feel than my usual go-to pallet. Any recommendations out there? Thanks in advance!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MegabrainComics Thank you so much! Really appreciate the shoutout @MegabrainComics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kristinnoeline Fuck yea!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @djvoltz1701: New Star Trek art today! This piece features the USS Discovery cruising through the galaxy at high warp speeds.   I've alw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Support the amazing work of @JJLendl on this #StarWarsDay ! Hes not only talented, hes a great human. Buy great art from great humans!  https://t.co/Jfo5bobkeB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kjmclaugh @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yay @leehoward_art !  https://t.co/ARDdkjlPwQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dimauro1234Tony @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus If this happens, pictures please!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erinillustrates: Im so thrilled to be part of this amazing project for @starwars! You can actually see our artwork on your TV on @disn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marythechief: Nothing says May the 4th Be With You like shouting Klingon in a sound booth! So much fun getting back to voicing Chance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@grazkatz @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HydraTheBlue @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpychalaM @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Never say never! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Culber has it goin on for this! Werque round the clock! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattXThorn @wcruz73 @gershaphillips ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NancyAnnBarr1 @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks a ton!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kimberlyhirsh Thanks for the shoutout!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SplatterDaddy @BatlethBabe @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rvaux16 @BatlethBabe @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemabean1 @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kitkatJanebae @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you Gabi!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OGTrekker @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Haha thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StarfleetQueen1 @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus I tried tons of show looks and this worked best. Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HenInAHat1 @wcruz73 @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Haha! Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look whos strutting his way down the #StarTrekGala carpet! Its Hugh Culber (aka @wcruz73), sporting a Glam Rock meets Mycelial Network take on his medical uniform  giving us a seriously striking lewk. The doctor is in!  #StarTrek https://t.co/ps01wcF8gh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@petzilla @starwars Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpychalaM @starwars Thank you friend! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May the 4th Be With You... Today, like every year since, I celebrate our general, the amazing #CarrieFisher. I made this portrait after her passing  I cant say enough how important this woman was/is. Much love!  #StarWarsDay #StarWars #MayThe4thBeWithYou https://t.co/WjeLdYnWAe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are so excited to see this @leehoward_art ! Its stunning  #WomenMakeTrek cant wait to share your final piece!  https://t.co/3KJSnAFsNn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalstonDesign: Here's the whole collection of sleeves I made for the MCU https://t.co/hBrmVzv4TS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisEvans: As someone who grew up with a lot of VHS tapes, this is pretty cool.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ortrek @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks Rich!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TrekkieCJ I did as well! Nice acquisition!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PhilipR00889802 @TheDeniseCrosby Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheDeniseCrosby Also, Im hoping @TheDeniseCrosby  @wcruz73 save a dance for me at the Gala. Just sayin. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickScalan @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Sigh... Creative license.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is this real life?! My two favorite Trek characters/actors are courting each other based on my #StarTrekGala art project and I am LIVING for it!  https://t.co/BB8TXWdtU4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LauraRacero @neilfraser78 @PrintedinBlood Thats really gorgeous work right there!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mr_sosotris @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissAmyNelson @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Aw jeez!! That means the world coming from you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mightykungfool @mysterzip @BatlethBabe @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Im planning on doing as many as humanely possible! Thanks for enjoying them  the kind words]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mightykungfool @mysterzip @BatlethBabe @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus They sure do!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the heck kinda bug crawled up this reviewers butt? This is just a poorly assessed and mean spirited review. Shame on them. I agree with you @ThommyHutson https://t.co/y1PNSR1RFZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@summerartistart @CaptainCKCoffee Hi @summerartistart - we at #WomenMakeTrek are super sickened by the blatant theft of your art. Wed love to have you as part of our initiative if youre interested. Feel free to reach out to us! @BatlethBabe  I love your work. https://t.co/LPBfQalyF7 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow... Seriously? Care to explain @cosmicAnik22 ? Unless theres an epically good answer, you should be ashamed of yourself. https://t.co/qNHOSVb2lc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cosplayandnails @wcruz73 @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus If that happens, pictures please! Faboosh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Perfection right here. Having had some dark moments in my life, this resonates so truly. Many (including those closest to you) say they dont define others by their lower moments, but Ive experienced that a lot do. Its been eye-opening  sad to see, but one perseveres.  https://t.co/cy7SXdu72P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nikodals Thanks so much!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy belated birthday to the incredible #MichellePfeiffer! Her talents have graced us for years  we couldnt be more grateful. I dont know about you Miss Kitty, but Im feeling so much...Yummier. https://t.co/8cDPqcg2WS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wcruz73 Jeez, thats beautiful. Ive been to #PuertoRico twice and not experienced nearly enough of what it has to offer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wonderkrisp Fingers crossed! Good luck!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TK9582 What the very F is wrong w/ this country and its priorities? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Larkistin89 @floobish Sold. Ill bump it up on my list. Ive been on a Murder Show kick recently haha.   https://t.co/SqWavTm1wN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@floobish @Larkistin89 Forgive my stupid question, but this is the latest from Ronald D Moore, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neilfraser78 @cmloweART I adore this so so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Larkistin89 Oh! I want to watch this! Is it as good as I would hope?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- The villains... Ah, forget it.  - Raidens eyes...   - My brother really enjoyed it but he also had very little exposure to the game franchise outside of casually playing the new installment. (5/5)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- In a day in age where we are more aware of the role and importance of women in society, the handling of Sonya (1 of 2 featured female characters in the film) was super tone-deaf. I could go on for days about how annoyed this made me.  - Kano worked for me here. (4/5)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- I know this is an action film based on a video game, but I could not get into or root for any of the characters I was supposed to. Or in general really.   - The films action sequences were super dull for me. Its the one thing I expected to really be done right. (3/5)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[- I didnt enjoy the film much outside of the opening. It felt cinematic  like a completely different film. This was also probably my favorite action sequence in the entire run-time.  (2/5)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So I watched #MortalKombat (2021) with my brother last week  here are my thoughts. If you loved the film, rock on! Im not here to dissuade or be controversial, these are just my personal thoughts: (1/5)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@squallina Stay tuned! I have a couple male characters coming up really soon. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mysterzip @BatlethBabe @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus The point was using the insignia, not combadges, in the place of buttons.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TrekFanLV @wcruz73 Thanks Chris! I appreciate it tons! I hope to see you soon for sure. Possibly Vegas. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/Ci9iuQHSTs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wcruz73 @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks Wilson! As usual, you rock.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@trekcatcatcat @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank youuuu!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heartsib Gasp! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NancyAnnBarr1 @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thanks so much! I even added a little callback to the episode we dont speak of with her shoulder spikes . ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OGTrekker @TheDeniseCrosby @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!! So happy you enjoy it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samgilbey: Loved working with @ArrowFilmsVideo on the steelbook and slip-case covers of their forthcoming 4k release of 90s classic #Tr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look who just arrived at the #StarTrekGala! Tasha Yar (aka @TheDeniseCrosby) is rocking a glam, retro/modern military look  ready to jump into action. Thanks to everyone whos enjoying this new art project  stay tuned for more.  #StarTrek https://t.co/a2Z9jRIsFp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KellenDotCom @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus The idea was floating in my head for a bit, without the gala part. Im a big comic book fan, so that was an extra push for sure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carry on indeed! Thanks @gates_mcfadden !  https://t.co/AHreLl1Jnz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@onlyhumannature @TuvoksTricorder Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CabinCampbell Thank you! Thats very kind of you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CuriousGeek82 @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Haha! Thank you so very much. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gerardtieng @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus I have something rad planned for Kira! Stay tuned!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beverlyscrusher Thank you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fivs Aw thanks so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JJLendl: It's always tough when I want to promote my Star Trek episode designs on Twitter because I have SO MANY and can only post 4 in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heartsib Thanks so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kjmclaugh Thanks!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemabean1 @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OGTrekker @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks so much! More to come VERY soon. I have a list going already. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thanks sooo much! I appreciate it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@astersymbiont @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks a ton!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarenRobersn Haha! Thank you! I loved adding in the wide belt for the lewk!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KarenRobersn Thanks! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Babsiwuff @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus This is definitely going to be open to other artists]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NancyAnnBarr1 @ThriftyTrekkie Thanks so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThriftyTrekkie Thanks!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cosplayandnails @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Babsiwuff @gates_mcfadden @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus Thanks a ton! That means a lot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TuvoksTricorder Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome to my latest #StarTrek art project where I envision our fave Trek characters attending the intergalactic #StarTrekGala! Heres Beverly Crusher (aka @gates_mcfadden). Her look is 50s Nurse meets Dixon Hill meets Glam Couture. Stay tuned for more attendees very soon!  https://t.co/9B2JTB9pVc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #StarTrek fam, whos ready for the first arrival for my new art project, the #StarTrekGala? One of our faves has arrived early to the intergalactic fashion extravaganza! ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>