<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCUc2c: Our new episode is live! We go back to the early days and talk about the First Avenger...Captain America! Take a listen to see]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its been another one of those weeks. #DoctorWho https://t.co/wHcpirEYFZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jamesthewhovian Favourite Doctor - Thirteen  Favourite Companion - Amy Favourite Villain - Mondasian Cyberman Favourite Season - Classic: 4, New: 12]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sapphicsensate @Tardis_Ladylord @SafeSpaceDrWho @TheFansOfWho @dwfan89 @DrOho @mrsjmccrimmon @Positive_Who @WhoPositivity @PositiveWhovian @geoffcockwill That's very kind of you! And right back at you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SafeSpaceDrWho Rose!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is how I would rate each episode in series 12!!   Please remember that this is just my opinion and that opinions are not facts! #DoctorWho https://t.co/0WDm0G7Bfj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You're too kind! Thanks so much! https://t.co/NjrMcX2reT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soundsmythprod Season 7 is one of my favourites, some really fantastic eps there. Same, it has such a timeless feel about it which I love! Also when you do get round to watching again be sure not to forget the two movies!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soundsmythprod Definitely The X Files. Its one of the best shows ever made!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mrsjmccrimmon Aw, thank you so much, you are very kind!   Also if you haven't, be sure to follow @mrsjmccrimmon, they are one of the best on Twitter!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimelessOwen: "Rose, before I go, I just want to tell you, you were fantastic. Absolutely fantastic. And do you know what? So was I."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrOho @MCUc2c Oh yes, I agree with you, it is a lot of fun. I mean, when I first watched these films, the only knowledge I had was on spiderman . Just wait until you get to phase 2, that's where things really start to unfold and grow!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MCUc2c Another great podcast! I quite enjoyed Thor. It may not be my favourite, however, it does have a lot of great moments and heaps of fantastic characters. Looking forward to the next one!   Also, you don't know what the Infinity Gauntlet is? For shame ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tom_Chappy_man: NEW ARTWORK!  After many weeks work!  Here is my Third and Final Promotional Image I've produced for #KeepingFaith Ser]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCUc2c: Our new #podcast is here! This week, #mcu C2C looks back at #thor! What did we think? How much do we love Darcy? What were our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheCityOfJeff Thank you so much Jeff! That really means a lot! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GallifreysMWPod Thank you very much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThomasH90175738 @TheCityOfJeff Thank you so much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Glitter_Rock @soundsmythprod Thank you very much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I can't believe it's been a whole year since I made and posted my first two artworks! I still have a long way to go and a lot of things to learn, but I'm happy with how far I've come along in such a short amount of time! Thank you all for your support along the way! #DoctorWho https://t.co/cKxyQR3Djf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fitgeek_uk They are from here! https://t.co/DJKBFlbizr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My top 4 favourite stories of all time!  #DoctorWho https://t.co/xSVeaACb3V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarvelStudios: Happy Birthday @SimuLiu! We hope you enjoy your birthday present.  Watch the brand-new teaser trailer for Marvel Studios]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And Ive still never seen a single episode. https://t.co/a6Pbtn0t96]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MCUc2c Another great podcast! Absolutely love Iron Man 2, its fantastic from start to finish. But I do have to agree with the fact that IM3 is the best one!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCUc2c: Our new episode is here! This week we are looking at Iron Man 2! Is this a weaker entry in the MCU? Just a lot of set up and no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thepIanetskaro: hi! im doing a watchalong for my birthday on FRIDAY APRIL 16 @ 7PM BST.  itll be THE WATERS OF MARS, which is my fav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its been another one of those weeks! #DoctorWho https://t.co/t9ZdH8BaCY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MCUc2c https://t.co/pMOKnvepQB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for the tag @TheCityOfJeff   I invite four other artists to QRT four fine examples of their art! They are: @Aaroonio @arbrax @IvanArnerich @TheCyberdevil https://t.co/46hZ6eanxj https://t.co/F5yKSE148u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OneWhoniverse Thank you very much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFansOfWho This is very kind of you, thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFansOfWho: Check out Coopers brilliant art! https://t.co/JD9Yp55eUn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@timelessnoble Thank you so much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimelessOwen:  THE SEEDS OF DOOM   NEW POSTER: A pod was found in the Antarctic. The Doctor soon discovers that the pod is extraterre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tardis_monkey It's been 24 hours and im still shocked by what happened!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCUc2c: The first episode of the MCU: Corner to Corner #podcast is now live! Find us talking about Iron Man and Incredible Hulk on all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thirteenspotts Welcome! Hope you have a great time!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AManOfFilm Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntoineFruit Thank you very much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@whovianer I agree!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andy984 @whovianer Thank you so much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ben_Ripley42 Thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rytoc12 Thank you very much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jodiesTARDIS13 Happy Birthday! Hope you have a great and safe day! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["None of us know for sure what's out there. That's why we keep looking. Keep your faith. Travel hopefully. The universe'll surprise you... constantly."     Here is my complete series 11 artwork. I had a lot of fun making this and I hope you all like it! #DoctorWho https://t.co/tPStvozLkF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just a regular day on Doctor Who Twitter! #DoctorWho https://t.co/gLr2AHamxw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_cosmicangst Rose Bill or Amy Nine Thirteen and Two]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@helloobenjamin Apart from watching Rose, I remember getting upset and scared from watching The end of the world. Tbf i was like 5/6 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MCUc2c: COMING SOON! Two geeks. One universe. A brand new podcast which looks at the MCU from one corner to the other, talking about ea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today was a great day! #DoctorWho https://t.co/AYmmEKLLMK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@geoffcockwill I'd say The Grudge. I have only seen it once though because it genuinely terrified me so much that I can't even look at a picture of it lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I only speak the truth! #DoctorWho #FalconAndTheWinterSoldier https://t.co/AVF1oIXa1i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I see your bet and Ill raise you 1 million #DoctorWho https://t.co/5CLp5s7cxQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OliverStreet76 Happy Birthday! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TheFalconAndTheWinterSoldier is just: *Chefs Kiss* https://t.co/EydQUXEAHP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EyeofHarmony_ He runs the Dc films devision!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look at what the Kerblam Man delivered!!  https://t.co/voerkeX5CC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UnovaMaster Good luck man, you've got this!  syart lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @geoffcockwill: If you see this and you love this Doctor and dont want her to go, let the TL know by liking or RTing! #jodieourdoctor #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BarbaraYetaxa I'm up to The Abominable Snowmen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm having a lot of fun making my way through classic who in order for the first time. So far, these four stories are my favourite!   What are some of your favourite stories? #DoctorWho https://t.co/c7b5RstrlR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimelessOwen Captain Marvel Sea Devil Dr Fate Scarlet Witch Avatar Aang 2nd or 13th Doctor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can tell that I'm really excited about getting these sets. Especially because I already have my shelf ready for them!! #DoctorWho https://t.co/Fnd7Hwx5mp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheCityOfJeff The Ghost Monument, but it has Koquillion and The Monk!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jameswhovian Happy Birthday, hope you have a great day!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IvanArnerich: I've always been a fan of @MrJohnDorney's work for @bigfinish and one of my all time favs would have to be Requiem for th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dwfan89 Once we get that, it will be all we ever talk about!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its been a really fantastic week! #DoctorWho #TheSuicideSquad #TheFalconAndTheWinterSoldier https://t.co/0urR3CtdMr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cant believe that its been 16 years since Doctor Who landed back on our screens. Ive been here since I was 6 and Ive been travelling through time and space ever since!     Thanks for taking me on the trip of a lifetime!! #DoctorWho https://t.co/LJsgACqwyT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TeaRexTeaGenie Awesome!! I refuse to miss out on them again! Also, this may be an unpopular opinion but I actually prefer this style of packaging ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess what I just pre-ordered?!! #DoctorWho https://t.co/R2Qgdh6qfr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheCyberdevil Speaking of, I really hope that they get re-released here as well!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one loves their job more then Jodie loves playing the Doctor!! #DoctorWho https://t.co/cyeTMKCisq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Revolution of The Daleks was finally released in Australia, so that means it's time for a collection update!! #DoctorWho https://t.co/Wlm1gySWnN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am going on a Twitter break. See you all soon!! https://t.co/JHTHrjJidu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundsmythprod: "my name is Vision, and this is the story of how I died" https://t.co/EBJ3uD2dmM https://t.co/VbL8j9GJwl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is my review/thoughts on ZS Justice League! #ZackSnydersJusticeLeague #SnyderCut https://t.co/Fs2gcd9paT https://t.co/PpS8NJWiYf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundsmythprod: "By midnight tonight, this town will be pulled inside-out" https://t.co/Mo6SBBKQcT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DalekBrittney Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, the time has finally come. See you all in four hours! #ZackSnydersJusticeLeague #SnyderCut https://t.co/X5IP6BtamI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soundsmythprod Im honestly so blown away by all these. You have done a really fantastic job. I cant wait to see the next one!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundsmythprod: Wanda and Vision are about to discover what happens to alien spies https://t.co/kfqLDWUAIq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As much as i love DC comics, i really hope that i don't end up wasting 4 hours of my life watching Justice League!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundsmythprod: That's two decades down, four more to go  https://t.co/EBJ3uD2dmM https://t.co/X36OkxbtIB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Star_Chasm @okeechoBree Yeah, it really sucks that they changed it. I hope you are able to find one. I'll also keep an eye out!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Star_Chasm @okeechoBree You can still pre-order season 8 from jb-hi-fi or sanity but I'm guessing you want the UK version?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@arbrax I mean Im not 100% looking forward to it but anything has to be better then what 2017 gave us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundsmythprod: This is *extremely* silly, which in turn means it was very fun to make https://t.co/6yz924Rx9k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She is beauty, she is grace, she is timeless, she is The Doctor! #DoctorWho https://t.co/u1Bdzr5vg4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DannySorrell3 Thank you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonathan_lumb Thank you very much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Touyarokii Np, you deserve it! :) I have been good, I hope you have as well! And yes I will try to go on discord more lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Touyarokii Happy Birthday, hope you have a great day!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All of this is new to me. New faces, new worlds, new times. So if I asked really, really nicely, would you be my new best friends?    Here is part 1 of my new series 11 artwork. I hope that you all enjoy it!! #DoctorWho https://t.co/iSVqTff1Kw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soundsmythprod: On this day 50 years ago, #DoctorWho began the fight against The Claws of Axos! https://t.co/iMreRWyQax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sapphicsensate @Tardis_Ladylord @SafeSpaceDrWho @geoffcockwill @mrsjmccrimmon @jameswhovian @dwfan89 Thank you, this is so kinda of you. Its been awesome having you/everyone as a friend!!  https://t.co/chGowBuRNm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ME_Mustafa_Arts Talent!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ME_Mustafa_Arts Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1 - Photoshop 2 - Exercise 3 - Learning 4 - Cooking 5 - Music 6 - Cleaning https://t.co/RV4z16VP39]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>