<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom .@gavinnewsom cases are down because the diagnostic criteria was changed! running lower PCR cycles results in less (false) positives the shot #doesNotPreventTransmission #doesNOTCONFERIMMUNITY Its NOT a vaccine it is an experimental gene modification procedure for w/ no LIABILITY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShivversLaw: Anyone who speaks Italian that can verify the titles in this clip?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShivversLaw: Covid and the  is one big lie.   Try to find one tiny piece of evidence that proves this amazing doctor wrong. You can sp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: When guys like Klaus come out   "warn" of a possible threat, could it be that what hes really saying is "This is what we are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SharylAttkisson: I didn't know until a trip to Europe a few years back that this movement didn't start in USA.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarahsuss: Why is the CDC processing our VAERS reports in a 3 month window? No bureaucratic institution moves that slow, not even the D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#AquariusIsRising #GetItDone #FreedomOverFear #FearIsALiar #NoMasks #MasksHarm  #JustBreathe  step outside your  job description WE WILL REMOVE YOUR BOND! https://t.co/0lYD9cZKVh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TomSchuIz: Yesterday, I had a heart attack  My cardiovascular system is completely normal  healthy  But last week I took the Pfizer va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Trinity_Aus: What did he just say?  "Worrying that they're running out of ppl to be euthanized...I mean immunized"  https://t.co/5Tr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pdubdev: Texas school stayed 100% open.    No masks. No social distancing.    Saw almost zero Covid.    youve been played.   https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: This needs to happen more, for a number of reasons.https://t.co/2XxbQ4cvIZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GillianMcKeith If you wonder how the holocaust came into being, look around you! The media is sowing the seeds of #hate #division #propaganda to #dehumanize the #GreatReset is about #depopulation of all regardless of your political stripes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: This is just not acceptable......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tedcruz: The Bill of Rights is hanging in the balance. https://t.co/HHprQ4KjVO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CovidBlindWife @AstroPhoenix9 I am so sorry- this experiment on humanity is criminal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LionelMedia: Not in the narrative. Sorry.  https://t.co/U7i4oyvyMv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stephanieseneff: The problem with blood clots is not restricted to the JJ and AstraZeneca vaccines. https://t.co/UKrgub3LWF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EpochTimes: Gov. Ron DeSantishas been at the forefront of the effort to demonopolize Big Tech, said Rumble CEO @ChrisPavlovski.  #Fl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti2: DR MIKE YEADON former VP at Pfizer  https://t.co/MjMOIVBfOR https://t.co/DYgyPwvlWJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sallyKP: https://t.co/DQXbDS59P3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: Its just as easy to buy a scientist as it it to buy a politician.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BishForCongress: Did you know many of the contracts CA counties signed on the Dominion Voting Systems  subcontractors are expiring?  H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JesseKellyDC: Those dudes diving in the water to see if someone needs saving, be those dudes. America baby.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Spotted https://t.co/Lc8mqCvjxM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreitbartNews: Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) announced Sunday that she plans to introduce a resolution in the House of Representat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @avoiceforchoice: Exclusive: California sheriff overruled health official, linked mans death to #vaccine https://t.co/gTY0rpJu8C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conservative874: If you believe an unvaccinated person is a risk to a vaccinated person, then you dont really believe in vaccines do y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevinKileyCA: A new study shows regular exercise makes hospitalization or death from COVID much less likely. It's a good thing Californ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#buffaloBills can #suckit #NoVaccinePassports #NFLisDead #Bills #NFL better rethink this lunacy they will crash and burn  https://t.co/8zinJXEzgx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: Here's your chance Bills Mafia. STAY AWAY.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: BREAKING REPORT: FDA Recommends Pausing Johnson  Johnson COVID-19 Vaccine due to reports of too many blood clots...   C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @elgueroatl: People who took the Johnson  Johnson vaccine seeing the CDC stop the use of the vaccine  https://t.co/uBrMKTZcwG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @larryelder: Elder: Let's Talk About The Actual Police Numbers  https://t.co/5DobZLfZqM  #SystemicRacismBS #BrooklynCenter  #WeveGotACou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Is2021_overyet: The fact-checkers need fact-checking as much as the people they fact-check. https://t.co/JvZiLeD5Yu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EpochTimes: 4 masked intruders armed with sledge hammers barged into the @EpochTimesHK printing plant in the early hours of April 12, d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @momof3_nj: Husbands office never had a case of Covid until 2 months ago. 40 employees, all working in person since May of 2020. People]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megynkelly: Maybe shes re-thinking capitalism after all. Maybe her millions of donors are re-thinking things too. https://t.co/q3eg5oF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ErrolWebber: ArcLight Theaters is closing.  Los Angeles voters have overwhelmingly voted Democrat for the past 3 DECADES!  When you vot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IngrahamAngle: You dont say!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BillGatesBioTerrorist #billgatesisevil #karmaiscomingforhim https://t.co/FkRTHn2RIr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vaxreactions: I'm the only one who decides what passes through the boundaries of my body. No one else. Why is this concept so difficult]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HighWireTalk: "ASouth Africanvariant of theCovid virusaffects people vaccinated with the Pfizer shot more than unvaccinated people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeibtNaomi: Would you know that theres a pandemic if the media had never told you about it and the testing never started?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepThomasMassie #yikes https://t.co/2zS7pyJbVX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @med1cinewoman: The "Greater good" is a platform designed to destroy humanity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MavericTV: Flu Cases   2020 - 21 Flu Season: 1,822  2019 - 20 Flu Season: 38,000,000]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drshannonkroner: I have seen more serious Covid vaccine reactions and deaths on Twitter and FB than I have seen complications to actual]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Disneyland @DisneyParks #NoVaccinePassports excited to visit the #happiestplace once there are #nomaskmandates  and #nomedicaldiscrimination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: Good Monday morning.  This made me laugh!  https://t.co/5X25csbQ3U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: 2020: guys relax theres not gonna be a vaccine passport. Anyone saying there will be is a conspiracy theorist spreading misinf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: Airlines are racist. People of color cannot obtain IDs according to democrats, therefore its travel suppression.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepThomasMassie: https://t.co/PeTLrE8Rp3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanielKelly150: People don't wanna be forced to exercise and eat clean.  But they wanna force others to take a vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MavericTV #NoVaccine for me  #NoVaccinePassports #bodysovreign #mybodymychoice https://t.co/fDJ3CgZmOU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@united #wokeairlines your #virtuesignal is #blinding #nounitedairlines for me oh and PS #NoVaccinePassports they are #unconstitutional #medicaldiscrimination you will be sued out of business]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AniyaBakerMD1: Im a developmental behavioral pediatrician.   The CV policies of obsessive hand washing, child masking (a way to create]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GingerGano Not tested and not planning to take any type of testing #mybodymychoice #myfreedomdoesNotEndWhereYourFearBegins #bodySovreign #notesting #NoMasks #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Redefined_cool Do not get it- look up https://t.co/j47dFc5z8A for info]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crxss_righteye Did he take the vaccine?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is #childabuse https://t.co/0opL4rM6FK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidwebbshow I #WillNotComply]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MavericTV https://t.co/x5XgdfhR2m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RichardGrenell: Unbelievably scary. They think we get our freedoms from the government.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mchooyah: I dont mean to get all technical but I have the same medical degree as Bill Gates.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom @CSUBakersfield #NoVaccinePassports #nojabforme #RecallGavinNewsom #dontbeaguineapig #youaretheExperiment https://t.co/7w7mRUzlfw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepMontague: The world isnt divided by race, gender, or sexual orientation.  Its divided by the wise  fools,  fools divide themselv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: He is risen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kirstiealley: Lets wear masks for the next 40 years. Just to make sure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erinhaust: If you are vaccinated, why do you care that I am not?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JS49: https://t.co/TqOre0nOZu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @realstewpeters: Gym Owner Offers Free Membership To Non-Vaccinated  https://t.co/TyHvTOc5he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: https://t.co/hhEGY9AJBC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidwebbshow The #endofamerica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: Pass this along.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: It's go time for humanity.  We must rally together, every race, every country, every religion, to break the chains of me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: This is what they have planned for all along. They will adapt this technology into as many jabs as possible.   https://t.co/dQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MiamiHerald In other words #springbreak2021]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AstroPhoenix9 Robert are you on a new platform yet? So sorry Vimeo screwed you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dahboo7: RISE! https://t.co/VTeezTCWwr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: The dog knows wtf is up.  He goes after the brute's club.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonottibis: Today, veterans and healthcare professionals formed a human shield to protect the demonstrators in Amsterdam The Nethe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AstroPhoenix9: These men are heroes. God bless'em.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @2ndfor1st: BREAKING: Government to rename the Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System, otherwise known as VAERS, to the Vaccine Coincid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BenMitchellSong: We the people have the power. We the people can stand up for our freedoms. We the people are more connected and loving]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaFeid: HUGE Protests in many countries today, 14 in this video. Lockdowns - never again. #WorldWideFreedomRally  #WeWillALLBeThere htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@GovernorRon #weloveyou #nomandates #myfreedomdoesNOTendwhereYourFearBegins #freedom Vaccine Passports Totally off the Table in Florida https://t.co/UaJojoVQsT via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AstroPhoenix9 So disgusted! #1984 #orwellIsNow #bigtechmafia #censorship #BillGatesBioTerrorist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kathrynbarger @AVFairgrounds @KPSCALnews I understand you mean well. You and all elected officials need to listen to scientists sounding the alarms- this is going to create a disaster with asymptomatic super spreaders who have NO INNATE IMMUNE SYSTEM LEFT after being reprogrammed by #mRNA  https://t.co/eFQ9e2c1a6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYC School Inclusive Language Guide Encourages Students to Stop Saying Mom, Dad https://t.co/liMEPPumgc via @epochtimes #JesusPleaseComeSoon  they have literally #losttheirminds #goodisbadbadisgood #brainwashed #culturalmarxism #propaganda THIS IS A PRIVATE religious school]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[39-Year-Old Healthy Utah Mother Dies After Taking Second Dose of Moderna Vaccine  https://t.co/ePxBVAvAcD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Dozen Cases of Spontaneous Miscarriages, Stillbirths Occurring After COVID-19 Vaccination https://t.co/lBMD2GDz2o via @epochtimes #nocovidvaccine #depopulation #Agenda2030 #plandemic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccineForMe #nodiscrimination #nomandates #separateisnotequal https://t.co/XxvFNdTaiA https://t.co/P7m5T5OPCQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FOX26Houston: Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said he is working on a plan to remove all statewide coronavirus restrictions and will make an ann]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@repdarrellissa EVERYONE should be going back to normal life! Not just the vaccinated! These vaccines which are actually gene therapy do NOT PREVENT TRANSMISSION  do NOT PREVENT CV! #separateisnotequal #reopenamericanow #NoVaccineForMe #novaccinerequired]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kryrees: @GavinNewsom Or you could save all that money, end the lockdowns and open up businesses so everyone can get back to work... li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Voddie is suffering from heart failure- Pray  contribute if you feel so led..Voddie Baucham's Medical Expense Fund https://t.co/gN4yADoe9H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidwebbshow Globalist swamp creature criminals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Memphis surgeon dies of COVID-related illness weeks after receiving second COVID vaccine https://t.co/0EdUAm2a36  #NothingToSeeHere #NoMandates #GoodLuckWithYourVaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler I will not wear any masks  https://t.co/6u4GmWz7PM]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>