<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine day!!  Let's hear it for the amazing @NHSuk @SheffieldHosp, providing great health care that is free for all at the point of delivery and rocking this whole vaccine roll out thing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfMcCann @ILO_Research @vdoellgast @ColinFenwick2 Thank you! It won't be as lovely as in Geneva, but I'm still looking forward. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProfMcCann @ILO_Research @vdoellgast @ColinFenwick2 How exciting. It's always such an excellent conference, can't wait to see the program.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UNCEurope: Tuesday 5/4  "EU Supply Chains and Trade: Improving Worker Rights?" with panelists @GLeBaron, @__lisalechner__, @thwillow,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A very important voice in labour studies  @LayaBehbahani https://t.co/O9ezer1yw7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy #MayDay https://t.co/vZO2xgK49E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SionPhilippe: #investors  have the "incredible power to address forced labor in supply chains" but we need more from them, and "have th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SionPhilippe Thanks Philippe, and thanks for all of your support!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McCainInstitute: Public and private cooperation will be necessary to #EndTrafficking. How can this be done and what steps need to be ta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting in an hour... https://t.co/8syLnuyme5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is happening now and is excellent  https://t.co/knbWIeUheB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KieranG77 @TRF_Stories It's all been so productive and fun, and I've learned a lot from you along the way. I really hope we'll keep working together too! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New podcast from the ever-insightful @Prof_LSpence about role and importance of SMEs in #bizhumanrights. https://t.co/WDWLBIzvGl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KieranG77 @TRF_Stories You are such a force, Kieran!  You've done amazing work at TRF. Enjoy your well-deserved break and can't wait to see what you do next! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgetownKILWP: A New Social Compact for Global Supply Chains   Thurs, Apr 29  2:30pm - 4pm ET  Feat. @sarahpnewell of @WSRNetwork,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honoured to speak on a panel with @theresa_may, @senrobportman, @cindymccain  @AbramsKL at the @McCainInstitute #SedonaForum21 https://t.co/hqlA7Oj2ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lovely write up of our Re:Structure Lab brief on #HRDD from @ciw today. Thank you!   https://t.co/1cx6aRNFBx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join me, @ScottNova_WRC of @4WorkerRights, @sarahpnewell of @WSRNetwork, @RosenbaumJJ of @ILRF @GLJhub to talk A New Social Compact for Global Supply Chains.    Thursday April 29th at 2:30 EST / 19:30 BST.  Register here:  https://t.co/oo76HRwvPZ https://t.co/meYQMv7AUO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cindy0berman: Looking forward to reading this. Co-editing another #EndChildLabour2021 edition for https://t.co/tHsOrvciuj. Submissions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MPIfG_Cologne: Missed @GLeBarons #MPIfGLecture Combatting Modern Slavery: Why Labor Governance Is Failing and What We Can Do About It]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChSempere @remi_edwards @_penelopeCK @tomhunt100 @NPEjournal @SPERIshefuni ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big congrats to my PhD students @remi_edwards  @ChSempere for getting their first academic journal article (co-authored with me, @_penelopeCK  @tomhunt100) accepted in @NPEjournal  https://t.co/07vfm2lOxI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@remi_edwards @tomhunt100 @ChSempere @_penelopeCK Dream team ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChSempere @SPERIshefuni You are an RA extraordinaire! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@emilykenway Congrats Emily! Can't wait to read it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yuhline It doesn't have to be. I'm in England now and thanks to our fantastic @NHSuk, we get prescriptions for ~ $10.  Its  free for those with certain chronic conditions / low incomes. Incredibly good and efficient health care that makes the US system seem absolutely bananas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jknyman @INTPOLITSOCIO Congrats friend ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@genderCSR Love it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarciaMEugenio Of course!  I believe @UMSocSolutions is making the 20 Ideas list available.   Some highlights for me were chatting about the continuities in business dynamics of slavery over centuries, and changes since legal abolition. Our book on this is out soon. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SionPhilippe: A great opportunity to fight #ModernSlavery with @Freedom_Fund as their next Director of Programs based in London https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us  https://t.co/aXD6awe28X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sheffield, you beauty. https://t.co/RAL9QBWbNh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StanfordHumRts: We are excited about our partnership with @GLeBaron from @ShefUniPolitics and @AmbCdeBaca from @YaleGLC on the new http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WiddisRachel Thanks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TWZinger: When you're reading a policy brief like it's a church sermon... I keep saying AMEN! Can't wait to write about this...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TWZinger ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChSempere: Pour les ONG, entreprises, responsables RSE, syndicats et groupes de dfenses francophones travaillant sur les questions d'e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidlevifaur Ha! :)  And thanks for the most downloaded stats on my #RegGov articles today, David. Nice to know! I hope you are well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Re:Structure Lab launches: new collaboration between SPERI, Stanford and Yale  https://t.co/JIfAcpgygt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chloe_cranston @sarah_mount @AndreasRuhmkorf @StanfordHumRts @SPERIshefuni @AmbCdeBaca @remi_edwards @ChSempere @tomhunt100 @YaleGLC I'm so happy to hear that. Makes my day! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this new Brief, we explain why transparency laws have failed to eradicate #forcedlabour, how to ensure that #HRDD doesn't replicate these failures, and outline key components of a robust legal regime to address forced labour in global supply chains.  https://t.co/4rNQ2jjrug https://t.co/pNm89aaBHx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@profmikebarnett No, three days left]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MatPaterson @MartijnHuysmans Exactly. Ideally, even if a paper is rejected, reviews give the author(s) really valuable and constructive feedback that help them to revise for resubmission elsewhere.  But not this time... poor authors, they are being deprived of my insights! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartijnHuysmans No, I'd prefer that they pass on the insights and feedback I spent so long writing up to the authors, since they might be helpful, and also for journals not to ask for reviews that they don't need ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianosaurRex Ha! Tempting, but can't risk being blacklisted by the editors. It's a rather important one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClaraSandelind Really? Gosh. I've edited journals for years and I didn't know this was a thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worked really hard on a review for a journal. Was literally moments from uploading it. Then got an email from the journal: they don't need my review anymore bc they made their decision. Not great practice, especially when academics are so stretched amidst the pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheUrbanBeth Thank you Beth! Hope you are well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AmbCdeBaca: Interested in new ways of thinking about business models, supply chains, and value? Concerned about modern slavery in your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New from @_penelopeCK  me in @DissentMag https://t.co/HdTozDpYOJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coming up this Friday at @The_OAH's #OAH21, our panel about slavery past and present with @DainaRameyBerry  @davidwblight1 @AmbCdeBaca @Bridgette_Carr  James Robinson:   https://t.co/rvu9H5OJMd https://t.co/XhGfxMdmyf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShefUniPolitics: You can also find @GLeBaron discussing how multinational manufacturers frequently game the audit process while conduct]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShefUniPolitics: Garment workers who lost jobs in pandemic still wait for severance pay.  Prof @GLeBaron discusses the millions of doll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Academic pals: you've got a year (or so) to contribute an article to @ethicscrane, @Vivek_Soundar and co's special issue of Journal of Supply Chain Management on working conditions in #supplychains. Would love to see some business of #forcedlabour scholarship in there! https://t.co/MFTUjesfOV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I don't love these kinds of lists, BUT this one is made by the fine scholars at CBOS and includes my PhD students @remi_edwards  @ChSempere, as well as co-authors @KamPhung  @LayaBehbahani, amongst other bright PhD students, so it's gotta be good!  Congrats to all.  https://t.co/eCq9fajbVO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DViederman Thanks so much Dan!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeganhMackenzie @binadcosta Congrats @ElisabethPruegl  @binadcosta !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@swatisrivast @erinkaylockwood Couldn't make ISA this year but would love to read this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WiddisRachel Thanks so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_SimonBlack @SPERIshefuni @Stanford @Yale @YaleGLC @remi_edwards @tomhunt100 @AmbCdeBaca @davidwblight1 @AndreasRuhmkorf @HumanityUnited @Freedom_Fund Thanks Simon. Hope you are well!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmeSagiv Thank you Ame. Wouldn't have happened without you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Steve_New_ Thanks Steve! That means a lot coming from you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amolmehra Thanks Amol ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LayaBehbahani Thanks Laya ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Modern_Lockey Thanks Alan!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Announcing   Re: Structure Lab, a new collaboration between @SPERIshefuni, @Stanford  @Yale   to feed academic research into debates about how business models  supply chains can be restructured to end forced labour and promote worker rights   https://t.co/3xvnfqeSeG https://t.co/y2LWrr8aZN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes yes yes, love to see this recognition of @KieranG77's brilliant reporting and editing work on modern slavery and supply chains.  https://t.co/fIZ2EOVeMi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KieranG77 @TRF_Stories Congratulations!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DissentMag: Our Spring 2021 issue is now online!   The special section, GLOBAL ECONOMIC DISORDER, is edited by @MarkLevinson6 and Julia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Skipped ISA conference this year for a bit of RR.  Sorry to miss the great scholarship and friends, but also not sorry bc this year has been . https://t.co/EzfaeKkyW3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoyed chatting about the flawed social auditing regime  brand sourcing strategies to avoid forced labour with @petersgoodman for this @NYTimes story.   https://t.co/tcj9AyyPfx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top notch reporting by @LizziePaton for @nytimes on non-payment of worker severance pay amidst the pandemic.   I stressed that when workers "arent paid what they are owed, many are forced into taking desperate or dangerous measures to survive."   https://t.co/18mRer1pJX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cannot believe the new @DissentMag  issue featuring my article with @_penelopeCK is illustrated by one of my all-time fave artists, the extraordinary @mollycrabapple  https://t.co/vCnZ62rn1X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @4WorkerRights: Workers in apparel supply chains are facing a crisis of food insecurity. New commentary from Penelope Kyritsis, Director]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MkBlyth: And in  the Daily Outrage, how come this gets reported every year, people say it's an outrage, and then we do it again next ye]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thwillow: The @APSAtweets Political Economy section invites applications for a mentoring workshop for emerging scholars, to be held at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanPriceSeattle: Workers around the world: lost $3.7 trillion in the pandemic Billionaires around the world: gained $3.9 trillion in th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinWAlger @OUPPolitics Big congrats Justin! Fabulous news! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Woodpolitics17 Agreed!! The worst. Hope your ankle is better!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blossom running season   After an injury, string of knee surgeries, prolonged recovery, and  infinite lockdown, being able to move and enjoy spring weather again is so tremendously good.  https://t.co/c4iDaJRzM8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Congrats on the Killam Prize, @PeterDauvergne!  So hugely deserved. https://t.co/Cf2nr6ojEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mdiasabey: Bleak future for workers in Britain.   Presents an opportunity for Labour to demand that "building back better" should inclu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really excited to be part of this.  Congrats and thanks to @Joe_R_Atkinson for organising, and re-organising, amidst pandemic pressures.  https://t.co/OG6RZCnZQU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sylvia_a_fuller Jealous!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yessss  https://t.co/VS3ZmViEWT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlescho7705 Spoken like a true accounting professor ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inbox count on supply chain sustainability consultants trying to get my (free) help to transform (remove the teeth from) my research so they can sell it to corporations for big money - just surpassed 20 for this week ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YaleGLC: TODAY at NOON watch Ambassador Luis C.deBaca, Senior Fellow in Modern Slavery @YaleGLC  give testimony on Ending Exploitation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These special issues were a huge pleasure to work on over the last few years. Thanks to @RIPEJournal  @NPEjournal editors and staff, our contributors and reviewers for their hard work and support.  Here's to tackling blind spots in political economy, and beyond!  https://t.co/mAnPXWtTfB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Prof_JPSingh @JacquelineMBest @MahaRafiAtal @GKBhambra @deGoede9 @KristenHopewell @_paullangley @erinkaylockwood @MatPaterson @ElisabethPruegl @LenSeabrooke @RobbieShilliam @dmugge Thanks for your tremendous support and participation JP!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JacquelineMBest: Our *double special issue* of @npejournal  @ripejournal on #Blindspots in Political Economy is now out online as RIPE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_paullangley: 'Assets and Assetization in Financialized Capitalism' is out in print today @RIPEJournal It contributes to the fantastic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CSociologies: Check out our Colonial Global Economy unit with resources on:  What is Colonial Global Economy? - @paulrgilbert   Legacie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The book can be pre-ordered through @CambridgeUP now and will be published in May.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The book introduces the main fissures and fault-lines in the fields of #modernslavery and #humantrafficking, their intersections with labor  migration, and histories of slavery. We hope it will be of interest to academics, but also and especially to students and the public.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In it, historians  social scientists, modern slavery champions  skeptics, debate big questions like:   Do anti-slavery efforts crowd out support for migrant / labor rights?   Do they mask  naturalise racial / gender inequality?   Are uses of history accurate and appropriate?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Behold, our Yale Working Group on Modern Slavery book. Five years in the making!  @YaleGLC @CambridgeUP   https://t.co/idp7lUVwBv https://t.co/u9nBkn43hp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another excellent contribution to our @RIPEJournal Hidden Costs of CSR special issue...   @JaneLister24 @GlobalRepCentre https://t.co/O8W93YWxBR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ethicscrane: Perhaps it is no surprise that purchasing practices lead to disproportionate exploitation of black and brown people when o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hayley_stev: Pandemic burnout is rampant in academia https://t.co/zE0CGhhLHP]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>