<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFetterman: and https://t.co/gXKCJmLDQG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenn1cole Yes. The hell cycle of response tweets and articles and backlash. BYE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RIP Anita Lane, a massive part of the Birthday Party and the Bad Seeds and a queen in her own right.  https://t.co/QoxxDJFYs8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey Originals: I found a box of these in a closet. If you want one (or two+), send me your address. Id be happy to point them in your direction via USPS Media Mail gratis. Feel free to tag others as well, because theyre getting recycled otherwise.  https://t.co/WoSoli1goK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@USmayors @nanwhaley Please hear us out. @louisvillemayor was complicit in the killing of #BreonnaTaylor. We need you to #FireFischer. He is a poor representation of leadership. Please do the right thing. #BlackLivesMatter  https://t.co/yIT7gWn2Kq GREG HAS GOT TO GO!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@usmayors the city of #Louisville is asking you to #FireFischer. Thousands of call, emails,  posts have been sent. Do the right thing. #BlackLivesMatter   https://t.co/MFWCnwCu6I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nanwhaley @usmayors we need your response ASAP. What will it take for you to #FireFischer?   https://t.co/jVZCe7UFTa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rossritchell Thanks for reading (and sharing)! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Since it's apparently already been five years since Prince died, here's what I wrote in the immediate aftermath, in a haze, for @floodmagazine. Sharing because I still stand by most of it and I often need the reminders in it. https://t.co/ouhM2hiWwi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ryepastrami: Today's a good day to donate to the fund for Darnella Frazier, the teen who filmed George Floyd's death.  https://t.co/bXb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @byjoelanderson: If Daunte Wrights family is extremely lucky  and they probably wont be this is pretty much all they have to look f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bDquw0b1vE https://t.co/hXSLbInTDm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nate_Rgrs @nytimes Nate, this is so cool to see, for at least two reasons. Excellent work, and congratulations!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johncardillo I always forget that the 2nd Amendment only applies to white people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make that today. Pfizer #1 done. https://t.co/KxzPhVJrVL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cc: @marchxness https://t.co/oyfnWMpWvo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rob and I are getting vaccinated next Wednesday and I want to cry.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Eve6 Not for lack of trying (credit to Wendy O. Williams where its due) https://t.co/4QqEh8uFg6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am now up to date on @ScaryStory_Pod, which means I will either 1. start it again or 2. listen to @annadrezen react to @thatsajellyfish's self-portrait circa age seven, straight from the Monster Folder, on repeat with it open on my screen. ("Oh...my...god.") https://t.co/eLW93Eloua https://t.co/JkS4e62qL8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VeronicaKlash @marchxness I'm also having to send an off-Zoom toast to the writers for their work and the Selection Committee for facilitating this much-needed bright spot. Thank you all! https://t.co/vGrVKkrySa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jrmcconvey: @marchxness Thanks to all the organizers, writers and hecklers for a month of nostalgic fun. @marchxness is the best thing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marchxness: MARCH PLAIDNESS FINAL SCORES (certified):  @LocalH, Bound for the Floor (@AlgaenTentacles): 1520  @kingsx, Dogman (@PCMadde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you, Beverly Cleary. https://t.co/VXyJazwTFs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bQYO6N7b8A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness https://t.co/AdHIj0fRDU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vote Muses. Let's get Radiohead out of here. (I'm not bitter; you are.) https://t.co/NmmaetJrLn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For @post_trash_, I reviewed the latest @babehoven release. Maya Bon's work is always impressive, and this EP is a stunner. https://t.co/YwGzxrmZ3Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shabbahdoo @Change Signed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Social_Mime: According to a Doritos bag I'm a "Family."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm thankful that my semi-early @marchxness exit means I don't have to go up against Local H.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Substantial list of #StopAsianHate resources, statistics, news, fundraisers, etc. Take time and read this. https://t.co/8TFsp8zD6E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I miss Pittsburgh so much. https://t.co/waOeskIxI1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossyair Thank you for your essay, because the glam-grunge overlap cannot be overstated. (More than a little relevant: Duff McKagan is from Seattle and was a big part of the mid-80s scene. He was ready to go pro and deciding between LA and NY, but he knew his car wouldn't make it to NY.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness Kurt was already over it. (via https://t.co/PCPchjWS4i) https://t.co/26pWzpvehe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamCharlesworth @_robarnold Thank you, and thanks for reading!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alyssadehayes: Thanks @DoritosHangover for suggesting @ArrowhawkRcrds for this list of woman-run labels :) https://t.co/oCe2wezOIX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_robarnold @JamCharlesworth Thank you for your service. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DiggumF @templeofthedog ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness Thank you all for everything you do here!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Couldn't be in better losing company. Went hungry, but this is so much fun. https://t.co/s4vlpwFsit https://t.co/BPq7UcBkq7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_robarnold: Seattle, are we going to let the legendary Radiohead beat the decidedly mediocre Temple of the Dog in this grunge showdown?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness https://t.co/v4TshKzWEl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alyssadehayes @ArrowhawkRcrds Of course!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PearlJam squad, activate! Please help "Hunger Strike" advance in March Plaidness. Vote in the Twitter poll and at https://t.co/MXCVs9bZiC until noon EST! https://t.co/VMkDGPi8fY https://t.co/Olj3OmFN4d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mossyair: I listened to Hunger Strike roughly 100 times while researching my extracurricular essay and the thing is, it feels like to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mossyair !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamCharlesworth: Folks, it's time to fight for the very soul of the @marchxness tournament. I love Creep too, but c'mon people, Hunger]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jrmcconvey: @marchxness @radiohead @templeofthedog @DoritosHangover Just gonna leave this here this AM for anyone who's considering bla]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Forget Eddie. Vote @templeofthedog for Andrew Wood! https://t.co/VMkDGPi8fY https://t.co/khQ2LCBpD8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shabbahdoo: Vote for Hunger Strike now! Its a close race.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shabbahdoo ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HorrocksCaitlin ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HorrocksCaitlin: I was seeing them on their I-need-some-cash tours in 2006 to support the my-kid-needs-a-college-fund comeback album,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cubist_octopus: For me, Creep is much like Zombiea great song but a total grungified outlier in each bands respective catalog whi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlgaenTentacles: @marchxness @radiohead @templeofthedog @DoritosHangover This moment in @DoritosHangover 's essay: "But I was ready for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlgaenTentacles @marchxness @radiohead @templeofthedog ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melissafaliveno ...Ive said too much.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This choice is nearly impossible, but I'm giving "Good" my vote because it's my Achilles heel and because the essay by @raginits is so damn good (sorry)the perfect companion to a lifelong earworm I had to identify by searching "chorus a wow a wow a wuh huh" many years ago. https://t.co/TJVgoPabkk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These are some grade-A "WAH-AH"s (my now-husband and I recorded a cover of this song 10+ years ago drunk with a banjo, so I am something of a "WAH-AH" expert). https://t.co/zkJm7Fnb1P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Heisenhaus: Radiohead sucks ass, vote Temple of the Dog. https://t.co/gMxRtkaZIj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ToddKaneko: Official, Schmofficial! Vote for Temple of the Dog! https://t.co/VSJZHWYvGL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @epmornsesh: Creep is a cool song, but I cannot go against Hunger Strike. And just for the record, the Temple album came out four mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OhPipeDown: This vote is for my friend Julie who used to kiss her boyfriend (a poster of Chris Cornell) goodbye every night before she]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OhPipeDown Thank you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jrmcconvey: @marchxness @radiohead @templeofthedog @DoritosHangover TOTD is arguably THE most grunge album (though maybe not the grungi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness @templeofthedog This is an extremely fair point.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MattK_FS: I swear, if the combined powers of Eddie Vedder and Chris Cornell -- paying tribute to one of grunge's true forebears here, m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All due respect to Radiohead and Rob Hays (whose assessment of Radiohead as Cool Big Brother in band form is excellent), this is a grunge bracket. Vote for me and @templeofthedog's "Hunger Strike." https://t.co/VMkDGPi8fY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pixies/Bikini Kill https://t.co/3xTR0l2u0B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@picturesofdives Today, I'd pick Screaming Trees' "Nearly Lost You" at 9:45 PM but then "Alone" by Heart around midnight, when I probably start crying with my fist in the air.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LucindaBliss @marchxness Local H, Pearl Jam, R.E.M., Babes in Toyland, Weird Al, Janes Addiction, Dinosaur Jr., Soul Asylum, Butthole Surfers, Lemonheads, Weezer, Pixies, Radiohead, Smashing Pumpkins, Flaming Lips, Stone Temple Pilots, Chris Cornell solo (some at festivals and none in the 90s)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I live for the @Jezebel "BYE BITCH!!!!!!!" https://t.co/D6brMQCFVM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Babes/Trees https://t.co/EES1TECHhU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GregOldfield21: Waking up after 8 days of @marchxness https://t.co/HMqR069qfg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I will be blindly voting for STP as long as theyre in the running, so its great that the Sex Type Thing essay is wonderful as well. https://t.co/5XwlZeiru4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[100% Placebo here because the essay rules and I cannot stand Wayne Coyne. https://t.co/lOu7T2FkXo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness @offspring @t_mcallister @mudhoney @DoctorFanboi Between the excellent opening (and subsequent) lines in both essays and my love for these songs, I'm almost torn, but I can't not vote for Mudhoney here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sablaah: remember the nirvana baby? this is him now. feel old yet? https://t.co/p6WLnrQpxT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@angermonsoon @marchxness @emilylauracosta Yes and yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@megangalbraith @MartinSeay @marchxness Amen. As far as I'm concerned, this is #AWP21.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every day at 10:30 AM, one of my neighbors fries up what smells like 50 onions. That's all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@raginits @marchxness @betterthanezra @soulasylum I loved your essay. I have such a soft spot for Good, and you were the exact writer it needed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness @buttholesurfers @elturk7 @TheLemonheads @GregOldfield21 Two more perfect essays and favorite songs, but I went Lemonheads.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness @betterthanezra @raginits @soulasylum Had to split my vote here because every song in this tournament is my favorite song, and these two essays are excellent. (My last live show before lockdown was indeed Soul Asylum at Metro in Chicagowith Local H opening.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@markyarm @Elana_Brooklyn @marchxness @thenurtureboy @LucindaBliss ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elana_Brooklyn @marchxness @thenurtureboy @LucindaBliss Yes! I saw that! But you correctly identified him as Mark Yarm and not the leader of Mudhoney, which I just did even though I'm staring at the spine of the book as we speak. More caffeine plz.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness Oh no. I bet he had the best life. To Toulouse. &lt;3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marchxness @thenurtureboy @LucindaBliss @Elana_Brooklyn Mother Love Bone may be out, but I love that the two Andrew Wood tributes won here ("Hunger Strike," of course, but also "Would?", which I just learned from Mark Arm's grunge oral history Everybody Loves Our Town and seems incredibly obvious but here we are).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just exhaled slowly in my apartment. Weird Al was my #2 shortlist pick. I would've voted for him if the other option weren't me, and I don't think he could've asked for a better advocate than @jrobertlennon, so I was sweating right up to the buzzer. https://t.co/YtLUz9GpTR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elana_Brooklyn @templeofthedog Thank you! I love yours because its I dare you not to vote for Janes Addiction in essay form. Just a completely bulletproof argument and a perfect encapsulation of the band (and I agree with you re: Dangerous Angelsand most points, really).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mvankerckhove: I went with Temple this round, even though I love me some Weird Al. The wonderful @marchxness essays by @DoritosHangover]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinSeay @marchxness #AgainstKool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinSeay: Given the extreme anxiety  resentment over the topic of selling out during the @marchxness era, @DoritosHangovers accou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thenurtureboy Its one of my favorites so far, along with @erinequalss I Alone essay (gone but not forgotten!).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mossyair: "And then I showed up, beyond excitedand holy shit, was I late." Feeling every moment of @DoritosHangover's @marchxness essa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KathleenMRooney: But also! Don't miss @DoritosHangover's essay on Temple of the Dog:  "When I finally made it to Seattle at age 27 (thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erinequals: The 'is grunge even?' dialogue btw these pieces by @doritoshangover and @jrobertlennon is worthy of its own essay, but real]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shabbahdoo: Vote vote vote!... For @DoritosHangover (and Hunger Strike/Temple of the Dog). Read the essay while youre at it. Its re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlgaenTentacles: @marchxness @DoritosHangover @alyankovic @jrobertlennon Love that @DoritosHangover wrote my favorite Nirvana lyrics on]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>