<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neal_katyal: This decision seems very, very significant. Judge Jackson is an incredibly careful jurist. This is a big deal.   Judge ord]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neal_katyal: New #Courtside (my short video/podcast legal explainer series) up tonight: Examining the FBI raid of Rudy GIiuliani and wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neal_katyal: And Derek Chauvin's brief opposing the sentencing enhancements is here: https://t.co/J3ev2EtGWY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neal_katyal: Informational update on the Derek Chauvin trial: We have now filed our sentencing brief, arguing that his sentence should]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Health care should be a right, not a privilege in America.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoeBiden: 100 days inand America is getting back on track.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tribelaw: Trumps stooge Bill Barr blocked this very warrant to search for and seize evidence of Clown Rudys crimes on behalf of Trump]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scobie: Prince Charles has written a message to the people of India, where Covid deaths have now passed over 200,000 people. https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @asunnydisposish: Frankly, I don't have strong opinions about Brad Pitt and Plan B so you can stop @-ing me in their defense because I d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @asunnydisposish: So it's ridiculous that this is being framed in Western media as "omg Yoon Yeo-Jung fangirls Brad Pitt how relatable!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @asunnydisposish: She specifically asked "where were you during filming?" to Brad Pitt during her acceptance speech because he was a pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @asunnydisposish: Yoon Yeo-Jung said in a Korean interview after the Oscars that Plan B didn't give Minari enough funds to work with so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mkraju: DC Metro Police officer Michael Fanone, who was brutally attacked by the mob on Jan. 6, said on @CNNTonight: Its been very di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scobie: The Sussexes are campaign chairs of #VaxLive and will deliver an urgent message for vaccine equity during the event. They have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scobie: Right now, only 0.1% of worldwide doses have been administered in low-income countries, leaving millions vulnerable.  On Saturd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@meenaharris I thought that was normal!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLastWord: In documents obtained by the New York Daily News from a 2015 deposition, former Trump Org. CFO Allen Weisselberg said he d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepJeffries: The Honorable John Lewis urged us to confront injustice whenever and wherever it could be found.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @amyklobuchar: Great news: Two-thirds of seniors are now fully vaccinated in the US!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Get vaccinated, folks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neal_katyal: We just created oxygen on mars. Methinks there must be a way for America to get more O2 to India.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @djrothkopf: It tells you a great deal about the magnitude of the change brought by @POTUS  his administration that today the world ful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CoryBooker: Millions of Americans are now eligible to receive a COVID vaccine.  Get your shot to travel, to hug, to laugh, to love toge]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeremynewberger: Every day, and in every way, we should remember what happened on January 6th, how Kevin McCarthy's ineffective call wi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Rep. Val Demings confirms she's "seriously considering" a run for the U.S. Senate or to be governor of Florida. https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: President Biden is expected to announce tomorrow that the CDC has updated its guidance for wearing masks. Multiple peop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABC: Tyler Perry was honored with the Jean Hersholt Humanitarian Award at the #Oscars! https://t.co/cjCyHPfGms https://t.co/qHbxoqrJOa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scobie: In this time, with all of the internet and social media and algorithms and everything that wants us to think a certain way, th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Just as India sent assistance to the United States as our hospitals were strained early in the pandemic, we are determined to he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VP: The U.S. is working closely with the Indian government to rapidly deploy additional support and supplies during an alarming COVID-1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidmweissman: The fact that Kevin McCarthy refuses to answer what Trump told him during the insurrection on January 6th should put hi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Our best days still lie ahead. https://t.co/QiTZbt8OTK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SURPRISE!!  https://t.co/Fg44tXU0jW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: President Joe Biden says he has a strict rule about his phone: No matter what's happening, he always answers a call from one of hi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaraReinstein: ?!!/$::@!!!!##   (Note this was my reaction and not the name of Musks child.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marceelias: I expect a busy week for the courts next week. Stay tuned and follow along....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tomandlorenzo: Ten years ago this week, we got our fanblogger asses off blogspot and launched our website, with the somewhat insane goa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoJoFromJerz: Speaking of traditional values... Newt Gingrich met his first of THREE wives in high school. She was his geometry teach]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@neal_katyal Ridic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KamalaHarris: Get vaccinated. Wear a mask. Save lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: This Earth Day, Im proud to say science is back.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VP: .@POTUS made a promise to get 100 million shots in arms in our first 100 days of office. Today, we beat that goalby 2X.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tonyschwartz: The first three months of Biden's presidency exceed anything I could have imagined. He has been courageous, steadfast, an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: America is back. We rejoined the Paris Agreement and are ready to rally the world to tackle the climate crisis. Lets do this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepJeffries: The House will pass legislation to make DC a state today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoyceWhiteVance: When people ask what they can do to make our union more perfect, tell them to be like Darnella Frazier.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mimirocah1: Yes although we also need more body cameras so we arent dependent on the bravery of people like her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @usweekly: Exclusive: Pregnant Meghan Markle is being intentional about maintaining her mental and physical health while expecting baby]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AliVelshi: BREAKING: Justice Department to launch investigation into Minneapolis policing practices https://t.co/Nu86dkoSll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @usweekly: Queen Elizabeth II is 95 today.  https://t.co/QWVn9PwYDW https://t.co/mkT7UwN3Pd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanRather: Please get vaccinated and encourage others to do so. These shots are a literal gift of life, for yourself and the rest of th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MollyJongFast: Important thread on Columbus Ohio PD.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Yamiche: Thinking of Darnella Frazier who filmed the death of George Floyd at 17 and quite literally changed the world. She testified t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NYGovCuomo: I will be giving a COVID update and making an announcement at 11:30am ET.   Watch here: https://t.co/Fq5qEF73TB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: As of today, every American is eligible to receive the COVID-19 vaccine. For yourself, your neighbors, and your family  please,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Fauci to CBS on vaccine skeptics: "The ones that keep saying you're encroaching on our liberties by asking us to wear mas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepJeffries: Believe your eyes.  Not the defense attorneys lies.  Convict Derek Chauvin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: As of today, all adults are now eligible to be vaccinated across all 50 states. The CDC says 50 percent of all adults h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WHCOS: Big week of vaccination milestones: - SAT: 65% of 65+ FULLY VAX'ed (was 2% on 1/20/21)  - TODAY:  50%+ of ALL adults w/ at least]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brianstelter: CNN producer Carolyn Sung was wrongfully arrested by Minnesota state troopers on Tuesday night. This letter from a group]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mccaffreyr3: WOWSER!  This is demonic. These are extremely dangerous and deluded people. Democrats need to gather people of goodwill to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProjectLincoln: The Oath Keepers are trained by active-duty law enforcement officers....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maddenifico: Oath Keepers: a fascist militia w/ members who are overwhelmingly linked to white supremacy are being trained by police?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: Doctors say many young people are suffering coronavirus complications they didn't expect. And it's time to ditch the belief that o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AP: My angel. Rest in peace. Alma Wahlberg, the mother of entertainers Mark and Donnie Wahlberg and a regular on their reality series]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilArballo: This is a reminder that my Republican opponent Devin Nunes needs to be unseated. Retweet to join the campaign that will do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProjectLincoln: Jan 6, 10:15PM: The Senate votes 936 against the objection raised by a handful of Republican senators against the coun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: The Justice Department is suing Roger Stone, accusing him and his wife of owing nearly $2 million in unpaid income taxes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Breaking: Mike Pompeo violated federal ethics rules governing the use of taxpayer-funded resources when he and his wife a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewSolender: More:  7 of those 8 + Mo Brooks, Ken Buck, Jody Hice, Bob Good and Paul Gosar voted against creating an advisory board]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewSolender: Just 8 House members voted against a bill requiring the FTC to "submit a report to Congress on scams targeting seniors,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: The new evidence linking Trumps 2016 campaign directly to the Russian government is not surprising, but still appallin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scobie: The Palace has shared the Order of Service for Prince Philips funeral, which was planned with his help and reflects military l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepSwalwell: Thats a wrap! Donald Trump sold America out to Russia before he was elected. And once elected, Trump consistently chose R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepJeffries: We defeated fascism in Germany and communism in the Soviet Union.   Why cant America find the strength to end gun violenc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robreiner: No surprise. Trump colluded with Russia. Weve always known his Presidency was illegitimate. Now it has been proven. For the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @meenaharris: Even if youre fully vaccinated, the CDC still recommends that your meeting should've been an email.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaraReinstein: Hi. I wrote 4000 words about the insanity that was the 2011 Oscar ceremony. But unlike the Oscars, I promise this doesn']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JillWineBanks: Here's my Tues trial summary: Prosecution presented a great case and is now eviscerating the defense witnesses. Masterfu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @scobie: A touching tribute to grandfather Prince Philip from Princess Eugenie on Instagram. I remember your hands and your laugh and y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProjectLincoln: Matt Gaetz should be removed from his committees.   RT if you agree]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robreiner: The only way Republicans can maintain White Supremacy is through voter suppression. With every major corporation coming out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BetteMidler: In Germany, police have to have 4 years of training before they are allowed on the job. In the US, they train for less tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ananavarro: A picture speaks a thousand words.... https://t.co/bRqizLO6Ak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[F that https://t.co/jsn0SslsYO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alyssa_Milano: I mean, if you cant tell the difference between your gun or your taser maybe you shouldnt be a policeman.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Today Im thinking about Daunte Wright and his family  and the pain, anger, and trauma that Black America experiences every day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gtconway3d: imagine being the former guy's cellmate and having to listen to him bitch about McConnell and Pence ad infinitum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @POTUS: Gun violence in this country is an epidemic  and its long past time Congress take action.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JetBlue DONE. Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JetBlue YES. And it says there is no Travel Bank acct associated with my TrueBlue, however, I have the email with my Travel Bank credit from last year. This system is FAR TOO COMPLICATED. Please help.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey @JetBlue -- finding it next to impossible to access my Travel Bank acct and also totally impossible to reach Customer Service, why is it so hard to use my credit?????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalFamily: The Royal Family join with people around the world in mourning his loss.     Further announcements will be made in due cou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalFamily: It is with deep sorrow that Her Majesty The Queen has announced the death of her beloved husband, His Royal Highness The P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @60Minutes: Campaign finance reports obtained by 60 Minutes show that weeks before Florida Governor Ron DeSantis announced a partnership]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JillWineBanks: Probably not a coincidence.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @60Minutes: "What you're saying is wrong," Gov DeSantis tells Sharyn Alfonsi in response to a question about whether the Publix grocery]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Just weeks before Republican Ron DeSantis announced a partnership with Publix grocery stores to distribute COVID vaccines]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: This is pretty striking and counter-intuitive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepJeffries: Millions of Americans of every race suffer from opioid addiction.  It is not a crime.  And George Floyd is not on trial.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>