<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@maz_marianne @Figuregirl55 I'll have a look, thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maz_marianne @Figuregirl55 Thank you. Any info she could pass on would be much appreciated ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maz_marianne @Figuregirl55 https://t.co/I4505wGCAL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@maz_marianne @Figuregirl55 Oo, where did you get that please? I was eyeing up this light in BQ yesterday. But that one hung from the ceiling. I want something that would sit on the table. They look very similar ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@louisebentley10 @RealRealise1111 Perfect choice of music. I first heard of The Score when someone put The Fear against a Trump rally. Fitted it so well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nudger1966 @lamps_manson Definitely. Can still picture it now ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DinoJoachim Love it   Would definitely want to stay in the Trump room ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonnaB5125: @MaajidNawaz @JuliaHB1 @Iromg @LozzaFox @MartinDaubney @awilliamscomedy  This doctor is asking why people aren't being offe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exactly  We should all do this. https://t.co/n6lOU9gS5f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoriartyProfJ3 @chriskeebs @Littlejems3 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaajidNawaz @JuliaHB1 @Iromg @LozzaFox @MartinDaubney @awilliamscomedy  This doctor is asking why people aren't being offered treatment for Covid to prevent hospital admission.  WHY do people with a "deadly virus" just get sent home?  WHY are no journalists asking this question? https://t.co/o3q194N301]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonnaB5125: Where's Normal Bloke's account gone?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where's Normal Bloke's account gone?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ROZ777artist: @MoriartyProfJ3 Just watched dr Coleman - Im really scared for all of us now. Seriously you need to get this to everyone]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UnityIsStrengt5 @BorisJohnson @ClimateEnvoy @COP26 @AlokSharma_RDG @FCDOGovUK Exactly !!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings Good, you should be   Much the same as alot of others petal. Getting more angry with the wnkers in charge and the sheep following them. Angry over Trump too obvs. Still won't be having the "vax". Etc etc. How are you? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings Soz, couldn't resist. You should be honoured I returned from Gab just for you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings   https://t.co/LZF8nB1aeo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DesmondSwayne W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy  https://t.co/MoYGU3c0bq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy Damn, can't you re-enact it ? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy I wanna see a video of that !!  Happy birthday  https://t.co/MU5LzvX2Y9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TykeTalking Happy birthday Val. Hope you have a super day  https://t.co/pUWn653j4s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ParkLan73862488 If only Mabbers was still playing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ParkLan73862488 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Normalbloke71 Ah bless you. I do check in now and then and it's very hard not to interract, but got to stay loyal to the Donald ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Normalbloke71 Absolutely. And fingers crossed she continues on the road to recovery. And remember we are here for you too. But please don't think I don't care if I don't see your posts, coz I left Twitter when Trump did. You are the only interraction on here I have had since ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Normalbloke71 Good news indeed x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Normalbloke71 Hey. Thinking of you both and I hope everything goes well  I don't come on here now, moved to Gab, so out of the loop a bit. Truly hope she is ok  x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Normalbloke71 I was going to message you to see how you both were. Wishing her all the very best ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Stephen90182822 @sekotser_ Oh I didn't know that. Haven't been on here for weeks. Very sad news indeed ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Maestro82342676 @MartinDaubney @BorisJohnson @JoeBiden I have done. Over to you as it's obviously passed you by ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Maestro82342676 @MartinDaubney @BorisJohnson @JoeBiden Do some research]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BorisJohnson @JoeBiden He will stab you in the back as soon as look at you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RupertaMargate @BorisJohnson @JoeBiden Exactly, and they don't think we can see right through them ??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinDaubney @BorisJohnson @JoeBiden All globalists. Build back better bollocks. We see them ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy I'm blaming it being my first smart phone, although that is no excuse ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy  Well when we got married in the US a few years ago, we bought new phones here, but bought sim cards out there. Couldn't work out why we couldn't hear the phones ringing. Eventually went into a ATT shop who turned the volume up for us.  How embarrassing ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy Haha, you can try. I watched a video on YouTube to work out what the symbols were ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy Ps. If I can suss it out, anyone can ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy I can't stay on here with all conscious. Look me up when you get there, Marty ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy You always talk alot of sense  I do miss people on here, but it's so less toxic over there. Plus I won't forgive them for what they did to Trump. It's a bit slow at the moment but that's because of the mass exodus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy Exactly. I don't understand it either, but it seems to be a lefty mindset. Those who hate Trump, Brexit etc seem to be so easily persuaded to take the vax. Will do no research. We must be free thinkers who can find the truth out for ourselves rather than relying on the MSM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy Ps. Please move to Gab. You are the first person I have spoken to on here for days. Miss you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy Yep, quoted the ONS figures and the WEF plan. Won't have it. Too "busy" to look  truly delusional. Just sent them a Biden video fcking the vax numbers up. They won't watch it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Grumpyme4 @debatenothate2 Already there ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KungFuMovieGuy They won't look. It's too scary for them. I had that exact conversation at work today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonnaB5125 https://t.co/8pALWETB5J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The truth about the US election  https://t.co/cIlTNOVXYW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@or_dodo Gotcha. Following you on there too ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@or_dodo Hiya. What is your name on Gab ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings Done  I had been looking under your @reals name.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings Couldn't find you. Will try again now I'm getting the hang of it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings No couldn't you..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gab is pretty damn good !!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LozzaFox Move to Gab please Laurence ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TykeTalking @getongab I guess that's fair enough, as long as they are even about it. I will persevere for a while ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TykeTalking @getongab I finally got on it today Val. Kind of getting the hang of it. loathe to stay on here though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davomooregmail1 Unfortunately not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well they've just put Dumbo in the Whitehouse. https://t.co/DVlM3FeLjs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey all. Moving to Gab. Please let me know your names to follow if you are on there ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic Agreed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MartinDaubney Scary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aTeXan575 Yes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CromwellStuff @JoeBiden ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@irishinmanches1 @_BillyTheFish_ @MattHancock ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BCugny @DrStefanieW Exactly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PainPrincess3 @Iromg @NancyWindsorUK @Nigel_Farage @talkRADIO Yes we do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@landersue13 @Iromg @NancyWindsorUK @Nigel_Farage @talkRADIO Please do ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @3_resurection: So just looking at the numbers and there is 43 behavioural scientists advising government on covid and just 12 epidemiol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Iromg @NancyWindsorUK @Nigel_Farage @talkRADIO Tell Nigel to tell Donald we love him ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mrdeeds1111 I bet he can barely sign his own name.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShellyL61140599 @Mrdeeds1111 Totally]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drekaplan: NEVER FORGET  He worked 4 years at 0 salary, while abused   Ended ISIS   7 million new jobs  Middle-class income up $6,000]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrStefanieW: Why are we not treating Covid early (or at least in vulnerable patients), on an outpatient basis, for example with ivermec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WiganEmptySeat: @SocialM85897394 Turkey locks up 1000s for daring to dissent. Iran hangs athletes for criticising govt. Pakistan kills]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spot on https://t.co/LlafPhAbdm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tonywesson @spikedonline https://t.co/q0Q05KqvTT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saltairebkshop @spikedonline @DiGada1 Already there. He will never be scrutinised.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@spikedonline Sickening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/MhRRYgAdcq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ha. You can feel the love they have for him !! https://t.co/bFNZJa4yed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/BQVardiEmY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mlkeyboy @_BillyTheFish_ @DominicRaab @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris https://t.co/xW5C33y1zO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_BillyTheFish_ @DominicRaab @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris  Give him time. Just when you thought he was a good guy. They all let you down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gladly https://t.co/8xhwvylAFL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@debatenothate2 Kin right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aTeXan575 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aTeXan575: When you just shook hands with Biden      https://t.co/zyus73ANip]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bbclaurak @BBCNews Fuck off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BorisJohnson @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_BillyTheFish_ @MattHancock Nope]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off globalist puppet https://t.co/63IrAlIkhh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic Agreed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: Once Trump is gone, who will all of the emotionally unstable malcontents worldwide blame all of their personal problems on? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LadyNoo22 True ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robertwlk ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirrthonsimon @talkRADIO Ah. I thought they had some idiot on there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgegalloway God help them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirrthonsimon @talkRADIO Who said that?]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>