<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SameOldStory55: @TheFreds IF they try and push this back there should be riots and or mass protests there would have been in the 70s/80]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFreds: subject to view. Presumably this is code for well change our minds, mess with your lives and your heads whenever we feel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @2020Cofi: @garethicke It's the goof of all time Look, but Don't Touch Touch, but Don't Taste Taste, Don't Swallow  And while you're jum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Proper gutted footie training is off tonight.  Which is odd given I've gone a year without it.  But then that's the psychol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @21WIRE: They know the penny is about to drop. Desperate damage control propaganda here by Pharma  Gov't: "According to Fact Checkers..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MurielH75470335: @TOTOWANJE @DickDelingpole @twitchy56209254 People are going to pubs because they don't want their pubs to die. Unfort]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TOTOWANJE: @PaulHobson247 @DickDelingpole @twitchy56209254 A lot of people who go around bullying others and act like they are enforcin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BareReality: Covid fines are a monstrous assault on justice.   I wrote for @spikedonline about the unlawful issue of Covid fines, the h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Enough is enough. We've got six weeks to show the government that if they don't give us our lives back we're just going]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: A very good article on how many people now have a chronic fear of reintegrating after lockdown ends. So many people been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: This is an outrage  We wont let this happen in UK  Allowing only those that have been vaccinated to participate freely?  Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: Governments around the world stole our humans rights  freedoms  now want to implement digital control over every aspect]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: I glance at replies and most of mine are currently filed under "Show additional replies, including those that may contain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @calvinrobinson: We should ditch masks in schools with immediate effect.  Leaked Public Health England documents show officials failed t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: "Build back better" just became more terrifying than "for your own safety"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: If you have never fought for anything else in your life, then let it be this   A domestic vaccine passport is not your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: A must-read about Vaccine Passports from the folks who built the no-fly list. Spoiler alert: they confirm that Im right to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1CryptoRyder: @pokaaaahh @zoeharcombe @lisakeb007 Were never returning to normal, thats not the plan and people need to wake up to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pokaaaahh: @zoeharcombe @lisakeb007 1. Ongoing restrictions mean an emergency situation is active.   2. Emergency situation active mean]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wellboy: @zoeharcombe I've never seen the likes of how bedded in some of my friends and family are. It's like this is black and white a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bailiejames81: @Nb0816Bishop @baldwin_malachi @zoeharcombe It means they are going to hire private contractors and deputize them to enf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @baldwin_malachi: @zoeharcombe this No.10 website is sourcing marshals for the next lockdown into 2021- newly posted 26 April. Tender cl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KellyMartin_UK: @zoeharcombe @UnityIsStrengt5 Me too, this is what I don't get. We get called conspiracy nuts, as if informing people o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheUglyGuy13: @zoeharcombe Zoe, i wish it were not happening but everything is in plain site, so obvious, i cannot believe the amount o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KimFlorey2: @zoeharcombe 624000 side effects in just one month from az/izer, many serious/fatal. Could this be about what your feeling/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: You cannot imagine how badly I want to be wrong about what's happening in the world right now. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nightingale_31: @GrunterMr Absolutely. There is liquid soap in the restrooms. The media and gov have been bombarding us with their rule]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denidarcel: @InfoBears @joeyjojojunior_ @HilaryWallace1 @Nightingale_31 @Christi75367510 I agree and support you. But others have been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InfoBears: @joeyjojojunior_ @HilaryWallace1 @Nightingale_31 @Christi75367510 I hve never worn a mask. Hve never had one strange or angr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joeyjojojunior_: @Nightingale_31 @Christi75367510 Thankyou so much, the amount of hate Ive had because I cannot wear a mask has been t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesSi41932301: @Nightingale_31 @Heather65557169 Eminently sensible. I also feel sick when I see mask wearing people looking sick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HenryLatham6: @Nightingale_31 YOU ARE SUPERSTARS!!! Wishing you all the best and a  hotel full of informed people, boosting your busine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nightingale_31: Before booking with us please read the information on our webpage.   Additional information: we are a hotel for mask ex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reasonoverfear: I never imagined that speaking up against the tsunami of self inflicted destruction of peoples health would risk my li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferSey: You realize your role model was the evil villain in this movie? His only moment of redemption was when he removed the mask.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: @BrianOSheaSPI drove 500  miles today - were at a bar in Cleveland - to get me to Lansing in time for my event with MI l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoelOsteen: The enemy wouldnt be fighting you if you didnt have greatness in you. Dont fall apart; get your sword out. Start swingin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilHendoFanCl1: @TonyEvans92a As with everything in life there are those who either support or criticise, it seems its far easier for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @darranlea89: @TonyEvans92a Fucking hell Tony I'm in bits here. I know people will tell you this who know you, but from someone who has]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TonyEvans92a Hi Tony. I've no idea what has been said/done (now) to prompt this thread, but I just wanted to give you a big hug. I wasn't there  can't truly imagine what u  others have been thru, then  since. But as part of #LFC family, I stand with u and u are NOT alone! #YNWA https://t.co/rjcbEyOYSY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Corballyred @spiritofshankly Not for me. Thanks to FSG I've seen my club bring in the greatest manager, the stadium expanded, my team become Champions of England, Europe ( world) in last 2 years. Doesnt get better than that! Yes, they've made mistakes, but they're listening to us! #CarefulWhatUWishFor #LFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: BREAKING. Bill and Melinda will no longer be fucking each other, but will continue to work together to fuck the rest of us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid21 was leaked back in October 2020. It's all been planned this way..... @ukcolumn @Albion_Rover @briangukc @mikeukc  https://t.co/tsSUgxAnUC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JMC_Starbug: @views_politics @localdecorator @reformparty_uk @drdavidbull My medical records are not on my phone. Pretty major '10%'.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gerie15: @shawnwatson5 @JMC_Starbug @views_politics @localdecorator @reformparty_uk @drdavidbull Er, no.  The NHS app gives access to A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cryptocm81: @shawnwatson5 @JMC_Starbug @views_politics @localdecorator @reformparty_uk @drdavidbull And what will be done with that sim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reformparty_uk: A warning about vaccine passports  From @drdavidbull https://t.co/zGLCz6VJeM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cjm691972: @piquesghost @NicKeaney @Mogsy67 Look a flag waver. Its ridiculously typical.  Im sure a tax funded yacht will be an asset]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @averyangryplace: @carr_steven @NicKeaney Ok, taking that logic forward, why can't multimillionaires be responsible for buying their own]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kronstadt2kool: @NicKeaney Well you see, rich bluebloods need yachts more than poor children need calories. It's a question of prioriti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NicKeaney: Why are we using money for another vanity project when there are literally children going hungry. A massive cladding scandal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NicKeaney: WHY COULDNT WE FEED THE SCHOOL CHILDREN THEN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @squeezyjohn: Builders who installed deadly cladding on Grenfell Tower have given 2.5 million to the Tory party since the tragedy. 50k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mark_George_QC: Of course they would.  That how the system works.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RosieisaHolt: Theres no money tree, we couldnt possible pay back the 400m we owe Iran who are using our debt to keep Nazanin Zaghari]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lovely_Laura_F @RevDaniel When will u wake up  realise that even if you DO follow the rules, we will NEVER go back to normal? It's people following the rules that has prolonged it this long, not protesters! There is plenty of science but it is being SILENCED by money. Wake up 4 yr kids, if nothing else! https://t.co/frmfUKyy5V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thismynewhandle @fromwhereimsta1 @FionaLegal @NHSuk Hardly a 'tirade'.... But knock yrslf out - highlight abbreviations to save characters, cos u can't pull apart my argument.... https://t.co/o7QMQayjw6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abhidaga09: The Premier League have released a statement saying Man Utd will be hit with a severe penalty following the invasion of Old]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AJKasonde: @StanCollymore Doesnt matter about disruptions to prep time etc, corporate wanna make their money, nobody cares about playe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StanCollymore How on earth can the game go on as normal? I don't want it called off, but safety of both sets of players has to be at risk at mo??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hxpefxl Not sure how u picked up that I'm happy with this? Both sets of players will be affected. If they do lots of damage, the game will be called off. It will backfire on all of us - they'll no doubt tar us all with same brush  use it as excuse not to let fans back in....!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cantsey: @EvinPaulDaniel @vishy_united Oh shut up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @vishy_united: #mufc fans Protesting near the Lowry, where the team will board there bus to Old Trafford. #GlazersOut https://t.co/n4X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WebbyONeill: #MUFC fans break through barriers at Old Trafford at #GlazersOut protest  https://t.co/K473ZHqy6l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFergusonWay: Fair to say Old Trafford isn't ready for the game.   - @mufctilIy https://t.co/AxuEsIGT8d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StretfordPaddck: Fans protesting on the pitch at Old Trafford. https://t.co/ocfy5uGy4A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gezz_MUFC: We're in. Old Trafford is stormed. #GlazersOut https://t.co/cuBg1xqEEz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Am SOOOOO glad that's not us..... we'd be crucified if we did this. #LFC #YNWA #OldTrafford #MUNLIV https://t.co/ugaboSNJ1P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterStefanovi2: Now on 14.2 million views! @BBCNews @bbclaurak @BBCBreakfast cannot ignore it forever and maintain any degree of credi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LouisJo20715674: @BBCNews come on, you know you want to  #NeverVoteConservative #VoteConservative #ToryLies #MajorSleaze #ToriesOut]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @snowleopardess: What has happened to the UK, that we are allowing a corrupt regime to destroy us? We must be a laughing stock the world]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pti_Singe: @MattHancock @Conservatives Let us know which areas youre visiting so that we can get our buckets of sick ready!!! #Conserv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pcrclaims: Just watched a fundraising ad on TV for kids being diagnosed with cancer during lockdown. Meanwhile the gov blows billions o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Doctah_T: Dr Reiner Fuellmich, international lawyer has all the evidence that pandemic is crime https://t.co/vOSxvhfsBj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nightingale_31: Breakfast is included? Yes breakfast is included now sit down enjoy it and stop acting like this isnt normal! Not gett]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: Not once but almost always, Greta Thunberg wears disposable masks, whilst lecturing us about our irresponsible actions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ollybishop: Dominic Raab just said on #marr that masks and distancing will remain after June 21.   YOU ARE NOT GETTING YOUR LIFE BACK.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Neozeonchar04: @ollybishop The only reason were not getting back to normal is because all of the mindless morons playing along. The go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tweet of the day https://t.co/3xzEfbr1tY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StopTCensorship @garethicke Afraid of your peers too...... #wimps #throwthemaskaway #NoVaccinePassports  #NoNewNormal  #EndCovidRestrictions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LLees13: @StopTCensorship @garethicke https://t.co/wOSUGFFM0b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StopTCensorship: How true is this!  https://t.co/8ALKWobcWX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Danwhite1972: Can I ask all friends old  new if they could bless our project @DUnionUK with a follow?  We believe in the power of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArrrJack: @garethicke Dont worry, itll be fact-checked soon saying conspiracy theorists are causing hesitancy again. They done the sa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ancap102: @garethicke Must be the same coz it looks the same   Folk who think this drug is for the greater good are exactly who this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nickynoble: @garethicke Just watched a video of the head of the FDA saying he wont be taking the jab along with the 17k employees. The]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Trev_EFC1878: Yet more Tory cuts. If they hadn't handed Bs of crony contracts there would be enough  for every one of us #TorySleaz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DGWilkinson: @BigBrotherWatch Has the government ever lied so blatantly about something as important before? Well, at least since Bliar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hardistymark: @BigBrotherWatch @Fox_Claire @IainDale etc should have the Minister back on and play back the video and ask why he lied a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BigBrotherWatch: The Government repeatedly told us there were no plans for vaccine passports...   We now know that while these clips we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LivEchonews: It is 80 years since the May Blitz devastated large parts of Liverpool and claimed 1,746 lives https://t.co/ACd413PwzA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arobbo28: @Rachael_Swindon If the centrists couldn't bear to vote for actual positive change with Corbyn, why do they insist we vote fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidLloydWill8: In Lewes today near Brighton. Went to go into MS but queue outside. Asked guy in front: Why the queue? Covid mate don]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @eji_org: On this day in 1963, hundreds of Black children began peacefully protesting segregation in Birmingham as part of the Children']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RevDaniel Such Christian understanding.... https://t.co/ShQd1Tclxn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thismynewhandle @fromwhereimsta1 @FionaLegal @NHSuk Think u have misunderstood the tweet - they're saying that mask exacerbates Mum's condition but she wears it cos she doesn't want people like u giving her a hard time. Seems u have proved her point!!! But I agree with u that YOU'VE failed us as a species - you fell for the scam! https://t.co/sEc0A1ppVX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fromwhereimsta1: @FionaLegal @NHSuk My mum was nearly killed by flu in 2009 and has been left with permanent breathlessness which mask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkC48322041: @Jaq100 @FionaLegal @NHSuk Do not cough, they will have you sectioned under the mental health act for not following the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jaq100: @FionaLegal @MarkC48322041 @NHSuk It's hay-fever season.  I find myself swelling like a pigeon when I'm out , trying not to cou]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>