<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[As teens, they're marketed as 'innocent' and 'virginal'; then as 18 approaches, they're 'almost legal'. https://t.co/kfXy7QAL3X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the women helping skaters of all ages and levels to congregate freely without judgement. https://t.co/NbbbcpyIpU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This years event on 13 September will be hosted by co-chairs Timothe Chalamet, Billie Eilish, Amanda Gorman, and Naomi Osaka. https://t.co/aDUfzTtbrr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take that, TikTok. https://t.co/RCQm6okfyK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What does the week have in store for you? https://t.co/wBTvKZyw0t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From deep breathing to a healthier diet and optimised hair care regimen, trichologist Bridgette Hill has some sage advice to solve your scalp issues. https://t.co/i6SWqY9KFQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Her successes still feel personal to her fans. Eilishs stardom reflects the contrary teenage aspiration to be validated for your differences. https://t.co/BB7u4qjfcH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["My place was so good  Prince came over once and he was like, Oh, I see why you dont want to go out https://t.co/hjNehxbogg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The phrase "like mother, like daughter" is certainly true with these stars. https://t.co/aGBPsdPWAU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chanel and Gucci are offering face jewels in monogram crystal. https://t.co/EWxxJciugv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Recent graduate Josephine Philips is the founder of @Sojo_App, the Deliveroo for clothing repairs. https://t.co/waaQxWItcQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The heiress weighs in on Instagram and reclaims a historical but false moment. https://t.co/7TddHX4n1j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following the tragic news of the designers death at the age of 59, revisit 21 archive Lanvin looks from the Alber Elbaz era. https://t.co/xTGMOIYOSV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Parisians unsurprisingly have their own approach to childbearing and it revolves around a mantra of live and let live. https://t.co/Y7x6FfkOet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bobs to suit every age and hair type. https://t.co/Xv8lxpij0S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When youre 50-plus you do not give a flying f**k. About anything, pretty much. https://t.co/33c3UPQMl4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's not always been leather suits and feather boas for Harry Styles. https://t.co/aHFrPzNEJj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VB is synonymous with the LBD. https://t.co/HaQQzQl8YV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The age of the face mask has coincided with a new generation of lip balms that are as covetable as any luxury lipstick. https://t.co/QyqcPJi6Yj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[British Vogue meets with @AshleyGraham as she lands a new role as the face of Pandoras new campaign. https://t.co/TUVEFORdjK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Behold, the Chanel lip stud. https://t.co/7kWxRK2hpV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From the haircuts to try now, to how to enhance your waves for that perfectly tousled effect. https://t.co/hAEIzO5yOb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When two fashion behemoths collide. https://t.co/0aweo3hq9X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A powerful new work begins a fresh chapter in novelist Jhumpa Lahiris now bilingual career. https://t.co/in0dCfSJZ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As India continues to struggle with a surge in Covid-19 cases, Priyanka Chopra has set up a fundraiser in a bid to help her home country. https://t.co/ImqCzkyd9O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It happens to half of the population at some point  but how much do we really know about the menopause? https://t.co/inu8zjkMDv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The supermodels obsession with leather biker jackets dates back to the 90s. https://t.co/A0Lo0YBRFQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From the hair mask that was made especially for her (and remains cult today), to her religious use of SPF. https://t.co/BA1xzHMf2t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The skin concern facing most clients streaming through salon doors? Dehydration. https://t.co/9nNYwHRa57]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vintage fans, take note. https://t.co/PKmaSFTV0U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[25 years later and that infamous red velvet suit is back on the runway. https://t.co/lDal2AxwSj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The social media commentary is half the fun. https://t.co/fL6l0HMHeN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's just one more trend Harry Styles started. https://t.co/7WN4GNuykW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This wholesome headgear is starting to look like a summer essential... Just ask Bella Hadid. https://t.co/JYzFt0KBYb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to optimise what you eat, drink and do based on your menstrual cycle. https://t.co/dRqD1uLdBM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Cindy Crawford in full bombshell mode as Richard Geres date, to a red-carpet appearance from a young Lily Collins. https://t.co/FHaXNChbFP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The perfect street-style inspiration. https://t.co/9jshbbGb78]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What exactly can we expect of Aidan in the 'Sex And The City' reboot? https://t.co/6l5GHjZRmT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Charlotte Casiraghi has inherited the polished style of her mother, Chanel muse Princess Caroline of Hanover, and her grandmother, Grace Kelly. https://t.co/58K8LPkNFq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hailey and Kaia are raiding the rambler wardrobe again. https://t.co/3ROW2kVIDg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rihannas obsession with vintage goods spans far beyond her wardrobe and jewellery box. https://t.co/n5Rqofc61i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate doesnt have to be on the runway to create a stir. https://t.co/W5xMGh3Npl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 2019, a report published by MBRRACE-UK, found that Black women in the UK are five times more likely to die during pregnancy and after childbirth compared to their white counterparts. https://t.co/MkvUR9Dqel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[High school movies swept cinemas, and inspired a generation of young women to lower their waistbands, hike up their hems, and acquire as many logo T-shirts, micro bags and sky-high pointy heels as possible. https://t.co/WxxNmrGm0s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is there any actor quite as versatile as Cate Blanchett? https://t.co/DEui5xHlWs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its unlikely youll be packing your swimwear for the Med any time soon. But you still need something to wear as you embrace the British summer (sunshine pending)... https://t.co/UUceKDGEth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From styling the Schiaparelli Marvel hero gown to taking tips from Kim on balancing motherhood and work. https://t.co/IF0u9c1fp5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are writing to regrettably inform you that Emily Cooper will need to remain in Paris for an extended period of time.  Sylvie. https://t.co/Thfma4M45K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This seasons hero trouser shape leaves little room for debate. https://t.co/znD0RGbnZt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle will release her first childrens book, The Bench, about the relationship between Prince Harry and baby Archie. https://t.co/w6CM3zutKX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not quite the best morning person? https://t.co/OIWr2sU6CR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crystal artist @SaraShakeel has put her own stamp on @BillieEilishs June cover shoot. https://t.co/IvRF3o9Y5S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Lady Whistledown confirms the Duke won't be returning to the Ton in season 2 of 'Bridgerton', revisit all the extravagant details from his nuptials to Daphne Bridgerton. https://t.co/uoB91DIhCs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heres everything you need to know. https://t.co/eTjedD2qBc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Zendaya in Bulgari to Daniel Kaluuya in Cartier, who wore diamonds best at this years Academy Awards? https://t.co/GwwtoUlJrP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gatess divorce announcement is a headline-making reminder that global divorce rates are soaring, heres how to transform a tumultuous time into something positive. https://t.co/U2WO84R3BR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virginie Viard took Chanels 2021/22 Cruise show to the South of France. Her modernist collection was rooted in the familiarities of summertime travel, says Anders Christian Madsen. https://t.co/3sDwCJ70GC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[British make-up artist Diane Kendal has collaborated with the global fashion brand for the creation of affordable make-up line, Zara Beauty. https://t.co/1vzopDuceC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If 'Normal People' left a TV-obsession hole to be filled, this is it. https://t.co/P8SXeOtKoB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the unplanned year off, @BillieEilish kindled a love of songwriting  which once tormented her  and learnt to engineer. And shes proud of the work: Ive grown so much and gotten so much better in my voice, its crazy to think about, she says.  https://t.co/Yabh8Fc8sB https://t.co/OyNgnHPHjZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@BillieEilishis the voice of a generation, and shes using her platform to challenge misogynistic narratives around women and the way they dress. In the June issue, shes taking the power back. https://t.co/Yabh8Fc8sB https://t.co/ay3WzNao5H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shes the youngest winner of a Grammy for Album of the Year, shes recorded a Bond theme, and shes the first artist born in the 21st century to have a US number one. Now, @BillieEilish stars inBritish Vogues June issue as youve never seen her before. https://t.co/Yabh8Fc8sB https://t.co/ZFMfye8YzG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While@BillieEilishs new album comes at an exciting time of change for the singer, her focus remains on creating music that she is proud of. You should be exactly who you feel like you are and want to be in that moment. https://t.co/Yabh8Fc8sB https://t.co/Yh3FvS4S9B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was ready for it to suck says@BillieEilishof getting used to being a blonde. In fact, shes found it transformative. https://t.co/RC5HIpfStw https://t.co/vt96Y8doBm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In his first televised interview since coming out as transgender, the actor Elliot Page told Oprah Winfrey his surgery had been not just life-changing, but life-saving. https://t.co/C0ZCnXPfzr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sophie Turner certainly evokes a skater vibe with ease. https://t.co/K2V3mYbbjx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get your socks at the ready. https://t.co/TLptXSfDa3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a new kid on the beauty block. https://t.co/kiQTRuQY5D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even when shes enjoying some downtime, Jennie Kim will opt for pieces by the revered French house. https://t.co/iRrISah77O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's what to do instead. https://t.co/NM62ywTIMI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[British Vogue's June cover star @BillieEilish will co-chair the event alongside @RealChalamet, @TheAmandaGorman, and @NaomiOsaka. https://t.co/da6M68ALFQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[British Vogue sits down with Tinuke Awe and Clotilde Rebecca Abe, the incredible founders behind @FiveXMore. https://t.co/a4pxrpfrvd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[British Vogue meets pioneering skateboarders Shannon Moss, a founding member of skate collective Grlswirl, Briana King and Stephanie Wise. https://t.co/wQW5hdHqZa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MissVogueUK: In a sustainable move, the collection comprises 80s and 90s denims reworked with playful Miu Miu embellishments  https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You will be open to having new experiences this week, and will want to just go with the flow. https://t.co/2TIYzCsoe6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A sure-fire way to put spring in your step. https://t.co/tnQonc2d8Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The supermodels obsession with leather biker jackets dates back to the 90s. https://t.co/tV3tdsh1iu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why stop at Mean Girls? https://t.co/vCCjUd1Wvc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leave it to Netflix to bring the Habsburg court to life. https://t.co/RopJKu7OHG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember Kate Mosss Met Gala debut, dressed in a minimalist Calvin Klein dress? What about Diana, Princess of Wales, who stole the show in 1996? https://t.co/bjpRDL12kf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The look is relaxed, but never sloppy. https://t.co/7PeMrUnvD8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shop the striped cardigans you'll be living in this year. https://t.co/ou6EmVD6aG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the weather gets a little warmer and the days a little longer, its time to bring back aperitivo hour, with @gizzierskine and @malfygin: https://t.co/gs5IHkRv9p #VoguePartner https://t.co/y49kIjvs8g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pop stars dramatic inking is visible in her transformative photo shoot inspired by classic, old-timey pin-ups. https://t.co/xu8u57nWxk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billie set a new agenda (and changed the course of fashion) by being entirely herself. https://t.co/DgKsIps4sN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gatess divorce announcement is a headline-making reminder that global divorce rates are soaring, heres how to transform a tumultuous time into something positive. https://t.co/VH3rfd419V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gigi Hadid and Dua Lipa are part of the fan club. https://t.co/CVBdQOuEFx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Her first book is partially inspired by the relationship between Prince Harry and baby Archie. https://t.co/1SzrPXfi8Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Artist @SaraShakeels work took three hours of continual digital rhinestoning @BillieEilishs pictures. https://t.co/KSIBo4Mysv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From eyeshadows to lipsticks, the new line is refillable too. https://t.co/1RIuU9WJWY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@TheeStallion is one of the hottest hip-hop stars on the planet. Here, she discusses why the beauty industry needs to do more when it comes to inclusivity. https://t.co/NiXaSvWsrJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From 'Halston' to 'Never Have I Ever.' https://t.co/bj4Swfl4UZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Think bespoke engagement rings that double up as modern-day talismans. https://t.co/peJPFOnDay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honour this years upcoming event with a look back through the Met Gala archives, and enjoy a selection of matches made in fashion heaven. https://t.co/s6ugq9QWOS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im the only person that needs to like me, what I wear, who I am and what I say, the June cover star tells British Vogue. https://t.co/YPPbRgW782]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just like Hailey Bieber and Dakota Johnson, Turner has a Vans habit, too. https://t.co/23qlYXVEZt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vogue sits down with two-time Oscar-winning costume designer Jenny Beavan to talk about transforming Emma Stone into Disney supervillain Cruella de Vil. https://t.co/HUeplcj5SI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Beyonc in Gucci to Harry Styless 70s suits, Amy Winehouses ballet pumps to Courtney Loves 90s grunge dresses  here are some of the most important looks to define how we dress. https://t.co/osGhh0eeLd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The bob is set to be the reigning hairstyle of 2021. https://t.co/j0wSOx9bNY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont think I can properly express the strength, or even the exact nature of the emotions I was feeling, writes Vogues Erin Paterson of hearing the actor openly discuss his life-saving transition. https://t.co/mfR0Pf0FVy]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>