<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive loved Jack since the start. His voice is now grown. #blackish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FeelGoodPage11 That smile on the horse is too much. :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atrupar Shell be walking without grandpa or anyone else in 2 weeks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLewisBlack @HenryLouisGates This was a wonderful episode!  Thank you so much for participating!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roywoodjr @HenryLouisGates Thank you so much for participating in #FindingYourRoots    It was wonderful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wonderful wonderful. #FindingYourRoots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PippaSheaIsMe @Delavegalaw Me too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nebula_One @TheLewisBlack @roywoodjr #FindingYourRoots  ended on the best episode.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HenryLouisGates @TheLewisBlack @roywoodjr Thank you so much for this wonderful series. Ive learned so much from you and your shows, all of them.  Im so grateful for all you do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last episode of the season????  Crap  #FindingYourRoots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FeelGoodPage11: Bears pool party  https://t.co/CyIuuiiqvB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im excited about this episode. #FindingYourRoots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OperativeXRay Not this? https://t.co/4KpHko2Sli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont like those vessel sinks. Toothpaste looks awful in them. #neighborvsneighbor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ooooh Hoarders cross over! #neighborvsneighbor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant get over how cheap these houses are. #neighborvsneighbor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the Seattle area these are $750k more houses. $350k gets you a 1 bed condo. #neighborvsneighbor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FeelGoodPage11: Share this photo until we reach world peace https://t.co/Lx5yxXtxJn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Groan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OrangePaulp Loved that HBO series;  I just loved Bobs humanity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Of course I cant get a contractor to call me back. #unsellablehouses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RyanBartholomee Enough with the copper. :/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OMG. Im going to re-do my kitchen in next few months. Didnt need to hear about cabinets being hard to order because of demand. #unsellablehouses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catsofinstagram Kisses!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgehahn Guy is much too friendly a term.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SLessard And also with you. Sign of peace.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Catsnotbelong: https://t.co/YhiEQ1TdAj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidmackau Young Makeup versus old cranky depressed makeup.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KooTonyD @davidalangrier @roywoodjr And thats why Im not visiting my grandson tonight. :/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidalangrier @roywoodjr My favorite PBS show. And tonight with Roy Woods Jr and Lewis Black!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liamstack Known as sleep injuries]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KFILE In my pre diabetes life thats about 5 servings. Unless I make one of these. https://t.co/CWYk6AIQh5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveKrak Nope.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OperativeXRay @TheRickWilson Tumblr - prior known for porn and now not known for anything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MysterySolvent Dont quite know but hes Koo koo for Cocoa Puffs and just plain Koo Koo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ashtons_Journey Such a wonderful time for your family and happiness for both boys to spend time in the pool!  Much love and thanks for posting your pics. Always so welcome. Xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenthehough Im alarmed at some of your responses. Not  especially clever folks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OzbatRisa @CarterCenter @POTUS @FLOTUS Look in the mirror. Insufferable and not clever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HistoryLink Do you know Which of those streets turned into Rainier?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liamstack And no decent memes yet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FeelGoodPage11 A very worried puppy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richard collects junk with maggots #hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im on the episode with the lady with a fondness for teddy bears. #hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Yay for CCs!  Much friendlier vibe and not scary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenboebert You have a long list of people you dont love. Youre a hypocrite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulRudnickNY Is Springfield in a community property state?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanRather Very good news!! Grandson misses it by a year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgehahn Whole family vaxed and had family dinner last - first time in more than a year. I ate baba ghanoush and cried.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 Jeezusgawd JS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ashtons_Journey @McDonalds Sweet!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ashtons_Journey Xxxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 No like for you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgehahn Itty bitty teensy junk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OperativeXRay Jezuzfckingchrist. Colorado make up your mind!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catsofinstagram @kitten Pink is her color.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FeelGoodPage11 Your wife is correct. :).   Congratulations!  Kitty is so lucky to have found you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realThrilliam Beautiful. Ive never been.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatgirljacqs @yashar Shes gorgeous. The difference is prior she gave off teenage vibes. Not wi this cover]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TIFF_NET One thin wafer. https://t.co/5y5Q6jFhr2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClareLococo Tales of the City for me. Mrs Madrigal. https://t.co/dc71IU3Qyk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Theres nothing that will make them give up. Theyre nuts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mfbenji @yashar @alexkbenjamin Hes the one in the middle right?  Happy Birthday Hank!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 With you on this one. Thats how one becomes a subject on Hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OperativeXRay What a douche]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JReinerMD https://t.co/QvKmu0rIKv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgehahn My cat has been getting those calls also]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@funder Yes and no. He doesnt deserve to be booed for doing whats right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickyHilton @yashar Here in Seattle too. Not good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jaketapper My mom died over the course of one day. Her stomach hurting to gone in one day. Id give anything to tell her how much I loved her. I know she knew but I miss her so much. Blessings and love to you Jake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast We need to get it off experimental so people will have to get jabbed. Like the flu shot. Worked at a hospital and it was the rules.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sfordnyc @KFILE Thats what I was thinking. Not quite the horrible starling]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HistoryLink Love it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 Youre a bad man YS. https://t.co/KFMHcCXlkx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheTweetOfGod And the fans stopped the super league. Id bet that Glazer had no idea hed have to cave to them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheTweetOfGod I just read everything I could on Man U. Stadium used to hold 80,000 people. And boy do they hate Glazer. I had no idea.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HistoryLink I learn so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@georgehahn Xxxx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OperativeXRay Tiny junk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen And they smash it too much in the guac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 https://t.co/Hc8eNEqdHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kirill!   #lifeunderrenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spokane family is stressed. #lifeunderrenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love that kitchen. Budget?  #lifeunderrenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JULIAS GIRLS IN UGANDA https://t.co/iXwCKIiIHo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan I always zap finished smores in microwave just to melt the chocolate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poor mom.  Hold on. #lifeunderrenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#lifeundertenovation https://t.co/Cokc0EoBxM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickiNickiMusic And are there windows in those bedrooms?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cyndi_mich @hgtv Asbestos. No good. They need big buckets of $$]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OperativeXRay What you said. ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I like this couple. We can do demo in 1 day . #lifeunderrenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@getmohrcreative Looks like a school house.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@that_mikeyguy Yep. And all adults in my family.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That house is scary guys. #lifeunderrenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BetsyJoye So restful!  :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Okay. Ill give this a go. Just hope I wont get scared off renovating my kitchen. :).   #LifeUnderRenovation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidalangrier My blood sugar just jumped.  :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weedwhacker! #escapetothechateau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The photography of the outside is so gorgeous. #escapetothechateau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No James!  Stay!  #escapetothechateau]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>