<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Queue up like cattle along with 300 other people? Can't go to a restaurant though, or hug my family.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ljubica1 @alison1928 @JuliaHB1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robingrimmer @JuliaHB1 Your 2 tweets counter-argue each other..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NEUnion @GavinWilliamson Also, community transmission is extremely rare, especially amongst children.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrDCross1 @BenthamDale @ianbrown Again, if the vast majority are willfully taking it, then why the need for a passport? If you've got vaccinated, why do you worry about others? How can you "essentially give someone else the virus" ? When its also the disease you're inoculated from?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrDCross1 @BenthamDale @ianbrown When have you ever taken a medical treatment or procedure to protect others? I refer back to the bcg and more statement you made!?!?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NEUnion @GavinWilliamson You're a bunch of psychopaths, pushing medical devices on children with no data to back them up and no risk assessment per child!! Nazis, all of you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hoffers999 @8bitRevolt @alliemig @JoshLeslie17 @ianbrown You won't need  me to have it then, or for me to carry papers, thats good news for me.. now you do you boo-boo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thetimes Do you have the long term data to suggest his concerns are ill-founded?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hoffers999 @8bitRevolt @alliemig @JoshLeslie17 @ianbrown Is it the vaccine or the pass you have the confidence in?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sufcberry @indieimmy @ianbrown As apposed to the media and gov influencing his decision???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeilaniDowding: ...  @lorraine  @reallorraine It is so incredible that these photos meant to be taken a year apart still have the washi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TBoyd81004365 @NoPoke @ClareCraigPath Most mutations are 0.3% difference from the original, but I guess we'll never know due to lack of isolate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolutely disgusted in the customer care at @asda, no checkout staff, losing all scratch bakeries nation wide. What next? Nailbars and hairdressers? @AsdaServiceTeam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClaireL89735308 @EveningStandard @Edwina_Currie @annemcelvoy I've no doubt, because evil people are like that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterStefanovi2: Wow!  We did it!! 10 million views!!   By working TOGETHER we have sent a message to UK media that if they wont hold]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrianOSheaSPI: "Researchers Debate Infecting People on Purpose to Test Coronavirus Vaccines" (Some were against it. Fauci  Covid Passp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@asda @AsdaServiceTeam I've just heard that the Ashford store will be part bake instead of scratch bakery. Im absolutley confounded that you've come to this decision when it's one of the best bakers in the Kent area...it must remain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poll: Would you like to see 'vaccine passports' introduced in Ireland? (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/nQZw7ylCZa the gaslighting comments are severe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@No1Swann @WERD_music @ianbrown Yep..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EveningStandard @Edwina_Currie @annemcelvoy Yeah and those that don't comply should have a yellow star on their lapel so we know to avoid the disease spreaders until a containment camp can be built to hold them all, or maybe even gas them?? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: Why would anyone under 65, not obese/otherwise healthy, with slight risk of any serious effect from COVID, risk blood clots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: It's now not so much a matter of science, but a matter of gathering the evidence, arresting/charging/trying the criminals i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More bad stuff linked to the vax https://t.co/cKlm5UPQx3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats 68,100 preventable deaths thanks to lockdowns, that would bring the excess mortality down to pre covid years.   Still think it's about tour health? https://t.co/ity3hy4bAk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tynewrc: Where are the riot police, the baton charges @pritipatel, wrestling these irresponsible Covid law-breakers to the ground?! htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CraigChrist03 @drdrew I've never met a remotely intelligent pro-mask, pro-vaxxer, pro-lockdown, pro-gaslighter in my life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll make this very simple, you're a Nazi collaborator https://t.co/sxgf2BS9Yx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes texas.. https://t.co/ntXifVyt0w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xNOBRAINx @Complex Get a grip, you're like a child full.of fear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: Don't say you weren't warned. You were. #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/Md8Fj6Wc3B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gollyumami: GO THROUGH YOUR TIMELINE   RETWEET EVERYONE USING THIS HASHTAG,  KEEP IT TRENDING!! #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/qAvYl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattletiss7: Hey Government please dont send me or my family any covid tests as were not ill, (if we have any symptoms well stay hom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KathyConWom: Will you be testing yourself twice weekly so you can get back to doing the things you love?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sGilbs @MPSWandsworth To which 'law' do you refer?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@numbers_truth @TFather1776 @KatyLuciani @davidkurten @metpoliceuk You sure about that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GarySlegg @Dudley1945 @bugeyefly @C19Assembly @ClareCraigPath I never said it was inaccurate, you made that shit up. I said its a research tool, being used as a diagnostic tool when it can NOT be used as such, it can not detect if you're infectious, what part of that is hard???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SirSydneyCamm @PoliticsForAlI @Bel_B30 Its a shame you're so deluded, time to ask questions. https://t.co/xLoD46jW9g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidPhilllips2 @davidkurten Everything you just wrote is fascism, discrimination...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GarySlegg @Dudley1945 @bugeyefly @C19Assembly @ClareCraigPath The first wave was the only wave, the "2nd Wave" was down to respiratory illnesses caused by mask wearing and a misused forensic tool as a diagnostic tool, accrediting all deaths with +pcr as a covid stat. Only reason Y the numbers were high, dropping now due 2 end of flu season.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @C19Assembly: @ClareCraigPath announces the Covid Death Audit which will investigate EVERY official UK Covid death. https://t.co/ZjKAltB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ariel_Adam @diclexicon @ClareCraigPath How is it? What possible logical explanation do you have for this? A study perhaps? Or are you just guessing!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cassa748 @davidkurten Except when they eased the first time after "3 weeks to flatten a curve" look bellow, we're well bellow the averges for this year time.of year. https://t.co/vcoecGyKhY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@riker_dave Where you based?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@riker_dave thanks for the follow, dude.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackSmith1942 @Standby66393769 @davidkurten Perhaps listen to those without vested in the monetary gain from current Gene altering injections, currently peddled as a vax? People in the following fields epidemiology, immunology, infectious disease, pediatrics, preventive medicine, public health, virology. Want some names?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bexbel @davidkurten @FKGPML Reckless? Sitting at home is reckless...these people fight for your freedoms too..  Anti brxit marchers? What about the poll tax marchers on this day in 1991.. if not for them.. grow up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnleabraddarl @carlheneghan You say follow the rules? Do you follow their science too? Cos that being said, SAGE said outdoors its extremely rare to transmit. Also, if youre following the rules you'll be fine.. its not difficult, logic!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidkurten This is a trap.. its too orchestrated.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanpknott @carlheneghan @JuliaHB1 Do you know who the guy is you're replying to? Prat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gypsydog2 @davidkurten A passport to reunite families. Are you for real? Is this 1930s Germany?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GaySimonSub @davidkurten You've lost your marbles, protect and serve.. stupid comment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Smizz_x How are the other 5% of pricks in your life?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeremycorbyn: I will be voting against the Police Crime and Sentencing Bill in Parliament. The last thing the Police need is more power]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoTibballs @sonny8s @ClareCraigPath You've lost the plot, complicity theorists that love lockdowns and "variants" there have been 400,000 variants of this "novel" virus. Get a grip, get your life back.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidkurten And not a single police officer has died from/with/of/within28 days...this "disease"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@billeipzig @Snow_Mufc @davidkurten Oh look, another one who has jo idea how virology works... dick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peter_Clark8 How do you think that went then? Moron]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sunshine2014x @EugenieGrandet9 @MCharlesJ2020 @PrisonPlanet Know them personally, yeah?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buchanan17 @oliveropitz @ClareCraigPath From a car badge that advocates medical ppe mass wearing without proof it works? Without risk assessment and who has no clue how a virus works.. cool story]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@buchanan17 @lcbrown62 @ClareCraigPath 40,000 mutations of this before the "new varriant" mentioned by the gov in December actually was briefly mentioned in September.. look for yourself.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScepticBrian @onthemarch1 @davidkurten Royal family aren't English]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Scorpion1966 @Mad_Hatter_Tea @LauraHu88458980 @davidkurten Doesn't matter, you said it wasn't an experimental vaccine, youve bene shown that it clearly is. Anything else you now have to say, after telling DK to shush up, is irrelevant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rockyadams66 @davidkurten ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CurlyClareToo @ianbrown Move freely? Where are you, jupiter?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Carointhegarden @MandyLorijn1 @davidkurten Are you sure about that? There is no long term evidence that any of these "vaccines" are actually safe. Untill the trials end, then id rather wait.. and not you or anyone else has the right ro take that away...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: World wide Freedom Rally: https://t.co/fSCIerwqyc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@izzyturn3r_ @Ayesee10 @ianbrown Why say no one is listening then?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: Vaccine passports are the latest manifestation of medical fascism. A critical mass of people must resist now: No mask. No]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Burnside_5 @Barbara57595701 @davidkurten @AlexBerenson @NeilClark66 Based on 63million people. Not those that get hospitalised]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: The absolute state of UK police in 2021.  How about catching some real criminals instead of stopping healthy people from e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StuartGlass6 @davidkurten When the vast majority are of the mentioned are vaccinated? Who exactly are they catching it from?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Burnside_5 @Barbara57595701 @davidkurten @AlexBerenson @NeilClark66 Bout the same percentage as the amount of people that die from the virus/disease then?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SarahJa28484793 @davidkurten Have you been to China lately..?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@greg_travis @ClareCraigPath Thats cos everyone who dies has a pcr test and if positive, covid stat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnnycage2013 @KimCarolC @davidkurten Show your face? On twitter? Nutcase..! You complicity theorists are the cowards.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RussellOkung: Teach your children to fact-check the fact checkers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CoastalSe @markus7online @davidkurten But its different from Flu..right? This is the only non isolated virus, as far as I can find, anyway.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: End the lockdown. Vote https://t.co/fjNz8hD7LA https://t.co/SKKjtUiQ4S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rich_wiseman @ZokaShaun @davidkurten When you cant use the correct words or spellings in sentence? You're* Know* Theory* #ComplicityTheorist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidkurten You'd get my vote.... I never have voted in my lifetime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bazofroses: If Boris was to come on TV tomorrow and say this is over. Vaccines work. Pubs and restaurants are open as of wednesday.   W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: The BBC do not deserve a penny in licence fees for spewing out woke rubbish and climate alarmism, let alone an increase in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: Respect to the seven England rugby players who refused to kneel to divisive BLM cultural Marxism. https://t.co/REqg526cA8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: Coercing people into having an experimental injection of RNA or chimp flu by threatening to prevent services and travel fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are you wearing masks in your profile pictures? Snapchat primed all these years?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sure looks that way, yeah. https://t.co/mWxAs1BnHk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A man who wants truth and clarity for all, who was the most qualified to speak against the shambles that is the #UKgov and #SAGE #MikeYeadon Has been deleted from twitter. A witch hunt from the likes of this scum https://t.co/eTl9OSFgTE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidkurten: Report: Large increases in deaths recorded in UK care homes, Israel, Gibraltar, etc after the implementation of 'Covid vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fucking psychopaths, ive more biology degrees than this zionist https://t.co/oJAssZdwb9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: If you think this is only about a virus you are mad, crazy, you're crackers! nuts! Mad as a ship's frog! But we'll forgive yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: MASONiC LOCKDOWN IN YOUR HOMETOWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@barryspicer @MichaelYeadon3 Didn't quite think that one through, huh!?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: The bat was put into your mind as part of the spell. A symbol for the devil minded elite using poodle politicians to hold us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AsdaServiceTeam ill be making an official complaint about the security in your store, Ashford Kent. On most occasions, at the same time every day, I am harassed and questioned about wearing a mask. My complaint will go to head office from my legal representative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this decade I turned 30 split up from my kids mum who, probably the most toxic person in the entire world at 3 Returned to Greece, 2 of the best summers I'd ever had. 33 Turned up in Kent with someone I... https://t.co/jh83Yzuluo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone in Zante, May week of the 19th?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Driving a 400 break bimmer in snow is a lot of fun...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've been in a very dark place, those of you who know me well know how something as damaging can have an adverse... https://t.co/OiqUizf1Mf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess who's back... back again..]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>