<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmpressAdaeze @SpeakOnItTC @JimClyburnSC1 @VP @TimScottSC I saw Godfrey years ago at comedy union in LA. He had ppl falling on the floor in laughter. Hes brilliant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YtH8r: It's a crime just to be African/black in #Amerikkka https://t.co/9vxdAeW474]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NathaniNoShame I would bet some NGO is paying that asshole.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NathaniNoShame: Its the Harriet Tubman disrespect for me from ppl who know she was about that life. She was a fighter. Makes you wonde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Teodrose_Fikre: Paternalism is the most INSIDIOUS form of RACISM::  I'm looking at you "liberals"  neoliberals who are pretending to c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TexasFBA4Ever: @BlackBeautyFBA Facts. The "best" they do is a bunch of pump faking trying to appease the dominant society. That  has]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mr_Blk_First: @BlackBeautyFBA @TexasFBA4Ever Are you really surprised, he let hobama talk him and the rest of the league to resume play]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlackBeautyFBA: @TexasFBA4Ever Lebron is buckbroken. These c0wardly black celebrities are more concerned with their financial well-bein]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TexasFBA4Ever: LeBron says that he "fueled the wrong conversation" in regards to Ma'Khia Bryant and that he was "educated" on Ma'Khia.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Star_BLM: Aaron Lumdsen who is 13 has been missing from the Croydon Area since Fri 30 Apr. He was wearing a blue school blazer and blac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EritreaStruggle: Great conversation on how the Bolivarian Revolution is part of the Pan-African struggle, not something that is on its]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OgbeniDemola: African people are the only people that study the history of other races except their own.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Protecting Racist America While Black https://t.co/UfLCBmXTWU https://t.co/xUfls8rCY6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OliviaHoney11: This very disrespectful and very untrue. Please stop it with your ahistoricism and pseudo-history. And F.Y.I. Harriet Tu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: This was in Fish Fry Clys state of SC but it aint no racism  https://t.co/hjk4VB6yyG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kellie_Pryor: Do it!  Learn it!!!!! https://t.co/ZpZkLcwpsR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Haiti #HaitiaRevolution   They undermine Haiti and Cuba for failure because two strong black nations in the western hemisphere allied with Afrika will pose a threat to white capitalist interest.   The paragraph is from Howard Zinn's A People's History of the United States. https://t.co/gUkIYCxQtB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@madanboukman I saw this video on Democracy Now. I added a piece from Howard Zinn's book A People's History of the United States. #HaitianRevolution   https://t.co/M7cIQLlnMl https://t.co/OuhzNRqV0h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: Jim Crow Joe say if you dont take the jab you die. He aint say shit about the mfs who took it  died  https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaadyNYC: Never EVER Forget https://t.co/Jnj9A4cOHn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brown7Butch: Spiritual warfare is real just because people dont tell you many are being controlled by forces that hate Exposure of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @funshographix: The biggest problem in Afrika today is that many of us don't know our history. We're conquered people. If you look at Af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @askmamalouise: #Ancestorsproclaim You continue to rise to the occasion every time you show up with your sacred sovereign power! Make mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OgbeniDemola: Harriet Tubman was a kidnapped and enslaved African woman, she was an abolitionist, she escaped from slavery and freed ov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OgbeniDemola: I dont believe in Africans in America integrating into the American racist society. I believe in separation. You cant i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alwaysb110 @OfficialKYChick Agreed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alwaysb110: @OfficialKYChick @AfroInsurgent2 I disagree respectfully. I say it's black liberals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nasescobar316: I hit that unfollow button lightning quick after seeing this. I only started following this guy a few days ago. https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrendaSFBA: Look at him Their Holiday planning on big celebration Its my hope my Ppl sit down this day has nothing to do with Black Ame]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GolferGirl305: The Feds are scooping up rappers like ice cream.  Being a rapper is an occupational hazard in itself.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: Word on the curb is that these HBCUs are churning out Kabamas. If you know you know ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialKYChick: The bastardized mind of the Black conservative will be our biggest obstacle in fighting white supremacy. John Henrik]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EmpressAdaeze: African ppl are so complex but humanity has been conditioned to be seen through white male gaze, which is one dimensiona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DillardVicki: About last nights show... https://t.co/kjP8h52i7f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @askmamalouise: #Ancestorssay Your re-awakening will effortlessly support you in releasing what you have learned in exchange for what yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MGT_Modesty: Out here showing love to our men I love it https://t.co/m0ExcVgzTU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brown7Butch: Bill Gates split he gets a 97 yrs old Lawyer I bet Black Folks wish they could Raise Johnny Cochran from the dead. Crump]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Teodrose_Fikre: Jesus Christ! So @euronews  corporate-state media is really trafficking in this level of propaganda? The issue is not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZuluPanther: The murder of #LatashaHarlins will never be forgotten. Just as the physical attacks on Black women in Asian owned stores..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlackAlphaNetw1: The ONLY Black issue Democrats will Support...  "Voter Rights"  The Black Issues Democrats WON'T Support...  Black Rep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BLKLiberation84:  https://t.co/fqrCtMVen3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Teodrose_Fikre: Dude on IG just told me Im being selfish for not wanting my 22 month to be injected with experimental C19 vaccines b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IslamRizza:  - Order here:  https://t.co/llkBVVnKwQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IslamRizza: Work never stops! Hit Las Vegas and now on to the next city! What city cities should we hit??? Honored to be a part of the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @freedomrideblog: You will get no gobbledygook jargon from Black Alliance for Peace. We are precise. CIA won't repeat anything we have t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpeakOnItTC: Im led to believe theyre creating more sleeper agents to help prevent any Black Liberation and strives for Reparations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FirstThemNEWS: Uh oh...  The bootlicks to #democrats are admitting how stupid of a decision they made last November..   https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Snowden: You're seeking a 175-year long sentence for an internationally award-winning publisher of newsdespite protests from the Unite]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davisuniversal: Soon Bill Gates  the media he owns will be telling the masses to kill their own kids in order to save the planet  the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mxmovement: #MalcolmX on progress  reform within the colonial state. See how his charming laugh and demeanour suddenly turns when as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kellie_Pryor: .@VP,  you may wanna send ya gurl a clip of your latest video regarding America not being racist.    Angie Chang missed y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: Yall might have better ears than mines but I know what I heard ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GolferGirl305: People get attacked in NY every day.  When Black people get attacked or white people get attacked, it's never stop racia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaadyNYC I knew of Dane Calloway from years back. This mf denies the Atlantic Slave Trade took place. Hes some self-loathing negro seeking attention or hes an agent on the payroll of some NGO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TexasFBA4Ever: In Hopkinton, Massachusetts a 16 year old Black girl, Mikayla Miller was lynched. @tariqnasheed @BLKLiberation84 @Taurea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dalawhatilike: Bill Gates, Melinda Gates, Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk, Larry Ellison, Cyril Ramaphosa etc etc I wish nothing but death on you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kellyClarence1: "....the child that has his own."   el-Hajj Makil el-Shabazz  https://t.co/ckIfk2ZCvA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MGT_Modesty: We will continue to say NO to all Vaccinations #Elijah #Farrakhan https://t.co/BzolHlekkD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OgbeniDemola: I dont blame Europeans for looting Africa. Europeans are fighting for their own survival, Africans should fight for thei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Godfrey nailed it!   @JimClyburnSC1 @VP @TimScottSC you're scum. https://t.co/mYoldp2pxk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ARTESIA13: Unify us as a people. Melanin people have never been equal in this country.Since the  conception Construction of every Europ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love Jones (1997) https://t.co/Y3geCmrLoS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @indigenoussista: @AfroInsurgent2 Expect to see this hashtag again this summer, pertaining to your tweet  #TheSunSaidNope]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@indigenoussista LOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Shango5T: https://t.co/76BfM8uwHc https://t.co/ID8JakQgq8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Khadijahaynes1: Resist the urge to unload all your personal business and pain on people, instead turn within.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Khadijahaynes1 Yes. I learned this valuable lesson when I got older.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: I cant wait until it comes out that Jim Crow Joe, VP Sista Gurl, Bussy Barry, Fauci  Bill Gates took the placebo inst]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Khadijahaynes1: Don't sleep with people unless you want them to truly be apart of you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No sunscreen needed...it's the #Melanin ...or lack thereof for others   According to the World Health Organization, the top five countries with the highest melanoma deaths are: 1. Australia  2. New Zealand  3. Israel  4. South Africa (white colonizers)  5. Brazil https://t.co/ub2IfHlpti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrNasrAzUllah: Black kids getting sold into The CIA https://t.co/je8GThPFKv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrNasrAzUllah: Just to be fair to Southern,  Howard University has taken the most money from the CIA out of the BIG 5 HBCU'S where they]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrNasrAzUllah: The CIA is in multiple HBCU's, shaping the minds of future spies.These are bad partnerships. You're better off strugglin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AJNash10: The predecessors and descendants of the European, Middle Easterner, and Asian have NEVER liked each other, and that's why the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlackChannel: Is this because Biden was elected too? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dijoni: Did you know that America had labor camps for black American kids and their family long after slavery ended. https://t.co/3cirR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaxHPF: Big Pharma told Biden they aint lifting no waivers and its profits over everything. Yall boy Biden was absolutely positively]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: Fish Fry Cly was digging in his nose while talking to this man  tried to flick a booger on him. He kept his composure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlackChannel: These "polls" are just SATIRE now.  https://t.co/ThGNymos4X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: Wouldnt be surprised if we hear rumblings that he was cheating with men  https://t.co/PlGctajyI5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlackSheepWoke: Has anyone figured out how a vaccine that offers zero immunity by their own words lead to herd immunity? This is beyond]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NathaniNoShame: Did twitter want us to send tweets empathising w/Bill  Melinda or something? I mean they still use philanthropy to pus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are god's children ...people of the sun.  Embrace your #Melanin #melaninpoppin #melaninqueen https://t.co/b3aaGSSowP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Their agenda is using the legacy of Kwame Nkrumah to bring in a quadroon leadership caste in Ghana."  - Khonsu Nok   #DestructionOfBlackCivilization https://t.co/KbOctUIqn0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KingJames: Protect our Young Black Women  Men! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @song_philosophy: On this day in 1933   James Brownis born in Barnwell, South Carolina, but will be raised in Augusta,  James Brown]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kellie_Pryor: They should FORGIVE her and move on.    Did anybody ask the family if they forgive her yet?  Too soon? https://t.co/VFLc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MYAH19794482: CHILDREN OF THE EARTH, WE RELY ON THE EARTH AND THE EARTH RELY ON US. THE EARTH IS BEAUTIFUL, GREEN AND FRESH.PLEASE TOUC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kikispeaks2: Black Americans have mounting proof of a dire need for legislation that protects us from racist hate crimes, police brutal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ajamubaraka: BAP is only Anti-war organization consistently raising issue of Afghanistan and the game being played behind the backs of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamhudson5: And, honestly, if an African-American or any other African diasporan wants to repatriate to Africa to reconnect w/ their i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamhudson5: People think Pan-Africanism is supplanting another African identity w/ the identity you already have  were born with. Tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nunyabiz55: @oncodebrotha83 I just listened to Malcolm X's ballot or bullet speech the other day ... he was like "they got you out ther]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @oncodebrotha83: Aint no racism tho  https://t.co/6dLSHd55yB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RakeemShabazz: This nigga is a pseudo snake https://t.co/W3oVAthYzA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AgentOf11561669: Literally everything White Liberals said that trump was about to do to us they are literally doing NOW   And ne9ros we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @andrewbostom: 1/ Oped by Clinician/Epidemiologists: Whats the rationale for vaccinating children for COVID-19? Wheres the data, the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AgentOf11561669: @AJNash10 Thats why I always be clear to say Older Black Voters instead of just old ni99as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AgentOf11561669: The BLM organization has released a list of Demands and Majority of it Deals with Trump and the Capitol rioters   Thes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Black_Action: 'Slaves loved their masters': GOP women's club president defends lawmaker's pro-slavery comments https://t.co/j9cAvm2v86]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>