<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zarahsultana: This you? https://t.co/4SxKkCGgDv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zarahsultana: This you? https://t.co/5muAQcJSPL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidLammy: For my own mental well-being I am not doing media interviews on the race commission today. Like so many in Britains Black]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Altook Pro direct soccer does the current away shirt. Etsy does some decent remakes but the quality is a bit hit and miss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone checked on Aldo?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jamesdrodriguez: The merseyside derby is ours.  https://t.co/VBBYLUXfcc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sav4efc: Day 78..... https://t.co/86rPOx2sdb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[El Diego https://t.co/3M81tLrOPE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JimMFelton: Feeding kids              Bombing kids https://t.co/VmeM9FTmzU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScotteeIsFat: Empty plates left outside the local Tory HQ and Con Club after Southend West MP voted against feeding children most at ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AccidentalP https://t.co/2KwXG9wTAy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AccidentalP: "Hang on, you can't book me and ask me to pull out when Cliff Thorburn becomes available again. No look, you've got a choi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardian_sport: Marcus Rashford: A significant number of children are going to bed tonight not only hungry but feeling like they do no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mikeado: Makes a change for the kopites to be sending death threats to another team's keeper rather than their own I suppose]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LF_1906: The game is gone. https://t.co/Y3BwbyHiCp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarkOgden_: Everton need a reality check: Moyes is the best they can get https://t.co/bzcXB5O9KX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @awaybusblue1878: @jamesdrodriguez on the echo falls @SkySports @Everton  UTFT https://t.co/xZkaMAjiAG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Saint_Vespaluus: He's the most unlikely modern day Jesus you could imagine, and what an awesome human being in this land run by crimina]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASlavitt: BREAKING: The NBA just announced that all basketball arenas will he turned into 2020 voting locations.  Ample space for large]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Saint_Vespaluus: Neville Southall had no post-16 education, but he listened, cared and educated himself, developing an empathy and an e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zarahsultana: Migrants don't rob the public purse of billions of pounds.  That's tax dodgers.  Migrants don't buy influence  subvert d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlack_Watch: Our new issue is out in two weeks. This feature with ex-EFC Mark Leonard is one of the highlights. With no matches to s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CapitalLivNews: Liverpool will lift the Premier League trophy for the first time in the club's history tonight following the match agai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MirrorPolitics: Tory MPs vote down legal bid to protect the NHS in a US trade deal https://t.co/Tr1T4QwC4j https://t.co/62IylywVhC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Revenge is like serving cold cuts https://t.co/mwSJkAg2qu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alexandra_kuri: pint of carling please love, oop while youre down there, sorry cant say that anymore can you, cant even say youre e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CursedFootball: https://t.co/p2PqKUEUh3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brian_ban: The difference. https://t.co/o1FDsKk0gH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tories gonna be rifling through Rashfords bins for dirt this afternoon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BeardedGenius: It's fucking heartbreaking that there's working-class lads out there, struggling to make ends meet, who'll defend this m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tessicat: Were sorry that you feel it was disgraceful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hannah_natanson: The fence outside the White House has been converted to a crowd-sourced memorial wall  almost like an art gallery  t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jackeparrock: A crowd has climbed onto the statue of colonial King Lopold II in #Brussels chanting murderer and waving the flag of t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @classicshirts: Ed Miliband with a classic Champ Manager shelf   Via @FSWorldUK https://t.co/eXyKJiDnqy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @doctor_oxford: Yesterday the UK, population 66 million, had more deaths from #COVID19 than the *entire* EU, population nearly 450 milli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArmsControlWonk: Here you go. https://t.co/ApWhyxr6EN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bfeinzimer: The crowd is chanting I dont see no riot here, why are you in riot gear? https://t.co/DniKZKZkp9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrianReade: Never again can Johnson and his band of wealthy, right-wing conmen tell working-class voters that they're anti-Establishmen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Life_Disrupted: Walter White was also caring for his wife and child.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hassan_akkad: I hope you can help my get this message delivered to Mr, PM @BorisJohnson https://t.co/xUDl1rBPmu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mikegalsworthy: This superb video has now clocked past 3 million views.  Its a brutal 3-minute summary of New Zealands success vs the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some people are so far behind they think theyre winning https://t.co/QdOTebu4F4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NaomiAKlein: This is my first major piece of writing since the pandemic began. Because, well  pandemic and folks in my orbit were sick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ByDonkeys: .@BorisJohnson ignored the gathering storm, downplayed the threat then failed to act. He's not Churchill. Hes Chamberlain.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tomemoore: Can @MattHancock or @BorisJohnson_MP please confirm if it is true that the Gov won't be seeking a refund as it has lost the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RWGbluenose: Best thing on twitter for ages https://t.co/UOiFSHc7Is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Independent: All the MPs who voted against giving nurses a pay rise in 2017 https://t.co/uv05vIY3UB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PFR187: Incredible that they've managed to convince people that the NHS is a more like charity that needs donations from the public, ra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BareLeft: Not sure what's happening in that Emily Maitlis trend, but always remember that when she talks about preventing inequality fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DaftLimmy: https://t.co/fzIDfa9P4j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @di1cox: https://t.co/wufTbK3RVH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liquid football https://t.co/nqRTU3vmtY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elect a Clown, Expect a Circus. https://t.co/rUDWvluGoO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judging by todays papers the latest Toryopath blame pivot has lined up the general public, EU and China for NHS staff having to wear bin bags. Impressive diversion tactics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaulStaniforth: In June 2017 every Tory MP except 1 voted to oppose giving NHS nurses a proper pay rise. When the result of the vote wa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LucyScotford: You vote tory then you clap? Fucking hypocrites. The tories have been selling the NHS off, choking it to death, shitting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewCesare: Gangs in the Rio de Janeiro favelas have enforced a lockdown from 8pm tonight. The statement reads: "If the government wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sid_lambert: Its the 16th anniversary of Duncan Ferguson enjoying some playful banter with Steffen Freund.  Bring yer dinner.  https:/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @georgeeaton: The UK is the only major country in Europe not to have announced that it will subsidise employees wages or make direct ca]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jmemc55: You truly do love to see it  https://t.co/Sw736AsgNA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thhamilton:  https://t.co/fAc0tgyqbc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neonrated: Understandable, he can't read. #Parasite #BestPicture #Bong2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KateFlood: Kate and William spent 1,000,000 resurfacing their driveway so maybe she should fuck off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolute state of this Tory Meff https://t.co/6FwkjJdtfg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TracyBrabin: Disco outfit now available on eBay with all proceeds going to @Girlguiding https://t.co/RPUA8UiKhN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some great gk kits here #bignev https://t.co/wxnwg9IeiJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlack_Watch: Up the mighty Toffees https://t.co/F5qatV2Dyq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant beat a smash and grab. Best away in a long while]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @visualsatire: Tony Soprano with the face of Alan Brazil. https://t.co/1P66jAoSsM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_OliviaBlake: There's no place in Sheffield for hate speech - please stand in solidarity with LGBTQ+ people to oppose Frank Graham's pl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaThunberg: My gap year ends in August, but it doesnt take a college degree in economics to realise that our remaining 1,5 carbon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @foolsgold_: More than 200,000 raised to get Big Ben to bong for Brexit.  Meanwhile Im spending 50 of my own money to ensure the kids]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Idea for programme train mishaps. Like Portillos show but instead of wearing pink trousers and being a bell end focus is on drinking cans / eating sarnies. Stop offs in local towns will consist of trying to find a pint for under 2 then having a straightener with a local thug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AngelaRayner: Mark why not instead donate a 1,000 to yr local food bank, homeless charity, or fighting poverty. Think how good that wo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The last sentence https://t.co/cBBAfcmXrU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sid_lambert: 43-year-old Francesco Totti pinging in goals like hes pissing about on Sensible Soccer is precisely the sort of content I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheMichaelMoran: This prediction was bang on the money. It's just the dates and names that were wrong. https://t.co/1XJmuVMV5t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tanger_Dreaming: David Moyes: New West Ham manager says winning is 'what I do'..........42% of the time. https://t.co/RZb1DqyRRP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Knighthood for IDS #PeoplesGovernment #oneofus #toryopath https://t.co/WruJxErW7t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoeNBC: Who said it?  I never understood wind. You know, I know windmills very much. Gases are spewing into the atmosphere. You know w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlack_Watch: On sale behind the bar @TheSpellow today - ask behind the bar and look out for the ramshackle makeshift sign - and from]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HichamYezza: Sometimes one needs to re/state the obvious in its stark, naked, undeniable ugliness to make people see it.  https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biggest fraud in the business this fella https://t.co/IYNK5y8Eud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @akalamusic: That Corbyn was called a racist probably more times than any other person in this nations - mildly colourful - history is a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get Genny Savastano in the dugout for Saturday, Carlo #forzatoffees https://t.co/usIUGW3QdX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just seen that the bloke who advocated forced labour camps a few weeks ago won his seat and now Im off to down a pint of Domestos #happyfriday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bertie_Wooster Aye, theyve dug their own graves]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People of Blythe, Im sure bojo has got your back!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamtweets85: Due to austerity, Blyth Valley has 14,847 (24.18%) children living in poverty.   26.7% of households are classed as fuel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spot on https://t.co/X9CHTPy2BN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidschneider: The poor are depending on you. As are the sick. The vulnerable. The disabled. The old. Doctors. Nurses. Teachers. Minor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#VoteLabour and kick these lying charlatans out of office]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OwenJones84: Everyone needs to watch this. https://t.co/U2gnx8RP6n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeremycorbyn: This never happened.  Invented by the Tories to divert your attention from a child having to lie on a hospital floor; rep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_OliviaBlake: Today we ran 8 doorknocking sessions and a phonebank!   Same again tomorrow!  We have 5 days left to transform this cou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck the Tory gobshites. You either care about other people or you dont]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets go down in style! https://t.co/gd56MKCWRV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @googlyeyecat: Just fuck off now @Everton he's just been fined for sending abusive messages to his ex-wife.  https://t.co/2XUMHEVlH2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dog whistle racism here by the chief toryopath https://t.co/rAz19PkaJk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philn1 Absolutely!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>