<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NormanBrennan: A very remarkable man!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @grizzlybr: Serco the Serpent company ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LynnClark1 Your not wrong]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@celebrityradio What time you on? did not get home until 18 mins past 6 were you on, can't see anything???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Waterstones @theartoffunnews  I thought you supposed to write what you know. Wouldn't buy  it for any of my children ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A real vaccine then. https://t.co/O79b20fmpf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ProKlausSchwab I'm wondering if this divorce is so that she can have half the money and therefore it's protected when he eventually gets penalised for the evil he has thust on the world.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheConWom: Vaccinating children is a crime against humanity, top banker warns   Administering a new vaccine with a new technology to an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: Whistle-blowing NHS Board Member says The Government are committing Genocide, and your children arenext https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read this look at the data. mRNA seems to affect the lymphatic system the most..... https://t.co/bu2ot0rnWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@org_scp Dear reader do not download  any app whatever they call it. It's biometric surveillance it will collect information about you and relay it back to people you don't even think about. But they will have control over your life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdvertMan999 @petemorristwit Mmm like the Kung flu virus escaping from the lab....... accidentally ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@educationgovuk @DrAmirKhanGP Child abuse.....stop it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SafeSchools_UK: Hate crime is not the only thing that trans groups such as Stonewall have too much influence over. They are also exerti]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKIP_PBO: Hundreds of #Peterborough voters suddenly applied for postal votes at the last minute, many from the same groups of estates.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At the same old game of voting fraud again. https://t.co/XQaiJhk8Yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peaceful ones in the vicinity by any chance? Just before the fire broke out. https://t.co/4F7YggAMSP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngelaCockburn2 @Iromg The news is ok, but the music . I know it has to be something that doesn't need to be paid for....but uh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PompeyPals: Remembering the Blitz 1941: Freddy Harrison (aged 6). With his little hands he tore away debris and rescued sister Winifred]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Christi75367510: Which of the big supermarket chains will be the first to do their own research on mask wearing and scrap them? Whoever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brexitblog_info: Whats the matter with these people?  Emily Maitlis, lockdown hypocrite Beth Rigby and Laura Kuenssberg have all abuse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sjsampford @WendyPuerto @MSANNCOOPER Globalis just want to do what the EU's doing on a larger scale. We got out the EU .We are not going to sign up to even greater control from the globalist/technocrats ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @celebrityradio:  INSPIRING!   This is a leader!   #RonDeSantis frees Florida from ALL Kung Flu laws from July 1st and is putting an e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GovStitt: I am withdrawing Oklahoma's COVID-19 State of Emergency effective tomorrow, May 4.   Our 7-day average of new cases is down 9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YvetteHenson ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HotelLubyanka: Thread. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@airstripone84 @JuliaHB1 @DayTimeTony ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Political1010 @JuliaHB1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheEUEducator @JuliaHB1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: NEW: Please answer  retweet this poll. Of the people you *personally* know, how many are now routinely breaking the Covid ru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaWebbe When is it ever the parent's responsibility to take care of their children?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GlynMcbride: @ShivversLaw https://t.co/ehdr4d0RRD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IranHrm: #Iran authorities threaten political prisoner #VahidAfkari  with death if he does not confess  #HumanRights  https://t.co/XqNp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tractorgirly: The SNP has abandoned the poor - Think Scotland https://t.co/mvETifWsJH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RupertLowe10 @ChristineEasda1 They are all geared up for biometric surveillance, under the agenda of "build back better" all for the World Economic Forums delight. Technocrats will rule us. IF WE LET THEM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DJ_DarrenJames: Dr John Lee on talk radio with @Iromg talking more sense than I have heard in the last 15 months I would love to hear M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristineEasda1: The concept of Net Zero is as dishonest and dangerous as Zero Covid, and being pushed for the same reasons. WEF elites]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RomyCerratti: Prof John Lee is an absolute hero and one of the brave scientists whove kept me from despair throughout these dark times]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeonardRoxon: Looks about right! https://t.co/yGqsuVBjQ8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fed up with hearing "protect the NHS" their so bloody protected they're not really seeing anybody.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@b88949110 @avril86755253 @estherclimate Tell your boss to get stuffed. Bot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let's remind ourselves of Bill and his agenda. @BorisJohnson   don't let him buy the UK.  https://t.co/50SBChsxLZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NileGardiner Can't be bothered with Harry and his minger wife.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ft_content @NTTDATAServices That's  the plan , the great reset, world economic forum do you think with stupid]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RaheemKassam: A prime example of Chinese wu mao army activity which Twitter allows is @BAgrestic.  Brand new account. No followers. Fol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Zuchmir @BAgrestic Chinese Communist Party infected the world  with Covid. No bats involved.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: If you own a pub , restaurant , cafe, Hotel or an events business, please join our movement against Vaccine Passports. BOTH my]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jay_Beecher Because they will move the goal posts and when winter comes they will bring it in again because it's about control. until we have biometric surveillance otherwise known as a health passport. They will not stop.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do not give foreign aid to China. https://t.co/IiDMMfrxuG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They are going to make life so difficult for people that haven't been jabbed, that you will in the end give in and get one, or three as the case maybe. a third way will be created , the children's fault and the people that haven't been vaccinated. https://t.co/8GAWPAU3hK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jen70717630: I won't be signing petitions for change. Org. https://t.co/wxkLIDWdlZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jen70717630 @paulrey99 Waste of time only one to sign is the official Westminster ones. Not that they take much notice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There goes the neighbourhood again https://t.co/10hQKK81qK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Antipolluters: CANCELLED for expressing and opinion - a widely held opinion at that! https://t.co/FKHuDwvt5B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Only the left and block him out , the test of us still believe in him. So Let's tell them he is not Cancelled. And they must stop being so childish. https://t.co/R6C916s2S8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScotTories: Just another example of the SNP's soft-touch justice system   Our Victims Law would end early release and put the worst cr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Im hearing the service stations are packed today with indoor diners. A real kick in the teeth for those Publicans/Restaurant o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StopFundingHate ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: Sigh. You're not defending trans rights, @jameelajamil, you're destroying women's and girls' sport.   *She can't possibly re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CatharineHoey: It really is outrageous when you think how @ChiefConPSNI allowed a huge funeral crowd to gather and then parade with not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Alexverycalm: Is it time @bbclaurak to resign ?  RT please@]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rob_Kimbell: While Sadiq Khan is chauffeur-driven around town in a bullet-proof luxury vehicle, his policies would force market traders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rob_Kimbell @Dojo50113598 The Chinese Communist Party wins again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LittleBoats2020: "More than a quarter of British mosques don't have a space for women at all"   Why don't the BBC just come out  say]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@b88949110 @avril86755253 @estherclimate No it's abusing the Royal family. Ignorant much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That they do. https://t.co/pADo3qKPR4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LisaFrideborg @wilkiegog Was out Saturday did not sign did not were a mask no problems. Two different pubs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TiceRichard: WATCH THIS WARNING by @drdavidbull about what vaccine passports will mean if govt proceeds: thin end of wedge, your medica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Unlocked_UK_: YouTube have blocked our film with Dr John Lee we are in the processing of appealing.   Here is the link to watch it on F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not a fan of Russell brand but this is very interesting. It's about Bill Gates and how basically he's trying to colonize farming and take over the world along with his cronies.  https://t.co/FIDsZrQI9u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reformparty_uk: A warning about vaccine passports  From @drdavidbull https://t.co/zGLCz6VJeM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LozzaFox: Tens of thousands of jobs are at risk from Sadiq Khan's plans for an outer London tax.  As your mayor, I will scrap Sadiq's b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HotelLubyanka: 21st June 2021. #RedLineDay . Every single one of you that knows what is going on needs to work with others locally and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GuidoFawkes You know what. No to your masks,Not your biometric surveillance. Stick you bloody Frankenstein jab.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeneralGammon @GuidoFawkes Refuse to do it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IvWoodsy: Is this murder racist? https://t.co/3r9v4BgPZ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Floyd's parents done an excellent job bring up their boy's. Absolute pillars of society  https://t.co/SUUVa3Oo5h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Max46023367: @VMaledew A Warning about Vaccine Passports from Dr David Bull...please share the Message  retweet https://t.co/8TZ6bT3Fm5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrP_MD: Lockdowns don't work to stop viruses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Blood362: Just asking... Why is the Indian Government able to Afford a gigantic statue that cost over 400 million  And a Space Program]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @darrengrimes_: Preaching about Christ? Youre nicked mate.  Pulling down statues and desecrating war memorials? Set yourself away.   Pe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna Parents are mad. You don't know about this so called vaccine. It may cause cancer, infertility anything could happen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @missalicegrant: So the Track  Trace app was a precursor to the Vaccine Passport, which the government are rolling out with no debate,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @112Lock: @UKLabour https://t.co/eoeVkorQox]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @org_scp:  Your private health info should stay between you, your GP,  on highly secure servers, only to be shared in a very limited s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @org_scp:  #COVID19 vaccination 'status' is already available on the #NHS app via *acute medication history*.   Your private health in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrewLawDesign What are you the banner police?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Classic, perfect reaction to the BBC https://t.co/78sjGtutHj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LabourAreToast: Armed police tasered a man harassing people at a shop in London yesterday after he pulled out an axe.  If youre one of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Love to see it, it shows that those at top of power, know theres no risk now. The same with Boris walking round the cafe with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DR ROGER HODKINSON, MD SPECIALIST IN PATHOLOGY. THE MOST GRAVE INJUSTICE EVER. https://t.co/VbFCyuI0yO via @BitChute]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marty_Caine @Facebook Facebook , YouTube, Twitter all think they have the right to push their own narrative , and block anyone with an alternative view. Yes they are private companies but they're created for us. If we don't use them there is no need for them ,goodbye advertising revenue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicoliarSturge1 What's an awkward bunch ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bilks @PaulWat28159557 I was on it, I am absolutely fine and all my friends that were on it are all well. We walked 11 miles. Spoke to lots of people. No mask's.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charlie10cc: One for all the Vets.  Respect. https://t.co/Ikv9Uu7NFU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SueC00K: These dire egregious ads. 320m. Of our money. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is disgusting. Where are the police to shew them off. How dare they. https://t.co/dAh21dUzPS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Gates! The crazy man. https://t.co/1RWX7w32KJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JaneLor81308510: so #BillGates new vaccines lower population  heres me thinking vaccines supposed to save lives? We all need to giv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lienomail: Here's a picture of a plank !!!  He's thinking about building a fence to sit on. https://t.co/rQGKk8gdaF]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>