<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stacey_rudin: Lockdowns give weak, insecure nobodies a platform to dominate other people. Now we know: we share this planet with millio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I will be away for a bit for obvious reasons. I also just cant read anymore about how wonderful lockdowns are or how I need a passport to go to the beach this summer. Ill be back. God bless. Stay strong. Please give it one more day. #EndTheLockdowns #covidhoax #TrudeauMustGo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is evil. People have lost everything over this scamdemic. Suicides are rampant and you are dancing and laughing at our pain. Im too upset to say anymore. https://t.co/8PYJ5eb86B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada is dying  so many Covid cult members are happy to watch us all die. #EndTheLockdowns https://t.co/c3pWzybFs1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoMore  Those people gleefully demanding more lockdowns are sick. Do they understand what they are doing? https://t.co/KhW07KaV4H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cloakzy Very sorry to hear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My head is a mess. Ill write more later. We cant keep doing this. Suicide and depression are at all time highs. Ive fought with clinical depression myself. Banning gyms  places of worship have done so much damage to people. Physical  spiritual health go hand in hand for many]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A friend of mine just took his life because of these lockdowns. He said this is existing not living, something Ive heard many others say. With news today that Ontario may go back to code red  how they have falsified PCR tests to get a higher count . Its just too much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rpoconnor: While Toronto Medical Officer of Health @epdevilla asks the province to continue to ban gyms and in-person dining, the Leafs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ezralevant: Doug Ford believes this is a clever trick. It's the opposite. It proves that the lockdown class looks after its own and pun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rpoconnor: How much longer are Toronto councillors going to allow the Medical Officer of Health @epdevilla to mislead the public about]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow. If anyone needed further proof the government is at war with Canadians this is it. They denied his motion then agreed to cut his salary. Those in power want and need us to be bankrupt  #iStandWithRoman #cerb #FordfailedOntario https://t.co/V1EHODvZUH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robertbenzie: Independent MPP @Roman_Baber denied unanimous consent for his bill to slash MPPs salaries. But @PaulCalandra gets unanim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpencerFernando: Despicable: After Roman Baber Asks Ontario MPPs To Live On CERB, Legislature Gives Unanimous Consent To Cutting Only B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: This is messed up. Whatever you think of @Roman_Baber and his bill, he's clearly trying to draw attention to the hardship]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier @ctvedmonton @BrianPallister fined/arrested many pastors, ministers Rabbis in Manitoba. RCMP eventually refused his illegal orders but that didnt stop Pallister. He hired some sort of environmental cops to continue attacking The Church  synagogues. Its sick seeing what Canada has become]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well said.   Wow crazy reading the hate on this tweet. I cant imagine living like that, someone passes  people laugh  celebrate mocking those that cared about the deceased. Thats just sad. #RushLimbaughRIP https://t.co/MkSsgKHrtO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dbongino Amen. Well said sir.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Roman_Baber: At 3pm I will introduce a Bill  seek Unanimous Consent to cut the pay of all MPPs to the amount of the CERB ($500 per wee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@QuestionAwaken I agree. Im not doing well mentally. The hate coming from those in power along with the lies and continued power grab just exhaust me. But thats the point. Our leaders need us broken, we cannot give them the pleasure. But some days its tough. I hate what the world has become.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CFIB Very sorry to hear.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RiseUp2021: @smile28554950 ON adjusted the PCR testing going against the WHO recommendations. The false positives will now sky rocket!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@smile28554950 ON adjusted the PCR testing going against the WHO recommendations. The false positives will now sky rocket! As far as I know all other provinces are using the recommended test cycling, which is why cases are dropping.  @fordnation simply must justify more lockdowns anyway he can!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: Yup. The news of the fast decline in Canada's cases (and hospitalizations) isn't being amplified anywhere near as much as]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FranksBullitts Ya why not our students have a right to feel safe. I would 100% agree with that. All kids should feel safe.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miss ya Big Guy. #rushlimbaugh https://t.co/lVYO94XUn4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @johnrich: When I was on Celebrity Apprentice, Rush Limbaugh made a donation of $100,000 dollars to St Jude Children's Hospital to suppo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecjpearson: But say whatever you want about Rush, I guess. Show us how dark your heart is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thecjpearson: If Nancy Pelosi died and you celebrated it, youd be banned from Twitter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkDice @ezralevant All the left has is hate. Its sad . When someone I disagree with politically passes away I feel for their family. I pray for them. Im sure they were loved. They may have been wonderful we just didnt see eye to eye on issues. I would never want to live my life filled with hate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheAffinityMag You made a typo. He will be remembered as a hero, patriot , family man  humanitarian .  Dont feel bad Im a terrible speller. Thank God for spell check. Rest In Peace sir. God bless.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonkeyKonging: If ppl cannot see the hypocrisy  two-tier class system in ON, they never will.   And if you do see it, and tolerate i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @govkristinoem: Rush Limbaugh often said I have talent on loan from God. He understood that our gifts on this earth are not our own ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canada too! #TrudeauFailedCanada https://t.co/ipCZUCR30s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @denisrancourt: It's perfect: You cannot fight an entire ecology of respiratory disease viruses, so obviously you must keep giving more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: You campaign material didn't say you planned to collaborate with ethnic genocide and call it "different norms." My grandmot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @janagatien73: In theory, vaccines are helpful when there is no treatment, but are unnecessary when effective treatments  preventitive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: R.I.P Rush. A true American legend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rest In Peace Rush. Wow, not what I wanted to hear today. Very sad news. Such a legend. He will never be forgotten. #rushlimbaugh #RestInPeace]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Rush showed us the way https://t.co/gLQ7ukCrdH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ginacarano was right. History is repeating itself right before our eyes.  #COVID19 #GinaCaranoWasRight #Dictatorship https://t.co/7Oha6TRa19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: Something that should be so patently obvious, intuitive and without question. Any Dr who fails to provide an exemption sh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im almost impressed how governments were able to brainwash people so quickly. Less than a year and many now believe we must mask humans for life as humans are the virus. https://t.co/Ih7pBAJaYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TakeOffTheMasks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndyBird21 The narrative has really changed to WE are all sick. Humans are the virus. Im seeing more  more people believing we must mask people for life, Covid or no Covid, as WE are the plague. How governments were able to brainwash people so quickly is outstanding. Im almost impressed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nationalpost @healthing_ca Every other study says the exact opposite...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario is cranking the PCR tests up again in order to get a higher case count to justify new lockdowns. Its a scam people. If you need to alter the testing to get false positives its clear you are not concerned with health! @fordnation #pcr #PCRtest https://t.co/milnttOS6r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EWoodhouse7: End mask mandates.  Let people choose.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what Biden  Trudeau support. Of course this is just the tip of the iceberg. Forced sterilization  murder are also approved by Trudeau and Biden! Evil. #Uyghurs #UyghurGenocide #trudeau #biden #Genocide #china https://t.co/eVymWkclOb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CanAditude Thank god for these brave people! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank god for our health care staff.... https://t.co/yqGDrCUSWK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We wont be safe until all viruses/colds/flus are gone. Until then lockdown!  #CovidZero is literally that stupid. Its tyranny and nothing more. https://t.co/BLIFT1izUu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ValValpuriam: Go Roman! Expose Doug and his band of crooks. Thanks for taking a stand against the political class. A breath of fresh ai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: This was the one time Dr Barbra Yaffe went off script and said what was true, and not what was in the talking points prov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TakeOffTheMask https://t.co/jHSu6XDyyb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...and yet all the leaders want are more lockdowns! Heck Ontario altered its PCR tests back so as to increase case counts going against WHO regulations. They will never stop. #pcr #covidagenda #covid1984 #endthelockdown #NoMoreLockdowns https://t.co/eANUHxd6UX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation must be removed from office. Personally I feel he should be brought up on charges for the LTC deaths  the illegal lockdowns. But removal from office is a must! #FordfailedOntario #fordcovidfails #DougFord #ontario #Hypocrites https://t.co/1RgmBNb5vZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHO finally did what we had been asking since day one and adjusted the PCR test so it would be more accurate. All of a sudden cases drop. Ontario quietly jacked the test back up  their cases went up again  now looks like parts of ON will lockdown again based on these lies https://t.co/Zhuf4pFVuI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FreedomofSpeech #censorship https://t.co/jV9mLvbfsw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...and I see parts of Ontario going back into lockdown. The scam never ends. #covidhoax #covid19hoax #pcr #PCRtest #FordfailedOntario https://t.co/aWhbsDJ6mX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JCCFCanada: BREAKING NEWS! Justice Centre sues federal government for forcible confinement of travellers  https://t.co/jh1OHYCkZI https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: "Running out of energy in Texas is like starving to death at the grocery store - you can only do it on purpose - and T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AlbertaLeonidas: It is actually easier, cheaper and less legally problematic to be an illegal gun owner in Canada than than a legal one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bret_Sears: Are Vaccine Passports still a conspiracy theory like they were a few months ago?  Coronavirus insanity gets confusing somet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ToniaBuxton: Im so sadden by our Government, why dont they understand that Lockdowns are causing much more harm than Covid  they do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NickHudsonCT: A single chart can say so much. This one tells the story of how overblown models stoked a mania, how lockdown benefits we]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth I cannot believe Biden came out in favour of the genocide. This isnt a left wing/right wing issue. We must act now and save the muslims being slaughtered in China!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cannot believe Biden came out in favour of the genocide. This isnt a left wing/right wing issue. We must act now and save the muslims being slaughtered in China! https://t.co/QAT2XomPkM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep it up! @MaximeBernier has my vote. Dont let anyone silence you! https://t.co/NGTLqawOZd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now is the perfect time to buy a gun. Just saying. #trudeaugunban #gunbuyback #buyagun #guns #trudeau #TrudeauMustGo #canada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: It will only be temporary lockdown probably not more than two weeks to flatten this new variant. I suspect with only 200]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: A main argument for locking down Ontario was to lessen the burden on hospitals. But the number of people in hospital with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Damn Joe. He had previously mentioned the genocide. Seems he now sides with @JustinTrudeau and is in favour of torture, sterilization, and murder! https://t.co/7kqka0O19N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatTelegraph: Newfoundland COVID Testing Likely to Generate False-Positives  #cdnpoli #nlpoli #COVID19   https://t.co/uWot5lT8EA https:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust the science ? I prefer to trust the facts. #FactsNotFear https://t.co/zs5dOUqJkT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WeAreCanProud: #BREAKING: Justin Trudeau is turning his back on science. His government's vaccination guidelines want Canadians priorit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KimberlyNeudorf: Wearing a mask isn't actually respectful or helpful. Being respectful  loving isn't done by propagating peoples fals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @randyhillier: @onnimikki Actually all the peer reviewed studies demonstrate that lockdowns and masks have had no effect on spread. Imag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FactsNOTfear #BidenTravelBan #Florida #EndTheLockdowns #NoMoreLockDown #ImpeachBidenNow #impeachBiden #floridacovid #covidfacts https://t.co/YOGLhdWT0V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlueEyes653755: https://t.co/Od2YbXnYLK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mamorris777: TRUDEAU GOVT wants to take legal, non-automatic  highly regulated firearms from Licensed Legal Firearms Owners... To tack]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TravelGoC @GovCanHealth Call your lawyer. Trudeaus Covid concentration camps and mandates are illegal. Follow @RebelNewsOnline for more info on how to fight fines and get your freedom back.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brianlilley: The new gun legislation from @JustinTrudeau isnt about public safety its about politics, winning votes and wedging oppon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Awesome! #freedomIsEssential]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fivefivesix_ca: New poll.  Should the City of Calgary ban handguns?   https://t.co/YmzBrHa5Sw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelfingKyle: Where is the voice of opposition for Canadian gun owners.   The @CPC_HQ has been silent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Criminals get guns. Law abiding citizens lose theirs. Is this Canada or Bidens America?  #bidenGunGrab #trudeaugungrab #buyAgun #gun #guns #GunControl #GunBan #TrudeauMustGo https://t.co/ZOnKZL9Cl4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlushingBelles: Welcome to Canada. Where we're so inclusive our government divides everyone into little groups and pits them against ea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How is Trudeau still in office? I wonder if suspending elections out east is just a trial run for Canada? Will we have free elections or will we go the way of USA  live with perpetual election fraud? Im honestly not sure. If we are able to vote, then Im voting @peoplespca https://t.co/KJdn08r4gX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#TrudeauMustGo #NoNewNormal #NoGreatReset https://t.co/aWA4GSJ4gU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: Premier @fordnation, Minister @celliottability, Im willing to personally arrange a virtual public roundtable for you with th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im not an antiVaxxer. Im not even against the Covid shot in theory. Just know this is an untested medicine. Also taking the shot still means you must wear masks  still get Covid  transmit Covid. So at this point Why risk it? #COVID19 #COVIDVaccine #GreatReset https://t.co/JyIfUOQpzR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rpoconnor Even in USA gyms are safe.  Gyms are far more than places to build big biceps. As someone who has worked with people suffering depression the gym has been almost a miracle cure for many. Closing them is killing people.  Not to mention working out strengthens the immune system! https://t.co/tzrXpvok7E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rpoconnor The lockdowns simply are not based on science https://t.co/9jHAd2jf6B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: From an open letter signed by over 100 Canadian doctors, including many paediatricians: https://t.co/MRKEt2hK9u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@politicsfisher @ColinDMello Even in USA gyms are safe. #keepgymsopen. Healthy fit people have stronger immune systems. Facts. https://t.co/shjWMu3FqU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The facts do not support the hatred towards the fitness industry. Most provinces had zero cases connected to any fitness type Center. The mental health damage from denying people fitness however has been massive! #NoMoreLockdowns #gymsareessential #gyms #covidhoax https://t.co/id8n1kNBPW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rpoconnor The facts do not support his hatred of health and fitness https://t.co/naf7qSEyt9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@politicsfisher @ColinDMello #factsNOTfear https://t.co/Urap5LRssK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@politicsfisher @ColinDMello The facts dont support your lockdown agenda. Gyms nation wide resulted in almost no Covid cases. Most provinces had ZERO cases contacted to gyms.  The mental health damage from denying people a healthy lifestyle on the other hand. #gymsareessential #healthisessential]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>