<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WINDOCTORRX: Democrats pushed impeachment for 4 years. Republicans won't even mention what every Trump supporter knows.  THE ELECTION W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: Gun disarmament really means gun concentration in the hands of government.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Matthew_4_Trump: This American will not be vaccinated and I'll be celebrating July 4th.  I don't take orders from illegitimate traitors]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SKYRIDER4538: What happened to our men?  This is sad! https://t.co/52848pbWQx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GoodGri81780290: That is the most perfect reason why people should show respect, in addition to the fact that they cant give anything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @benshapiro: How is it not the biggest story in the country that one of the jurors in the most important criminal justice trial in moder]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: The state of New York is giving illegal immigrants $15,000.00 and automatic voting registration w/o valid i.d. or social]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec How cruel :(]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lsferguson: The election was stolen.  Just watching how hard they are fighting the audit in Arizona tells all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThePatsGazette: REPORT: Chauvin juror attended Black Lives Matter rally with George Floyds family last summer https://t.co/1OkGUd0BzP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: "The Thief has come only to steal, kill, and destroy."  - Jesus (John 10:10)  [The Thief]: @JoeBiden   [Steal]: US Presi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrShayPhD: This is not good at all. I do not want the government involved in religion.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: BREAKING: Lead story on Daily Mail https://t.co/N4CRAiCwjV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ leave people alone! Why such violence?! #StopAsianHate https://t.co/CY6lhAjX6x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Suzy1776 Absolutely! But Im sure antifa would attack]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Suzy1776: If President Trump has a rally in your area will you go?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrShayPhD: Kamala said Biden is sending an extra 310M to Central America. Well I'll be dog gone, I can't get the IRS to send me my refu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenboebert The money hes giving away has to come from somewhere and people are too stupid to see it comes from US. They all want free stuff but dont care when taxes rise bc they arent paying them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Biden isnt just raising taxes on the rich. He is raising taxes on everyone. The $400,000 number has been proven to be a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: $393,000  https://t.co/lZZIuiSNWV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 @BreitbartNews Hes a disgrace!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a disgrace! https://t.co/OiwtDfhH2L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTforAmerica: More governors need to be like Ron DeSantis!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: Trump was honest  upfront about everything that happened in America  from immigration to #covid, from the economy to Ch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Youre the best governor in the USA, hands down, so glad I live in Florida.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Election Integrity is a Civil Rights issue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: "America is the home of the free because of the brave."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WINDOCTORRX: BLM is by far the most disingenuous organization in America]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: WOW!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamAllenSC: You do NOT need a fourth stimulus payment....  You need a JOB!!!  OPEN ALL OF AMERICA NOW!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Melindas grounds for divorce: Husband wants to depopulate earth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GuntherEagleman: I dont give a fck if you get vaccinated..  please dont give a fck if I dont.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AliciaVincler: Bill Gates just asked us all for privacy..... let that sink in.   Privacy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch https://t.co/q6lmRQglU5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrMichaelBurkes: I must be the only person who doesn't care that Bill and Melinda Gates are getting divorced.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LegendaryEnergy: Some vaccines take decades to make  never get released, some take years then get pulled off the market... but these]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drefanzor Thats my prez right there!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirhottest Nm already following ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sirhottest Im gonna hit follow since they banned you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @a_centrism: The years will pass, and billions of tweets will be tweeted, but will anyone ever be able to improve on this performance? h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/VDYMDn09OX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: I am presently experiencing life at the rate of several WTFs per minute.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Breaking911: JUST IN: More than 31 people shot, 3 fatally, this weekend in Chicago]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepMontague: We went from 15 days to stop the spread to wondering if well ever be free again real quick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Why would any parent pay $200,000 to send their children to college to be taught worthless, woke, anti-American nonsense?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricMMatheny: Bill Gates is practicing medicine without a license.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@USArmyVeteranMP Stay safe!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McKaylaRoseJ: Our country is in serious trouble. The FBI only works for the cabal, the CIA is focused on hiring woke millennials, our m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thebradfordfile: There is more carnage every single weekend in Chicago than there was in DC on January 6th.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Breaking911: WARNING - GRAPHIC: NYPD looking for driver who was caught on video intentionally running over a school bus driver in Brook]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: Americas greatest enemies dwell in our nations capital..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Biden and company claim there is no crisis at the border... so what are they blaming President Trump for?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: Texas Nurse Says She Was FIRED for Refusing Covid-19 Vaccine(VIDEO) https://t.co/tbsINYjH8v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @miles_commodore: When I waited tables a long time ago I hated the idea of pooling tips with the entire staff.  I didn't know it at the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @americafirstmg: Arkansas Governor Signs Bills BANNING VaccineRequirements https://t.co/JcQyoIgdPs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Republicans need a ground game and it just so happens that President Trump has the best ground game in the history of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hell no. https://t.co/m8IW4utMBL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: The weekends are always so much more peaceful when they send Dictator Applesauce Brain back to his basement.  What an embarra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KymC1019 I dont get it at all. Idc how many people follow me its not a popularity contest to me. I only follow those I wanna see, if I dont want to see what someone is posting its pointless to follow them. But I do follow back if u like what you post for sure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @miles_commodore: When I was a kid Cubans were escaping Castro to get to Florida. Today its Democrats escaping blue states to get to Te]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Child sex trafficking is very illegal and so is election fraud!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: "Is that your Bible?", barks a #fakenews reporter as Trump leads his cabinet down H street  stands in front St. John's]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Oldgloryfighter: Isnt this the epitome of irony? A trans shirt but you choose Man or Women for the sizing. Liberal ideology doesnt ho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: I want healing in our country. I want peace in our cities. I want unity in our communities. I want love in our homes. I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BidenDumpsBack: Everything will kill you. Just depends what will kill you first.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeanFulce2040 @JoeBiden ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTforAmerica: MAKE AMERICA SAFE AGAIN!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @miles_commodore: Being a cop is an incredibly difficult job today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @matthewdmarsden: What we are experiencing is the result of years of teaching people what to think, rather than how to think.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joeecollins3: Im really tired of Joe Biden as President already.  Who else? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: TRUMP 2021 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheKanehB Nothing will get me to take it or any vaccine. They dont work, the side effects are awful: allergies, ear inf, neuro damage, infertility, death, low immune system, the list goes on. Those are vaccine side effects/damage not normal. Plus we have meds to cure almost all we vax for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: The CyberNinjas audit team is already done looking at the Dominion Voting Machines.  What do you think they found?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/QPhfEnnHdH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PascoSheriff: You are not alone. https://t.co/MEI0mLXI1r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cindycj60: You're welcome! https://t.co/pr2VR9vaAF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @miles_commodore: The fact that in some places in America it was the law to wear a mask while you walked your dog, lets you know how fa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SeanFulce2040: @Oprah is worth $ 2.6 Billion dollars...and she said she's oppressed. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GadSaad: Dear @JoeBiden, when Trump placed a travel ban on China (early in the COVID pandemic), you accused him of xenophobia.  You are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SassySemite @LivePDDave1 What in the actual cult is this crap? This is seriously terrifying.  what an embarrassment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats a hard no. #UnmaskAmerica #SCAMDEMIC2021 #Antilockdown #FreedomOfChoice https://t.co/ze9ukLFz9C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRightMelissa: @tariqnasheed Critical race theory is a demonic ideology  is itself racist.  It is an ideology created by white liber]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Just so happens, this one person has more experience in sports and transgender perspective than all of the radicals wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: California college professor is put on leave after flipping out at a 19-year-old student for calling cops 'heroes' during]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRightMelissa: @tariqnasheed The left wants black people to think the only time they can succeed is when the world is a Utopia  all]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SeanFulce2040 is there a reason I cant comment on any of your tweets anymore? It keeps saying the tweet is deleted/not visible to me even Though I see them. Is it just Twitter being butthurt?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN: The Truth The Whole Truth and Nothing but The Truth So Help Us God - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/1aKHfh6z6M via @Change]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dobetter_twter Holy shit.  I cant even wrap my mind around this. And things I want to say will def get me banned. Just. Wow. Heartbreaking. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LeslieP94310624: I can not say this enough!!!  I'm trying to show my boys that there is more to life than YouTube!!  https://t.co/ff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RED_IN_PA_2: This needs put all over the world! https://t.co/YX7ybTeEOz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Suzy1776: He won by A LOT, he won BIGLY, he won by an unprecedented historic landslide. So no, we are not moving on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealMkA20: I will never forget how the majority of the GOP folded like cheap ikea chairs in 2020.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GordonGChang: History has given us the responsibility to stop evil. #China]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MAGARebirth: I don't listen to my own doctor...  Fauci never stood a chance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChadwickWiz: Race only matters to RACISTS!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Oldgloryfighter: https://t.co/y2lqUALAvO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArtValley818_: They loved him until he decided to run as a conservative. https://t.co/19uBT0VjpH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec So if a jury convicts an innocent Iraqi American for a murder they didnt commit as a payback for 9/11...opposite verdict but same mentality-depending on race  whats happened regarding that race decides the verdict. Makes tons of sense...also called RACISM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NotAlexSheppard: Its not Arizonas audit.  Its Americas audit]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>