<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Im going to leave this here... Im absolutely livid. From : The Governments own Impact Assessment Report. https://t.co/8051y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If furlough was stopped, i suspect the majority of the country would suddenly hate lockdowns.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am going to vote for @LibDems tomorrow at the local elections. They are the only major party standing up against the appallingly illiberal and authoritarian Coronavirus Act and vaccine passports.  #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If we continue with over 1,000,000+ lateral flow Covid tests per day, with a reported false positive rate of 0.1%, it will be impossible for the UK to get below 1,000 new Covid cases per day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernieSpofforth: If you have never fought for anything else in your life, then let it be this   A domestic vaccine passport is not your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This isnt normal. https://t.co/i2pRdKWjEr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Slavery in 2021. Cobalt is found in every lithium-ion rechargeable battery on the planet  from smartphones to tablets to laptops to electric vehicles. Children in Congo as young as four are among those risking their lives to mine cobalt for some of the worlds biggest companies. https://t.co/q28Bbxs3pg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Try explaining safe safe to the families of the 4 million people who died of starvation worldwide last year. And this barely gets a mention by the media.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @n_plowman: My daughters class was asked today to put their hand up if their parents had had the #CovidVaccine . She is in 2nd class. SE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peter_mcgahan: You cant choose your: 1 parents  2 siblings  3 birth gender  4 place of birth  5 skin colour  6 birth name  7 ethnicity]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our elderly people should be given the choice on how to live their lives.   Cartoon by @bobscartoons https://t.co/tTu7LVIfDH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's easier to fool people than to convince them that they have been fooled.  ~ Mark Twain]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@B37boy Im good. Always have been. Always will. But Im a sentimental old fool. Thats all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A vaccinated person is still at risk of getting Covid (but are likely to have reduced symptoms because of the vaccine). And they can still risk transmitting the virus. So therefore, a vaccine passport makes absolutely no sense. Its authoritarian crass logic. #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccine passports for domestic venue entry is one of the most appallingly illiberal and authoritarian ideas ever floated by a UK government. It risks discrimination, a two tier society and a huge infringement of human rights. Please retweet if you agree. #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/9QIQJs7w0b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: If you have never fought for anything else in your life, then let it be this   A domestic vaccine passport is not your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The world that we live in. https://t.co/Eo4jr7bznX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If someone has a different opinion, dont be a twat by trying to undermine or mock them. Try and get to know them, listen to them, learn from them. Because theres nothing worse than someone who thinks they are always right and that those with different opinions are always wrong. https://t.co/ewkV58EPqs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: We will Not be asking for Covid Certification based on Test to Enter or any other health papers. We shall be #openforall ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rhianbach They do!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doxing someone just because they have quickly built up a massive following and who just happen to be better and more influential than the doxer is never a good look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernieSpofforth: After a week spent in solidarity confinement in Twitter jail, I have now been released. Full sentence served, not even]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernieSpofforth Welcome back. https://t.co/J9V4oDPog2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BernieSpofforth Welcome back, Queen B! https://t.co/2zM9jm0zkO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice https://t.co/aOdUQsE7Od]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@siegmund1979 Same. I adore it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@siegmund1979 Best Ice Cream shop in Cornwall.   Angelato in Truro.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice  https://t.co/exMDjX6eQE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HJMovingFarAway Best Ice Cream shop in Cornwall.   Angelato in Truro.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My afternoon treat.  Black cherry. As always.  https://t.co/VzBrIq6DAg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @johngreenstree4: @JamesMelville @JuliaHB1 @talkRADIO Yes, if the left wants to know how to talk truth to power they should listen to JH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jamesrbuk: @lukemcgee Person Interested In Politics Has Private Political Views is not a scoop. It is *especially* not a scoop when the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lukemcgee: I am not normally one to punch down on small media orgs, but given they are punching down...   I cannot for the life of me u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zoeharcombe @Elanders_Voice Very true.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jennyrickson: @JamesMelville @JuliaHB1 @talkRADIO Julia hits the nail on the head - it is insane]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: How outrageous that someone who writes tweets about political stories should be exposed for, er... having political opinions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: @Larry_Mogridge @danwootton Yes. Dan Wootton. Dan and I disagree on many things, but we also agree on many things. Hes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Larry_Mogridge @danwootton Yes. Dan Wootton. Dan and I disagree on many things, but we also agree on many things. Hes a friend of mine. Hes a lovely man.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This one is about toxic tribalism, hatred, division and social media trolling. Instead of hating and abusing those who have a different political opinion, we should try and find some common ground. We might just find out that we like each other.   https://t.co/xIzTgyZlAO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCTimDonovan Hes a bit better at boxing than his boss.  https://t.co/isSKD4YIyi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Julia Hartley-Brewer @JuliaHB1 grouts her @talkRADIO studio floor with Liz Truss when discussing the illiberal and authoritarian government response to Covid.  https://t.co/tiFKIipZTV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: Absolutely stunned this morning to hear Liz Triss drop the bombshell that the UK government aims to eradicate COVID.  L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice  https://t.co/OXdlyoa0dO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 650,000 people lost their jobs in hospitality in 2020 despite only 226 outbreaks of covid in pubs and restaurants. And now SAGE U-turn and say pubs and restaurants are relatively low risk. Following the flip flop science has cost the livelihoods of thousands of people. https://t.co/fWKn0O0xHy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How can we follow the science when the science keeps on U-turning?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So SAGE now admit that the risk of Covid in a pub or restaurant is 'relatively low' with just 226 outbreaks in them since the pandemic began. Yet SAGE previously advised the government to restrict the trade of pubs and restaurants for an entire year.   https://t.co/M6U8RnlDly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And yet, according to UNICEF, 117 million children may miss out on receiving the life-saving measles vaccine during the Covid pandemic.  https://t.co/AXZFVC11oK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickbailey317 Conveniently ignoring the success of the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have always had an enormous solidarity with the self employed. They are the bedrock of our economy. They are the risk takers, wealth generators and the job creators and get hardly any financial support from the government. And right now they need support more than ever. https://t.co/sWpybYngg3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The UK government are quite happy to spend 200 million of taxpayers money on a new royal yacht, but yet continue to overlook the 3 million self employed workers who have received no financial support from the government since the Covid pandemic began.  #ExcludedUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An inconvenient truth for the Covid collateral damage deniers. https://t.co/AJehCo8lPN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1 UK Covid death in the past 24 hours (deaths for any reason within 28 days of a positive test). 450 UK cancer deaths in the past 24 hours (on average). 450 UK heart / circulatory disease deaths in the past 24 hours (on average).  Guess which gets all the media coverage?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peter_mcgahan: Structured investments are like cheap genetically modified food on a supermarket shelf. The vegetables having been ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WorldwideFP: This library drone delivers books to children in Indonesia. #tech #innovation #SDG1   https://t.co/OfijvOJwuU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zerocovidzoe @DrHoenderkamp @PatriciaMunn604 In her career @DrHoenderkamp has probably saved thousands lives. She sees the Covid debate in the round. For her, its not just about Covid. Its about all aspects of Covid, including the collateral damages of the lockdowns. That doesnt make her a monster. It make her decent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hats off to @GovRonDeSantis for  signing legislation that prohibits COVID vaccine passports in Florida. Sometimes it takes someone to be a Trojan horse in standing up against illiberal authoritarianism. History will judge him favourably.   #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/ten9doezYK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1 Covid death today Hospitalisations and death rates way below the 5-year average 50 million vaccinations 99% of the vulnerable vaccinated Cases plummeting  Yet we continue with this half-life. What are are we waiting on? Curbing Covid wont get much lower than this. https://t.co/gL5A8uAGjL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Never ever ever ever ever give up. Nighty night.  https://t.co/KYtyTG6xQ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: @JamesMelville The Covidians don't actually want this to end my friend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickgibbens Im sorry to hear that Nick. X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickgibbens How did it manifest itself? Because of Covid?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A very good article on how many people now have a chronic fear of reintegrating after lockdown ends. So many people been conditioned by endless fear. And I blame the government and media for this. Because fear sells.   https://t.co/JPt0oTu030]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: Request:  This is gonna be a big 2 weeks  Its going to be when we get gov to either listen  have our freedom  Normality  O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheBembridge That happened to me a long time ago. https://t.co/xvpAA0djPr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheLadOrlando: @Angelsfeartogo @JamesMelville Follow all the plans that had been extensively researched and in reserve for many years []]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLadOrlando @Angelsfeartogo  this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheLadOrlando @Angelsfeartogo Exactly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The majority of kids and elderly welfare charities are absolutely disgusted by the treatment of both groups through the Covid restrictions. How dare our government and sanctimonious bullies force our kids and elderly people to live like this? Shame on all of you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coercive control is the worst form of psychological bullying, both in terms of individuals and society. And yet our society is sleepwalking towards being coercively controlled by our government. It often happens in the blink of an eye, and it takes real courage to stand up to it. https://t.co/dqa4X9wK6w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enough is enough. We've got six weeks to show the government that if they don't give us our lives back we're just going to take them anyway.  @danwootton   https://t.co/jLz4C3r5wy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice And will any of our media mention this? https://t.co/wjDPe0ObBI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Calumets You seem nice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice https://t.co/McGdBDRAv8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: The U.K governments 320 million Covid advertising media contract has been won by Omnicom Group.   Their CEO John Wren]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So how come we can sit inside a service station cafe and have a meal with friends but we arent allowed to do so in a pub or restaurant? The whole thing is ridiculous.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid hospital deaths reported today:  East of England: 0 North East  Yorkshire: 0 North West: 0 South East: 0 South West: 0 London: 2 Midlands: 1  99% of our vulnerable have now been vaccinated.  Yet 2.75 million kids are still wearing masks in school for 8 hours.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice The media wont bite the hand that feeds them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And this hasnt aged well... https://t.co/gs8WegkIs6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LlDDIsyPCi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3kuSAkVhTp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/B2e6Nk1enl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MuCCSGPs77]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pgxIXYWQJL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/W6zp7jPyRZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont believe what the government promise you.  Thread/ ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alzheimerssoc: Jane has written a heart-breaking poem about how coronavirus has affected her and her mother, who has dementia.  She sha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice Them and us. We are banned from overseas travel but MPs can still travel to renovate their second homes in Tuscany and business leaders can still travel for meetings in Barbados.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theyve run out of lockdown justification supply.   Cartoon via @bobscartoons https://t.co/98foUGWV2k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As hospitalisations and death rates are now significantly below the 5-year average in the UK, this is now less about the virus and more about coercive control.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@when_cats_away Yes. I had to go private for dental care. It was impossible getting an NHS appointment to resolve a pretty serious tooth problem.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cinnibob2 @Elanders_Voice Sadly, I agree with all of that. Its about coercive control now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vsb69 The surge of respiratory diseases that occurs every winter.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Elanders_Voice Boris Johnson stated last week that there was a very good chance that all restrictions would be lifted after June 21st.   https://t.co/hO4quhuVd7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two-thirds of beds in private hospitals from June to September 2020 were not used by the NHS, despite the NHS paying more than 1.6 billion to use them. This is despite more than 1.7 million waiting beyond the 18-week target for NHS treatment.  https://t.co/8GPsMrxzH8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With hospitalisations and death rates below the 5 year average and we enter the summer season of lower NHS demand, what are the government doing to ensure that the NHS is ready for any winter surge in demand? Theyve had over a year to ensure that the NHS is protected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid-19 has created record waiting lists and a logjam of care for heart disease, stroke and cancer patients with charities and experts warning the NHS will have to operate above pre-pandemic levels to clear waiting lists.  https://t.co/nk7YNgT62T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it a pyramid or is it a hole? https://t.co/2c0gzO0COb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning from Cornwall  https://t.co/DYqbgxT5S9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nighty night from Cornwall  https://t.co/QZhPbaM4xP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its time for Gin James. https://t.co/RqRUhFps5I]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>