<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Fair play City ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dirty cunt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PSG lost their heads again ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 https://t.co/vZ3LuTEzFN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Neeeeeed to go to this #OnlyFools https://t.co/DlxMFbdfRQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CDCHistory: 1984: Portsmouth fans welcome Southampton to Fratton Park https://t.co/Jj6oCD67ZL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mkasztelewicz: "We don't want to see fans storming stadiums" well, we don't want to see billionaires exploiting social institutions for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off Graeme Souness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wholelottadej: Bruno when he sees one of the protesters put the ball on the penalty spot. https://t.co/PifE3bYSYz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fucking hell  https://t.co/19HSW6GFJ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StretfordPaddck: #MUFC fans protesting outside the Lowry Hotel  https://t.co/hg78rOB1ue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elyounoussi so awful  praying we get rid of him on a permanent this summer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JasonNIS_: Genuinely in my top 5 favourite Saints players of all time both of them  Like this photo brings a tear to my eye. #saintsfc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im off his chest, go on Roofe ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why?  2 relegations in 2 season, the guy is fucking shocking https://t.co/LrXvdmCim7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HistoricalSoton: #OnThisDay in 1976, the victorious #SaintsFC squad paraded the FA Cup on a triumphant procession through the streets o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quali time.. Lets go @LandoNorris @McLarenF1 #PortugueseGP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great fighting sprit to get a point out of that boys! Up the Saints]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come on prowseyyyy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ouchhhhh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Theyve turned it around ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Awaydays23: ON THIS DAY 2012: Southampton celebrate promotion to the Premier League #Saintsfc https://t.co/06ugepsOzh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Accrington Stanley, who are they? Exactlyyyyyyy https://t.co/qWY8wYlb0T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SouthamptonFC: They all count!   Two own goals saw #SaintsFC overcome #EFC at St Mary's #OnThisDay in 2014: https://t.co/96yMh35nmU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a fucking finish ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rickygervais: Its The Oscars tonight! I wasnt invited. Was it something I said?  https://t.co/P87Uau4D9u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Son crying ahahaha ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SouthamptonFC: #SaintsFC is joining fellow clubs and organisations within English football in a social media boycott, in response to on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brentfordddddd ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still am  https://t.co/aymeFwUsdV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a lad  https://t.co/nQtPc6eCXE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jlavooo Absolutely not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Danny boyyyy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @george_downes17: Wrexham, Leeds, Boston, Portsmouth, Cambridge, Rotherham, Luton, Bournemouth, Dagenham, Southampton, Stockport, Palace]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shouldnt of joined it on the first place! Hes not a hero because hes withdrawn Chelsea, hes still a cunt who wouldnt piss on you if you were on fire https://t.co/uoD3fFxTnR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LewisDeighton17: Man City have NOT done the right thing. They are merely scared to do the wrong thing.   Bayern, Dortmund and PSG did t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SouthamptonFC: Club statement on the European Super League:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SouthamptonFC: On behalf of the 2014/15 champions, we would like to extend our congratulations to you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What makes them think that fans are going to watch the games? Or that broadcasters will even show the games? https://t.co/yJqrTCmi85]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/Cz6RsXubMs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesPearceLFC: Hundreds of fans protesting outside Elland Road. F*** the Super League is the chant. Followed by six greedy bastards]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaintsfcViews: In 2009 Saints fell into administration, were given a 10 point deduction  relegated to L1. Yet funnily enough, thats t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NathanJudah: Its absolutely glorious   Wolves TikTok on another level   #wwfc #europeansuperleague   https://t.co/7BCtpsFe4W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheRedmenTV: https://t.co/Jh6zyQyDC6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @footballdaily:  "It's unacceptable what is happening behind the scenes."  Ralph Hasenhttl says he is against the 'European Super Leag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a man  https://t.co/n1AqMDpnJ9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thechicoazul: Breaking: Tottenham Hotspur have fired Jose Mourinho after an explosive morning where he refused to take players onto tra]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ if hes stood up against the club about the super league  walked away then fair fucking play to him https://t.co/ZtddtBCEPR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ESPNUK: This banner is currently in place at Old Trafford  https://t.co/2BBaoUaHrY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @XabiAlonso: Lived it. Loved it.   Farewell beautiful game. https://t.co/1aSN7GGNzZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone who buys a super league ticket  goes to the game are part of the problem and can fuck off aswell]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off https://t.co/0wm9abULQy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off https://t.co/HLldMKQS0v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off https://t.co/Tn6wb5g3m1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off https://t.co/UWQGXoEqbu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck the so called big 6 out of the premier league right now https://t.co/fVzb3YZ8xI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jlavooo A manager thats about to be relegated ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is fucking shocking ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @footballgraphx: It started without them and will continue without them #UTT https://t.co/E307ofapht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoToEuropeanSuperLeague]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fucking well said @GNev2  https://t.co/gnH4lTM0hU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come onnnn  https://t.co/BcSaXmPNPQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant wait for #MclarenUnboxed for this race  #ImolaGP @McLarenF1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bobbi_efc__ Yeah, 2,000 I think! Local residents that live around Wembley only though]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RonaldKoeman @FCBarcelona ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ R.I.P Prince Phillip!  God Save The Queen  https://t.co/p0y0ywfQPg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quali time! Lets go @McLarenF1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loved that tonight, good to have the team back  #theghosthunterchronicles @Yfielding @realkarlbeattie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twice! Lost 3-0  Won 1-0 https://t.co/IsIYjbvGPA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We deserve that! Fucking useless]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love this  https://t.co/ciXhyxSBaO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Both the mens  womens teams are winning the Fa Cup this season then  https://t.co/C6SzbDPDoE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ASM is so class ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6k there on an Easter Monday! What a day  https://t.co/gEwcfDJyfr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When big brother was actually decent back in the day, she was brilliant in that series! Horrible news  https://t.co/FTYPVMYtc5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Burrows Saint in 4th at least I placed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/R4KFH6wcuo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/6wjrSFbBST]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry but thats quite funny  https://t.co/laR8wRAfPu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lingard is so class ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SfcBxn: Southampton vs Burnley- Alternate commentary https://t.co/gdAK7UcbEQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Literally needed an assist from him thats it, then I would of won the head to head this weekend  https://t.co/KjXtwaqU4T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rehabkendoll: my nan testing out the first ever electric wheelchair in 1916 https://t.co/U7EOyGMGG7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BMW cunt overtaking a driver doing the speed limit then getting arsey when the other driver honks him! Cunt https://t.co/JNW1LQA1rn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adams is defo Scottish ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ahh big Fras with a massive save there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Walcott ffs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yessssss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fucking come on! Ingssss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unpleasant  Intimidating  fuck off https://t.co/ZhmUe2IVNh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Right now come on ffs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beer, Chocolate  Saints Fc Sundays  https://t.co/mN9RKPVexh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Joner07 Ah mate they were, just a shame we fucked up on the penalty shootout ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scenes in that away end  https://t.co/FISG3Yi5SZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyStar_Sport: Ex-Premier League star Jhon Viafara sentenced to 11 years in jail for cocaine smuggling | #SaintsFC https://t.co/7dbdX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Newcastle Ipswich Chelsea Kilmarnock https://t.co/0MY6FXfvxa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RangersFC: Former teammate, captain, friend and now a First-Team Coach at @SouthamptonFC, Kelvin Davis, credits @StevenDavis8 with play]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_kjs1874: James Charles pretended to be a pregnant woman, pretended to be bald, messaged little boys and yet whilst being an obvious fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BensBanter: If anyone want a reminder about the joys of watching Football live. #SaintsFC https://t.co/UKiBYHweRt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conorj1878 I can hear the commentator right now ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>