<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/imCGwudj5M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nothing I do or say matters. #juststop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColumbiaBugle: Not shocking, but disturbing as hell. https://t.co/JWxnjgIJMo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing prediction powers, Bill. https://t.co/SEPXyChDzS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saying Spanish flu is insulting to Spanish people.  Did I get that right? https://t.co/3uEW56h9j9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CDC is insane in the membrane. https://t.co/lWI4aedvSm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Usually, vaccines go through years of clinical trials before they get FDA approval, but not this time. The COVID-19 vaccines went through months, not years, of trials https://t.co/mFPbCTjrcJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@McKaylaRoseJ I see it all the time in Wilmington, DE. People running, walking, working out, outside, with face diapers. It's MORONIC. What else could one expect in JoeBidenville?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mari0br03 @Breaking911 no, you don't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CDC can kiss my fat ass.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Davem04942855 @newsmax almost everyone I see in Wilmington is wearing them outside. They are in the cult of Joe Biden aka IDIOTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My loved one is still fighting for his life @PierreKory and I can't help think, every day, had he had access to IVM perhaps he wouldn't be in the ICU. What the powers at be are doing is CRIMINAL. Please, keep fighting for life-saving medication! Grazie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @amaurotto: @ChristaScalise Goebbels in 1939 said the Jews were spreading cholera and typhoid. So they had their passport stamped with a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@therealarod1984 Geoffery Morgan is one of my favorite albums (saw UB40) live in the 1980s. Conversely, one of my least favorite people, Fauci. https://t.co/Hh6fwhzjQ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck #VaccinePassports. https://t.co/yBpqrT8xPn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why would anyone block the science of proven treatments to help patients overcome covid19? Because it would NEGATE Big Pharma's EUA (Emergency Use Authorization) by the FDA for a multi-billion dollar vaccine payday. -&gt; No EUA is a proven treatment is available.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Covid19Critical I'm glad I watched/shared it before anti-science bullies took it down. YouTube's action simply confirms (not that we need more evidence) the unconscionable censorship of science  the realness of the disinformation campaign by three-letter agencies and BigTech. #FightOn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Kory and the physicians on the frontlines of covid19 treatment are being treated like conspiracy nutjobs on @YouTube. Despite voluminous RCT (randomized control trials) about #ivermectin's efficacy, SCIENCE is being flatly blocked.   The WHO and Big Pharma's power is deep. https://t.co/bG56E5nJsh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierreKory: Less than 48 hours [after the first dose of ivermectin] mom was taken off the ventilatorIt was nothing short of miraculou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PierreKory I've got a loved one in ICU (ventilation/EMCO) past 10 days. He got monoclonal antibodies 5 days after being diagnosed with pneumonia then days later remdesvir. Can't help but wonder, b/c of you, if ICO could have been avoided had IVM been given after testing positive 4 Virus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Joeinblack: This will be an utter disaster. Youre gonna steer traffic away. A lot is at steak here, it would behoove you to drop this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @William230616: @BenIrvineAuthor The precursor of the Nazi Holocaust was the obsession with racial health and purity. Their first victim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ivermectin. Ivermectin. Ivermectin. https://t.co/aIYjBkmQFa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night I met the psychopaths who concocted the Wuhan virus. Let's just say, the dream ended better for me than for them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristaScalise: You all deserve early treatment for covid19. Ask your doctor what protocol they are using in the event you get sick and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jaysanchezdorta: I asked a doctor in India (a fellow who is on the ground and not compromised - unlike most of those reporting on what]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElijahSchaffer it will be if we all conveniently die]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[City dweller in Wilmington, Delaware and I appreciate every police officer willing to protect me and my property. #BackTheBlue https://t.co/T8CTCcmTay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS piss off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wonderful news this morning from UPENN about my loved one in ICU. Thank you to everyone who has been praying for him. Progress continues, hoping he will be off ventilator fully this week. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly I actually took the picture without my glasses on. I just NOW saw there were in the pic. I'm a total idiot. I'm  at myself. I'm going to put myself in a Twitter timeout. lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Date night  Me and #ThomasSowell https://t.co/BEz7rvjKbM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly mi dispiace https://t.co/GvGdiJsWJO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly that's a good combo. I made an apple and onion compote last week to accompany a bone in pork. Frickin delicious]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FreedomIsrael_: For all the so-called main stream media journalists smearing the attendees of the #LondonProtest today as the dregs of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @soupcanarchist: *fans self* lord jesus! Preach the Gospel  https://t.co/cje1n8AIx7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: London stands up in droves. Enough is enough. #londonprotest #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/8cQOTOgDQ9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@soupcanarchist I bet her parents are proud.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly lost 45+ lbs on keto. I love carbs. And carbs love my ass and thighs. It's not the best relationship. *laughs*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drnickUSA: #VitaminD deficiency is extremely common in modern society, even in young healthy athletes! Low Vit D is associated with num]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NickHudsonCT true. I haven't owned one in many years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmeraldRobinson ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FreedomIsrael_ f-ing hate this guy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to the lung specialists at the University of Pennsylvania for taking great care of my loved one. He is making progress every day. Hoping and  he will be off ventilation and heart machine this week.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fauci is an ass clown...burn all the damn masks and BREATHE for God's sake. https://t.co/niTfUMuH3O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly I don't buy apples, too many carbs...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mask-free on Montrose Street, former block where my great grandparents, Giuseppe  Giuseppina lived. https://t.co/pQ9rPztdsX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly didn't see any but wasn't looking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lovely day to buy produce on 9th Street. https://t.co/jNbuiE5VMW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gifted another day! Celebrate the good things. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CsXIGoKZ5d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec love to see you reporting on Dr Kory's work about covid treatment and how the WHO plays a role in blocking it. #Goliath #David #EUA @  https://t.co/T4SZiT0pbT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EpochTimes: #Indianapolis lawmakers incorporated language in a bill that would ban state and local government units from requiring #Vac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former legal client of my partner calls the other day to say he'd gotten the JJ vaccine, is in the ICU with blood clots, wants to sue. Partner had to tell him BigPharma and states have immunity from prosecution. #InformedConsent #Delaware #USA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmeraldRobinson it's as easy to buy scientists as it is politicians]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just had a Zoom meeting with a local politician about #VaccinePassports. Although I appreciated the 14 minutes of time, I would have also appreciated his full  undivided attention. He barely made eye contact, was too busy scrolling through his cell phone.  @drsimonegold]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You all deserve early treatment for covid19. Ask your doctor what protocol they are using in the event you get sick and need help. There ARE treatments available but you need to get them early before being hospitalized. By then, it may be too late. Advocate for yourself!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Covid19Critical I'm watching now. I'm grateful for all the clinicians working hard to illuminate and educate the world about early treatment and clinical treatments for covid. Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierreKory: Gave a lecture last night.. to end all lectures. I put it all out there identifying the forces actively working against ive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Wuhan virus was created in a lab specifically to kill people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeFareed2: NIH should have started this 12 months ago with funding frontlines: Drs. Zelenko, McCullough, Proctor, Kory and more. We]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlayMsT4Me @justin_hart @Stanford @pnjaban channel your rage and fight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe medical tyranny will wake up @Stanford students. Perhaps a peaceful protest needs to happen on campus? I'm sure there are some Antifa or BLM members who are willing to do some consulting work to help students organize. https://t.co/1S49eCvqT7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@C__DiLorenzo This one time at Tuskegee bandcamp....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If "they" really cared about our health, why aren't they testing people for covid antibodies before the jab? Why are those who jab not properly informing jabbees the jab is EUA and not FDA approved? Why is ivermectin being cock-blocked by the WHO if it's helping to save lives?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes. https://t.co/BYRDz2U8z4 https://t.co/KzBrimwGl2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RogerMarshallMD because it's not a vaccine #genetherapy and it's still in trials. It's not hard to grasp.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/mr3WobAJmU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll be working to "fortify" the term Wuhan Virus, then. https://t.co/bxuDozgy81]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why don't you just kill all humans, then @JohnKerry? Would that save the baby icebergs and clouds? #LeadersClimateSummit https://t.co/KvbR1TWook]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrenmark69 where is your grandson? Another country?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MdTeryn Thank you. I'd like to get your thoughts on this tweet. Is it considered a best practice that a doctor's office wouldn't have a patient sign off on an EUA vaccine? https://t.co/cdBmaJ9etI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So, I just learned from the scheduler at my doctor's office vaccines are being given in the office but patients are not being provided with or being asked to sign any document acknowledging they are consenting to an #EUA product. #InformedConsent]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The World Economic Forum and all of its supporters are cancer for the world.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Some may argue that vaccine passports are the first step towards eradicating a disease. Rather, they are the first step]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fascismo https://t.co/zdTTMXvSCd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Le persone non riescono a vedere che siamo ritornati al fascismo." #italia #greenpass #VaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apparently Italy is positioned to pass a "green pass"...  my liberty loving friends in Italy responded like this:  "Siamo sotto il nazzismo."  #VaccinePassports #italia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDJinPhilly sempre sempre   il caff  vita]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roses are red.  is delicious.   #poetry https://t.co/iD0PKuFkg1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Critical: Dr. @PierreKory will discuss a massive disinformation  misinformation campaign by the @WHO to convince the world that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danielkotzin: Covid is almost gone in America.  Hospitals are literally empty.  Every willing senior has already been vaccinated.   In]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last time I read Fahrenheit 451  was in the 1980s, a worthy and timely read in 2021.  Burning books, #censorship, #thoughtpolice #deplatforming should be non-starters in Western society.  #YouTube #twitter #google #apple #AppStore #FreedomOfSpeech https://t.co/Edx6QBJfSr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists, like politicians, are bought and sold every day.    Follow the money.   Illuminate malfeasance.   #wef #who #nih #cdc #fda #covid19 #treatment #EUA #vaccines #fauci #Gates https://t.co/TqzPQpJrzY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Joeinblack virtual exorcism, stat, padre!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Executive Orders banning #vaccinepassports is not enough. If any of these governors are serious, they'll press state legislatures to pass laws banning them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Open up the State of Delaware @JohnCarneyDE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrShayPhD I'm on it. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drsimonegold this link is dead, it's a 404 error]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrShayPhD This is not okay. I think some of your followers, like me, would be happy to contribute funds so you can pay for a diagnostic exam. Please let us know how we can help.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peaceful way to start the day.   https://t.co/DudkrwmnLV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLelandMD @travtravtrav @jeffreyatucker @mcfunny @mc93823939 @stellalimelight @stephaniecivel2 @naomirwolf the people who concocted this virus better never cross my path]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You are loved. We love you. Please, Holy Spirit, surround my loved one and all the medical professionals offering care with love, light, and healing. Grazie e Amen. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you to prayer warriors @sscjusa @Joeinblack @smintz7179 and others for keeping my loved one in prayer. Minutes ago we heard from the ICU with some improvements.  Grazie, Dio.  We continue to pray for healing for all those infected with COVID-19. Amen. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please pray for my loved one. Please...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Correct @ZeekArkham.  I live in a high-crime area in Wilmington, Delaware. Less than 2 weeks ago someone was shot dead a half-block from my house. We NEED good cops in 19802, especially those of us who don't have private armed security guards or live behind big stone walls. https://t.co/3oixvTYJFD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Americans concerned about #defundthepolice rhetoric would be wise to adopt a pro-#2a stance (if not done so already), purchase weapons, get trained in the use of firearms, buy ammunition, and prepare to defend your life and family when police have been run out of town.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If wearing a non-medical grade mask has no impact on the transmission of a virus, why do it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fact: if you have taken any covid19 shot in the United States of America and have had an adverse reaction, or die, you and your family have ZERO legal recourse. Big pharma has immunity from lawsuits. #informedconcent #Covid_19 #liability]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Any state or federal entity that doesn't make it ABUNDANTLY clear covid19 shots are Emergency Use Authorized and not fully FDA approved are NOT acting in the public interest. #informedconcent #publichealth #disclosure]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>