<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Chlorine dioxide is not bleach. Mainstream media lies again.   https://t.co/fT87yRrC5E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MuellerSheWrote @rozmcdermott @AshaRangappa_ @UROCKlive1 I don't really care if you wear a mask or not. As long as you don't care if I don't wear a mask. However, cutting oxygen off to your brain while you're driving or biking is not safe for you or the public. Our brains need oxygen to function well.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Think twice before getting the Pfizer or Moderna EXPERIMENTAL vaccines. It can cause #infertility in females and males. https://t.co/DsQPhpAHpV?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The California legislature is dead.  Bills in opposition to the current administration are simply being stalled in committee and then law is set by the governor illegally using self granted emergency powers. #RecallNewsom  https://t.co/pQHNfDAUHu?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are the Vaccinated making the Unvaccinated sick? Critically Thinking with Dr. Tenpenny and Dr. Palevsky - Episode 44 https://t.co/h1cJLvYJZM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fatchancemate: USA  I cannot believe this. Watch as Anthony Hopkins, fakes getting the Vax. After pretending to inject him, the nurse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gerardbush @GavinNewsom Wohooo! If you're so liberated then what's with the mask? I hope you don't wear a mask when you're driving ALONE in your car? Lol. https://t.co/9ci7og7Bjq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlancaIsela_A @CREConstSvcs @gerardbush @GavinNewsom CA is still locked down. Millions out of work and facing eviction. Drug abuse, spousal abuse, depression, suicide, and poverty all skyrocketed. Schools are operating in other states but not in CA. (Private schools like the one Newsom's kids are attending are open though!) https://t.co/dqO6FGVXo9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jrusso691 @AgirlnamedDon @GellerGreen4 @jennytyoung @MrAndyNgo @KOINNews No riots at the Capitol on Jan 6. Just Antifa pretending to be Trump supporters. It was all a setup.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeterSchiff Our grandparents didn't own any cryptos. Didn't exist back then.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Notyour28981739: You know the covid vaccine for kids will be granted EUA by school time. Are you willing to vax your kids with this exp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom You just helped me win a bet. Mass shootings are up once Biden took office. Ha, ha, ha.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LorenaSGonzalez Why are places like Target and Grocery Outlet closing their restrooms? If they are afraid of covid then clean the restrooms more often.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom If the covid vaccine works then why are they planning a "top-off" or "booster" shot this winter? https://t.co/XFhscRBZdN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could the covid vaccine cause Mad Cow Disease?  https://t.co/L1GMqJnipO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/G3bEU4LepD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If your #dog or #cat is not 100% healthy then check out their diet. Feeding exclusively raw meat is not the answer. And neither is a homemade meal.  Whats Wrong with Homemade Dog Food?  https://t.co/eyhdedOeii]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Shame on Daily Wire for pushing the UNAPPROVED and experimental covid vaccines. And shame on #MorganFreeman for allowing himself to be used to push Big Pharma LIABILITY-FREE products. I trust neither the Daiily Wire or Morgan Freeman.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NDGGriff @CryptoManifest1 @VancityReynolds @jessicamalaty India with a population of 1.3 BILLION people has 165K covid deaths. Their sanitation is subpar to ours and people literally live on top of each other. MAYBE the U.S. death count is over inflated? Doesn't make sense we have almost 600K deaths and a population of 328 MILLION. https://t.co/7SQtpHPcYx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepMTG: NEW BILL ALERT!  The "#FireFauci Act" will slash the salary of Dr. Always Wrong to $0 and the "#WeWillNotComply Act" will ban]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If #vaccines work then why do you support vaccine passports? Why would you give up your freedom to be able to come  go in society? The vaccine passport is the gateway to a Social Credit System just like the one China has. Say no to anyone or any company that requires a passport. https://t.co/8CKmhlCmoT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sfchronicle Yay for the A's. If you're sick then stay home. Otherwise, people should go about their business without having to be tested all the time or be guinea pigs for the experimental unapproved covid vaccines.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJHopkins_Z23 Internment camps will ever happen. Afterall, the gov't needs the unvaccinated to blame when the vaccinated get sicker and sicker from their covid shots come this winter. Plan for it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing video of a woke person trying to wake people up about #COVID19 using a bull horn. Truly sad that not everyone can hear the message.  https://t.co/K8yoUAhYvn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Goingbr0ke @ZubyMusic @harrylitman https://t.co/yZIAMoQ2JH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@a_standal @gordyb1872 @harrylitman @WmDeanFrench If I'm injured by the covid vaccine which was required 4 my job should my employer be responsible for my medical bills  loss of wages? What if the vaccine killed me? Will my employer be responsible 4 my family? Since you can sue the vaccine manufacturer can I sue my employer?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@harrylitman Why would any logical thinking person risk serious vaccine injury or death when the recovery rate from Covid is over 99.5% for people under 70? https://t.co/jFxYjdUaaM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What if Big Telecom were able to put 5G antennas on top of any residental or business rooftops? Every house surrounding your home can have a 5G antennas! We don't need 5G. 4G/LTE is already killing us.  https://t.co/GbcuKEGKVF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marwilliamson It has nothing to do with age. It's about being open-minded and seeking the truth. Most people want to live in their lies b/c the truth hurts. Knowing the truth means taking responsibility for your actions or inactiions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RipesWendy @Electro_Couture @GavinNewsom Yeah who cares that billioniares and companies like Telsa, Charles Schwab, H-P and Oracle have moved to TX! Less tax revenue for CA, more tax revenue for TX. Hooray!!  https://t.co/FRmYVtJj0X]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BigTimeReg @GavinNewsom Really 530,000 Americans dead from Covid? Bet you didn't know that the CDC lumps pneumonia, influenza and covid deaths together? And how do you explain that India with over 1.3 BILLION people has only 157k covid deaths? India where living conditions are subpar to the U.S. https://t.co/vOf1xzVe49]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@doomsdaydouglas @herrmanndigital @GavinNewsom Wow. That was rude telling someone to shut up. Obviously, you don't believe in the freedom of speech unless that person agrees with you, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bobichette11 @Earthlingz963 @SnacksJohn @RealCandaceO So FBI shows up @ your house or place of employment to question you about the "uprising" is not intimadating? In front of your neighbors, family or maybe even in front of your boss and fellow workers? People have been harassed or fired by their employers for attending the rally!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHY PRIVATE PROPERTY MATTERS: PROSPERITY  STABILITY  FREEDOM. https://t.co/TiDWoZpCYa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SnacksJohn @RealCandaceO It's NOT a crime to attend a rally. They never went to the Capitol where the "insurrection" was happening. The FBI is deliberately harrassing Trump supporters. This is America. It's not against the law to be a Republican.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KPIXtv @CAgovernor @GavinNewsom This is John Hopkins University graph of # of covid deaths in the U.S. compare to overpopulated India with their subpar sanitation and living conditions. Could the covid death # in the U.S. be inflated? And why is CDC lumping pneumonia, influenza  covid deaths (PIC) together? https://t.co/8q1CQVz2P1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom THIS IS RECKLESS. https://t.co/pjchY74hvb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@glennC26713345 @AlMcGartland Florida is open and there is no mask mandate there. I'm still waiting for the Covid spike from all those Super Bowl parties.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlMcGartland @JennaEllisEsq @GavinNewsom What a stupid statement. And you're a scientist? Lol. We got eyes for seeing, ears for hearing and a nose for breathing!! Cover your nose and you're depriving your body of oxygen and inhaling the toxic CO2 captured in your  mask. Physiology 101. If you're sick STAY HOME.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marwilliamson Stop it. It's a wave of LEFT WING AUTHORITARIANISM too. Both parties are guilty of eliminating our freedom. Until you can see that clearly you're part of the problem too. #Agenda21 #Agenda2030 #GreatReset]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Kids should not be wearing masks. They need to breathe!!! Depriving their growing brain of oxygen is dangerous. I can't believe the stupid things we are putting our kids through for "safety." Well, safety doesn't mean healthy. https://t.co/Z5dXJIDyJy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BGibbles @GregAbbott_TX Hey Blaine.... you're free to double mask, vaccinate  stay home. In the meantime people need to work to put food on the table and pay their rent. Unless you don't care about their lives? Graph is from John Hopkins. Compare U.S. deaths to India. Something isn't adding up. https://t.co/ZTNWti8Lfi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom If you're sick then stay home. If you think the vaccine will save you then get it. If you think depriving your body of oxygen with a mask is keeping you healthy then wear one. BUT END the LOCKDOWN  SOCIAL DISTANCING! Kids need 2 go back 2 school. People need 2 go back 2 work. https://t.co/HlnzZDZYUD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@siushi @GavinNewsom But in the meantime we are destroying our economy, family and health. https://t.co/Pyv2geeAxd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CaliforniaGlobe You mean this lawmaker? Bought by Big Pharma. Of course Senator Pan wants to ban anyone who questions the risks of vaccines. In fact Pan has BLOCKED me from his twitter account. If Trump can't block opposition from his Twitter account why does Pan get to do it? #PanRan https://t.co/pUxsiDVqVO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndiHK @HEYJBMC @SenFeinstein Businesses are leaving CA too. Oracle, Tesla and Charles Schwab to name a few. Really, the weather is so perfect in CA 95% of the time but is it worth it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef @WEFUpLink The only solution is to reset life back to December 2019. As if the covid-19 never existed. Or at least no worse than the seasonal flu. Yet, here comes WEF with a mask that can tell us when we need a breath?? Are you kidding me?? https://t.co/jicJNX2ZXk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@coreajulio11 @SoCal_Fantasy @UTLAnow End the lockdown. Kids need to back to school. And teachers need to be back in the classroom. If teachers don't want to teach in a classroom then they need to be terminated. Life is risky. https://t.co/tX7p97cfku]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You might feel fine after getting your #COVID19 vaccine but what health issues will arise 4 mos to 1 year from now? MS? Damaged nerves? Seizures? Permanent disabillity? Death? Listen to Dr Sherri Tenpenny explains how the covid #vaccine is a Trojan Horse. https://t.co/py5BCSmpGS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lindyli Well, looks like someone forgot to deice the blades. https://t.co/JZZfkhTJfe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@spencermorgan93 You think we're going back to normal if we got vaccinated? Ha, ha. Then why do we still have to wear a mask and do social distancing? Stop being a dumb f. Covid is just a coverup for #TheGreatReset #Agenda21 #Agenda2030]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Wow. If we are doing so good then why is CA still in a lockdown? Why are people not back at work? Kids in schools? All restaurants open for businesss? Why are we still wearing masks...  double masks?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Shelby0296 @DanScavino Too bad Biden can only win by cheating. Do you really think Biden got more votes than Hillary and Obama? Ha, ha. https://t.co/qUzuuf9i5V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is AIDS US $90B Taxpayer Dollars A Global Slush Fund? It's just another scam to enrich the elites. #ClintonFamily   https://t.co/GMAgelfa8V]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevinKileyCA: Its official. 1.5 million signatures.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@skylarbone_ @Mostlyh42903645 @jmartNYT How quickly we forget the riots and looting by the "peaceful" protesters after the George Floyd's death. Not just in Washington DC but in Seattle, Portland, NYC, LA, Chicago, San Francisco, Atlanta, Detroit, etc.  https://t.co/QYtf9rBfKj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mostlyh42903645: @jmartNYT Would have been better used during the summer of riots https://t.co/Mumub340fP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SexCounseling Really? You can't even see that this is 100% BS propoganda. And now social media wants to ban anyone who dares question the integrity of the election. We are no longer the Land of the Free. We are being destroyed within and sadly you can't even see it. https://t.co/AZnEthpFi3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@melico24 @brianstelter The covid death # is overinflated! CDC lumps pneumonia, influenza and covid deaths TOGETHER. The total # of all deaths in the U.S. for 2020 is only about 20,000 deaths higher than deaths in 2019 and 2018!! We have been played. Yep. We have been played. https://t.co/uw492zruzF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brianstelter What terror attack? Oh do you mean the fake Trumpsters (aka Antifa) "storming" Capitol? Why was the Capitol not protected? The Dems wanted the Capitol breached so they can blame it on Trump, impreach him and pass a bill that will make every freedom fighter a domestic terrorists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marwilliamson What about working moms? Kids who do better in a classroom? They don't count? If a teacher doesn't want be in a classroom b/c of covid then quit. Tired of teachers saying "I became a teacher b/c of the kids." What a joke. Living is RISKY. People rarely get #COVID19 from children! https://t.co/caGks49bco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@flameboy_xxx @TheShawn4Real @BencomoGail @SInow @NFL Why would anyone want to cover their nose whose primary purpose is to inhale oxygne and exhale CO2? Depriving your body of oxygen will lead to serious lung problems down the road. Yeah, I know you believe in science but science has been hijacked. Question everything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dclanders @lance_nimmo @BencomoGail @SInow @NFL If there were 400,000 more deaths b/c of covid then why aren't there 400,000 more deaths for 2020? And did you know the CDC lumps pneumonia, influenza and #covid together (PIC)? Another way to over inflate the # of deaths to control people through FEAR. https://t.co/teutspXg1u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sdaws5MUFC: The ignorance.. https://t.co/ax7cgbPdDj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you continue to wear a mask.... then we're not going back to normal.   https://t.co/Q3ALu76Kd1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LorenaSGonzalez So did you husband NOT say this or what? If he did then what is the big deal? People get their info from watching the news on TV. San Diegans already missed out on 3 major holidays. It's time to end the #lockdown! Small businesses are especially hit hard. #COVID19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nesto_92 @LorenaSGonzalez Lorena got a lot of flack for authoring SB5 from Uber, Lyft and many other independent workers. The bill was passed. Uber and Lyft were forced to put a proposition on last November's ballot and voters overwhelmingly stood by Uber and Lyft. Lorena doesn't listen.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom END the #lockdown if you want to save small businesses. 60% of all restaurants that shut down in March 2020 are permanently out of business. And you're responsible for that. Students lost one year of their lives sitting at home. Kids need to interact with teachers  others. https://t.co/R9ZZOD8Gs5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LorenaSGonzalez Give me ONE person who escaped #death? Because we will all die one day. You, your loved ones, me, my loved ones...  everyone. Each day is a promise of life or a promise of death. I choose life. END THE LOCKDOWN!!! #COVID19 #coronavirus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you want #freedom? Then we must draw the line. NO to #GreatReset #Agenda21 #Agenda2030 #BuildBackBetter and #NewWorldOrder    https://t.co/VNUz03HvdD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NY students learning REMOTELY are still required to get childhood vaccination!!!! So is this about safety? Or BIG PHARMA PROFITS? Or government control? And Sonja Sotomayor is an Obama's appointee.   https://t.co/ltNwqyGwfs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excellent video. Must watch. The New Normal. #COVID19 #CovidVaccine   https://t.co/tRWwUTsB5Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Simone Gold and #CovidVaccine. Worth a listen.   The Stand | The Truth About the COVID-19 Vaccine https://t.co/EkmwX5mzil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bennyjohnson: MILITARY SOURCE IN DC: For the last week my battalion has been sleeping on the floor in the Senate cafeteria. Today the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ha, ha. I love drinking hot water. Why Do Chinese People Prefer Drinking Hot Water? - Why Chinese (E2) https://t.co/1OQWLYBJC3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump activists destroying property in 2017 during Trump inauguration. And the Dems never mention this. https://t.co/ugcsLWsuIM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @unhealthytruth: Do any of you understand what this means? The ramifications? This is horrifying. https://t.co/MAz10AFFXH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 #CovidVaccine #coronavirus https://t.co/xz0xpiJrNt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferMarguli: Who is crazy? History will not look kindly on this moment in America. https://t.co/9bIPDLn0Ke]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LorenaSGonzalez @Castro4Congress LOL. Eric Swalwell is the Representative that slept with a Chinese spy. I wonder how many lawmakers have taken money from China? BTW, there was no "insurrection" in Washington D.C. It was just a peacefull protest. https://t.co/HMCWDjn9yr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Big Fake Media lied about the "insurrection" on Jan 6. Why? So they can pass laws to call Trump supporters domestic terrorists. What D.C. was REALLY Like for 99.9%.  https://t.co/wvlvUFYJUT via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marwilliamson There was NO insurrection at DC. Was a lawmaker held hostage, injured or killed by Trumpers? Was paintings and furnishing destroyed by the Trumpers? Was Congress set on fire? The breach was preplanned by the Dems using Antifa disguised as Trumpers to cause trouble. https://t.co/aziKaTMsN3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@spicy_raviolee @MrAndyNgo Relax. She's alive. False flag. She's probably enjoying her new identity in a new location. She's set for life. We have been duped by the Democrats.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris https://t.co/1KGQfiQwDT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear Twitter,  YOU SUCK! Banning President Trump's account is a low blow. I can't wait for President Trump to create his own platform. You can be sure half your subscribers will be gone!! You, MSM and Fakebook kill the golden egg. Ha, ha, ha. #JoeBiden cheated. #StopTheSteal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCandaceO: In ONE YEAR, the Left has normalized:  Shutting down businesses  Shutting down churches Force masking citizens Censoring]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Actually there was a FIRE. Our Democracy and our right to a transparent and honest election are going up in smoke. Too bad your hatred of Trump has blinded you to your prejudices. #StopTheSteal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antifa tried to incite a riot at the Capitol. Not Trump supporters. #StopTheSteal https://t.co/nKJKL4R02M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@veronicabee @RockNPolitics @aTimeQ I heard Newsmax was becoming more like fake news. I believe it now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samanthamarika1: There will be no unity in America until people start doing the inner work.  For four years I watched democrats project]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caitrionambalfe @IvankaTrump Hardly any security in Washington DC when everyone knew about the rally for at least a month. Plus my friend who bussed it from Florida saw buses with police escort filled with Antifa. Imo, it's a setup. Not to say there are no bad Patriots. Still be careful what you post. https://t.co/Vo21kEw56n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kd_singh This guy with the gun is Capitol security. Do you have a picture of a Trumper with a gun pointing at lawmakers or law officers?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HIZ0USE: @JustInformU Thumbs up, end of scene https://t.co/TPW6Gbcb3g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep. Antifa were bussed in to the Capitol. They were escorted by the police. https://t.co/TNlKVccgTF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nobody45984549 @3days3nights @Bekjjj Looks staged to me. Usually people will scream or panic if there's gunshots just several feet away. No one did.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeviousAquarius @3days3nights Imo, she is an actress. Not dead at all. All staged.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Staged by the Democrats!! And in light of what happened at the Capitol today GA folded in the electoral hearing! Well played cheating Dems. #StopTheSteal https://t.co/tK9Gay6Gru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PatrickByrne The march was infiltrated by Anitia. It was Antifa that breached the Capitol. Trump supporters were peacefull. Was there looting? Rioting? Buildings set on fire? Crashes with law offiers? Except for the woman who was shot (not by Trump supporters) it was relatively peaceful. https://t.co/A7x9iJiroS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kommunal_rave @ggreenwald I guess you missed all the rioting and looting done by BLM and Antifa protestors in multiple cities soon after Floyd was shot? The police stood down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ggreenwald: How have hundreds of billions upon hundreds of billions of dollars been spent in the name of security since 9/11, along wit]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>