<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Great colors!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt So beautiful! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dame_deviant So cute!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K It's so nice to see you and your players smiling! DD makes people happy ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt You too! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeanChillie Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's never too late for an introduction, right? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hello, I'm Shade! I paint sci-fi and fantasy, fan-art and original characters. Commissions are open, all the info is here: https://t.co/A17wiMQNsK https://t.co/18eBbWkaiP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rashiduzzaman82 Thank you so much! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Zeithri Thank you. It's not a pointed ear, it's just the turn of the head makes it look this way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SMFulton3 Thank you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thank you!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt My friends say I am ready to try, but I don't feel that way. It's like I know I have almost everything I need for that, but something is missing. I just need one more year of practice before I try to get a real job (I said that a year ago too ).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StarTrekOnPPlus Thank you so much!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt My goals are to be good enough to paint for DD books, that's my dream.  You know, at first I had the same thoughts, now I improved so much and there is always more to learn! It never ends.  By the way, your skills are really great, you always capture the likeness perfectly ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt I'm still not even close to my goals, but this is a good motivation for practising more ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@djvoltz1701 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thank you!! It usually depends on a reference ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AFurryFriend Thank you very much! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@misskiranerys Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MHecubus Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Aussieriffic1 I feared that too. I think, it was intentional, to make us a bit nervous and than prove admirals can be great.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael Burnham. She is just brilliant, and finally I painted her.  #digitalpainting #startrekfanart #startrek #StarTrekDiscovery https://t.co/nwJFbx5PA1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SMFulton3 Thank you very much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mLouisep Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeyStevieLee Thank you!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rashiduzzaman82 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ArtofTrek Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NancyAnnBarr1 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt I'm so glad you like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Awww, thank you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Admiral Vance. I like him very much  #digitalpainting #startrek #StarTrekDiscovery #startrekfanart https://t.co/24dyWtsszD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two days ago I got my second dose of the vaccine. It was not my best weekend ever, and I still feel not very well, but it's for the best.  Stay safe, everyone!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K @may_wise That is so great!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeanChillie Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K @FriedaRachelle I'm so glad!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FriedaRachelle @N_A_K You are Noah's mom?? OMG! I'm so happy you like it! This means so much to me, thank you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thank you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AFurryFriend Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K @StarTrek @StarTrekOnPPlus @TrekMovie @TrekCore @TheTrekCentral I just hope this would make you smile! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to @N_A_K !  For this occasion I wanted to paint something calm and warm, so Ryn is going to see the Andorian system (don't ask how and when) and I hope he would enjoyed that. https://t.co/BOg8UnNvRF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K Happy Birthday! I hope you'll have a great day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt She's beautiful!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K Congratulations, It's so great! I'm so happy for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Commission: Reva. It was nice to work on this piece, I enjoyed it. #digitalpainting https://t.co/43dpiLLkc7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeanChillie I found a pattern translated to my language, but I think original pattern is called "Comet the Unicorn"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt I usually listened to music, and I thought I can't listen to books, my thoughts will distract me, but turns out I can, and I'm happy :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thank you!)) This pattern was a bit difficult for me, I'm still have a lot to learn, but crocheting is fun. And my daughter will love it for a day or two, then it will be forgotten as was all I made before]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These books mean a lot to me. I missed R. Daneel so much... Oh, I just wish I had a robot friend... as always 2/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Recently I discovered, that I can listen to audio-books while I'm jogging (yes, I've never done that before). I wanted to start with something very familiar, so now I listen to Asimov's Robot series novels. Actually, I've never read them in English, so at least this is new. 1/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I took some pause in painting and crocheted this unicorn for my daughter. https://t.co/ApsJgU67L0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Landylachs Thank you! I'm so glad to hear it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Landylachs So beautiful! I love it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Big hug! I hope it will be better soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt I'm so sorry!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GCAT01Living It's a good game! I just could't enjoy some of the content. As for the plot... it's ok to have no plot, but my brain always looks for some hints of a story, I really thought it was "some experiment went wrong" or "we found an ancient artefact" scenario :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As you may guess, There were NO answers... Can't say that I'm really disappointed, but the concept "It can mean all the deep philosophical thoughts of your choie... or nothing at all" is not my cup of tea. BUT. It's still all about puzzles, and they were mostly good. 5/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[positioning of the player instead of logic, and also there is no plot, or story, or characters... I just wondered the whole time "Does this have any meaning? Those statues must be here for a reason! Audio logs must tell the story! All the answers are on that mountain!" 4/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The Witness", on the other hand, was a good game for me. I liked the majority of the puzzles, everything looks beautiful, though it takes time to get used to the visual style. The only two things, that I didn't like was that some puzzles need perception and the very precise 3/5 https://t.co/9p6g9lZsDY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The Turing Test" didn't impress me at all. The puzzles were not bad, but not really challenging, and the plot... well, I wish there were no plot at all. You know, if the plot is simple and predictable - it's ok for a puzzle game, but this ending was one of the worst ever. 2/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really like that good feeling of working brain, so I thought it might be a good idea to look for more puzzle games - recently I completed "The Turing Test" (AI theme again!) and "The Witness". 1/5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt It's amazing, I love it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K Each set is so beautiful! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Echodonut I uploaded it here in high resolution https://t.co/hf7906muOT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DMravunac Thank YOU for working on this great game, the music is so beautiful! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danny_hr @DMravunac That's great!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DMravunac I'm so so happy you like it!  I thought, maybe you'd like to have it in higher resolution, I uploaded it here  https://t.co/hf7906muOT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JonasKyratzes Uriel deserves it! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajorasMark It's just irresistible! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajorasMark You need this one?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajorasMark I agree, it might be with me for the rest of my life (maybe, some questions will have another answers when I'm older?). As for the second part - perhaps you are right, but I have to think about it...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MajorasMark @TalosPrinciple @Croteam I'm not selling anything, but I can just share larger versions if someone need them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt No, that doesn't sound right... Do you have Steam?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrFreekNik Thank you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NakamuraRTS @TalosPrinciple @Croteam Thank you so much! I thought no one would bother to read the codes, but I just had to put those thoughts in the painting, so I'm very glad you noticed ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gorudencash For me it's also really important. I wish I could convey all my thoughts...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toffy346 Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Croteam @TalosPrinciple Thank you!!! And thank you so much for creating one of the best games ever!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt I played on the computer, it's definitely there :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perry_rexanne Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt Thank you so much!! Floor mosaics and statues in the game are incredibly accurate recreations of existing ones, I love this fact.   Ir really worth playing, it's one of my two "best games ever".  As far as I know, it's available on many platforms, including PC.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In fact, when I played it for the first time it made me rethink everything about my life and beliefs. Those thoughts were depressing and difficult, and so were the conclusions, but sometimes we need to go through it to change and evolve. 7/7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you ask me, what is the best story about AI ever - I'll name "The Talos Principle". It's much more than just puzzle solving, there are so many philosophical questions about AI, and also about human nature, soul, mortality, faith. 6/7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I also loved Alexandra Drennan, we've never seen her in the game and yet her thoughts in the journals and her time capsules are unforgettable. I wish I could paint her too, maybe sometime in the future. 5/7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[and in "Road to Gehenna" he saves everyone. In my ending he died, sacrificing himself so no one is left behind, and his death was the most terrifying thing I've experienced in games - somehow It felt so real... 4/7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I can't express the feeling I had when the player actually meets him at the top of the tower. Uriel4, on the other hand, represent faith and Elohim, but I see also some similarities to The Shepherd - he also stayed to help others, 3/7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Shepherd is a true hero, and we know it only by some QR-codes. How many lines do you need to like a character? It was enough for me. I think, he was even more important, then the player's character, and it's so sad he didn't make it to the reality. 2/7 https://t.co/ewCwX4mQe9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I finally finished this painting - The Shepherd, Milton and Uriel4 from "The Talos Principle". I was really impressed by those characters. 1/7 @TalosPrinciple @Croteam https://t.co/ugDnwJciT2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Well, it's good to remember the ending of "The Road to Gehenna" - the most beautiful scene I've ever seen in games... though my ending was not only beautiful, but also scary.  2/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've been working on "The Talos Principle" fanart for more than a week, and and it's just now when I had a great idea to listen to it's OST for inspiration. This epic composition from the DLC is perfect. 1/2  https://t.co/lP01qyjFPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@N_A_K Great interview! I really hope my daughter will love StarTrek. She's now too young to watch episodes, but she already knows some characters - of course she loves Ryn, and asks about Andoria when we learn planets ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamDavidAjala Thank you so much!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In my first playthrough I ignored all optional puzzles and bonus levels, and now I completed all of them.3/3 https://t.co/XgzKo4VD4x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[but then started solving puzzles and couldn't stop. I played it 6 years ago, and of course now I didn't remember any solutions, I was afraid 3,5 years of babysitting turned my brain into jelly and I won't solve anything. Good news: I'm still smart!2/3 https://t.co/diVclmCpbd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just finished my second playthrough of "The Talos Principle", the greatest puzzle game. At first I just wanted to go wander in those ruins again - It's beautiful, I'm alone there, and I'm a robot... maybe to reed some depressing texts there... 1/3 https://t.co/KZamA8am9h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rashiduzzaman82 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DahkurArt @iamDavidAjala Thank you, Gabi! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Book. He is kind to all living creatures, I really like that about him.  #StarTrek #StarTrekDiscovery #digitalpainting https://t.co/JqrCF8eYa8]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>