<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Did my nails all cute   #nails #cute #excited https://t.co/4MwnZE77KT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finals season is starting and Im already having so much anxiety and have been so depressed. 2 more weeks   #finals #exams #depression #anxiety #badday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Playing sims today   #sims #gamergirl #fun #relax]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saw Mortal Kombat today on HBO Max  I feel lowkey dumb tho bc I just realized my school gives it to us for free   Are you going to see Mortal Kombat?  #MortalKombat #hbomax #UNCG #feelingstupid #free #collegelife #blood #gore #violent #videogame #Polls]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["If life were predictable it would cease to be life, and be without flavor." -Eleanor Roosevelt  #eleanorroosevelt #quotes #lifequotes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im so tired of life at this point   #life #anxiety #depression #tired]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My new little body-marker tattoo  #bodymarker #faketattoo #idrewthat #butterfly https://t.co/mWQUw8Egkn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SimonWhistler AHHHH OMG I AM LISTENING TO YOU RIGHT NOW!!! You are so awesome ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love this podcast so much  every Tuesday and Thursday I check in for the new ones and relished to the old ones every night! @SimonWhistler  https://t.co/mMe7fX14Yr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Covid vaccine update: lots of rest and water I feel much better my arm is still a little sore and Im still tired but much better then last night   #COVID19 #COVID19Vaccine #COVID19 #maskup #water #sleep #bedday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/rf0FqF33dn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Round 2 of the vaccine is kicking my ass... can some please give me my mommy   #CoronavirusPandemic #COVID19Vaccination #wantmymommy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you like Kong vs Godzilla #Godzilla #GodzillaVsKong #Kong #movies #poll]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really miss my one and it isnt fair that I cant have him with me all the time   #Lonely #misshim #love]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Busy week this week! I have lots of homework to get done along with some plans that I cant wait to update on later! Most of all cant wait to get McDonalds because I gave it up for lent with my fam and now I can have it!    #McDonalds #busyweek #collegelife #student #plans]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cant wait to wake up and talk to my one and only tomorrow   #inlove #oneandonly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My babe and I tried some new foods this week! All the vids are on my tiktok so if you want to get some tips on yummy international snacks check the link in my bio   #linkinbio #tryingnewfood #yummy #TikTok #fyp #bfgf #funtimes #funinthesun #internationalsnacks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was super productive today so yeah Im going to bed at 9pm cuz I earned it lol   #early #sleepy #productive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got Covid shot # 1   #CovidVaccine #COVID19 https://t.co/mBac9ONEg9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @InDyingEyesBand: The wait is over! Our debut album Decedent is out now! It's available wherever you listen to music! Click the link bel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InDyingEyesBand ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do I bother ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do I keep trying when others wont try too? Life is just getting too hard without consistent love and support. Ik I have loved ones but I honestly feel alone most of the time... life just sucks right now  #loveyourself #sosad #lifesucks #needsupport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so sad  I was supposed to spend the next couple days with my Bubs and now I cant  its for good reasons but I want snuggles   #lonely #misshim #snuggles #bubs #novisit #sosad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Messages like these  You're the light of my life and I cannot imagine a happy life without you. You're my universe. You're my soulmate. I can't wait to move to Canada with you and our puppy and Kitty and start a beautiful family with you  #canada #family #loml #happy #txt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone else have a messed up sleep schedule and has quickly become dependent on having your significant other in bed to feel safe enough to sleep... no just me? Cool   #sleeplessnights #dormlife #clingygf #needcuddles #warm #lonely #bfgf #dependent #sigother #goodnight #bedtime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so excited for tomorrow! I get to see my babes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Idk how in Colombia they dont have a life sentence/death penalty for someone like The Beast who raped  killed over 148+ children! Where are the inmates in Colombia that kill chomos! I feel sick listening to this podcast  hearing he might get out this yr   #wtf #Colombia #crime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Omg! Watching a criminal podcast talking about a 17th century crime and it said remember ladies if you have sex before marriage you WILL become a murder!   #poison #crimepodcast #17thcentury  #casualcriminalist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I really need to fix my sleeping schedule so I can be more productive! It's 2pm and I haven't even really started my day. All I have done is shower and write my To-Do List for today...   #notproductive #help #homework #collegelife #student #shower #sleep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Can you go your turn on cup pong pretty please   *goes turn* tank you   No problemo baby hehe it means a lot   *plays game and I BARELY win*  did you let me win   You won fair and square  #imsggames #games #bfgf #baby #cuppong #hehe #text #date #convo #ily]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/wniwRtUfiI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please save this beautiful puppy https://t.co/N1itYwhela]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mistakes were made... just finished a Starbucks espresso drink so I could get my homework done... oops   #oops #leftunattended #Starbucks #collegelife #homework #calculus #managementclass #school #college #dormlife #adulting #mistakes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im obsessed with criminal podcasts lately   #Criminal #podcasts #thecasualcriminal #sleepy #biblejohn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hayden02597070 Congratulations! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hayden02597070 Ask Matt ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Hayden02597070 After you date for a while you dont even do that ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ I love that you are a dork and a nerd but I love that you are one of the most unique people I have ever met   I love you b/c you know how to take care of me  I love that you are the most loving man Ive ever met  I love you b/c you make me happy when I'm sad   #ily #bfgf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Convo signs for ppl   me   babe  roommate  bf band mates   my besties   bf best friends   my fam   bf fam   #txt #convos #irl #emojis #bf #fam #reallife #mylife #welcometomyworld #Friends #love #fun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When your boyfriend sings you back to sleep while hes at work because you had a horrible nightmare   #boyfriend #Nightmare #SweetDreams #worklife #bfgf #sleep #singing #musiciangf #sweetheart]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InDyingEyesBand It was amazing!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InDyingEyesBand Cant wait ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My boyfriend told me he got electrocuted at work (keep in mind he works in gm retail) and when I ask how he tells me it was on his nipple and I lol be honest I busted out laughing... oops   #oops #gmretail #electricity #shocked #worklife #bf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Marlebean: [outside a blazing house]  Firefighter: ... Me: ... Firefighter: ... Me: ... There was a spider.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@InDyingEyesBand ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gf: Can I ask you a few silly questions  Bf: Yes baby girl Gf: Do you love me? Bf: Endlessly with all my heart Gf: Will you love me forever? Bf: Forever and always Gf: Will you marry me one day? Bf: One day sooner than you might expect Gf: Hehe  #reassurance #text #bfgf #convo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woke up to this sweet text today   Good morning baby! I hope you have an amazing day today! I love you so much and I hope you slept well and feel good! Today we're going to have a cute date. We're going to watch Hallmark movies and drink lots of coco   #text #goodmorning #ily]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gf: I wish I felt beautiful  Bf: I'm in love with your appearance Gf: Thank you Bf: You're my favourite person Gf:  mean it?  Bf: 10,000%  #love #beautiful #favperson #cutie #sweet #bfgf #musiciangf #missyou #text #convo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @XplodingUnicorn: 8-year-old: Does your diet include birthday cake?  Me: No.  8: Then your life is meaningless.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bf: I wanna watch frozen with you Gf: I thought you hated frozen Bf: I love frozen when I'm watching it with you Gf: How iz I so lucky Bf: I feel the exact same every day  #frozen #ily #love #DisneyPlus #lucky #blessed #bfgf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gf: can we umm... Bf: can we umm what baby? Gf:get umm engaged while we are away...? Bf:  maybe I had a plan Gf: well just do your plan Bf: good hehe   #Canada #trip #summervacation #weddingtalk #adulting #bfgf #inlove #engagement #plan #forever #iwannagetmarried #excited]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virtual movie dates are awesome!!! I miss snuggling with my babe but soon enough we will be together and never be apart again! Home Alone 2 movie date   #Virtual #moviedate #disneyplus #cuddles #fuzzyblankets #facetime #COVID19 #misshim @MattStretz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/1auZakvKWW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nothing is cuter than talking to your boyfriend about getting engaged and planning cute trips for your future together   #Forever #BOYFRIEND #girlfriend #future #cutetrips #Canada #engaged #love]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol when you get a notification that it is your Twitter anniversary   #anniversary #twitter #notification]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love when my bf drives by my house and talks to me while I sit on the porch! Its the only way we can see each other right now but I lover every minute   #inlove #Gemini #libra #bfgf #Corona #2020life #loveyou #porchvisits]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When you had a really bad day and your boyfriend sings to you to calm you down   #bf #badday #musiciangf #calm #lovehim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@XplodingUnicorn Ouch ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gf: Hey imma call you Mon Futur Mari from now on Bf: okay but what does it mean? Gf: It means my future husband in French! Bf: I love the new name   #french #bfconvo #mygoofball #realconvo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone seen a grinch ring??? They are the cutest ever   #grinch #rings #sales #cutest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hate being sick (not covid)  #sick #hate #notcovid #vomiting #fever #3daysstrong]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[            #starbucks #coffee #finalexams #stressed #funnyfont #hotmocha #please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have been watching Buzzfeed Unsolved everyday recently because my bf and I always watch it together and since we are apart I have been watching it since I miss him. It is making me feel like I am still with him! Thank you Guys so much!  #BuzzFeed #buzzfeedunsolved #loveyall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unpacked all my clothes and made my bed but my room is still a huge mess of random stuff that had to come home from the dorm.    #clothes #unpacked #moving #dormlife #winterbreak #homefortheholidays #cleaning #ocd #collegelife #CollegeStudent #Quarantine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stuck in quarantine with the fam  I cant see my bf except for when he drives by and I feel crappy cuz we havent been FaceTiming   #bored #facetime #bf #Quarantine #lonely #sad #2020sucks #coffeethoughts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so thankful to have you in my life @MattStretz you are my king, rock,  savior. I know in your arms I am safe. I love you with all my heart and I am so thankful that I get to spend another holiday calling you mine! I only wish we could spend it together.   #Thanksgiving #ILY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nothing like coming home for winter break and picking on your little brother with your little sister   #Siblings #home #winterbreak #lilbro #lilsis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3/4 projects done!!! I have to write a 12+ page paper today!! The stress level is rough   #projects #longessay #stress #school #collegelife #today #sleepy #explorepage]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/tVUDQVLXh9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have so much homework to do in addition to packing and I am so overwhelmed that right now I am in a team zoom meeting trying not to cry my eyes out.   #stressed #needabreak #help #cry #overwhelmed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do people eat dinner after 9:30? I dont get it. my family was always the 5-6 dinner time with an 8:30 snack time and a 9:30-10 bedtime. As an adult I dont get it and its 10:45 at night and I was just told I interrupted dinner cuz I called a loved one...   #wtf #idontgetit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My printer only printed the odd pages of my report! Life is going just great! I can't wait for winter break!  #holidaysarecoming #saveme #printersucks #printers #reports #FML]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next Monday is moving day! 3 projects still need to be finished and all the things I need for the next 2 months need to be packed! Someone, please send food and coffee ASAP!   #monday #twomonths #projects #packing #coffee #food #feedme #stressed #anxiety #homework #explorepage]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why am I still up? I have to be up and on my way to the bus by 6:15 tomorrow morning   #latenight #busride #early #whyamiawake #maskup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just sneezed so hard the spinny chair moved backwards and I almost hit my head   #ow #oops #maskon #library #sneezed #spinnychair #hwtime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Random Gemini Fact: It doesnt take much to make a Gemini happy, but it takes even less to make them mad.  #gemini #Zodiac #ZodiacSigns #Facts #FactsAboutMe #geminifact #happy #mad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boy: We need to talk Girl: Okay, what's up? Boy: Oh not now, tomorrow after work Girl: *has massive anxiety all day* Boy: I'm not leaving you Girl *tries best not to kill boy*  #realconvos #loveyou #relationships #Anxiety #weneedtotalk #gfbf #why]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl: EMERGENCY QUESTION...  Girl: whats your fav animal  Boy: turtle Girl: Otay bye   Boy: wat? Girl: thats all I needed love youuuu   #suprise #sneaky #hehe #CoupleGoals #convos #RealLife #turtles #loveyou #heconfused]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ we won   #SteelersNation #steelersvscowboys #winning https://t.co/D8ZtVR77GU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So not only do my team members like to stress me out by waiting until the last minute to do their work but now one of them plagiarises his entire part of the project due tonight! Now I and another team member have to redo his entire section! I am so over group work!  #pplsuck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me: Please turn in all parts of the assignment by Saturday so we can use Sunday to edit and format. Group: *Starts project Sunday* Me:*freaking out because its due tonight*  #stressed #groupwork #project #college]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New emojis on the iPhone are so cool!!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do ppl always push you to your breaking point?   #annoyed #disappointed #why #pplsuck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do teachers not understand that most students take more than just their class in a semester?   #stressed #schoolsucks #teachers #semester #class #Students]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who says I spent the last 2 quarters of an hour instead of half an hour?  #twoquarters #hour #halfanhour #whosays]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[21 days until I go home  I have to pack up all my stuff for 2 months but also spend as much time as I can with my bf (who has no car at this time) b/c I cannot see him once I go home. Plus do 3 group projects and 2 final projects and 5 exams ontop of all my normal hw #2020sucks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#stolenfromfacebook #ElectionDay #ElectionDay2020 #Vote2020 #Trump2020 #Biden2020 #Steelers #funny https://t.co/B4ezascjTg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I voted by mail (so yes I voted) but I'm sad cuz everybody I know got a cool pen and it was my first time voting   #Vote2020 #votepens #VoteByMail #FirstTimeVoter #Biden2020  #Trump2020 #ElectionDay #Election2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl: You called me a monkey. You said sleeping with me was like sleeping with a monkey! Boy: Yes bc you were all over the place! Girl: Hehe Boy: It was very cute. I enjoyed every second of it! Girl: Oh? Boy: 100/10 would do it again! I love you endlessly  #love #text #real #fav]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bf got in a car accident so we are having a junk food filled cuddly movie date tonight  I love this man so much   #caraccident #junkfood #cuddles #relationshipgoals #moviedate #2020sucks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so sick of schoolwork today! School this year has been so overwhelming.   #schoolwork #burnedout #needabreak #toomuch #homework #groupprojects #tired #forums #Essays #vidassignments #2020schooling #needanap #examday #zoomclasses #school #overwhelming #2020sucks #Drowning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cooked today! I made yummy raviolis and garlic bread   #adulting #cooking #garlicbread #raviolis #successful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gone in 60 Seconds has got to be one of the best movies of all time!  #gonein60seconds #movie #awesome #nicolascage #2000s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 group projects overlapping and both had sections due today! All done but its been a long day!   #groupwork #businessclass #projects #reports #part1 #international #groups #stress]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why does my milk taste like salsa?  #salsa #milk #gross #why #sadness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone else need a mental health day full of cuddles, Disney movies, and junk food?  #Mentalhealth #DisneyPlus #movies #cuddles #chinesefood #junkfood #fuzzyblankets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do you do when your boyfriend passes out drunk before you fall asleep? Draw on his tummy with henna ink ofc!  #henna #tattoo #drunk #21bday #October2020 #loveyou #bf #relationships]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Asks everyone in my group if the time for the meeting (that I took the time to put in their time zones) would work for everyone and get left on read for 2 days now... Love group work so much   #groupwork #timezones #international #nohelp #leftonread #Russia #Ecuador #Canada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that Marilynn Monroe and Queen Elizabeth were born in the same year?  #Queen #QueenElizabeth #born #year #MarilynMonroe #funfact #1926]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>