<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Today on the blog I'm reviewing #TheNatureofaLady by @RoseannaMWhite ! #ChristianFiction #amreading https://t.co/Bab73cnEBB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to The Nature of a Lady by Roseanna M. White https://t.co/JSHfLBe4Vj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to The Nature of a Lady by Roseanna M. White https://t.co/JSHfLBe4Vj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookgrace11 That's what my grandmother always called them! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's always funny to me when I see "writer" on lists of work at home jobs to make extra money.  Trust me, this is NOT a get-rich-quick kind of job.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I read A Peculiar Combination by Ashley Weaver https://t.co/2FQp1iUFLB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isn't she precious?!  https://t.co/TctfsRne5i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I read The Sign of Death by Callie Hutton https://t.co/hTuZwRtFpt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This beautiful #HistoricalFiction by @RoseannaMWhite is releasing soon! Follow this link to pre-order your copy of Libby and Oliver's adventure. #TheNatureoraLady https://t.co/ISarHLICxW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I got vaccinated! https://t.co/LTmKectaEx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ COVER REVEAL  Presenting the cover of my next novel, Murder at the Picture Show! Follow this link for the full synopsis!  #amreading #NewBook #mystery #HistoricalFiction  https://t.co/NU8igE5AU4 https://t.co/yNbJbeeAHG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Murder at the Picture Show by Miranda Atchley https://t.co/gFNS9HYh5Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookgrace11 Oh no  what a bummer!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoseannaMWhite: #NewEpisode - If life as you knew it ground to a halt, who and what would you still be? Me--I'd still be a writer. http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoseannaMWhite: #ThoughtfulThursday - Walk worthy of the calling. This is a phrase that's been lingering in my heart and mind for the l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookgrace11 Boo  Sorry this happened to you, Grace.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AmandaGeaney @bondbooks @Julie_Klassen @AnnTatlock @kcbmiller @GailGkittleson @DNBocek @LeanneWSmith @AR_ContiFulwell @sarat1701 @CLMillerbooks @J_C_Hopkins @kendypearson @CUBrakefield @KathleenRouser @MeganBesing Thanks for mentioning me, Amanda! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Hope Between the Pages by Pepper D. Basham https://t.co/nLOZyL5yPL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Paint and Nectar by Ashley Clark https://t.co/KjIdNozQPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want a signed copy of this gorgeous #HistFic? Are you ready for a new adventure? Preorder @roseannamwhite's NEW RELEASE today! Releases May 4, 2021. https://t.co/oe4P38qYr4 @roseannamwhite #thesecretsoftheisles #TheNatureofaLady https://t.co/YsB7RLZDNa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookgrace11 How funny!  I was never eager to drive and still just do it when I have to. I'm definitely not one of those who likes to just drive around. Lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 facts about me: 1: I self-published my first book at age 19 2: I collect peacock anything 3: My favorite book is The Blue Castle 4: Didn't get my driver's license til I was 20 5: My mama's my bestie ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow Abi Hensley's journey through 1920's Europe in A Time For Adventure, #free in the #Kindle store this week.  #Kindledeals #ChristFic #HistFic #amreading #WomensHistoryMonth https://t.co/lxDkwXSht4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Harbor Secrets by Melody Carlson https://t.co/EmzcyQBHog]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After the Great War, Abi Hensley faces grief and changes in her writing career. Of Things To Come is #free in the #Kindle store this week.  #Kindledeals #ChristFic #HistFic #amreading #WomensHistoryMonth https://t.co/pAFKfCl9KT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the midst of WWI, Abi Hensley becomes involved in the war effort at home, as well as the women's suffrage movement. Download All The Future Holds for #free.  #ChristFic #HistFic #amreading #KindleDeals #WomensHistoryMonth https://t.co/MidmDuabC7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 1915, Abi Hensley fled an unwelcome proposal to persue her dreams of independence. Read her story in A Castle in the Sky for #free.  #KindleDeals #amreading #ChristFic #HistFic #WomensHistoryMonth https://t.co/i2SzkKnNYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love Roseanna's books and can't wait to read The Nature of a Lady! Sign up for her mailing list for exclusive sneak peeks!  https://t.co/gjo1VouNnR @roseannamwhite #thesecretsoftheisles #thenatureofalady #sneakpeek https://t.co/faFBCg18iX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celebrate #WomensHistoryMonth with The Abi Hensley Series, the story of a woman's journey to independence in the early 20th century. #Free for #Kindle this week!  #amreading https://t.co/bEORXdVfyo https://t.co/CIrHAz74LQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This book  It's Drew Farthering, my favorite 1930s sleuth, in the Yorkshire moors with shades of Bronte. It is all my catnip! #amreading https://t.co/YjqeyfXiD5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Miss Lattimore's Letter by Suzanne Allain https://t.co/8xh9gpaEjd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 of 5 stars to Where'd You Go, Bernadette by Maria Semple https://t.co/voerc5uURU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Winning the Gentleman by Kristi Ann Hunter https://t.co/qSM8LJ635h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does anything taste as good as a mocha frappe?  Nope. Can't think of anything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Miranda and Me by Miranda Hart https://t.co/zHiwnEjcb7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CameraCourt I absolutely love #AllCreaturesPBS  and want a million seasons of it! And yes, I definitely think/want Mrs. Hall and Siegfried to be together. When he held the hymnal for her on Christmas Eve... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 of 5 stars to The Paris Dressmaker by Kristy Cambron https://t.co/XsFbZBsjFo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I read The Sign of Death by Callie Hutton https://t.co/hTuZwRLgO3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: The Nature of a Lady by Roseanna M. White https://t.co/4R5GO82bJF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spending this #Snowmageddon2021 indoors with Fiona and Max, working on their next adventure in Murder at the Picture Show. #amwriting #amwritingmystery]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to Dressed for Death by Julianna Deering https://t.co/KbwWf9PFlj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: The Thief of Blackfriars Lane by Michelle Griep https://t.co/M7cyyJMona]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enter for the chance to win @allisonkpittman's PUDGE AND PREJUDICE, from @crazy4fiction  @Relz https://t.co/aC5ENO7sKS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: The Ice Swan by J'nell Ciesielski https://t.co/IZs1lKL2ZJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CameraCourt Yum, I love gelato! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It was 70 degrees today. In January! Coffee ice cream was a requirement. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: The London House by Katherine Reay https://t.co/7bGE3xyRgR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 of 5 stars to No Filter by Heather Day Gilbert https://t.co/05q1BeiYgh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Beauty Among Ruins by J'nell Ciesielski https://t.co/ajNbdqKcVl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to The Trouble With Love by Toni Shiloh https://t.co/mUKcuXPjdG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to From the Start by Melissa Tagg https://t.co/DF0RpQAgV7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Murder at the Mikado by Julianna Deering https://t.co/asBpfuaPHq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoseannaMWhite 's #DreamsofSavannah is #nowavailable ! Drop by my blog to learn more about this amazing novel. #amreading  https://t.co/625RagzJ1P https://t.co/rbasbhzsYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Dreams of Savannah by Roseanna M. White https://t.co/jJpABTeRAs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Dreams of Savannah by Roseanna M. White https://t.co/jJpABTwss0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 sucked for many reasons. One being a health scare for my Mama, my bestie. Thankfully she's doing better now, and we are just praying for continued improvement in 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you ready for an #adventure? "Because stories change the world." #DreamsofSavannah #amreading #new @roseannamwhite https://t.co/jPtCzrn1xK https://t.co/f8OkfukpJ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Jocelyn by Sarah Monzon https://t.co/oI5zBCqWhW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Dearest Josephine by Caroline George https://t.co/AuDL7WPtYs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to To Steal a Heart by Jen Turano https://t.co/WnI9MzgSvb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How beautiful is the cover for Roseanna M. White's next book, Dreams of Savannah? I can't wait to read this Civil War set novel. #PreOrder it today! @roseannamwhite @bethanyhousefiction #DreamsofSavannah #roseannamwhite https://t.co/KF2pq2qsKJ https://t.co/OG9IrC9lrV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can't wait for Dreams of Savannah to release? Sign up for a #sneakpeek! (Sneak Peek releases Dec 1st) https://t.co/gjo1VouNnR @roseannamwhite #dreamsofsavanna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you're like me, you're craving #Christmas more than ever this year. The Christmas Book Shoppe, a love letter to all things bookish and holiday, is a great addition to your holly jolly TBR at just 99 cents, or #free for #KU. #amreading  https://t.co/j9HNWwOjrH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Masks are an easy way to slow the spread of the virus and a simple way to save lives. #Wearamask #maskup ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happiness is buying a 2 pack of Lindt Lindor truffles and finding 3 truffles inside. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CameraCourt @hallmarkchannel @hallmarkmovie I agree !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RoseannaMWhite: Sneak Peeks are coming your way! Make sure you are signed up here: https://t.co/QF1qTkhkeK! First peek goes out on Dece]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CameraCourt @hallmarkchannel @hallmarkmovie I second this. My favorite Hallmark Christmas movie is An Old Fashion Christmas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Up on my blog is my review of The Red Canary. I absolutely loved this roaring twenties tale filled with the beauty of nature and music!  #amreading  https://t.co/qrdlxlKDWM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Of Mozart and Magi by Rachel McMillan https://t.co/gQrOCse9Sw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rachel is always so encouraging. https://t.co/WVrnMiPgS6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Dearest Josephine by Caroline George https://t.co/WTotSPc2KF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Christmas Cake Kisses by Lena Goldfinch https://t.co/bgD9nEEdVg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I loved this book. Highly recommend! https://t.co/Ryk8Dh47Bx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#KindleUnlimited subscribers can read this book about an Irish immigrant and a Great War vet solving a #mystery in 1920s New York for #free. #amreading #HistoricalFiction  https://t.co/GWJuuPJKAU https://t.co/imSjOqsOJI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Beauty Among Ruins by J'nell Ciesielski https://t.co/ajNbdqKcVl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: The Thief of Blackfriars Lane by Michelle Griep https://t.co/oX3yAVYtYz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Learned yesterday that I didn't get the job I reeeeally wanted.  So this morning I decorated my tree early to cheer myself up. https://t.co/DW8XBJXS76]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookgrace11 You have a beautiful cat, Grace! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to The Red Canary! I absolutely loved this roaring twenties novel. #amreading #HistoricalFiction #ChristianFiction https://t.co/eUGHrpRiXa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rachkmc We are, too. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CameraCourt Yes! Cashmere Glow was my favorite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to The Love Note by Joanna Davidson Politano https://t.co/gy2bLKWUex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to A Very Merry Holiday Movie Guide by Rachel McMillan https://t.co/RDcvj2MZOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York, 1922: Intelligent Irish immigrant Fiona Clery and haunted Great War veteran Max Gillespie meet as they each attempt to solve a murder... and they just might fall in love along the way.   https://t.co/V3jqOTqHtI #mystery #romance #ChristFic #HistoricalFiction #KU https://t.co/X5gUyXQ14R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to Murder Aboard the Flying Scotsman by Lee Strauss https://t.co/6RHQiCj8NM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Jazz Age New York, Fiona Clery and Max Gillespie meet as they each attempt to solve a murder...and they just might fall in love along the way. #amreadingromance #amreadingmystery #ChristFic #HistoricalFiction #KU  https://t.co/V3jqOTqHtI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last day to enter the #giveaway for this Jazz Age cozy mystery!   https://t.co/Oa6cLHoMrC #NewRelease #amreading #amreadingmystery #amreadingromance #books #ChristFic #HistoricalFiction https://t.co/Q5ViU5mXEJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CameraCourt: Book Review  Blog Tourv "Deadly Pearls" by @miranda_atchley  #giveaway #mystery https://t.co/lQABg8tHJy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Deck The Shelves by Toni Shiloh https://t.co/eBQgYwSKMd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BeautyInTheBind Thank you, Jolene!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BeautyInTheBind: #BookSpotlight  #Giveaway! Three copies of #DeadlyPearls by #MirandaAtchley are up for grabs! Learn more about the bo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CameraCourt @rachkmc @monzonwrites @AnnaLeeHuber @tameraalexander @teresa_tysinger Thank you for including me, Courtney! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What an honor to be listed among such talented names! https://t.co/tq4zmMN8kS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hjsnyder28 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enter to win a copy of this Jazz Age cozy mystery!   https://t.co/Oa6cLHoMrC #NewRelease #giveaway #amreading #amreadingmystery #amreadingromance #books #ChristFic #HistoricalFiction https://t.co/qPYvaxpvvN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wishing @rachkmc 's A Very Merry Holiday Movie Guide a happy birthday!  I can't wait to read this beautiful book filled with Christmastime goodness!  https://t.co/YoTiMzD5FE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today's the day! Happy birthday to Deadly Pearls!  You can now purchase this Jazz Age #mystery in both paperback and ebook formats, or #read for #free with #KU! #amreading #amreadingmystery   https://t.co/V3jqOTqHtI https://t.co/rxv5KoW06O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to Murder Aboard the Flying Scotsman by Lee Strauss https://t.co/UKVKnmcris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoanPNienhuis: My #BookReview of Deadly Pearls, a good historical novel set in New York in the 1920s by Miranda Atchley. Enter to win a]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>