<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @L4L_UK: The NHS collects confidential patient information from all NHS organisations, trusts, local authorities  private hospitals pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sar247365 @Pmason74 @Sleng401 @AsemHamdy55 Sweden doesn't use the Euro. Are you getting mixed up with somewhere else?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sleng401 @AsemHamdy55 @sar247365 I have family over there. It is vastly better than this nation of bedwetters....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@landingsaregood @AsemHamdy55 @alan_lingwood It isn't as simple as that. Sweden had much lower deaths than their neighbours in 2018/2019 so 2020 was distorted. Look at the longer picture and nothing is exceptional.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liamtreacy @AsemHamdy55 I have family in Sweden. Don't believe the b******t from msm. Life has remained pretty normal (it was so nice to visit last year) and their death toll is unexceptional.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robinmonotti3: Is what the WHO  local governments did, namely witholding simple treatments (HCQ, AZ, IVM), inducing fear (SPI-B-SAGE)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LonRomy @BBCPolitics You are not sent to the front line until you are 18 so the chances of dying for your country are pretty slim.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GBGabBrunner: Your kids are growing up like *this*. Why? Because you chose this. You accepted needless and useless torture of your chil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @McGiff: "I believe it's only our own actions that can stop this never-ending insanity" says @DanWootten https://t.co/ziBAXxOcks and I s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whitford747: Too near the truth for @theSNPs liking! Theyve become cultish with too many Scots falling under @NicolaSturgeons dream]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @org_scp:  The Vaccines Minister @nadhimzahawi is doing the media rounds this morning.   We'd like to remind him  viewers of his lies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timfprice: RETWEET if you think vaccine passports are a fascistic evil.   RETWEET if you also think that Boris Johnson and the entirety]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: A huge group of Doctors from around the world have united to tell the public that the C0V1D jabs are Unnecessary, ine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ericdun19416783 @Shelo78334355 Take up is falling off a cliff. They reduced the eligible age three times in a week. That speaks volumes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlackersNot: If you are still wearing a mask you are literally doing a performative little dance because the government is entertained]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: Well? https://t.co/wueGOaoKwg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrunoAm05317727: Poll: Has Boris Johnson done a good job during the pandemic? Vote and retweet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrettMendoza_ WTAF?!?! The world has truly gone mad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What changed your mind @MattHancock ? https://t.co/1FyTaYSBaM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AdamWagner1 @OversightBoard @Facebook This 'eminent' board includes Nick Clegg. Are you having a laugh?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joanna96678313 He does seem a sandwich short of a picnic...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joanna96678313 I noticed that both of them attacking you were cyclists. No further comment needed?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @maverick2u2: Think about your vote Londoners PLEASE.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@myGP_app @AliJaneMoore They won't admit a breach of data protection on here. Make sure you opt out of providing your data asap.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julianspinks @AliJaneMoore @myGP_app I have the NHS app but, apart from basic info and functions (repeat prescriptions etc.) it wants me to sign up with various private providers selected by my surgery. Looks like they'll have to put up with me ringing them!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: Psychology Exam 2021  Q. Identify the two major Symptoms of Stockholm syndrome  A. The victim develops positive feeling]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cat5weaver @AndyEMorrison @NicolaSturgeon This would need to be agreed by rest of UK and the way the Nats have been to the English it isn't so likely. Perhaps the hate will come back and bite......]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BlackersNot: Normal = Life pre Covid = No masks/No vaccine passports/No social distancing  It also means not being continuously bombard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: A good summary of recent events. https://t.co/RBVxDvBLtu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: BBC in 2001   "Children will never see snow in Britain by 2020"  Yorkshire in May 2021 "Yeah, right!" https://t.co/02ak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: If the face mask you're wearing isn't fitted with a radio to call ground control, you're not actually a WWII fighter Ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @northerness: A reminder that, on Thursday, *nobody* can be prevented from voting because they are not wearing a face covering. Thus, yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProfKarolSikora: Will politicians ever accept the full scale of the cancer crisis?  Probably not, but what's so frustrating is that an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: They have led to distrust, anger and protest. The idea of domestic vaccine passports was what most high level MPs in Governmen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LorettasmithJ: Has Covid affected irreparably relationships with any of your loved ones?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rosellacottage If you are using Android you need to go into settings and disable everything to do with Goigle. Maps plots your location even when the app is closed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miguel_says @rosellacottage @signalapp @DuckDuckGo @ProtonVPN Sensible advice. Do a search on Google then repeat it on DuckDuckGo and see the difference...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: These people are psychopaths and shouldn't be allowed anywhere near any child at any time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joserosado: Who did this? https://t.co/XpK0cY8FBb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CrimsonCode1: CV19 Conspiracy Theorists - Are the people who have taken the time and effort to research official and clinical trials do]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StrumpetsV: If you have the vax now and further down the line regret it, you can't undo it. If you don't have the vax now and further d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Brian_Hunter @JamesBr45845054 @Vaso90645963 You have just contradicted your earlier comment and admitted they only have emergency authority as trials aren't complete!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@helenma02769447 @madashington @JuliaHB1 And 25 years of public service too....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@madashington @JuliaHB1 Please provide evidence for your claim.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wobblybob2020 @psymonbee @IceCameron @eisa_salimian @JuliaHB1 Member of NEU so vested interest in keeping kids masled.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joeyjojojunior_: @EssexPR They are a joke, any parent should write to the school ask for the risk assessment that proves reduced oxygen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cricketwyvern: Update to various Covid-19 indicators for England:  Deaths continue down at a good rate.  Hospital admissions (7-day a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drucroft @PHE_uk Went past a jbbing site earlier today. A couple of months ago people were queuing but today nobody waiting outside at all...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Another low low data day. We will have catch up tomorrow, but the 7 day average date of deaths must be single figures?!  Curre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThisIsTheWorl18: @MattHancock FOR BALANCE - ADVERSE EFFECTS UPDATE (at 14 APR)  Update: deaths now 1,047 at 21 April   #VaccineSafety]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NewtonClarkeUK: After each piece of Government propaganda or coercion are you more or less likely to accept the vaccine?  Please RT  #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @favp_org: It couldn't be clearer that the next month and a half could define freedom and civil liberties in this country forever.  We h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nicolaannjames @PoliticsForAlI Wannabe barrister? Yet you have done no research and just parrot the gov't lines. Suggest you use your education to do some research.....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheYetiBum @sambo2690 @NEUnion @GavinWilliamson Please provide links to these studies showing their effectiveness in controlling a virus. I'll wait....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Brian_Hunter @JamesBr45845054 @Vaso90645963 They are not approved. They have been given a temporary authority under Reg174 of the Human Medicine Regs 2012. They are still experimental and have not completed trials yet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesHamiltonB: Are we where we are because of Gain of Function research?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BHAFC_NEWS: Time spent watching this gif:   Nowhere near enough.   #BHAFC https://t.co/tKNiI72LG2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@apsmunro @LubnaKerr Please provide the evidence to back up your statement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: Me  "Have you had your vaccine?"  Them  "Oh yes!"  Me  "Ya stupid muppet."  Them "...                        "  How's i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KieranCHodgson: A little treat for fans of #LineOfDuty   Bad TV Impressions: Line Of Duty Series 6  SPOILER ALERT #comedy #impressions]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FlorinInteriors: @MattHancock Can you provide the independent safety data first and you've been asked twice in the Commons for data reg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elizabe32413720: https://t.co/tGwrH5fsr3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @13orangesbc: Chance to exercise your democratic rights: on May 6 Im going to vote for...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LonsdaleKeith: @hughosmond So, the legal arguments were not even judged. It was thrown out on the basis of timescale.  What utter conte]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: So SAGE now admit that the risk of Covid in a pub or restaurant is 'relatively low' with just 226 outbreaks in them sinc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tufoniti: @CromwellStuff https://t.co/bfUC0docNT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @T4Recovery: "Our supposed guardians in the media havent merely looked the other way while our livelihoods have been destroyed and our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Please read this. We all need to pause and reflect. Because what is happening right now is so profoundly wrong. On so ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Antipolluters: This goes for any celeb and sportsperson.... https://t.co/912Esm72hg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HabberleySteve: How do you know what they died of because covid related deaths do not have a post mortem?  There is no other definitive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @simsy1977: Stay home, stay safe, wear a mask and get your jab. While we destroy the economy, small businesses, jobs and take away your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KRudence @moongazerale Sadly, they have that power. Remove the licence and the publican's livelihood and home is gone.  If it is a tied house the brewery will soon get a new manager in to take over.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @STattisconie: Any time you think you're having a crap day and it can't get any worse, think about this Brazilian prisoner, spent 5 year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamFit45249570: @ToniaBuxton They want to put experimental emergency use drugs into children that have a 99.99% survival rate.  Out of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Has the 'old normal' gone forever?  @mrmarkdolan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @forrestmaready: 1. A lot of people are taking a second look at vaccines these days. As someone whos written several books about them,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DJSiri: Denmark Ditches JJ COVID Vaccine, Says Benefits Do Not Outweigh Risk of Blood Clots  Children's Health Defense https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nick_the_geek78: Deaths in single figures Hospitalisations near zero Cases at false positive levels No imminent wave expected Scientist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LorettasmithJ: God forbid! https://t.co/QVK4kUMKvk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hughosmond: News: after unexplained 2 week delay, Court ruled our claim "academic" as would not be heard before 17th May. After the rul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BenRogers223 @bear44willis Texas, Florida, Sweden? Wake up bedwetter....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AnneMar45451941: @flossyflange True https://t.co/KRgdWCDJWL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nozzie_5252: @Daktangle @shrinkingvio1et Christ on a bike my Dad has made it to 91 without ever wearing one ! He had no shoes till  he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JOHNPAULMABBS: How to leave a supporter of lockdown, masks and social distancing completely flummoxed ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @northerness: Masks are the least "normal" part of the whole pandemic response. These comments/stories about masks staying should be rin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sophiecbrr: @MattHancock April 23, a molecular biologist  toxicologist, w 30 yrs exp, incl. in vaccine development, told the CDC that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samasjapi: Us none testers, none social distancers, and none vaxxers, are all breezing through life without as much as a sniffle.   Whi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsPollss: Boris Johnson has offered some words of hope to Britons, asserting that there is a good chance that one-metre plus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rosellacottage: Were awake @rosellacottage https://t.co/MTgpQ5Gv5z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lisajblee: @Telegraph @lensiseethrough My children are adults now but I would never let this government near my child with these new, s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KRudence @moongazerale Sadly if they ignore the draconian rules they will have their licence rwmoved and will be closed down. Councils have a lot of power over them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrislittlewoo8: @allisonpearson @BBCNews After only 1 death reported today, ppl need to ask themselves:  Why do they want to jab child]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: The limit on the number of mourners at funerals will be lifted in two weeks.  Ian Collins: You were the government that sto]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cricketwyvern: Update to various Covid-19 indicators for England.  Deaths have continued to fall steadily over the weekend.  Positive]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AeroTory @KingBobIIV Bloody fat fingers.... Hancock and Sunak]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@letseathh @Anshul__K I take it you use eye peotection when venturing out as, if it airborne, the eyes are a great place to pick it up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DancerDad: Yes lets get this trending again folks. We need to keep encouraging others to go exempt. I feel many are toying with the id]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EU_NO_MORE I cannot and will not vote Tory all the time Johnson and Hancock are in post and they continue to turn the party into the Green Party. Lifelong Tory - they are not Tories.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KathLaw5 @LozzaFox You can get attachments for electric guitars that connect to bluetooth headphones.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: NEW: Please answer  retweet this poll. Of the people you *personally* know, how many are now routinely breaking the Covid ru]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>