<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#MUFC #MCFC #CFC #AVFC #AFC #LUFC #LFC #SWFC #SAFC #NUFC #BORO #THFC #EFC #RangersFC #CelticFC #WHUFC #WWFC #CPFC https://t.co/jzJgn3ghEb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timfprice: RETWEET if you think vaccine passports are a fascistic evil.   RETWEET if you also think that Boris Johnson and the entirety]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BrunoAm05317727: Poll: Has Boris Johnson done a good job during the pandemic? Vote and retweet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Vaccine passports for domestic venue entry is one of the most appallingly illiberal and authoritarian ideas ever floated]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mybollix: Cork gym plans to defy restrictions and open at end of May @Dempz8  https://t.co/fGrT8EfGXY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#SAFC #NUFC #Boro #MFC #LUFC #HCFC #theTigers #Darlington #darlo #Hartlepool #HUFC #Pools #Durham #HeedArmy #blyth #southshields #northshields #tynemouth #hebburn #jarrow #carlisle #cufc #hull #sunderland #Newcastle #sunderland #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/oJVMvrwBl8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/oJVMvrwBl8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danbloom1 People really need to snap out of this and reject this sh*te. Insane giving in to this for a holiday. If no one participates they cant implement it. Even for international travel #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These really are taking the p*ss niw. UNLOCK!! #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/ScAvfKoPWX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MUFC #MCFC #AFC #THFC #EFC #CAFC #NFFC #SWFC #SAFC #NUFC #LFC #LUFC #AVFC #WHUFC #Hartlepool #tuesdayvibe #tuesdaymotivations https://t.co/tEa8QJZ273]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GallionHallion: @apsmunro Prosecutions are needed. Needless and widespread harm inflicted on defenceless, voiceless children by our scu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ThisMorning #tuesdaymotivations #tuesdayvibe #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/gzIYNDOnEU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports #ThisMorning #tuesdayvibe #tuesdaymotivations #TuesdayFeeling https://t.co/9Cdg0ZBpT1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hubculture Scum sell outs. You can stick your vax passports up your a*se #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/5bqTZAzyuM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/P51Dq90yCR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/d64GMwcTxS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeNews: Were back after 7 days on the Twitter Naughty Step.  Please like / retweet if you can see this tweet!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/6WOq4ZXuUM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: #EFC #MCFC #CFC #LFC #LUFC #THFC #AFC #AVFC #WHUFC #SAFC #NUFC #CelticFC #RangersFC #NFFC #SWFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: DEADLINE 2100hrs TODAY. Takes 2 mins and all evidence there for you. Please RT #MCFC #MUFC #SAFC #NUFC #LFC #LUFC #WHUFC #C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: NEW: Please answer  retweet this poll. Of the people you *personally* know, how many are now routinely breaking the Covid ru]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports #takeoffthemask https://t.co/COQlYfgMOM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beverleyturner Easy way to complete. Takes 2 mins and provides the evidence for you https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GMB @devisridhar I think she is talking out of her unqualified a*se #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alanvibe @ToniaBuxton This is an easy way to complete it. It takes 2 mins and provides the evidence required https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaneLor81308510 @calvinrobinson @Unlocked_UK_ @pow_rebecca This makes it really easy to do please share https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cathyk567 @calvinrobinson @LozzaFox This makes it really easy to complete and provides the evidence for you. It only takes 2 mins. Please complete and share https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RitaCoaching @calvinrobinson This makes it really easy to complete and provides the evidence for you. It takes 2 mins. Please complete and share https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnTShallow @calvinrobinson @LozzaFox This makes it quick and easy to complete mate. Please share, takes 2 mins https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GarethEllis80 @calvinrobinson This makes it really easy to complete mate. 2 mins https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Emma_A_Webb @calvinrobinson https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@calvinrobinson This makes it really easy to fill in. It takes 2 mins and provides the evidence #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Josiestweet Get on to @hollywills  @Schofe and the rest of them at this morning. Surely they would support this #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/TGpqtnoHcD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna @Josiestweet @AlisonHammond @JuliaHB1 all would surely. @NoelGallagher has spoken out about this madness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dreamboats_1 @BreesAnna @saveourrightsuk The deadline for this is not until 9pm tonight. You still have time! Please complete and RT #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VERY IMPORTANT. Takes 2 mins and all the work is done for you. DEADLINE 9pm TODAY. Please RT https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3 #BankHolidayMonday #boohootreats #mondaythoughts #MondayMotivation #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DEADLINE 2100hrs TODAY. Takes 2 mins and all evidence there for you. Please RT #MCFC #MUFC #SAFC #NUFC #LFC #LUFC #WHUFC #CFC #AFC #THFC #EFC #CAFC #CelticFC #NCFC #WWFC #DCFC #MFC #RangersFC #BRFC #NFFC https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darjamfar I dont think so mate, they are just gathering evidence for the consultation. They got 50k responses apparently last time then for some reason decided to do it again]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deadline 1145 today. Takes 2 mins  everything done for you #ThisMorning #mondaythoughts #MondayMotivation #MondayMorning #MUFC #MCFC #CFC #LFC #LUFC #WHUFC #THFC #AFC #AVFC #EFC #SWFC #NFFC #SAFC #NUFC #RangersFC #CelticFC https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/BySgzJeF1B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna Particularly in light of these finding from the prestigious Salk institute. The spike protein the vaccines use actually cause disease themselves #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/w76ivewDlr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: Come on it couldn't be easier to submit evidence against vaccine passports. Its all done for you  takes 2 mins #EFC #MUFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/FbR0EwNsUs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: @Freedom49503795 @Demo2020cracy Everything done for you here with links to evidence. Takes 2 mins https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3 #]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pisces20203 @PaulRChase @YardleyShooting Lets not forget the seasonal nature of these respiratory infections]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulyherts @PoliticsForAlI @Telegraph You are either thick as f*ck or a sick b*stard. If youve got kids they should be taken off you #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kishlight @smile28554950 @thefoxtully I presume you believe the testing regime etc, the validity of tests etc to give you your figures. This is, unfortunately, the crux of the problem. These PCR tests are fundamentally flawed as several courts across Europe have ruled.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @darrenmark69: Dear @BorisJohnson if 21st June 2021 does not end everything associated with coronavirus act, be it social distancing, ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef You creepy f*ckers #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/VwYUy1gd8E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kishlight @smile28554950 @thefoxtully You can ask professor John Ioannidis for his thoughts on this. He was widely regarded as the worlds leading authority in this area. I suggest you look into what he has to say]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Freedom49503795 @Demo2020cracy Everything done for you here with links to evidence. Takes 2 mins https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3 #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/kQwpqZMJzv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kishlight @smile28554950 @thefoxtully These diseases arent even in the same ball park mate. For example Yellow fever has a mortality rate of 30-50%. Covid-19 is about 0.15%. This is total overreach. Its not about the virus #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DailyExposeUK: BREAKING - Adverse Reactions to the C0V* -1D jabs include 7,699 cardiac disorders, 10,633 eye disorders including blindn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mcdonagh_quinn: There needs to be more TD's like Mattie McGrath, Peader Toibin and Michael McNamara in the dail.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna This is a quick easy to complete submission with all of the evidence already cited. Please RT #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Come on it couldn't be easier to submit evidence against vaccine passports. Its all done for you  takes 2 mins #EFC #MUFC #MCFC #CFC #AVFC #AFC #LUFC #LFC #SWFC #SAFC #NUFC #THFC #RangersFC #CelticFC #WWFC #NCFC #DCFC #MFC  #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/KRJjMtOGw3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: #MUFC #MCFC #AFC #AVFC #CFC #WWFC #WHUFC #LUFC #SAFC #LFC #EFC #THFC #RangersFC #CelticFC #NUFC #CPFC #NCFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SPassports: These are coming if you let them. YOU can stop them!!! #MUFC #MCFC #LFC #LUFC #THFC #AFC #AVFC #WHUFC #SAFC #NUFC #CelticFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#EFC #MCFC #CFC #LFC #LUFC #THFC #AFC #AVFC #WHUFC #SAFC #NUFC #CelticFC #RangersFC #NFFC #SWFC https://t.co/HLlKCNE5f7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Heachy_1979: Vaccine passports are the biggest threat Western democracy has ever faced. They will not be confined to Covid they won't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MUFC #MCFC #CFC #AVFC #AFC #LUFC #LFC #SWFC #SAFC #NUFC #THFC #RangersFC #CelticFC #EFC https://t.co/65S4PFI2XR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Ireland #irishhistory #IRISHRISING22 #IRISHRISING22 #rugby #hurling #Dublin #CorkCity #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/6qSh2N3cmo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jackiedoran10: Mattie Mc Grath needs your support, he needs to hear from you, the media are being positioned to destroy him and the onl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@woodsk @AI_Clayton This is f*cking disgusting and shows the government overreach they are intent on. We must push back. Its totally out of order #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nicktothecore74 @trevsayers @DebraClaridge If i was trying to roll out a jab with questionable safety data, maybe diluting the effects with saline jabs might be a good way of diluting the negative effects?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nicktothecore74 @trevsayers @DebraClaridge Very sorry about this  It does make you wonder about people having terrible reactions and other people being ok from the jab when you see reports about people being injected with saline in error.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeterStefanovi2 @BBCNews @BBCBreakfast Well done Peter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Independent A) why photoshop what type of beer hrs drinking? B) Who gives a f*ck about what beer hes drinking anyway? #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JJ56123 C*nt /politician @BorisJohnson]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joeycicer0 Look at the cross section of society on this and other marches @nadhimzahawi @BorisJohnson @MattHancock We DO NOT WANT THIS YOU TRAITOROUS B*STARDS #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am a nice man. A mild mannered man. I would get banned for saying what i would do to these 'rulers' of ours given the chance #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philosopherssto @eddiebouncer196 This is what we need to start doing  #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Henriet63798768 @animatorforlife @UnityNewsNet You're missing the point. A real pandemic is pretty obvious. It certainly doesn't need a marketing campaign]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @Independent Nah thanks, im still not getting tested #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AI_Clayton Not only that. A new media is a must. One that is accountable to the people. One that is constantly challenged. An independent regulatory body to be set up where the public can challenge the narrative and a full response to each is mandatory]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ericdun19416783 Im more annoyed about the insult to my intelligence. We aren't buying this sh*te any more #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere COME ON #IRELAND ! #DUBLIN #CORK #EIRE #HURLING #IrishCup #irishhistory #Irish https://t.co/CPIdonCbtX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @Telegraph Unbelievable that a fit healthy young person would even consider taking it. Absolute madness. No upsides but the risk of side effects. Absolute no brainer #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnBoweActor: I have received an email from this family. It is unconscionable that the hospital is refusing to abide by the court orde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These are coming if you let them. YOU can stop them!!! #MUFC #MCFC #LFC #LUFC #THFC #AFC #AVFC #WHUFC #SAFC #NUFC #CelticFC #RangersFC #EFC https://t.co/mPQuEG0C6l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rtetwip @mattiemcgrathtd Well done mattie. A man of integrity ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SamWhiteTky: Tested to get in and tracked after. And people are celebrating that. I don't know what it is, but it's not liberty.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Vespa2Vespa @LozzaFox @Keir_Starmer I pay that little attention to the rules i didnt realise what the issue was here #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThisIsMadness5: I'm not forcing or even asking anyone not to have the vaccine. I genuinely don't care what others do with themselves. S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember folks. Things are soooo bad in India the police have time for this.... Oh and the IPL cricket still going on as normal #MCFC #MUFC #EFC #LFC #LUFC #SAFC #NUFC #WHUFC #CFC #THFC #WWFC #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/OCiSlzARnd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI @oddschecker Could do a lot worse. I had high hopes for @Keir_Starmer but hes been woeful. Has offered absolutely nothing. Just do SOMETHING, anything!!! Starting with voting down #VaccinePassports #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottyVsTyranny @SaffaCrypto @ToolstationUK @ToolstationUK this is outrageous!!! I hope action is being taken against this lunatic #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cjsnowdon This seriously needs stopping now. Enough is enough #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MUFC #MCFC #AFC #AVFC #CFC #WWFC #WHUFC #LUFC #SAFC #LFC #EFC #THFC #RangersFC #CelticFC #NUFC #CPFC #NCFC https://t.co/eTSWAjbOSW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#johnbarrowman #MayDay #SaturdayVibes #SaturdayMotivation #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.co/z3LMQKqfcy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere #NoVaccinePassports #takeoffthemask https://t.co/I7ZkLP9Tgn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hats off to #RoyalChallengersBangalore for managing carry on despite #india and its health system collapsing under the strain of #COVID19. Cricket going on as normal doesnt really align with whats being shown on MSM https://t.co/NYjWGJxitX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheSun No one is buying this indian scaremongering surely? They are blatantly taking the p*ss out of you. Its carnage on the streets but these are dancing on video? Oh and the IPL is still going on. People dying in the streets but they still playing cricket ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SorchaGarduce @BreesAnna @AlisonHammond Its not. If the vaccine works it protects you. You take it and good luck to you. If i choose not to take it and die, thats my choice and have no one to blame but myself. The same is true if you take and have sude effects. Bodily autonomy is a basic human right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@battleaxeBrit1 I loathe this b*stard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemcook69 @AgreeT0D1sagree I just mean its probably not worth an assassination if there's a bigger network and will draw attention to his cause]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jemcook69 @AgreeT0D1sagree The good thing is it's not just him. Its a network of 80-100 lawyers worldwide. Spreading the risk.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>