<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[As we all know too well, namecalling, cruel #taunts, #cyberbullying, and physical #bullying happen every day to #kids. What to do when your #child is being bullied? https://t.co/hjNpakvJvj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[By the age of 13, 80% of girls distort the way they look #online.  While the dangers of social media have been widely documented, concerns over the harm of retouching apps and filters are only just starting to show.  #socialmedia #screens https://t.co/rzihuHd0sU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The story youve heard about the creation of the famous board game #Monopoly is far from true. #games #boardgames https://t.co/j5PPMVFHu5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Insights Family issued the #Kids  #Family Industry Report 2021. #toys #games https://t.co/4lcvwGWcqg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The opposite for #courage is not cowardice, it is #conformity. Even a dead fish can go with the flow. Jim Hightower https://t.co/TrAfvBVl1R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Although video #games are currently top of any childs wish list, construction sets are set to overtake video games in both popularity and revenue generation.  #toys #toyindustry https://t.co/9PZ7D2gtZ6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is common between driverless cars, humanoid #robots and a primitive computer? All of these things were invented by Leonardo da #Vinci.  https://t.co/XdE0tzJWIU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here is the list of upcoming hot #toys in 2021. #games https://t.co/P1mX6lWVI4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is #creativity? https://t.co/iZP7IcHXal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The rise of #jigsaw puzzle sales during the COVID-19 #pandemic is, well, puzzling. Social media is filled with images of completed, half-completed or sometimes abandoned #puzzles. What causes this trend? #toys https://t.co/IJ2skh6L04]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The popularity of blind bag collectible #toys is rapidly growing among #children. How does #psychology explain this?  https://t.co/NvgIyKnRFL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UC Santa Cruz #School of #Engineering professor Katherine Isbister does #research on #fidgeting and fidget #toys  https://t.co/DUbYrzEfzW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to boost your #creativity? https://t.co/J4ZHgBEdfj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Modern information technologies changed many fields. #Photography is one of them. No longer do photographs primarily function as works of #art or memorial objects. #technology  https://t.co/ZLLHFwaj14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today, a lot of people praise the advantages of #technology but how many of us think of psychological challenges (such as #fear of missing out) and organizational problems (ex. complexity) associated with #tech wonders?  https://t.co/3gFNUztOdf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Education is not the #learning of facts, but the training of the mind to think. Albert #Einstein https://t.co/3y9Aj2bHPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A study from researchers at the Technical #University of Denmark suggests the collective global attention span is narrowing due to the amount of information that is presented to the public. #research #technology #socialmedia  https://t.co/HOZ9XBAjzu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Steve Pasierb, president and CEO of the US Toy Association explores the wealth of trends and tones that have been set the #pandemic and their likely impact on the toy space for years to come. #toys #games  https://t.co/WjWeVHBVRz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Almost all #creativity involves purposeful #play" Abraham #Maslow #playmatters https://t.co/mfCuOlrE5m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Toy industry expert, Richard Gottlieb, thinks that the passion for #games and #puzzles, fanned by the #pandemic, may well be with us for a long time to come. #toyindustry https://t.co/xlJQjSkjYk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Inventables guys, Zach Kaplan and Keith Schacht, demo some amazing new materials and how we might use them. Look for squishy magnets, odor-detecting ink, "dry" liquid and a very surprising 10-foot pole. #innovation #creativity https://t.co/u00wFg1tSw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roger #Bacon was a medieval English philosopher, and one of the fathers of modern scientific method based on gathering and analyzing data from experiments.  https://t.co/DNWMO7kddD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The most beautiful experience we can have is the mysterious. It is the fundamental emotion which stands at the cradle of true #art and true #science." Albert Einstein https://t.co/fCsUigOFgZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The origins of balls and #ballgames can be traced back to over 3,000 years when the Olmec who were known as the rubber people created #Mesoamericas first civilization and left a rich cultural heritage to later groups, from the #Maya to the #Aztec.  #games https://t.co/Vwu7eSu3me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heard the one about the academic who spent years trying to find out how #jokes work? According to Graeme Ritchie, of Edinburgh University, his efforts to pin down the mysteries of #humour will take years. https://t.co/fj2E2UHSKn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy #Passover  Happy #Easter to All! https://t.co/aGRilOeW7Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Business Insider consulted with experts at the Toy Insider, who identified 22 of the best-selling #toys of all time. The information is broken down by year and number of units sold. #games #play https://t.co/xHBLPeagqJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Developmental psychologists have long been interested in how #parents affect child development. However, finding actual cause-and-effect links between specific actions of parents and later behavior of #children is very difficult. #parenting https://t.co/u7znpRuIhO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Reading is more than just a fun pastime. It is an important element in intellectual, psychological and emotional development. https://t.co/gjxhEIXjit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Play-based #learning helps #children develop social skills, language and numeracy skills. Taking initiative, focused attention, and curiosity about the world are a part of #play. Children are naturally wired to do the very thing that will help them learn and grow. #playmatters https://t.co/EeSXdRqQIj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Before there were Transformer action figures, digital cameras, or #Playstations, there were #Tinkertoys. #games https://t.co/r5sP9PSKy5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Toys and #games can tell a lot about us - human beings. This article explores what scientists can learn about our forefathers by studying #prehistoric toys.  #research #science https://t.co/Wp9XorJKr9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new review from the Heart of England Foundation NHS Trust reports that #kids are coming into classrooms ill-prepared for #writing and other activities that require finger muscle strength due to excessive #gadget use. https://t.co/pMOhConMd5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An influx of virtual meetings might not be the only factor causing Zoom fatigue in potentially millions of people during the #pandemic. #Technology like Zoom places physical restraints on users and requires more cognitive labour. #zoomfatigue  https://t.co/0sFR0d1c4p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The ills of excessive #screen time have been well-documented, but a recent study just identified another possible risk. #Children who have more screen time are more likely to develop binge eating disorder (BED). #socialmedia #health https://t.co/oTTXaLjdX2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During the #pandemic, we mostly focus on the challenges of online #education for #children. But #adults face similar difficulties. This post by Ta Silvestre Godfrey describes numerous problems that adults encounter when taking online courses.  https://t.co/XlBrUQukzz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #pandemic posed new and reinforced existing challenges in #education. One major challenge has been how to assess #students fairly when #learning is done remotely.  https://t.co/kvqfRaOvd6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Failure is our best teacher but fear of failure is our worst enemy." Debasish Mridha #failureispartofsuccess https://t.co/K7HWuY3ltc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Toys R Us has a new owner  again. The brand management company WHP Global acquired a controlling interest in Tru #Kids, the parent company of the Toys R Us, Babies R Us and Geoffrey the Giraffe brands. #toysrus #games #toyindustry  https://t.co/lcyEOuuREk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As streaming and digital #gaming become more popular amidst the #pandemic, new concerns are rising about kids' #privacy and susceptibility to tactics designed to keep them hooked on screens. #children #screentime https://t.co/3FnXmjwgNu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brian Goldner, #Hasbros CEO, believes heightened interest in board #games may continue even when the #pandemic is over and families will no longer be confined to their homes.  #toyindustry https://t.co/rDomdSHI75]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While the future remains uncertain amid the continuing #coronavirus #pandemic, there have been ongoing discussions on what the future of #education for elementary and high #school #students could look like. https://t.co/C0cYVVcLam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting! #TikTok is driving massive #toy sales as #play dates become less frequent during the #pandemic https://t.co/NvhXX5fN03]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Toys Can Help Build Emotional #Health in #Children During the #Pandemic, Experts Say #games #playmatters https://t.co/qNQSNCj48q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We focus on retrieving #information, rather than on understanding. The results are less depth of #knowledge and the lack of ability to make connections between disparate bits of information, which is the basis of #creativity. #technology https://t.co/0zR44lGQ4U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When #children #play in an adventurous way, climbing trees, riding their bikes fast downhill, jumping from rocks, they experience feelings of fear and excitement, thrill and adrenaline. #playmatters https://t.co/PbxNwZzUKe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Several pre-pandemic studies have shown a correlation between the use of social media and lack of social skills in #children. The #pandemic is making the situation even worse. #internet #socialmedia  https://t.co/3xzs5o11pf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Women's Day to all the incredible #women! Shine on.... Not just today but everyday! https://t.co/4v5jslpjqU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A recent Census #survey said 16 million Americans have canceled plans to go to #college. The biggest reasons given were fears over contracting #COVID-19 and not being able to afford college given the economic disruption caused by the #pandemic.  #Students  https://t.co/XWwv15HEmU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Math can be one of the most frustrating subjects to teach! However, math is used everywhere in our lives. These #TED talks will inspire #children to enjoy math a little bit more, or at least make it tolerable. #Stem  https://t.co/JXzIOIRCob]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["What Is #Math?" - a teenager named Gracie Cunningham asked that age-old question on #TikTok, creating a viral backlash, and then, a thoughtful scientific debate.  https://t.co/WoY9D8NiZK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blocks have many benefits for #kids who #play with them, read about the top 10 benefits here! #playmatters #toys #games https://t.co/PW7ScnfxnG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Empathy  the awareness of and ability to share the feelings of others  is a very abstract, yet important task to teach to young #children. Here 5 tips that to raise a caring #child. #parenting https://t.co/tKFnpoBunp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Can #Play #Therapy Help #Children Heal and Thrive? #playmatters https://t.co/tMvHxrXVIO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why #play matters for #children's #health and development? #playmatters https://t.co/opRbTn6Mgi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is #play important? In this #podcast, Rachel Robertson, Bright Horizons #education and development vice president, and new mom Amanda, tackle this increasingly popular question.  #children #playmatters https://t.co/KwBDrcmabJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 ways #reading improves your #mind and body https://t.co/CwncA8TIpn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Radio journalist Emily Hanford has created a series of documentaries that explain why so many #children cant read. One of the key observations she made is that good #reading skills require good #vocabulary to foster comprehension  https://t.co/VWyoY1nHyR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You may be hearing over and over that #learning through #play is the best way to teach your young child. Read on for 5 ways to incorporate learning through play in your home in the early years. #children #yearlyyears #playmatters https://t.co/B61f3Ykjyp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What are the causes of #creativity? https://t.co/hOW8XTO1Rd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When life throws you a rainy day, #play in the puddles https://t.co/kFjaneHJ28]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For #children under the age of five, #Covid restrictions have been in place for a big chunk of their lives. For the very youngest, daily life has never been Covid-free. What should #parents and carers of young children be concerned about?  https://t.co/TH4IueKGQM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The theory of multiple intelligences was proposed by American Psychologist Howard Gardner in 1983. It describes nine types of intelligence: https://t.co/VW8snIxeH8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want Smarter #Kids? Teach #Music, Not #Coding, According to #MIT. The latest #neuroscience shows that learning a musical instrument increases brain power https://t.co/2EfIq1fWv0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How a sneaky rise in #oil prices could affect #toy prices #toyindustry https://t.co/LgFvBY65FU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THE TOY INSIDERS TOP #TOYS  TRENDS TO WATCH IN 2021 #games https://t.co/KgwUZZZRhL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the #collectables market can survive the pandemic #toys https://t.co/IyD1OcyOzk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#UNICEF published 5 ways you can help keep your #children safe #online while stuck at home during the #COVID-19 outbreak #pandemic https://t.co/YHNOfTmALC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a study that followed #children in grades two through five, Virginia Berninger, a psychologist at the University of Washington, demonstrated that printing, cursive #writing, and typing on a keyboard are all associated with distinct #brain patterns. https://t.co/KNaQHK2ach]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 2012 study led by Karin James, a psychologist at Indiana University, shows that #handwriting is important for child development.  #Children  https://t.co/FsUdTZYCnF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We tend to see art in terms of its results such as pictures or sculptures. For #children, however, #art is something they doit is a process. #creativity https://t.co/YyBUkhoAlw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new study into the effects of #play has uncovered that playing board #games can have a significant beneficial effect for those with Alzheimers. #playmatters https://t.co/9pXuaxQlmv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Research demonstrates intrinsic motivation and #creativity are closely linked.  https://t.co/O8afe5sx60).-,Intrinsic%20Motivation%20and%20Creativity%2FInnovation%20Performance,the%20creative%20and%20innovative%20outcome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A year into the #coronavirus #pandemic, more than 800 million #students continue to experience major disruptions in their #schooling, according to a new report from the United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (#UNESCO). https://t.co/9rYI2YQqlP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Closure of independent #toy stores means more than just loss of jobs. It also means fewer opportunities for #innovation. #toyindustry  https://t.co/0BkNEDD4HT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 national US poll found the major concerns of #parents during the #pandemic. The top three concerns were on how much time #children were spending on #screens and social media, and on #online safety. https://t.co/VSFuArbXCn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hedge #mazes have been a fixture of imposing estates for centuries. Below, a selection of the most interesting and eye-catching from around the world. https://t.co/rlHUjicH7A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Despite the challenges cause by COVID-19 #pandemic, U.S. toy industry sales grew by 16% according to The NPD Group. The latest NPD data reflects $25.1 billion in sales last year, an increase of $3.5 billion over 2019. #toys #games  https://t.co/OzskSlVL5a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Albert #Einstein once said, #Information is not knowledge. Interestingly, the rest of that original quote ends with, The only source of #knowledge is experience.  Here is a comparison chart of information and knowledge: https://t.co/WF89W2G59J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many scientists conclude that content knowledge is crucial to effective critical #thinking. And they say that the best approach is to explicitly teach very specific small skills of analysis for each subject.  #education #science https://t.co/yfAxb8qOVq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While the light bulb inventor, Thomas #Edison, considered this #innovation his crowning triumph, it was just one of many inventions that he made. Edison was a record-holder for sheer number of U.S. patents  1,093  until the 21st century.  #creativity  https://t.co/BR4GkHVL4a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Children will face "a period of epic withdrawal" from their tech #screens once life starts to return to normal from the #pandemic, an addiction specialist tells The New York Times.  https://t.co/w30eYKZws6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 1983 an American developmental psychologist Howard Gardener described 9 types of #intelligence. What other scientists thought were just soft-skills, such as interpersonal skills, Gardener realized were types of intelligence.  https://t.co/OKhtyAtb8r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the #pandemic continues, may #children develop anxieties and other behavioral disorders. One of the best ways to help anxious children is play #therapy because #play is natural and essential for #kids. #playmatters https://t.co/vm9JmdnA3P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The lockdown success of the #games and #puzzles market, a surge in the #kidult market fuelled by the restrictions and implications of the #Covid-19 #pandemic, has helped the UK #toy market hit a five per cent sales increase for its overall value. https://t.co/w0w0yrM0CA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this episode of the Power Kid Podcast, host Phil Albritton of Power Kid Design welcomes legendary #toy designer Eddy Goldfarb and his daughter Lyn to the show. #games #toyindustry  https://t.co/AKSnqKPa1P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Early #Learning Centre has partnered with experts from across the educational sector to launch a new hub of content aimed at helping families throughout the #lockdown period. #children #play https://t.co/s2RLPNblPO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During the #pandemic, many #children experience #anxiety, worries and fears. It is important that #parents recognize such troubles early enough to support their #kids. This poster provides a list of common children's fears by age. #parenting #yearlyyears https://t.co/fyBTZk1Mhl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A great way for you to support the #health, #happiness and development of your socially isolated #children during the #pandemic is to find ways they can #play at home. Playing can also protect your children from some of the negative impacts this crisis could have. #playmatters https://t.co/bYljqvAA0Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Mindfulness and detoxing from the #stress of life will remain a strong consumer theme in the #toy industry as we head into 2021, according to the UKs own Gibsons #Games who witnessed a 33% increase in #puzzles sales across the last year. #toys #games https://t.co/EdFP5JW30b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting summary of how #COVID-19 is affecting the #toy industry #toys #games #pandemic https://t.co/wIX7A2RPAM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Researchers found that #antibiotics, household disinfectants and other sanitizing products are killing the good bacteria that help us fend off disease. The shortage of certain microbes may explain recent spikes in #childhood allergies and asthma. #health https://t.co/hFlzy0YGa1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Benefits of block #play  #playmatters #Children  https://t.co/PW7ScnfxnG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wishing all of you #peace, #love, and #joy this #holiday season and throughout 2021! https://t.co/ELTPlagL6I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the social isolation continues, #children are living through a very new experience which is confusing and frightening. At times of crisis, children's #play may appear noisy and destructive. Here are several advices on how #parents can manage noisy play. #playmatters #parenting https://t.co/3gbogAsX2h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the social isolation continues, #parents complain about the inefficiencies of distant #education. But, as Erika Christakis, an early-childhood educator explains, these issues simply reveal the problems that existed in #schools before the #pandemic: https://t.co/vtXKjUmEN7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Challenge your child with these engaging activities that help them learn, grow, and thrive #parentingtips #children  https://t.co/RKaUxNswAW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is important that we support our #kids during the #pandemic. Saying something positive to your child is a good way to show that you care. #parenting https://t.co/6Lcao6i9Qn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Searches for #dolls prams have risen by 23 per cent over the course of the last six months, coinciding with the national school closures and #lockdown measures put into place over the past year.  #children #pandemic #playmatters #toys https://t.co/lBIxmX2dzx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Research from Australia demonstrated that children typically do not use e-readers to read. They prefer physical books.  #parenting #gadgets #techology https://t.co/tjZEMcOyMZ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>