<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@SharpieDj @EssexPR They now have  a distinct choice.. publically call supporters to join the ongoing fight an put 2milliin on the streets of London on the 29th or watch your business fail as autumn lockdowns kick in... YOUR TIME TO CHOOSE IS NOW!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SharpieDj @EssexPR I have some sympathy, except I have pointed out for months that this is a coordinated plan and hospitality will be collateral damage.. rather than join protests they tried on their own.. https://t.co/oK8gJKWVLi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: MHRA has been funded by Gates]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5FVFesuGLq  Ofcom investigating..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Elanders_Voice: If you have never fought for anything else in your life, then let it be this   A domestic vaccine passport is not your]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rainbowandsteel: @EssexPR It IS criminal. #wewillnotforget We support you @EssexPR and your industry. It's clear you have been played.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HowardSteen4: Good news from the German Constitutional Court in Karlsruhe. It has upheld the controversial Weimar ruling about masks an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jshshsh21702158 @Sacha_Lord Shock horror...  Get your people out on the fu^^ng streets now and join those who have fought this for a year... you have no choice now.. they'll be coming for the kids next!!!!!!! https://t.co/SntJPTjDG8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UKHospKate Shock horror...  Get your people out on the fu^^ng streets now and join those who have fought this for a year... you have no choice now.. they'll be coming for the kids next!!!!!!! https://t.co/SntJPTjDG8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hughosmond Shock horror...  Get your people out on the fu^^ng streets now and join those who have fought this for a year... you have no choice now.. they'll be coming for the kids next!!!!!!! https://t.co/SntJPTjDG8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Shock horror...  Get your people out on the fu^^ng streets now and join those who have fought this for a year... you have no choice now.. they'll be coming for the kids next!!!!!!! https://t.co/SntJPTjDG8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RailwayMobb https://t.co/7shOk85XEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_brewersarms  @EssexPR  @mitrebarnet https://t.co/aLSSO7PYuR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Nope.. its a plan...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@the_brewersarms https://t.co/vxYiv3IYQR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mitrebarnet  @EssexPR https://t.co/vxYiv3IYQR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1BJDJ @EssexPR They just don't want to believe its deliberate.. I'm getting close to giving up  with them.  If they don't wake up soon its over for them and they'll move onto the kids..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @1BJDJ: @EssexPR Many of us did warn that this would be the case.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UKHospKate https://t.co/OQ6hRl24hq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mitrebarnet @EssexPR @AspinallFifi https://t.co/hSsCMrdIo3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord You've been played.  Come on here and admit it and tell all your followers to join mass protests... https://t.co/P2g9oztieL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef SCUM!!!! https://t.co/9ZFS9v16vq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Francis_Hoar https://t.co/PR0VINPnF6  And PCR TESTS!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @theblogmire: Oh look. Govt has awarded contract for the "Provision of Media Buying Services for COVID 19 Campaigns".  Oh look. It's set]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: I was attacked as bonkers for the sin of reporting, before news outlets did, on menstrual  disorders, severe bleeding and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: @Bazilnova10 no we're talking about an evil/devil minded crew of globalist rich men who want to muzzle our kids and inject th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DPJHodges Hold you to this when  June comes!! https://t.co/7YfQMSJMxH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @org_scp: We're going to win this. There is no Plan B.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shellsXxX: @org_scp This is the attitude we all need!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LibertarianEcoS @Jannermaid1 Me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MoriartyProfJ3 @Kateandtheboys @TruthSeekerTKS https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool protest live feed ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@opinionatedmum1 @NewMumOnline @AlisonHammond @thismorning https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool protest live feed...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beverleyturner https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool protest today.. live feed..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justdazzling2 https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool protest live..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mitrebarnet https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool live feed of today's protest..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@covid1984sweden @FatEmperor https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool joins you in solidarity..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: Liverpool #LockdownProtest Live Feed:  https://t.co/Ud8Twam29w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@G_P_L_M https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Live feed Liverpool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FatEmperor https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Liverpool protest live feed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Misskb721 https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Live link]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stephWally2 @1BJDJ https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Live link..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1BJDJ https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Live link]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ful1jzMLVW  Livestream Liverpool]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HowardSteen4: French lawyers now active vs Covid measures - Criminal complaints prepared on 3 levels: - novel complaint from patients p]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanHarper58: As Ian suggested...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UKHospKate https://t.co/PR0VINPnF6  They've shut Liverpool down on a lie.. Swedish government trashed PCR TESTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@devisridhar https://t.co/cjly717rCy  International social credit scores more like it....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CGreenUK @EmilySiddall https://t.co/hZsmsagFsZ  As a treat you can have a copy early....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Watch They Live from the 1980's.. we had to order the DVD..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKcitizen2021: Over the course of this weekend, we are building up some seriously powerful collaborative relationships.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UKcitizen2021 You guys are amazing..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hughosmond https://t.co/cjly717rCy  Because they are part of the implementation of a bio security state with Chinese style social credit scores at the heart.. If the big platforms don't acknowledge this and get the messages out it will happen..  They are toying with you on the legal case!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bee42681881 @MsRightMsRight https://t.co/cjly717rCy  A bio security state with Chinese style social credit scores at the heart more like it..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nadhimzahawi   Coming your way!!! https://t.co/CGvV7dRWwS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrclaims I understand that completely. My 17 year old who I'm now in awe of as to how spirituality awake she is, told me to enjoy the moments away from twitter with more focus than pre March 20 and recognise how precious those moments are....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@talkRADIO Wouldn't go anywhere I have to attend a designated test centre to get a negative test to authorised my e ticket and face a PCR TEST after. I'd roll up to a club at 12.30 after a 4 hour bar crawl willingly!!! #nonewnormal https://t.co/gleUVQoJ2l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@naomirwolf Covid 21 vaxx appears on the EU vaxx passport . .. is Civid 21the one Bill Gates said we should be scared of? https://t.co/OLTETRi4es]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@noreward_norisk @Bluebell2201 Testing if the process and technology work.. e ticket only enabled with negative test from a designated centre.. The future!! Unless we stop it.. https://t.co/VBkO9iWOaM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkSharon_DP @noreward_norisk @standup118 Testing the process and the technology.. e ticket only activated if negative test at a designated centre.. this is the future... https://t.co/uIZr4g7UXC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrclaims None of the above as its not going to happen..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NoNewNormalEver: Testing at a government test centre just to go to an event and then testing again afterwards.  Positive test, no fun f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@1884DT @EssexPR I doubt it, unless we make it the end.. https://t.co/leraXZGhZO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Rhonda52807071 If anyone any good at enhancing pictures you might find the answer.. https://t.co/zxUq64IhnP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DancerDad Maybe, but this doesn't sound good.. https://t.co/Kpc4hUHEwV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI https://t.co/vm1zCdCsJM  Big Brother watch and the left waking up  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI https://t.co/PR0VINPnF6  They've shut Liverpool down on a lie.. Swedish government trashed PCR TESTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI https://t.co/cjly717rCy  The future ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsForAlI https://t.co/VlbYAuMdGx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DancerDad Couldn't fake the testing.. designated centres and e ticket linked to negative result.. ticket disabled if positiveor didn't attend for testing.. they are testing the technology.. https://t.co/i7HV3qJSTq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @flossyflange: Now look at the Liverpool nightclub pilot where they had to produce a negative covid test to gain entry... its a prelude]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFreds Except for the negative test result linked to the ticket testing out the technology and PCR TESTS after.. https://t.co/nnGa7VrtOm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EssexPR Plenty of opportunity to join us!!! https://t.co/q0EXPty05u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wordwhisperer Negative test..linked to ticket which shows they are testing the technology..and a PCR TEST afterwards.. https://t.co/oxUWOjdFEo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mixmag @yousefcircus https://t.co/cjly717rCy  Wake up.. or this is  the future ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mixmag @yousefcircus https://t.co/PR0VINPnF6  They've shut Liverpool down on a lie.. Swedish government trashed PCR TESTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mixmag @yousefcircus https://t.co/vm1zCdCsJM  Big Brother watch and the left waking up  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mixmag @yousefcircus https://t.co/2JBcr1tWz1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jordan120 https://t.co/9YjhtbuSR1  Your test is linked to the ticket..so a passport by any other name.. https://t.co/5PUgh6zAxX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jordan120 @SharpieDj 2 negative tests and PCR test after..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YJls5UspQV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NszfhT677E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/64XgNRia8t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scousescene https://t.co/bHr5JkClDA  Now you know the truth protest tomorrow ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scousescene https://t.co/vm1zCdCsJM  Even Big Brother watch and the left are waking up to the lies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scousescene https://t.co/PR0VINPnF6  They've shut Liverpool down on a lie.. Swedish government trashed PCR TESTS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scousescene https://t.co/cjly717rCy  The future ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scousescene https://t.co/cLdWnD4RJL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/0RTj0suZ4o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/dPXpq0jPaN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/CYtQhDWon5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/zHEB0pN5o3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/miM1rpVCBb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/j3KAzvkpc0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Liverpool https://t.co/faqwPBgtRd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @org_scp: 'Passes for pints' are back on the table.   For the 'forseeable future', you may be required to take a rapid test to access ce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pcrclaims No just the truth..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Anshul__K: @Sacha_Lord Needing a negative test is another name for a covid status certificate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord https://t.co/OnYxzMVScl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord https://t.co/cjly717rCy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord https://t.co/PR0VINPnF6]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>