<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrDrewseph Wooo!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItsLLBee @adamgreattweet ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ButtPosting Lol! The gift that keeps on giving]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jmugele Your art room is honestly one of the prettiest things Ive ever seen in my life]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ginadivittorio The peoples queen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lissielys  thank you that means so much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roxiqt Thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GoreHunter121 Thank you so much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@moniquemadrid Thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Been taking a bit of a break from social media, but alls good! Thank you for all the dms and texts. Ive been painting, reading, bettering the world around me as best I can. Heres a closeup of Miss Attie, my latest commission  https://t.co/0agZNScBrG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@okiecorri Thats so close!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SirEviscerate  thank you so much, Ray. You are a wonderful friend who deserves wonderful things ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UptownRocketTom Aaahhh!!! Yay!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@katewhiteshark Im so glad you like them ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@trumpetcake Thank YOU!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItsLLBee Her wings look like gold lam ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whatmaddness: Dark energy pushes the universe to expand faster and faster. Unspooling from a seemingly endless roll of both nothingness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whatmaddness: Violently wiggling and shaking my body hard enough so that my muscles and ligaments scrub at my skeleton like a car wash.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Composition and basic values blocked in on this piece. Its still early in the process for this painting, but Im really excited about this one. Its about the anxiety of being perceived as worthy and is part of an exhibition Im creating called Alive But Changed  https://t.co/gWSMKnrCs3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Browtweaten  adam you sweetie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianGurien hey Brian! Im not making prints of that piece,  but I will put it on my list to make more capybara art ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Tofireguy @trumpetcake For international shipments, I just stick stamps on my flat pack mailers so that i can keep shipping free. Its usually about $5-$6. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItsBeardoWeirdo @trumpetcake That smile ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItsBeardoWeirdo @trumpetcake That is so generous of you! My Venmo is https://t.co/mby83fmhN9 and PayPal is https://t.co/H66JpDjvew. Your babe is so beautiful. Mine turns 16 this year ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tschnor Hell yeah!! Let me know how they like it! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lissielys ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bornmiserable I need to buy you a trophy for being my #1 hype man]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wyrm__wraith Aaah!!! Thank you! Im really excited about how its shaping up ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@katewhiteshark Kate you sweet angel. Its only about 20% done, but I can dm you when its finished if youre serious!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Progress report https://t.co/jbvaQZQFAp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whatmaddness: In a dense nebula, two stars are formed. They twinkle shyly as they move toward one another, united by the bond of mutual]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roughed out the sketch for my next big canvas. Ive had this idea in my head for awhile now and Im so excited to bring it to life  https://t.co/Xp9R5wjBUb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @batkaren: "Would you rather eat a pound of bricks or a matter baby?" he asks.  "What's a matter baby?" I ask.  I'm shown a newborn so d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bornmiserable: lose an hour?  havent we lost enough already]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tLhOff17F4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Final  https://t.co/EgRoKcZdhj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its a snowy wonderland in Denver today so this seemed like a perfect subject https://t.co/AljUJ2YqC4 https://t.co/pJ886seljx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eff_yeah_steph Good luck good luck good luck!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garfpooop: You should be allowed to play defense at bowling]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Holy_Mowgli Aaahh!! Thank you, that means so much to hear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@flashember Jon, that is all so kind of you to say! Thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CourtOfTheWoods: i got one ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CourtOfTheWoods Court, you ANGEL, thank you! My studio assistant thanks you too https://t.co/ffsK64jQsW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I listed the individual studies here:  https://t.co/tQb4ls0PdA  :D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jun34u_sec: Don't forget to set your clock on fire this Sunday.  Time isn't real!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jmugele (No beard looks good too, but you really rock a beard)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jmugele Beard 100%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@willsmith I ended up making a slurry and shooting it like a water gun into her mouth. No one is happy here tonight. Hopefully she gets with the program in the next few days ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me: *dutifully hiding pills in yogurt, some pumpkin, rice, a banana, some salmon, some butter* Penny: *tying a napkin around her neck as she spits out the pill and looks at me eagerly for her next course*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the dexterity with which my dog eats the food ~around~ her pills is incredible. shes had a full 10-course tasting menu tonight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @domdyer70: Fox sleeping on sky light https://t.co/1uueXfPHhW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abbycohenwl: Cow it started             Cow its going https://t.co/8UyGxiw9b8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everybody say good luck penny (shes been a very sick baby for the last 24 hrs) https://t.co/AKfQgicVOq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nick_kaufman  Im so glad you like it!  The original sold, but I post new work on my website (almost) daily   https://t.co/ppg1o0F9ov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@upsidedowntrash That is the witchiest wall Ive ever seen it looks awesome ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ItsLLBee Awww yay!! Im so glad it arrived ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@npalumbo58 Nick!!! Hell yeah!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The gang and I are signing prints today. They turned out so great  https://t.co/tziEDnz7om]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@frankandrus Yeah, its supposed to be the in top 25 historical storms! Well see. Im excited]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@munificentbob So true!!! I was out in the world for 5 hours today and Im absolutely fried ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont get out much so these are my I drive and I go to the grocery store tweets.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Experienced a moment of unbridled joy as a man in a pickup truck, driving aggressively to pass EVERYONE, got trapped behind and between a bunch of people who all joined forces to make him slow the f dowb. Chefs kiss. Love to see it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just went into an absolute fugue state while grocery shopping to prepare for the big snow storm this weekend and Im excited to eat *checks bags* cheese and cereal for 5 days straight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excuse me look at these little sun rays https://t.co/4Pgtkbc4Yp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jpd256  thank you James!! Im so glad you like]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elle91 Theyre so goofy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SirEviscerate He looks like Jeff Daniels in the powder blue suit in Dumb and Dumber]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The final muppet https://t.co/DjFVEYFO88]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ok these birds dont make sense. Are they menacing? Are they happy? I did my best. https://t.co/qcV1cwQPvZ https://t.co/zzIskmgIUF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brianamrenda @sadgrrrrlsclub @Shenaniglenns Ahh!! Thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catttlin_: Feeling bad for your abuser is the weirdest part of trauma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fauxpaslogy Omg hi coco ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mccanncreates Thank you!! Im really proud of it  one of the few conception to production ideas that went off relatively smoothly.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fresh prints baby https://t.co/DlhFhlfPJj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sophenwrites @okiecorri Thank you so much ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jmugele Thank you!! It was a fun project]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MJohnsonFTW ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrMikeSpade Thank you! That was actually why I painted it! Im glad it translates, you absolutely made my day!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I painted 11 paintings of a match igniting and then slowly burning.  https://t.co/WE5qvXseaW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TweetsofOld: Women are usurping men's rights in Colorado. They have organized themselves into gangs and are stealing horses.   Missouri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @warmyellowlight: *holds microphone up to goose* and what do you have to say, my good sir?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamOehlert  that framing looks awesome!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SamOehlert: Managed to snag an original from one of my favorite artists! @whatmaddness thanks for the good luck hawk. https://t.co/sSf4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrincesaBallena  thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FeelingEuphoric @GrowlyGrego ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FeelingEuphoric: @GrowlyGrego @whatmaddness WE LOVE TO SEE IT https://t.co/WHrcNMJ7Kn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whatmaddness: dutifully populating my stomach with healthy probiotics and then absolutely annihilating them with all of my other choices]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ddub1314 Hey Dylan! It is for sale. Its on a 24 hour hold for my fanhouse peeps (they get first dibs as a perk for subscribing.) if youre interested, you can snag the code on my FH for $5 (https://t.co/OyCxcBHmjI) or wait until tmrw pm when its live for everyone! https://t.co/DlhFhlfPJj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DankAndDonuts For alla primas (the paintings I do in one sitting) Ill work on them anywhere from 1-4 hours! Anything over that and it starts getting muddy and overworked. This dude was a bit over 2 hours]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And yeah, Van Gogh really painted a skeleton smokin! 1885. An absolute visionary https://t.co/uJoOKyHTNd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rosesscythes Lol aww well thanks Im glad youre here and enjoying it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Final  https://t.co/zyCCqkvCHl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@upsidedowntrash We can be joint smoking skulls NOW, Will.  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to paint a skull smoking a joint, just like Van Gogh. https://t.co/RtglhwlfZF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would yall wanna paint and drink w me on Zoom this Friday?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PostCultRev He looks so grown up!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/ZiSXJhsLDL https://t.co/J3qhFJ6pnu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GrowlyGrego  I do not deserve you!! Im so glad you like my art. And I love the big mat on the armadillo, that looks real slick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrowlyGrego: Folks, @whatmaddness is at it again. https://t.co/1nAXWjrL0D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jpd256 https://t.co/XMdWq5kpvf]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>