<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@BillFOXLA Smart man!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @boulderpolice: #BOULDERSHOOTING Updated information, live press conference https://t.co/00999WftkY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovtsTheProblem Boulder is the most liberal city in CO. Thankful we got our protection set up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: #FranklinGraham  who are you serving? Because true believers know that no man can serve 2 masters! https://t.co/NgPDn83Vlu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BusyDrT What an apostate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BusyDrT Thats the dumbest idea Ive ever heard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jaredpolis @realist194 @GovofCO I get it!! You were using reverse psychology when you didnt want people to eat meat. Knowing people WOULD go out and eat it to support our ranchers. You dirty dog you. I totally thought you were an A hole this entire time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AbbyJohnson He looks like a Nazi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden is an illegitimate president]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@uTobian Meets Dumb and Dumber]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theblaze Spike Lee is still alive?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Let me know how I can help @SarahHuckabee!  Youre going to win and you will be great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Was there health insurance in the 1940s?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Well this makes me feel more stable even though my FIL passed away today. Im grateful for these psychos for putting my life into perspective.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MattWalshBlog: Periodic reminder that abortion has nothing to do with "reproductive rights" because reproduction has already occurred b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @classicallyabby: I didn't know that I, a woman, could be VP until yesterday. But I still don't know for sure. Until I see a 5'8" Jewish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RyanAFournier: RT if you miss the Trump Administration.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @politicalelle: Sad day for womens sports. Women must compete against biological males at the risk of injury and loss of title, thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WatchChad: Joe Biden sacrificed 60,000 American jobs with the stroke of his pen. But dudes can shower with girls now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull @PressSec Because she identifies as Strawberry Shortcake]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WoodrowForCO @laurenboebert Dang, this means you Dems think you dont have to follow the Constitution.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CurtisHouck  this chic is terrible]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Definitely has intelligent shoes to fill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanTames @MattWalshBlog Depends on the state for testing but no, you can do your own curriculum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 https://t.co/RcZgcGmfPO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Annakhait Im really starting to think you are an apostate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leadpastor @pastorlocke @RealMattCouch @BlackRobeChick @Annakhait @DustinStockton @JenLawrence21 Oh my word. What did he do???!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conservmillen The ONLY beautiful thing I can celebrate today. She was amazing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: How long will it take this tweet to get more likes than the people at Joe Biden's inauguration?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TXAG: My statement on Inauguration Day  https://t.co/Hb893NG91x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theblaze https://t.co/bwVLcYFH5l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@camorris @leadpastor @RealMattCouch Anyone who partake in illegal activity should be prosecuted. No matter which side they are on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovtsTheProblem @laurenboebert Its like in middle school where boys would be mean to the girls they liked.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laurenboebert I appreciate you so much. Im in CO but not a constituent. We need to get CO back to red values!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElijahSchaffer @Blklivesmatter When you have no words https://t.co/Jj3rXfszvh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TayAndersonCO @CNN @laurenboebert @KyleClark @CoriBush @SpeakerPelosi Who cares]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justiceforevee Im dying ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DustinStockton: My friend @leadpastor is doing things that have him catching flak from the media and the left. He's staying the course]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leadpastor Praying for protection over you and your family!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ElijahSchaffer  so glad I wasted my life watching this ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeighStewy Complete idiots]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @JoeBiden I really pray Greta doesnt get appointed to any jobs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClimateGuy101 @Transition46 So basically taking us into hell. Got it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Transition46 Thats a lot of big words for Biden.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 You mean committed?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Annakhait As long as that also means Kamala wont be either!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Praying even after Biden is in office it helps Trump  https://t.co/s81S3oDlmy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Annakhait @Annakhait when will the bomb drop on Biden and Benghazi and Seal Team 6??!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SecPompeo You will be greatly missed. Our country will go to hell fast with Biden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liars]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Annakhait Read this article... its long but a great synopsis of what we are seeing. Marxist ideology https://t.co/IC3AB2Zf6O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Millie__Weaver We heres the cancel culture on this guy ?!?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AutumnM_MI @mtgreenee @JoeBiden Sharia law absolutely does not belong in our govt. I agree!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Since everyone is talking about inciting violence, heres a relevant video. https://t.co/p71N4uyJPf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtgreenee: A radical BLM Marxist named John Sullivan was arrested yesterday for storming the Capitol on Jan. 6th.  @andersoncooper had]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Karl_Gray1210 @GeorgePapa19 Joe doesnt know what a mop is.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mercedesschlapp: .@Jack , call your crisis communications team.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: https://t.co/eWBLqNGVGd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jsolomonReports: LISTEN NOW: Bombshell revelations asTrump declassifies all FBI documents in Russia probe | Just The News https://t.co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mike_Pence Listen to this Biden convo with Ukraine https://t.co/D4DUNf5mhT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Annakhait: Why does @Jack have such a problem with Caroline Kennedy sharing photos of her brother, JFK Jr. and President Trump? They ju]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pearls? Ok grandma https://t.co/SWo4zhREPS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: BREAKING: @jsolomonReports President Trump has ordered the declassification of intelligence docs from Obamagate, includi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy https://t.co/foTx4qpBu1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII @Twitter @jack Wondering why you arent banned yet???!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch One would be preaching Jesus no matter what, the other one would be off the grid and fully prepped with his shot gun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv @LoriLightfoot The only time I support a mask is to hide her face]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VogueParis https://t.co/2rASyxJOJc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DustinStockton: Primary challenges start now for: Rep. Adam Kinzinger of IL Rep. Liz Cheney of WY Rep. John Katko of NY Rep. Fred Upton]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SecPompeo: No Administration has done more to bring lasting peace to the Middle East than that of President Trump. https://t.co/YViAE56]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HighWireTalk @PageSix He then apologized for his error in judgement. Not a hero]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtgreenee: President Trump will remain in office.   This Hail Mary attempt to remove him from the White House is an attack on every Ame]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MattWalshBlog: Democrats have just casually and automatically turned the Capitol Hill riot into a racist white supremacist event, even]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Twitter randomly shut my account down with no explanation.  They do this to thousands of conservatives every single day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @davidcordaro: PRO-LIFERS: RT this if youre still here!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksorbs Not so Die Hard after all, he retracted his actions like a sissy https://t.co/PfBvD1dTwm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepKatCammack: It took Speaker Pelosi six days to introduce articles of impeachment in the House, but it took her more than six months]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@disclosetv Why hasnt this been done before??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JulieJ2020: Me too! I listened to the whole thing never heard him incite the crowd.  Plz share the clip that demonstrates this.  Thank]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tomselliott: SUERCUT!  Media: Yes, violence is the answer https://t.co/1juSdYtKvD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ElijahSchaffer: IMPORTANT: I worked with the New York Times to help construct an official timeline of the events that lead to the Capit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If people are dumb enough to only take that as physical violence then its proof our education system and government and decades of programming as produced idiots https://t.co/T5BLMtWAGg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RepJayapal  because you know exactly where you caught it? Wheres the science on that ability? Cry me a river]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JennaEllisEsq Wonder why @JennaEllisEsq hasnt been banned yet????]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WaltsPrincesss: `I wonder if he notices me. How can I get his attention? He's so handsome`` #PelosiLovesTrump https://t.co/IKIyM6hEWA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love these super peaceful leaders. https://t.co/rWZp78bmSH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AbbyJohnson: For people who keep saying, Well, Twitter is a private company  they can do what they want. Ok. Then every private busi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TayAndersonCO @laurenboebert Thats funny. Nice try]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: I bet Jack Dorsey's beard smells like a wet muskrat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: Hatred for Trump and his supporters is what unites the Democrat Party.  Thats why they are moving forward with impeachm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#1984]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JenniferMarguli: Fascinating how just the suspicion of COVID-19 is automatically labeled COVID, but illness or death from the COVID-19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laurenboebert: #NewProfilePic https://t.co/030WtQbD2o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mtgreenee: Say His Name: Donald John Trump  Stop the Big Tech Censorship!  RT and make it trend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikkiHaley: Silencing people, not to mention the President of the US, is what happens in China not our country. #Unbelievable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Commies. Jack can bite me https://t.co/I45jng0xod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#trump]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MAGA Forever!!!! Trump is my President and Biden sucks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Free Speech Is Under Attack! Censorship is happening like NEVER before! Dont let them silence us. Sign up at https://t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/ScmE1RUiQy]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>