<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaraHusani Hi Gorgeous! Thank you for everything that you do. You are such an inspiration to all of us. Know that we appreciate you so much  I'm so happy to hear about your great experience with our foundation  Take care and stay safe my love!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VariJStylez: This new @hudabeauty luminous matte foundation is tea! My shade is Nutmeg https://t.co/McBu8JHW99]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VariJStylez Spill that tea honey! You're fire]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SHO_Shameless LOVE HER!!!! She's the cutest!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SHO_Shameless: We smell a new business opp.  https://t.co/wEFh7MCQbB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@superflydave Hi, can you send us your email address so the team can get in touch xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Billu_sahab Hi darling, the team have been in touch via email, can you check your mail/junk and let us know if you haven't received anything so they can assist you, they will send a follow up now x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClairePimf Hi Claire, this doesnt seem like an order number from our official site, can you email our team at shop@hudabeauty.com so they can assist you xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lol_Gambit Hi darling, can you send me your email address so we can look into this for you xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zainab96134472 Hi my love! Thank you for purchasing! I'm sorry to hear that. Can you send me your email address so we can look into this for you x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BambiieeLou Hi darling! Hope you're amazing :) I'm sorry to hear that! Can you send me your email address so we can look into this for you x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatpharmartist @Dimmaumeh @lhidhiastanley Awwwww you're too CUTE!!! Love you so much!! We would love to send you one my love! Whats your IG handle? Will DM you for your details ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vanessaracquel_ Hi beautiful!  You're SOO adorable! We would love to send you one my love! Whats your IG handle? Will DM you for your details  Love you!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RazaCheemA300 Hi darling, this is just a value for customs purposes, I dont believe you would have been charged at checkout but if you can DM me your email address the team will be in touch to confirm x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hafeezaxo Hi darling, Unfortunately this is not our authorized retailer, our legal team are aware of this site and working hard to resolve this!x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@vscott391outlo1 We'll look into this for you straight away. Can you DM us your email address so we can get in touch? x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Msloud7 Hi darling, the team have been in touch about your Desert Dusk palette via email. Just let them know if you need anything else x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fahimtahir16 Hi darling, hope all is well. Thank you so much for purchasing from us! So sorry to hear that, please email us at shop@hudabeauty.com so we can help you! Xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How I Learned to Love Myself - Part 1 https://t.co/VIP84TiXgL via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yoshitagrawal @MyNykaa Hi beautiful! Hope you're safe! Thank you so much for purchasing our products. I'm so sorry to hear that you may have had a reaction, can you send us your email address so our team can get in touch with you and look into this further x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MyNykaa @yosh59285132 Hi beautiful! Hope you're safe! Thank you so much for purchasing our products. I'm so sorry to hear that you may have had a reaction, can you send us your email address so our team can get in touch with you and look into this further x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chinonny_: @Nelie_Whyte Try @fentybeauty , @hudabeauty and this Nigerian brand #nubanbeauty]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_missxtine: Yeah the huda beauty setting powder is a game changer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AOC: @epicciuto Huda Demi Matte in Game Changer ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dreamy534 Hi Honey, we are so sorry to hear this. Can you please share your email address or order number so our team can assist you further? Thank you! x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@honeygarciiia Hi Honey, we are so sorry to hear this. Can you please share your email address or order number so our team can assist you further? Thank you! x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megangracemua: NATIONAL LIPSTICK DAY  . 1st - @hudabeauty Demi Matte in 'Boy Collector' 2nd - @hudabeauty Lip Contour in 'Wifey' and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MakeupEliana: Look inspired by @theestallion   I felt it when she said unbreakable protect your energy at all cost   @ABHco]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @makeupwith_ang: Obsessed with my @hudabeauty N.Y.M.P.H highlighter   #hudabeauty https://t.co/gJXATGkiKI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/2CkfuGXGP2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ayyyjam Hi darling, I'm so sorry to hear about this. We are looking into resolving the issue ASAP. In the meantime, can you please email shop@hudabeauty.com so they can assist you further? Alternatively, you may provide us with your email address and we will contact you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@butt_cheekz Hi darling, I'm so sorry to hear about this. We are looking into resolving the issue ASAP. In the meantime, can you please email shop@hudabeauty.com so they can assist you further? Alternatively, you may provide us with your email address and we will contact you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MannyMua733: i think the perfect way to celebrate the 4th of july would be to arrest the cops who murdered breonna taylor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gabrielzamora It left me depressed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @8ottz: Just arrest the cops my gawd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lewasntme: This is the stuff I love to see on my fuckin timeline&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChiomaMyah: Would you still? https://t.co/A6F6qgyqeF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPost: Here's how to support Black businesses while helping mitigate the spread of COVID-19. https://t.co/v1CFHfWKgN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPost: How to help teach your children about activism, tolerance, morality and violence against Black people. https://t.co/dAdfV47KIg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidBegnaud: BREAKING: the man who verbally  physically attacked 3 young adults who were putting up Black Lives Matter signs on the C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UberFacts: Today would have been Breonna Taylor's 27th birthday.  On March 13th, she was asleep in her Louisville apartment when police]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MeekMill: Breonna Taylor's murderers STILL havent been arrested or charged. Today woulda been her 27th bday!!! Hit the link to find ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NikitaDragun: today is Breonna Taylors birthday. she would have been 27. we demand justice for her murder! u dont shoot someone 8 tim]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ArianaGrande: #birthdayforbreonna #sayhername we are fighting for you  to demand justice for her and her family text ENOUGH to 55156]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3:    https://t.co/VchXrCMY3d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tashianafernz Hey my love! Did you get your products yet?! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VogueRunway: How to protest safely during a pandemic https://t.co/Gs7CUS4ZHx https://t.co/qFRt7a18ex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3: This is horrying. This is un-American. This goes against everything we stand for. It is beyond inhumane and we must end i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeenVogue: Dont just boost people who say what you want to hear; listen to people who challenge the way you think https://t.co/lSDtHJq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HafsaISalwe: @hudabeauty Two years later you started one of my favourite beauty blogs to date and now have an empire! Huge inspiration.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HafsaISalwe LOVE YOU SOOO MUCH!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @innatevalue: @AOC @vexwerewolf Cops are out there sexually harassing women and beating them for pulling away https://t.co/mK6GqeSVgX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AOC: Horrifying. You start with the tiny possibility that two officers may be walking over to deescalate the abusive one.  Instead, the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FastCompany: "We need to take care of our black women." https://t.co/HtDW3omI4h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @passthegospel: President Obama Singing Amazing Grace At Funeral. Wow this is awesome!  #GeorgeFloydMemorial @BarackObama  https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @aaronlmorrison: Rev. Sharpton asked attendees to observe an 8 min and 46 second long moment of silence  the time that Officer Derek Ch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanLeach971: This 8 mins and 46 seconds of silence at the #GeorgeFloydMemorial , the time the cop whos name I wont even use had his f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColorOfChange: Today, we honor and remember the life of #GeorgeFloyd. We're sending our thoughts and prayers to his family and loved on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @missnemmanuel: 8 minutes and 46 seconds is long time to stand.... and a long time to die...... and long enough for one of those of offi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mayawiley: When justice is done, it brings joy to the righteous but terror to evil doers: Proverbs 21:15: Judge: $750K bail for 3 ex]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hannah_natanson: Surreal, beautiful, peaceful scene outside the White House as a man sings Lean On Me and thousands and thousands of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kindahungrym: ben  jerrys might be expensive but at least i can eat it knowing they support the destruction of white supremacy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MannyMua733: everyone NEEDS to sign this! lets make sure police are held ACCOUNTABLE  https://t.co/bX1YurWd3g https://t.co/vu3nwKqcrG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @onedandre: Im raising a black Queen how could I not let her be apart of history  https://t.co/nngj5A2XWR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @arabnews: US-Iraqi beauty mogul @hudabeauty announced she will donate $500,000 amid US protests in solidarity with the black community]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nonie2tru: Soft Glam by me  @hudabeauty New Nude Palette  @Sephora 12hr Foundation  @ABHcosmetics Pressed Bronzer  @artistcouture Sexp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@adnandawood Thank you my love, just doing my responsibility!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nadia_b_mhmd: @hudabeauty You are an inspiration ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nadia_b_mhmd Thank you baby!!! Love you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamParkhomenko: Washington, DC right now. Please watch and retweet. https://t.co/becv0VKErJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3: Racism is a public health crisis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3: We need a leader who will bring us together. This president only knows how to divide.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3: This president only knows how to divide. https://t.co/NChT7NxLJv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @insanely_made: All 50 states. https://t.co/PzLQ7y969g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanHoppe: A powerful moment of protest in Homewood. An organizer shouts George Floyds last words while hundred lay on the ground for o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @djusatoday: An on-the-street demonstration at Lafayette Park near the White House ... note the new tall fence ... chants of dont shoo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @responsibleMDs: Doctors begged for a curfew to combat #coronavirus in #NYC. Didnt get one. Protestors get too close to Trump Tower and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JoeBiden: When 100,000 Americans died because of his incompetent leadership, this president golfed.  When Americans peacefully proteste]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3:   https://t.co/AQDv9w7od3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SAY HIS NAME #GEORGEFLOYD Bless this angel #GiannaFloyd https://t.co/ViwsPXHsHi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is adorable, and tbh I dont feel like this should feel like anything out of the norm, but it does right now. We should all love each other the way these kids do https://t.co/zCzxKLq7HH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3: https://t.co/llLa09GnbJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chrisinsilico: This is not law enforcement. This is state-sponsored terrorism.  https://t.co/jV3hL2ro3s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @m_d_mccoy: George Floyd and I were both arrested for allegedly spending a counterfeit $20 bill. For George Floyd, a man my age, with tw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HereForTheTea2: Official fund for Gianna Floyd, the daughter of George Floyd. Its managed by the Stewart Trial Attorneys and 100% of t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We have to unite for this change to happen https://t.co/rAPcJMxajC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/MrwjQsqb04]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @actually_ahitza: WHY DO PEOPLE HATE IMMIGRANTS WHO PAY TAXES BUT NOT BILLIONAIRES WHO DONT!!! MAKE IT MAKE SENSE ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zayer_dounya: This was me, and I want to make one thing clear to all the people that are commenting lies below this video. I did NOT sp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mynique8: @hudabeauty I will tell you the cops are attacking protesters and making it seem like where doing the looting and destroying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheJessieWoo: Dont forget about her  Louisville Police shot Breonna 8 times  in her own home on March 13th.  #BreonnaTaylor #SayHerNa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpiroAgnewGhost: An older conservative dyed in the wool Republican friend who has contorted himself like a pretzel to defend Trump sinc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @genmnz: this. https://t.co/0LC3DYoHer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jessicamanley_: Wow Denver is making me proud tonight!!!!!! Peaceful HUGE protest!!!!  #BLM https://t.co/1mfCdi2VMi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @brett_mcgurk: Heres how this scene was viewed live in Australia. One of Americas closest and most dependable allies. Rendered speechl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YourAnonCentral: New Zealand holds one of the largest Black Lives Matter protests outside of the United States. Global Unity Now, No Mo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow. The truth https://t.co/kBV4hAYJGM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoneyOsk: Yall can understand a white kid shooting up a school cuz he was bullied after 4 months of school but dont understand why an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UnrigLA: Even Garcettis rich white neighbors get it more than he does. https://t.co/jjZp9CEjLb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialMLK3: https://t.co/uWnF2LU6St]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>