<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MartinKulldorff: "After one year of covering the pandemic, it is surprising that some journalists still do not understand basic princip]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi Anna,  Could you please share this on your social media please. We are aiming for our biggest yet. https://t.co/0VqfvxhDE8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tackling two campaigns.. very busy so cant answer dms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please dont.. https://t.co/zwTELsueeB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please read the comments underneath this thread. Some say their two year olds have never left the house and the vax means freedom others are saying its evil and child abuse.   Its unbelievable what has happened here.. https://t.co/meXItSGdF3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AnaCabrera https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talkRADIO: Retired paediatrician Dr Ros Jones thinks healthy children do not need a Covid vaccine.  "As a society, adults are responsib]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@talkRADIO @mrmarkdolan https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UNICEF https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @andrewbostom: 1/ Granted low absolute rates, updated CDC Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System (VAERS) data reveal that for U.S. 18-49]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrEricDing: Over 800 pregnant women have died of #COVID19 in Brazil during pandemic (compared to just 95 in US). Brazil  is now prior]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KirstieMAllsopp https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: If you really think they will go to all the trouble of a vaccine passport, for 1 virus, which was associated with 1 death]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter jail for ivermectin. https://t.co/vYhKjgP0M3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@allisonpearson https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeremyVineOn5 @DrChrisSmith https://t.co/Lg666mJciu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I believe that when they start vaccinating children in America and Europe. The reports, speculation, personal accounts, hysteria will result in all posts being removed and many accounts being banned.   So please urgently sign up here https://t.co/vBO95Wzl83 https://t.co/9CwKaKFZ1x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I believe that when they start vaccinating children in America and Europe. The reports, speculation, personal accounts, hysteria will result in all posts being removed and many accounts being banned.   So please urgently sign up here https://t.co/vBO95Wzl83 https://t.co/TZyQQdqUd5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrEricDing Why have you posted this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neiljmcevoy: Last day to campaign to start to clean up Welsh politics. Polls open in 24 hours 30 mins. Time to #RestoreFreedom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Critical: After 3 days in defiance of a court order, @ElmhurstHealth is now giving Ms. Fype #ivermectin. You know, 3 days is a l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know children who are struggling to breath and too scared to take the mask off and a boy who has missed school due to anxiety from it https://t.co/ErXk3CfxAm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeremyVineOn5: "It would be like leaving the back door open, having bolted the front door, which means were more likely to get burgled]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @allisonpearson: Vaccinating children is wholly unnecessary and, therefore, morally wrong.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drdavidbull: OFCOMs Urgent Investigation into BBC Bias Against Reform UK https://t.co/8UmEo91pxh via @guidofawkes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BernieSpofforth: After a week spent in solidarity confinement in Twitter jail, I have now been released. Full sentence served, not even]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For those who are looking for it, its here   https://t.co/WSQqtB97Gi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: A bit about my political leanings and how I feel this time around. Please make sure you vote on May 6th... https://t.co/7ECG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Beckham: Vaccines Bring Us Closer | UNICEF https://t.co/8AUsDqEURB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I need to assess this but its been shared with me a hundred times today. Ill get back to you... https://t.co/DcbhragCQ0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Telegraph: Are you experiencing Covid-related anxiety now lockdown is easing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jimwaterson: Teenager works out to game Twitter politics algorithm better than any other news organisation, sends Westminster politics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@isaperena this isnt acceptable and its quite clear you agree - you look very uncomfortable here on @SkyNews when talking about vaccinating healthy secondary school children https://t.co/RDLLHPEgRQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust is key... more here on the plan to vaccinate secondary school children @SkyNews today.. https://t.co/Qu3jn3byUO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@isaperena vaccination starting in secondary schools come September? https://t.co/0rSElRl8EN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Covid19Critical: ***BREAKING: Judge orders hospital to administer ivermectin immediately to patient in Chicago after hosp. files motion]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@SophyRidgeSky I saw your piece for @SkyNews this morning on the May 6th Election - and you didnt talk to @reformukwales or @propel @FreedomWales and also your voice- over indicates you were there but I dont think you were...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/r9nrqWe8uP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/E1HT21hLuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When doctors and professors in their thousands come out to tell you whats going on but you dont listen - provide strategy and solutions please  @hartgroup_org @NursesCanadian @Covid19Critical @BIRDGroupUK @gbdeclaration @PanData19 @Drs4CovidEthics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#GatesDivorce #GatesFoundation #MelindaGates #billgatesdivorce https://t.co/WpfgEKUPbi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The biggest indicator of what is going on. https://t.co/WpfgEKUPbi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its not about money thats something im sure of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe he wrote a list of the pros and cons of the resources needed to sustain a global population growing out of control. @BillGates Ive seen children suffer and he has too. His wife no longer believes in the campaign. https://t.co/doymEVYuGk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Posted 11 years ago Bill Gates https://t.co/LBq8DlZqPu via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is important...  https://t.co/y8FBHwONEi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliaHB1: Remember, @SadiqKhan can do this, but you cant legally sit at a table indoors, at a restaurant or in a private home, and eat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please download and share - listening to the people and finding a channel who will listen https://t.co/RzJInmNpNF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks Twitter - the last 28 days https://t.co/MJKO51LqSJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GoodLawProject: The ability to hold an elected government to account is a central pillar of a democracy. Sadly, the UK government seem]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JolyonMaugham: For those who are interested, we have arranged an amazing panel with @libertyhq, @BindmansLLP and @DoughtyStreet to talk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Defamation law for activists: a guide to speaking truth to power Tickets, Tue 11 May 2021 at 13:00 | Eventbrite https://t.co/dBe0snkh0C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good one.. https://t.co/WQVSRloKON]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Longer video on this topic on my Patreon https://t.co/J2H2iU4Sd5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats all Im saying about #billgatesdivorce https://t.co/TrMx4Y858t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LibyanIntegrity: BBC asked the BBC to come onto a BBC programme to talk about the BBC but the BBC was not available! https://t.co/ukS6H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can they reinstate my report of talking to people in the protest too please? And I spoke to those not protesting https://t.co/ZD20qVdHao]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And this is why theyre going to push the vaccine on children.. https://t.co/lYIoO7Qnl1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its the passports and vaccination of healthy children we must now all focus on...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @naomirwolf: A must-read about Vaccine Passports from the folks who built the no-fly list. Spoiler alert: they confirm that Im right to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now 420 comments on the original @Telegraph article but how many under this tweet?   They should be paying me. https://t.co/rr0LeQ5i0z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe it had something to do with #ivermectin   BREAKING NEWS: Bill and Melinda Gates are divorcing after 27 years  https://t.co/YoHE9MJPpS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BillGates: https://t.co/padmHSgWGc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @melindagates: https://t.co/fCVHDlZbvq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Odd..   https://t.co/EnZmwm8WFt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SusanWojcicki: The COVID crisis in India is heartbreaking. Read more about how Google is working to provide support. At YouTube, we're]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@ukcolumn has moved to @OdyseeTeam along with others these last few weeks https://t.co/xOWTuM9gb8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just found out about these guys - Voices for Freedom https://t.co/TbqoGR6diD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alanvibe: Request:  This is gonna be a big 2 weeks  Its going to be when we get gov to either listen  have our freedom  Normality  O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kuwaitis not allowed to travel abroad without vaccination - ARAB TIMES - KUWAIT NEWS https://t.co/fg259Q3cFS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mistaNormski: Here here! Exactley why I like working with Electric Star Pubs  events ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Head of Health Analysis at the ONS... now standing due to @MarkDrakeford failing the welsh people and specifically children... https://t.co/sLXIXHpnwm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @freddiesayers: If the Times is right about this post-June 21st Covid regime, it will be so hilariously illogical and impractical that i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JohnBoweActor: I try to concentrate on the Ivermectin campaign but sometimes you come across something that underlines your belief that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HelenaRussell @ShelaghFogarty https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShelaghFogarty https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drcmday https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NadimJBaba https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nuwandiss https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SuseRichards https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EvidenceMatters https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinTallis https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AlStewartOBE https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShaunLintern https://t.co/BtwI4Oho6j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShaunLintern: Please stop generalising with 'the media' when making lazy attacks on a whole industry that has many varied and different]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShaunLintern https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KirstieMAllsopp https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KirstieMAllsopp: This is true, and I am guilty of this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThisisDavina https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThisisDavina https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MenoScandal @ThisisDavina @menopausalmave @Channel4 https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei https://t.co/ZMbMlhFT7g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bobscartoons: The lengths I would be prepared to go to in order to stop children being vaccinated might be viewed as pretty extreme.  B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @neiljmcevoy: Out early. Big diolch to volunteers also out. We need change. Vote @propelwales https://t.co/muLTT1lje7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KirstieMAllsopp: Dear Rick, you follow me. If you dont like what I am saying unfollow me. It  seems a little perverse, not to mention]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChristineBrett8: I really cant understand people like @sarajcox saying they havent seen elderly parents since 2019! The fear of passi]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>