<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thenatewolf: One of the best scenes you can do as an actor is crying against a locked door and then sliding down the door. Its called]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yankee Doodle wasnt calling the feather macaroni, it was the ponys name.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Workout partner: whats with the outfit?  Me: *dressed as a pawn* you said it was chess day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AeronauticsAnd Why is the human body skinless tho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatleeword A true artist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ygrene: 2.5 years 2 surgeries 28 rounds of chemo Countless scans  lab tests  One (1) phone call today to tell me that I am in remissio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New invention idea: online shopping but in person]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Workout partner: whats with the outfit?  Me: *dressed as a pawn* you said it was chess day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vFCoYFSBvA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me: *weighing in before a big fight but Im 1.5lbs over* Shave off my eyebrows]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Holy_Mowgli: my name is radio star jr. you killed my father prepare to die]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KalvinMacleod: Slippers made out of Lego so that when you step on Lego you just get taller.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fro_vo: its my favorite]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sploosk: if someone is choking: 1) Get behind them 2) secure a firm grip around their midsection 3) suplex http://t.co/UzStMsVhOF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@v_yancey https://t.co/ltEjEDDliG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@v_yancey Thats literally what I said lmao]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The one thing I have learned from this thread is that I have learned absolutely nothing from this thread]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@girl_from_mi Ironman 2 was the first I watched]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Reverend_Scott Captain America was basically a frisbee assassin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alisialynne @notnotscotty Imbued is not allowed during weekend Twitter imaboued to call the cops]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me: Im watching all the MCU movies in order  Her: youre already on Infinity war?  Me: well, I just started. The order is worst to best]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How does Captain Americas shield know when to hit and ricochet off things and when to cut right through them?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WhatsAGreenhorn: White person: *stirs a whole jar of mayonnaise into a giant bowl of cereal* Frosted Flakes salad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whatsJo: her: so what do ya think about kids?  guy who invented banana flavored candy: I hate them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[its my first day in heaven and I keep doing the elevator behind the couch trick but with all the clouds and God makes me fall straight to hell where I immediately start doing the same trick in lava]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: My wife who started having an allergy attack in the middle of yelling at me about calling her made up names  Me: haha whate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShortSleeveSuit: UNTRENDY MOSES: *side parts the Red Sea*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dealer: the bet is to you, sir  Me: *pushes in a stack of plywood* Im all in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My wife who started having an allergy attack in the middle of yelling at me about calling her made up names  Me: haha whatever, Julius Sneezer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: What if Eminem was telling us there is vomit on his sweater already and then was separately telling us that his mom is spag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @donni: The first guy to eat cheese had a creepy hunch that totally paid off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattPostSaysHi Final boss vibes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ValterSkarsgard Jfc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MavenofHonor: We all have that one friend who's a floating onyx decahedron]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Whatever your struggle, please know that twittercide is not the answer. Lowering my follower count isn't going to help anyo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThrillHicks: Just remember: if something I said or tweeted, or some small interaction we had, brightened your day even if for only a br]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pork_Chop_Hair: Im a people person. I live in a house home where I enjoy food meals and listening to music songs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Me: *walks in with my clothes shredded*  Wife: what happened   Me: (embarrassed that squirrels jumped me in the park for my]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mustardvehicle: *julius caesar getting stabbed a bunch of times* Yo name a salad after me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ygrene: [Neos Matrix bullet dodge but instead its me taking a compliment]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YounglingKicker ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Me: What do you give the girl that has everything  My Mom: Penicillin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CosmicallyF: I don't need the vaccine, I've already had a chip on my shoulder for years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Me: has anyone seen Dan  My friend Dan that died in a hunting accident: haha real funny, because Im wearing camo pants]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Me: has anyone seen Dan  My friend Dan that died in a hunting accident: haha real funny, because Im wearing camo pants]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pork_Chop_Hair: [sitting next to the trash bin as the truck pulls up] I SAID IM REALLY VULNERABLE RIGHT NOW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @whatsJo: date: can you take off your work gloves  Jim Henson: they have names]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @murrman5: my son whos allergic to peanuts: good morning dad me: what is it now Riley]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Trisarahjtops: Stones are nature's doorknobs and every time you pick one up you're opening a door to a world you know nothing about]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: She had matches for teeth and sandpaper lips, the kind of smile that could light up a room]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Me: *carefully going around the victims body with chalk*  Detective: We dont usually outline the balls  Me: oh Im not a c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hood your screaming baby like a falcon but as youre about to get mad you realize shes already calm and choking down the field mouse I have rewarded her with.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChucklebumJohn *flicks cigarette after a long drag* heres the thing, One is a thumb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Spanish04907406 The witnesses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ygrene Great question, *flicks cigarette after a long drag* heres the thing, does the whole glove go in the washer or just the skin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ygrene: [my wife to everyone at the pool party] pls don't tell him, he's never known the truth [me loudly as I jump off the diving boar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iamspacegirl: The whole band is mad because I keep trying to twirl up their guitar strings like spaghetti with a fork I brought from ho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamspacegirl So, so far..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamspacegirl Bold. I was afraid to touch the sun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iook, I dont know if the hamburger helper fights with his fingers or balls himself into a fist Im just saying good luck handcuffing him if he wins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iamspacegirl Eddie spaghetti Van Halen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Australia is not fucking around with these gender reveals https://t.co/cqo1us09OS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: *i get a second pringles can stuck on my other arm as scientists take notes from behind a two way mirror*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pork_Chop_Hair @KatieMoNYC @lolumOKUR @Impetermoran @mrjohndarby @DrakeGatsby @ElyKreimendahl @prufrockluvsong @chaotic_sub @DanManCarney @dan_wickes Thank you, Katie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: *being nailed to a cross* bro, you almost hit my thumb with that hammer,  oh my god lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pineapple_mist We can share an Uber]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesus: (rising from the dead) IM JUST BUILT DIFFERENT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*being nailed to a cross* bro, you almost hit my thumb with that hammer,  oh my god lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sock_holliday How many years A.V. is this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@numberboxer @dadthatwrites Selfish sunsah...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dadthatwrites @Mom_Overboard https://t.co/io1Kh5ZQQ3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Are You There God Its Me You Son Of A Bitch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SirEviscerate https://t.co/nfkUyLvSQq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lets be honest people named Scott. Youre just being greedy with the Ts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JB4Realz: giant sized bag of candy: i'm resealable  me: that won't be necessary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanMentos: "Edward, I gave you scissors for hands, but don't let that define who you are" Ok. BTW what's my last name? "Scissorhands"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: The struggle https://t.co/LSlrdmwb8x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LilNasX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The struggle https://t.co/LSlrdmwb8x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dorsalstream: When Grimace hunts, he bites his prey once and then pursues from a distance until the poison takes hold.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im doing my best  Been Eating Some Tacos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are You There God Its Me You Son Of A Bitch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@radponytail Like bat wings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@radponytail Hes currently wearing an under armor shirt telling me he will protect this house but honestly, he doesnt even have the abs for it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @adamgreattweet: bank account: $1400  me to a girl scout: give me the thick mints]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Ben and Jerrys Funky Cold Moderna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Your email didnt find me, Linda. You sent it to me, grow up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justky1018 Good morning]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KalvinMacleod: More like the suez cannot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben and Jerrys Funky Cold Moderna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dmorrison1979 With his fingers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Beast: Ill be like this until someone loves me for who I am  Ugly girl: Ill love you for who you are  Beast: not you, som]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: If Im on a plane at 10,000 feet and you jump off Im not impressed. If Im on a plane at 10,000 feet and you jump on? You]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dlicj: glad i decided to take the panama canal instead of the suez today]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@VikingBut https://t.co/iQWT62JVjS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dorsalstream: ME: I thought grandpas ghost reveal party was nice   WIFE: Please just call it a funeral]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MavenofHonor: Saw a deer on my bike but didn't have my phone to take a pic. Hopefully one day he will return my bike tho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bewgtweets: Smart guy: an island is land surrounded by water  Me (the smartest human maybe idk): buddy, all land is surrounded by water]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AngrySkycrane @LegbootLegit @Ygrene https://t.co/27drHyF1D5]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>