<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @julieacrisp: Yep - who else can we recruit to the #Bloodsworn?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julieacrisp We definitely need more to join us! https://t.co/WjCugeyKos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @julieacrisp: And if anyone else wants to recommend any high profile SFF fans for us to try to approach with a copy - just let us know.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were still on a Henry Cavill mission to get him to read John Gwynnes books! https://t.co/cpfRY3iEuW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julieacrisp @JohnGwynne_ Phase 2 is in progress - but no response on Instagram yet!  #HenryCavill https://t.co/jlci5vUCHH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mannyhenri @gollancz @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @GillianRedfearn Ive just finished writing my review and thats exactly what I wrote - its so original!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @imyril: The Obsidian Tower is the start of an epic new series by Melissa Caruso. Time to return to Vaskandar, where a vivomancer whose]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PetrikReads: As expected, Priest of Gallows by @PeteMC666 was so good! I need Priest of Crowns ASAP! Thank you @ellakroftpatel for the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LouiseMwrite @gollancz @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @GillianRedfearn Its brilliant! One I highly recommend ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today its I Could Do This All Day (Underdogs) over on the #WyrdAndWonder photo challenge!  I chose The Righteous by David Wragg, which is the upcoming sequel to The Black Hawks. This series has the most hilarious underdogs who go into battle!  Who are your favourite underdogs? https://t.co/3K7SCNmlbl https://t.co/63yfj6AQGH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnGwynne_ @k_villoso I loved your answer of Cate Blanchett as the shape-shifting dragon!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had a lot of fun watching @JohnGwynne_ and @k_villoso on last nights Orbit Live virtual event.  Thank you both for answering my question on adaptations of your series.  Really looking forward to The Shadow of the Gods UK release tomorrow! https://t.co/VAkzINmxYb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookwormkarou Me too ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_LLMacRae @_WordsOfAPaige Oh no! @julieacrisp another one for 12th May. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LostDunedan Really??? Must subscribe! Are you going to? You know you want to hear Pippin talk loads!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julieacrisp @_WordsOfAPaige Hopefully others will get it on time!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julieacrisp @_WordsOfAPaige Im not a Prime member. But even without Prime they used to deliver pre-orders on time. Otherwise whats the point?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@julieacrisp @_WordsOfAPaige Yep, pre-ordered the hardback and it said estimated delivery 12th May. Not happy at all, but at least Ive read it. I feel bad for those who havent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFilipMagnus Assassins Apprentice is a great choice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JohnGwynne_ Ill be there!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GabrielaHouston For me its dialogue. I really am put off by forced dialogue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cat_book_tea Now that sounds like a fantastic use of footnotes. Ive never read a book which has done that before]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cat_book_tea I like an Appendix too, and glossaries. Or are they the same thing? Anyway I love referring to those for certain terms Im not quite understanding or remembering. However I really dont like footnotes. For some reason those pull me out of a story more than maps do.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cat_book_tea Oh no, not at all. For me personally it adds to the enjoyment of reading fantasy. (Just dont ask me to read a real world/road map though! Im hopeless with those )]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cat_book_tea This is me! Every time characters start journeying or a new place is mentioned, I immediately refer to the map! You should see me get grumpy when a book doesnt include one ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cat_book_tea Oh no Asha, another thing were complete opposites on! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFTFPodcast1 Yeah hes the only one clueless for quite a while ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFTFPodcast1 @neilhimself  wait I hope I havent given a spoiler there?! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFTFPodcast1 @neilhimself Excellent choice! I thought you might pick Rand!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_WordsOfAPaige ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_WordsOfAPaige Thats so long!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_WordsOfAPaige Amazon have estimated my delivery for the 12th of May ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you for quoting my review from @TheFantasyHive for The Righteous by @itsdavewragg! I cant wait for this one to be released next month, its such a fantastic sequel @DHHlitagency https://t.co/h3sWvJERmw https://t.co/55CFzuSJqO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFantasyInn  ooh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardCox10 Will do!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardCox10  Ah Id forgotten that! Ill let you into a secret, I never liked End Game so Ive only watched it once. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardCox10 I cant remember what he did in End Game?! So I hope I havent insulted you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardCox10  https://t.co/9QsZJMV4Un]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardCox10  Im just teasing, you did great on the Gollancz Fest virtual panels! Nice that you can virtually chat to your mum now too. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EdwardCox10 Im proud you can too, Ed!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its day 4 of #wyrdandwonder!  I Never Knew My Father (Orphan/Secret Heirs)  For this Ive chosen Bod from The Graveyard Book by @neilhimself - this is definitely one of my favourite books by Gaiman. Check out my short Readerly review  Who is your favourite orphan? https://t.co/Lnn1bssGCu https://t.co/LxIOf48VAV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookwormkarou I miss you reading too my friend! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mellon_heads ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFantasyInn @tctippens Happy Birthday Travis! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimPaul_illo @TheFantasyHive @KitvariaSarene @ReadzandRunz @BethanMay @wyrdandwonder Excellent! Can you tell me which ones? I would have absolutely loved to have credited you, but I never know where to find out who designed the maps in books.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFilipMagnus @TheFantasyHive Ill take a look!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carolinehwrites @ChrisJPanatier I think youd like it. Its a slow build creepy feeling, not outright horror. Its part of a trilogy but I havent read the other two yet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFilipMagnus @TheFantasyHive This is a stunning map!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LostDunedan @EnglishHeritage Beautiful!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeteMC666 @jayjasonjayman @JoFletcherBooks Really? Well Im obviously in Our Ladys favour.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LostDunedan @wyrdandwonder @BethanMay @TheFantasyHive @KitvariaSarene @ReadzandRunz You could probably do that in Hobbiton in NZ. Just win the lottery first!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jayjasonjayman @PeteMC666 @JoFletcherBooks What can I say, Our Lady delivers! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EvanWinter @TheFantasyHive I can review books, but maths was never my strong point ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And here are my short Readerly reviews for the first two books in the War for the Rose Throne quartet   https://t.co/mUw2gsetYx https://t.co/iq4KPOaadF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you @JoFletcherBooks for my copy of Priest of Gallows by @PeteMC666  One murder can change the fate of a nation.  Just by that first line I know Im going to love seeing what Tomas Piety does next!  Look at this map of Ellingburg! Another worthy entry for #WyrdAndWonder https://t.co/13591aICJ2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patricksamphire This is awesome, Patrick! @BethanMay look at this stunning map!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EvanWinter @TheFantasyHive I meant three! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EvanWinter @TheFantasyHive Thank you, I hope you enjoy writing book four!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@carolinehwrites Ive only read Annihilation, but I enjoyed it! Quite creepy at times!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EvanWinter: Very deeply honored that @nilsreviewsit and @TheFantasyHive wrote/hosted this review of FIRES. Thank you so much for taking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EvanWinter @TheFantasyHive Thank you so much for a great series, Evan. Its such a pleasure reading your books! I thoroughly enjoyed Fires and eagerly await for The Lord of Demons - epic title by the way! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Macey6 @JohnGwynne_ @audibleuk @LittleBrownUK Absolutely loved this book too!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My review of The Fires of Vengeance by @EvanWinter is up on @TheFantasyHive  Winter gives us a relentlessly fast paced book, one where a battle for retribution and for love go hand in hand.  Heres the link: https://t.co/b6I55jKByu  @orbitbooks @bhvide @Gambit589 https://t.co/pGJ6wC4L2I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@v_knipe @TheFantasyHive @KitvariaSarene @ReadzandRunz @BethanMay @wyrdandwonder Its such a shame because that would be gorgeous to have framed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@v_knipe @TheFantasyHive @KitvariaSarene @ReadzandRunz @BethanMay @wyrdandwonder Omg! I love this! Theyve even included Smaug! I bet they were pricy too?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatdalglishguy And a ton of fun to discover!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikestepjack @papagaeio Oh!!  Yeah, ooft is a great way of describing them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thatdalglishguy I forgot to mention how much I love the annotations on this map! Im so glad you did these for each one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@papagaeio @mikestepjack I still dont know?! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LostDunedan @TheFantasyHive @KitvariaSarene @ReadzandRunz @BethanMay @wyrdandwonder This is fantastic, Kai! I bet theres loads of gorgeous maps in that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wyrdandwonder @BethanMay @LostDunedan @TheFantasyHive @KitvariaSarene @ReadzandRunz SAME! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikestepjack Bonus content! Lovely!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikestepjack This is SO NICE!!! Definitely go with this for the hardback?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveAryan @angryrobotbooks @papagaeio See now Ill be looking for the Easter eggs closely!  Ill have to keep note if I spot them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikestepjack Ooh I adore coloured maps, I wish more books included them! This great ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveAryan @angryrobotbooks @papagaeio Thanks for sharing!! Cant stop taking photos of that gorgeous map! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikestepjack @IlkkaAuer Ooh now this is a pretty map!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mikestepjack Whats OFT?? And you can show us your map if you have one? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its #mapmonday today over on #WyrdAndWonder   My choices today were the map from The Coward by Stephen Aryan - map created by Tom Parker, and the map from Voidbreaker by David Dalglish.  Your turn - show us your favourite fantasy maps? https://t.co/rA6PKwNT0K https://t.co/GJjZLVVm0Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joriestory I really hope you enjoy it Jorie! I thoroughly loved it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IainMacCallum2 @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @gollancz @GillianRedfearn Youre going to love it, its definitely one of my favourite. Great eccentric characters, fantastic narrative voice and the world building is wonderfully bizarre!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@grn_wonderland @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @gollancz @GillianRedfearn Thank you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoboftheHayes @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @gollancz @GillianRedfearn Haha! Thats very true!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shaunaLwrites Haha! Its out on Thursday!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@its_mohitd @RoboftheHayes @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @gollancz @GillianRedfearn It was brilliant though!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shaunaLwrites  Excellent!! We should have teamed up to do this together!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_Sam_Who_ @TheFantasyHive @AndreaGStewart @AlixEHarrow @LostDunedan @authorjla @BethanMay @ReadzandRunz @wyrdandwonder I have some serious shelf envy here! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shaunaLwrites We do!! I didnt know what to use for the goblins so I left it out! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RoboftheHayes @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @gollancz @GillianRedfearn Oh my god, you have so much to come!! Wasnt that tug of war scene so haunting?! I didnt know whether to laugh or throw up! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shaunaLwrites What do you think of my choice of emojis? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Wood0132 @Buehlmeister @TheFantasyHive @WillOMullane @gollancz @GillianRedfearn Id say another year, as the Hardback is out on 27th May]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jakeisreading @ChrisJPanatier This is a fab pic Jake!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shaunhamill Thats a great choice! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jasonats Awesome, glad you enjoyed it too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kestlong Ooh lovely! Ive only read Uprooted from this list, but the rest sound intriguing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LostDunedan @D_CurrieDC @mellon_heads No you may not! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive just finished The Blacktongue Thief by @Buehlmeister! Loved it so much!  Heres my emoji review!  Beginning:   Middle:      End:      Full review to come on @TheFantasyHive  This is my second recommendation for day 2 of #wyrdandwonder https://t.co/k0oFnOFcrr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SoManyBooks6 Basically its a month dedicated to the Fantasy genre. You read fantasy books, take part in their challenges, their readalong, and discussions. They have a whole intro post on their account.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@D_CurrieDC OMG! This is my grey haven!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mellon_heads This ones easy for you right Kai? @LostDunedan ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>