<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@JenniferMarguli Laughing at how many think it was you who took the vaccine.. they so do not know you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @silversynergy: Highly cited COVID doctor comes to stunning conclusion: Govt scrubbing unprecedented numbers of injection-related dea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss Did he really...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good point on SB1457, should have known Kathy Harrod was involved! Thank you @ApologiaStudios for your efforts to protect the unborn, healthy and disabled https://t.co/V2efWOujJJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pick your poison..   VAERS data released today showed 118,902 reports of adverse events following COVID vaccines, including 3,544 deaths and 12,619 serious injuries between Dec. 14, 2020 and April 23, 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gracetoyou: How can you raise your children so thatas much as it depends on youthey will commit their lives to Christ? John MacArthur]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoanneOsborne8 God Doesn't Judge?? I am all for encouraging one another but I sure hope you are walking in the fullness of the word and not as James 1 speaks as a double minded man?  Here are just a few scriptures I pulled up about Gods Judgment. Do not compromise, for the end is near! https://t.co/npBtTXSun6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still think this is about a pandemic.   https://t.co/Gvnh8r4HKz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AMEN! https://t.co/OoN8Vt5H2S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember that kids science project that isolated us from each other over a year ago https://t.co/Gh4McTMEdR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I got a fever.. and the only prescription is..."   https://t.co/OMBFzRMEQY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @talialikeitis: I dont know who needs to hear this but inhibiting your breathing with a muzzle for over a year is helping exactly zero]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ALLIE IS  https://t.co/3OMYdvdgkG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lifebiomedguru: I need 10,000 RTs on this.   https://t.co/0oRYLKpTgg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lifebiomedguru On it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetMeRoss: what https://t.co/XOVwIsJevg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetMeRoss: I wonder how @reginaldbolding and his caucus feel about this?  https://t.co/7fV5wdE4yK https://t.co/6YLZRbmvqc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CSLewisDaily: Forgiveness does not mean excusing.-C.S. Lewis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AntPar01 @lifebiomedguru @and_kell Omg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GarretLewis @DavidOAtkins Ill stand in solidarity with my free face and Immune system DAVID!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Va2021J @GetMeRoss @dougducey Safe... or dead??? Wouldnt you agree that there must be choice when there is risk?   https://t.co/NQ4apuXixx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BretRbrts Thank you for fighting for those of us who  have deep conviction and will never take this vaccine.   https://t.co/NQ4apuXixx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So why are we still under and Emergency @dougducey https://t.co/BbI4wtS2EF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#AllLivesMatter  #NoVaccinePassports  #SupportHB2190  #InformedConsent  https://t.co/NQ4apuXixx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[playing Russian roulette With your childs life! https://t.co/4jakw3z2fB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How's that lockdown in Toronto going?   https://t.co/MWdw1LmmiN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The only Truth is Jesus! https://t.co/3Ve64ozeB9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hows that new Covid campaign  Going for ya Fakebook. https://t.co/RAZPz5OeHw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetMeRoss: Just a reminder that the Mask Freedom bill was signed one week ago in AZ.  #HB2770]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@schwein10 @johnmacarthur And the great commission]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @schwein10: @johnmacarthur Its time for much of the American Evangelical Christian Church to stop chasing MAGA and to turn their loyalt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SirScandalous: @blakngold86 Ill take my 99%+ chance of survival]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BasedTradMom: I would be nothing without Christ, and I would be a far lesser human being without my husband. It isnt weakness to admit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_Drink_Mee: You know, I am tired of being civil. A small group of psychopaths is MURDERING people under the guise of healthcare.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetMeRoss: The #VaccinePassport idea needs to die TODAY.  The Johnson and Johnson suspension is all the proof you need.  End it. It's o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh these pour souls who think were going back to normal:( https://t.co/azKwE7O1Hr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new #peopleofwalmart https://t.co/y3KatzJEtg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Heart10Looks3 @WesHamrick1 @JosephChaplik @AZSenateGOP @AZHouseGOP @dougducey As long as they honor my exemption.. sure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JosephChaplik @GarretLewis @AZSenateGOP @AZHouseGOP Now lets get these kids in schools out of masks!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JosephChaplik @GarretLewis @AZSenateGOP @AZHouseGOP https://t.co/40hKvJwItC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss Maybe shes headed to the paintball field https://t.co/LtHhqBYKrO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @blanarovich: Our school just went mask free!!!! Thank you to everyone who helped me out last week with articles! It worked! Enough pare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: Bill Gates backs project to 'dim the sun', Tucker Carlson reacts https://t.co/WKGRmATbcZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss Took the fu!@ing jab  https://t.co/hzCKJ95qIP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss Must educate kids. Fast]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media and  will be pushing the narrative hard now. Just watch Don't fall for it! https://t.co/IO9CbMip9N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JosephChaplik @GetMeRoss @AZSenateGOP @AZHouseGOP ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BusyDrT ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I agree. why crickets from our Governor @dougducey https://t.co/vpr1hvVFtK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BuckSexton: Wearing masks outdoors alone to stop covid is stupid, theres no data to back it up as a policy, and the people who are c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Lequtis007 @BuckSexton what part of outdoors and alone did you not get. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@christianllamar @BretRbrts @merissahamilton mask bill is on the governor's desk. do you think he will sign it??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec makes me cry everytime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss why am I in tears laughing at this.. like tears..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @annavh14: This  show needs to end. https://t.co/NnMpRXIg3P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss she did give the left journalist a big slap in the face. and she does have some serious name recognition.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetMeRoss:  https://t.co/WPtbLmLZ13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just a reminder that today you can park in the parking lot at all city of Phoenix parks. Yesterday you could. it because @MayorGallego thinks she has more power then her Governor. https://t.co/hD2weS14O2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[you could sue JJ over Talcum powder. But get an injection and have a reaction and oh well.. #liabilityfree #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/GKpAJsHBv1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@waynerohde @MatthewdAncona you will own nothing and you will be happy. did ya not hear that one Matt another one asleep at the wheel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JosephChaplik @GetMeRoss  Martin and his "heavy hand of government"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GarretLewis this poor lady at frys is panting for breath in her mask. these poor employees need oxygen!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now Remember Kiddos  all city of Phoenix parks are open today, But the parking lots are closed and some guarded. you will be trespassed and fined because as I was told yesterday the parking lot is "private property" . be good little citizens today and OBEY  #commiekate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ACTBrigitte: Vaccine passports would be the end of freedom in this country! #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@h3h3productions hay potty mouth maybe you should read some science!   https://t.co/cw0Jf9SUQD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@painterly111 @ACTforAmerica @ACTBrigitte yet the CDC, HHS and NIH have all admitted the vaccine does NOT stop the spread. so what exactly are you saying here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trumpetytrump0: I urge all young people to share this document. #NoVaccinePassports https://t.co/ykP3TJ5y1t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Corporate Boycott starts now from my house... https://t.co/1uf0XOOPaq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll have what Kentucky is serving up! #nomandates  https://t.co/WaHeWvomEt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @govkristinoem: A vaccine passport is 100% hypocritical coming from those who oppose voter ID. But its entirely predictable after the o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ND5zannAsy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qYek0brsSg @MayorGallego  wants to take city of Phoenix employees time away from family to guard OUR park parking lots. So nice to know where your tax dollars are going this weekend. enjoy your parks but you can only park on the street!  @GetMeRoss @JosephChaplik]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/n76sdOS5J9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GetMeRoss: Daily reminder that @MayorGallego is a complete moron.  Take the L, just take it. This is silly KW https://t.co/0PMIKGBeon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ASU_CRU omg.. she better not even show her face back in AZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GetMeRoss Ducey needs to do this ASAP!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Surabees: 1: THREAD  Want to stop the vaccine passport?  Take a page from the left  start calling/tweeting America's biggest airlines,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KennyFitzpatr13 @Surabees oh boy have you been indoctrinated!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[beautiful work @JosephChaplik @GetMeRoss https://t.co/K1JY8m6ie5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mitchell_Bay7: Who walks around with a sticker? Answer: 5-year-olds  adult virtue signalers. https://t.co/yjVnX5yJdz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BretRbrts @JVarCont2 is it being amended?  I know our state director for NVIC is trying to get in contact with you. hopefully our group can support the final bill. we love your passion on this issue. I will email you her information.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NVICLoeDown: Factory Mix-Up Ruins Up to 15 Million Vaccine Doses From Johnson  Johnson  - https://t.co/d4m536fXp3  A manufacturing sub]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @annavh14: @mpsaz You obviously do not realize how discrimatory this is.  You either allow all volunteers or none.  This is absolutely a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How would it impact you if your suppliers required you to get a covid vaccine to do business with them?   If you are in healthcare or are school employees, we'd love a letter from you as well.  Find your legislators: https://t.co/X6JEkUArQn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also, if you are a business owner and against mandated vaccines for you, your employees and your customers, please write that in your emails as well!   Please explain how a vaccine mandate for businesses would impact you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Explain how you and your family would be effected by businesses requiring Vaccine Passports. Groceries? Sports for your kids? Gas for your car? Violating your individual rights, health privacy...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoanneOsborne8 as a Christian I hope that you truly see the truth in all of this. while I appreciate you supporting good bills I see you also pushing hard for this Expieramental MRNA vaccine which as believers in christ we should really consider hard before taking it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewHClark: President Trump calls out Biden's plan for a $2 TRILLION tax hike on U.S. workers  businesses.   "Biden promised to 'bui]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JordanSchachtel: Also important to note that your vaccine pass eligibility expires 90 days after last dose,  you're only eligible begi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[where there is risk, there must be choice.  #nomandates #novaccinepassports  #idonotconsent https://t.co/5fFwcdD0r2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SparkyPatriot: 53 year old friend takes the vaccine, less than 24 hours later in the hospital with fluid and inflammation around the he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mitchell_Bay7: Just called the Govs office for clarification on the Pima County mask mandate. Per his office, @dougducey order superse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ThatParentP4P: #HB2190 #VaccinePassportBan  @BretRbrts  gives the details to @GarretLewis   https://t.co/qEcjfBxN8w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BusyDrT: Will these type of testing results be recorded as vaccinated versus unvaccinated when new positive results are reported?  They]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MommyLobbyAZ @BretRbrts Where is the Bill with the new language. that link above is not it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lindama51800814 @lifebiomedguru @and_kell you really don't want to know, it's bad! real bad!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dwiggy333 @lifebiomedguru run by HHS and 10x worse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BretRbrts Thank you Representative Roberts!  we need this to fly thru and Ducey better sign this one. Calling all Senators thus am in Commitee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HB2190 will be heard today in appropriations. Call your Senators and tell them to support this bill. https://t.co/L19Fkig41W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lifebiomedguru: If businesses require #passports, I don't want their services or products.  Respect choice.  PEOPLE die and are injured]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>