<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld BBC fake news propaganda bullshit https://t.co/pyIRYmk6rg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld BBC fact checking remember WMDs and Iraq? Remember Brexit and we're all doomed, remember start of Covid and we're all going to die. BBC is dead in the water. Cancel your licence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews A poster boy for being the biggest C..T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarroniDean They're all transgender. Before and after pics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Same as the BBCs. Non existent . Along with labor. All corrupt spineless scum. Aided by a corrupt media which is why MSM is dying.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UnityNewsNet: This image shows the will of the people cannot be broken. Come the Summer ALL Coronavirus laws must be repealed or else w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StewartLopez14 @BBCWorld For a virus with a 99% survival rate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld So why are we letting people from  India into the U.K. then? On I know. Perfect excuse to lock everyone down in October destroying even more lives and pushing the agenda further.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulaLoud50 @CaligirlLeftie @Chrissy_2697 Same here. My work makes me meet new people on a daily basis. I can't connect or hang out with anyone as soon as they mention the rona and start spouting media propaganda . Occasionally I meet someone who knows what's really going on. It's a breath of fresh air.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews What a fucking pathetic nation we have become]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheGsUnit @RexChapman Shame he didn't have a light]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: Blair is a war criminal cunt that if I were ever diagnosed as terminal, would visit.   When he meets his demise, even the d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrissy_2697 I know, it drives me nuts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrissy_2697 Or just regular people who still have the ability to think for themselves and question what they're told, people who have been lied to so often by govt and media that it's only natural to distrust them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock @LennyHenry @davidwalliams @ElizabethHurley @eltonofficial https://t.co/avfDzqyl2m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock @LennyHenry @davidwalliams @ElizabethHurley @eltonofficial So why are the manufacturers immune from any prosecution ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews All the idiots waiting for the tv to tell them what to do. 16th May 'dangerous' keep masks on. 17th May, 'ok danger gone' wtf. So sick of this pathetic society]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld I'd say Florida or Texas would be a great place. Sydney also didn't fall for the bullshit. Basically anywhere but shithole communist U.K. and it's society of obedient drones.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KingBobIIV @StopTCensorship Worked the whole year, no mask, never used hand sanitiser, never social distanced. Still waiting to catch this deadly and highly contagious virus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews How about no masks and cheap fairs? Your compliance prolongs this bullshit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld All you people brainwashed by fear I'm pretty sure they'll be as fine as the thousands who marched in London the other week. Try unplugging yourself from the tv for a week or two, the virus will soon disappear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@robinmonotti2 @StopTCensorship Florida have their shit together. May emigrate there. Anything's better than communist U.K.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThomasDoak3 @BBCNews ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@leadershipindex @BBCNews It's called freedom of speech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews And I bet none of them will catch anything. Just like the 100,000 who marched in London , all fine. I wonder why? because Covid isn't deadly and highly contagious that's why.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@toryboypierce So they have an excuse for the next lockdown, and the one after that...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KismetandHope The science isn't corrupt, it's the people pushing it get corrupted]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld More fake manipulated news all you  are lapping up on here. Asking no questions? 'Karma' 'didn't trust in science ' . Fuck me people just sit in front of the BBC and dribble.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WoodySens19 @BBCWorld God provided vaccines?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Sure like the thousands of people with underlying conditions who supposedly died from Covid  more bullshit propaganda for the to lap up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock The virtue signalling on here is amazing.....'look at me everyone, I got mine.Matt, Matt look at me' .what the fuck]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mcfc__ste @MattHancock Like Matt or anyone else really gives a shit 'hey everyone look at me, look at me, I'm doing my bit, I'm complying..look at me everyone' ffs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GillianMcKeith @Keir_Starmer We need a new party. Or on the ballot sheet a box you can tick with 'none of the above, they are all corrupt']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theboyjai Just priming us for the next lockdown excuse in October. And guess what? All those vaccines you took! Well you're going to need more because of the 'India variant ' and this time everyone has to have it because those selfish people who refused have made it worse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sophiecbrr: If the government REALLY cared about your health and is willing to use authoritarian power to force it, then the war would]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock You need arresting. Can't wait for all the law suits to start kicking in.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garyphillips19 @Mailman92249262 @MattHancock The fact you're only having it because you believe your life will return to normal speaks volumes about you. You're the sort of person if the govt says you need to go suck your neighbours dick to get your holiday this year you'd do it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexasige1 @ianbrown67 @MattHancock It's called 'virtue signalling'. All these pricks are at it, buying into the bullshit they're saving the world. It fullfills their otherwise empty lives]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ianbrown67 @MattHancock https://t.co/0nbUHODV1I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock So why aren't  all freedoms returned then? You know full well the plan by your globalist masters Matt. There is no 'going back to normal'. Vaccine is a waste of time. It just lines your pockets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock You had an injection of saline Matt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrisb1993 @BillScrotum @duggo41 @darrenmark69 https://t.co/ss8O7tdCHy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrisb1993 @duggo41 @darrenmark69 https://t.co/SviUQa63Xe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock https://t.co/MpGdQPEE8Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrisb1993 @duggo41 @darrenmark69 Did they lockdown the whole country and destroy everyone's lives over aids and try and force vaccines on everyone over aids]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@crbarnes001 I'm pretty sure people would go to fema camps if told to. The amount of apathetic, non thinking mouth breathers in society is pretty scary]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Anyone else see reoccurring themes in the way the BBC reports? Doesn't it make you question the information you're spoonfed from sources that constantly lie to you? Remember WMDs? Iraq? Why do you still believe this bullshit?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrisb1993 @BillScrotum @duggo41 @darrenmark69 That's funny. You can go on gov.U.K. And put in your postcode and check how many people have died purely from Covid where you live. In my town of 12,000 there were 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Chrisb1993 @duggo41 @darrenmark69 hundred thousand haven't died 'from' Covid , they died 'with' Covid . Big difference . Maybe hard for you to understand or contemplate. Then the ones that died 'with' Covid were tested by a system proven to give false positives. Unplug yourself from BBC and govt propaganda ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock All the virtue signallers on here ooh look at me, I got mine sir. Look at me, I'm going tomorrow for my second. Anything you say sir! Fukin pathetic society]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Iromg @MattHancock I'd like to inject him with something]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock But did you really get the jab? I highly doubt it. That wasn't a regular nurse holding the syringe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Who makes up this bollocks?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCPolitics @BBCNews They're all pathetic . Labor/conservative, two cheeks on the same arse. None have your interests at heart. Stop thinking these people care about you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 Sounds a bit like WMDs and the Iraq war. All lies and b/s to push an illegal agenda. Amazing how quick people choose to forget. What makes you think the govt and media aren't lying to you this time?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Probably pushed out because he's a middle aged white guy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews today's society....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock https://t.co/XuzUdhnNeE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Adam_Stratford_ Have taught my boy since 15 it's ok to question authority. He's read some of Icke's books at 18. He knows what's really going on at 20]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld so the people who actually question it and do their own research instead of blindly listening to the man on the tv understand exactly how corrupt Pfizer is, and you think they'll listen to them let's go into Pfizer's history and law suits shall we, yeah! I trust them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCPolitics @BBCNews More filth in the corporation then.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock Such a tit how can you like this corrupt pathetic excuse for a human]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StewartLopez14 @BBCWorld  I lived there through the whole Trump presidency . My business did fine and my life was fine. The fool is a puppet completely owned by China]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Another hand picked few to push the narrative . 'random Americans' ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @YardleyShooting: Having been both psychologist  soldier, I can see what the Govt are trying to achieve with the Orwellian covid campai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock How about banning invasive Covid tests and injections on children seen as it barely affects them. That's child abuse. But no, that's your money maker isn't it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld You know over 20,000 people die daily in India from poverty related diseases right? Yet a few thousand from so called Covid and you're all over it. Just putting things into perspective]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock @pfizer @BioNTech_Group No wonder you have to push fear and lies. You now have 60 million doses you need to get rid of I have no idea how people can't see through your bullshit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: THIS IS HOW YOU DO IT............... #NoMasksInClass]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Meanwhile in Florida a packed ufc event of over 15,000 with no masks or vaccine passport. Just getting on with life. https://t.co/7SlzJKf7BA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @garethicke: This will seriously trigger the Covidians.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yeyDSzI7ow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 On you tube. Out of 56 million population 277 were watching the guardian stream]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Let's see how the vaccine works out for you in lockdown from the 'India variant' bullshit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews https://t.co/eQb8hlv1jG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld https://t.co/ZXsTli7RHe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Of course it is. That's because it's a globalists agenda.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Cancel your tv licence. This pandemic will soon disappear]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Bet you're glad you all rushed out and had your vaccine, right?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld How about reporting on Florida or Texas! Gotta keep the fear propaganda going don't you?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCPolitics @BBCNews Ohhh 'fact checked'glad that's sorted then]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Maggie247 @BBCNews nothing to see here. The media never lies or manipulates https://t.co/r8LLh123PE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Why concentrate on India? Why not focus on Florida or Texas?. Remember people, the media want to keep you in a perpetual state of fear, not hope. It seems to be working]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@smifffyd @smith_freddo @BBCNews @bbclaurak @mariannaspring the BBC and govt are the biggest liars out there. I suppose you still believe we invaded Iraq because we cared about the people. Remember WMDs and that monumental lie? Same shit now. You should move to China, you'll like it there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@smifffyd @BBCNews @bbclaurak @mariannaspring Oh god . Another drone who lacks the ability to think for themselves . Must censor anyone who questions the narrative . Unplug yourself from the tv.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews And so it begins. Just as predicted. The excuse to lock down everyone in a couple of months and push the agenda even further. Bet you're glad you rushed to take the experimental gene therapy . Seems like you're back to square one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock You tube right now. Matt Wancock live Covid briefing. Out of a population of over 56 million, 277 are watching]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld 50% ! That's pathetic . And you're all lined up like thinking your life will get back to normal. Needs to be at least 90% for me to even consider it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Check out the date! Question everything https://t.co/5mXemOFzKk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Look at that photo not set up or anything]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCIndia We know that's it's more overhyped fear propaganda to push the reason to keep locking people down this winter. Photoshopped pictures, selective interviews and fear from the media. Your compliance is prolonging this bullshit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCIndia @BBCNews Nothing to  see here...... just prepping the so they're convinced when we lock you all down again this winter https://t.co/bqPnSEJ8dc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Really? My mother has been to AE twice within a week after her second jab with severe breathing difficulties . My friend from Sydney had Bell's palsy after his dose. Not made up. Maybe it wasn't the vaccine. But extremely coincidental . Just saying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dawnsearlylig10 @BBCWorld Any parent making their child wear a mask and get tested without consent is a bad parent. How about that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MyOpini55028743 @BBCWorld Having the choice of being in Florida experiencing the amazing wildlife not wearing masks and being free and healthy or sitting watching the BBC being spoonfed fear and propaganda eating shit food and never seeing the sun, I know which one I'd choose.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@R3FX_ @G00ner5 @NoHartAnthony @Debra11661905 @Pfizer_UK @DiscoveryPark_ Let's see how the vaccine works out for everyone this winterback in lockdown with a fake 'variant from India' scare and now when you get a simple cold it will be life threatening because your immune system is on overload. Let's see how free all the vaccinated really are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MyOpini55028743 @michicaligirl @BBCWorld surely you're a bot. No one can be this retarded.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MyOpini55028743 @BBCWorld It's the people who believe the BBC who are stupid. Florida's been doing fine fully opened. England is a nation of dumbed down individuals still relying on the media and govt to hold their hands through life . The media are the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MendlerGary @BBCWorld Unplug yourself from your tv covidiotthat's not reality. Florida and Texas have been doing fine the last year while fully opened. Because they're not spineless sheep over there who rely on govt and media to control their lives.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SayingNiceStuff @RealTayoKuti @BBCWorld So brainwashed by tv. I've never worn a mask, never used sanitizer, worked the whole year surrounded by tonnes of people. So why have my family or I never had your so called 'deadly and highly contagious 'virus. Maybe my immune system is doing its job .]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>