<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PhilaUnion: ON. TO. THE. SEMIS.  Full 90' battle for this one - we take the series on 4 - 1 aggregate!  #DOOP https://t.co/oNg5rZt2GA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Braves: .@theynoaa is the first pitcher in Atlanta franchise history to homer in back-to-back games, and the first to do so at all for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The nflpa continues to tell the players not to show up to team activities or come to the facility and this happens. https://t.co/8ve6mh3OTy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If psg dont win Ligue 1, would the PSG chairman overreact and sack pochettino since they had a worse season despite him being in for 5 months?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Game, set and match. Very idiotic by di maria who has had a horrific game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mbappe needs to be on at half time for Di Maria.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mbappe is injured and cant see him having a Lucas moura like moment in Amsterdam for Spurs 2 years ago.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant see psg getting 3 goals here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Neymar and icardi gotta step up tonight https://t.co/NMY1SzXkX8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weather looks brutal at the ethiad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They need to let Ramsey and peters fight it out this year! https://t.co/nEdGopTdba]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheVolumeSports @marcuspeters @AqibTalib21 @bclark410]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Levy will be ecstatic to save money on not paying Jose anymore. Hopefully thatll get him to pay for a good manager https://t.co/K6k3ibQszB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ASRomaEN:     The club are delighted to announce an agreement has been reached with Jose Mourinho for him to become our new he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lmao. Potter isnt ready for the job. Steve hitchen stinks https://t.co/RyvJIAYLLt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AaronWilson_NFL @MerrimackFB @DACOOP66 @CoachDanCurran Congrats Sam!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@B_Wi11s Definitely. Just sent you a DM.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@B_Wi11s Im going to vegas which you should try to come. If not, we ought to do another away game this year. I Can get a very good hotel rate too. If youre trying to do Philly or Washington, 2022, good chance we end up In Washington, Philly or the giants as the 9th away game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@B_Wi11s Away games are very fun! I Actually enjoy it more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marlon_humphrey Also invading every away stadium as always!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delaware going to the semifinals! https://t.co/52X6ix3XeK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DelawareFB: Still Here.  #BleedBlue302 #BlueHens https://t.co/vb0WdoSUU5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sonny! What a finish!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bale hat trick!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bale!!! Spurs better activate that option for next season!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bale!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StanCollymore They could play it on the 16th. Move west Brom-Liverpool to the 12th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wouldnt surprise me if this game gets played on may 16th and west Brom-Liverpool gets moved to May 12th. https://t.co/i1A553htFZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChrisEriksen8 @Inter Congrats Christian!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lauriewhitwell: Groundsman inspecting pitch for possible damage. Reports of broadcast cameras being smashed. Serious doubts over match]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dude was chillin on the net at old trafford, another person kicked a ball into the net and knocked him off  https://t.co/gQDCWZtkoH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StanCollymore: Huge story developing.  Man United fans have got into the Old Trafford compound and onto the pitch.   https://t.co/8AyLr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UtdXclusive: | LOUD AND CLEAR   #MUFC #GetOutGlazers  https://t.co/ejL9NrQ5A6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricNjiiru: Scenes at Old Trafford. Call off the game and give @LFC the points https://t.co/tyPj2km4Ss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gezz_MUFC: On the pitch. #GlazersOut https://t.co/Q7n6Z9Jq1d]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[United protestors for on the pitch and threw a tripod on the pitch ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ryleyjackx: So United fans have stormed Old Trafford and..... https://t.co/e9czq7qoGa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StretfordPaddck: #MUFC fans protesting outside the Lowry Hotel  https://t.co/hg78rOB1ue]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing! Go kill it in Carolina brother https://t.co/6tk4D10LKN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nfldraftscout: Tylan Wallace to the #Ravens is a great pick. GREAT.  He's a tough SOB with very good hands. Knee injury in 2019 is nota]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jaguars Lets go JJs!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodness. 1 was drafted in the first round, 1 was a 5th round pick, 1 was a 6th round, 2 were undrafted and Wilson was the worst first round draft pick ever. https://t.co/xxARRicuVu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Steve6utteridge: Pre Khan ownership, Fulham hadnt been relegated for 20 years. Weve now had 3 in 7 seasons. Its long overdue that yo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Awesome! Hell of a back. Will be a good back up to cam Akers https://t.co/WhVcmJpxwL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@E_Dilla @TonyKhan Lets go JJs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love it! Especially for a short yardage Situations! https://t.co/wZniVU7TJ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MikeClayNFL: The Ravens drafted another Patrick Ricard by grabbing FB/TE/DT Ben Mason in Round 5.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @colecubelic: HELLO FULLBACK!! Its clobberin time for @UMichFootball Ben Mason. https://t.co/cyWje7B91O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ravens must have Kelly or Villanueva lined up for them not to address tackle in the draft. Actually surprised they didnt address running back as well today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will be a huge asset as a nickel corner especially if the ravens cant rely on tavon to be healthy https://t.co/xU2Q7WyiM1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @gdowning14: Getting Shaun Wade in the 5th round is a tremendous pick by the Ravens.   He was considered a first rounder going into the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A much better nickel corner than outside, could see Wade potentially being a Tavon Young replacement in 2022.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If we can get 2019 Shaun Wade, this will be a fantastic pick for the Ravens, especially the value. Potential 1st rd pick  if he declared in 2020.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The ravens need to sign Justin houston on Monday https://t.co/xyK8BRJGbO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lj_era8: @Primetime_jet  @Dev_Duv5  @jamesproche3  @Mandrews_81  wit My OGz already I cant wait ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dwright0660 Bateman, brown and Watkins are locks. Cant see them cutting Wallace as a 4th rd pick. I wouldnt be surprised to see Boykin possibly move over to TE. Cain either PS or cut, will depend who they value more in special teams for duvernay/proche.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They better have plenty of cleats for him to throw against receivers https://t.co/BZeSV2AP8M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dwright0660 Will be interesting to say the least. Id be nervous if I were Boykin and proche]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dig it. Good route runner and makes big plays https://t.co/IWqARddwIE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pulte I have them on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats a football player! https://t.co/Nw24F48f6t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PFF_College: Ravens newest guard Ben Cleveland across four seasons at Georgia:   Pass-blocking snaps: 741  QBs hits allowed: 3  QB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jeffzrebiec: Ben Cleveland likely competes for starting LG job from Day One. That again would lead to Bradley Bozeman moving over to ce]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yikes. https://t.co/zkzb83EPgv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hopefully Wyatt Davis or Quinn Meinerz make it to 94 https://t.co/LnVfUpWngW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That chiefs O line will be disgusting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColinCowherd: Between free agency and this draft  the @Browns have done a remarkable job improving their defensive talent. Really smar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rondale Moore in Arizona is going to be nasty!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great value for Walker little at 45. Last year he would have been a top 10 pick if he declared.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very good by Philly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great pick up by the jets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wouldnt mind seeing the ravens beating a packers team without Aaron Rodgers again. https://t.co/6UQHm2UcDV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ravens: We have exercised the fifth-year option for QB Lamar Jackson.   : https://t.co/vxN9yJEMhO https://t.co/0hrIxZZNlw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another terrible red by premier league refs and VAR. another early red for Southampton. Another 0-9 defeat coming?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CashApp $kyleterp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wonder if the Ravens still sign Justin houston and/or Dennis Kelly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thespursweb: Ralf Rangnick has been offered the Tottenham job. [BILD] https://t.co/sSf8HiXJNK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LedoPizza:  #FridayFeeling Giveaway    RETWEET  FOLLOW US  To be entered to win a $50 #LedoPizza Gift card  autographed John Carl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kansas actually got themselves a good football coach https://t.co/w5c2cRDJs9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @coachjfranklin: @PennStateFball @Ravens @JaysonOweh The @Ravens are getting one heck of a young man  football player! @JaysonOweh you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Law_DT: Tottenham sacking Mauricio Pochettino instead of backing him was one of the worst decisions ever. And now Daniel Levy is s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Graham potter or Scott Parker are not ready for the role. Need rangnick or allegri https://t.co/CTcwcmfOm3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another one bites the dust https://t.co/QLvb9UZdXG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Definitely a need! Hopefully he changes the ravens draft history of receivers. https://t.co/uScHVtgi4f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ravens: Bateman to Baltimore   Welcome to the family, @R_bateman2  https://t.co/AG1b0HImFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fantastic pick by Jacksonville]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fantastic pick by Arizona!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AroundTheNFL Who?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How did New York get more for their pick than Dallas? https://t.co/wawEVCnnm1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RedditCFB The owner is a owner of a wrestling company]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Awesome for Unai emery for getting that 1st leg win against arsenal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man U winning europa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[San Fran going to trade 3 to Green Bay for Rodgers?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orioles win!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 teams would be interesting https://t.co/zJGXedpk1j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LedoPizza:  Draft Day GIVEAWAY   RETWEET  FOLLOW  for a chance to win a $50 #LEDOPIZZA GIFT CARD! (2 winners picked at 9pm on 4/29/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Draft day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RBLeipzig_EN: Jesse Marsch will become our new head coach from the 2021/22 season!   He takes over from Julian #Nagelsmann, who is join]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daka is going to kill it at Leipzig https://t.co/Be4CT9DH8U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @edballs: Ed Balls      #10LongYears https://t.co/T4rubBUUK8]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>