<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UHTPodcast: For anyone on O2, you can get 90 day free access to @TheAthleticUK via Priorities  Worthwhile doing for the in depth Everto]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: Back by popular demand: its the Everton squad audit w/ the excellent @insightMrkt   A crucial summer ahead again for #E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stephenscott10: Signed up to abseil down the #liverpool cathedral for @AlderHeyCharity if you would like to donate would appreciate it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SJohnsonSport: Exclusive with Nigel James, dad to @reecejames_24  @laurenjamess22:  dealing with racism  backing social media boycot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: Ancelotti called out the attitude of his players after the defeat to Villa. But the other issues in this #EFC team shoul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DCT1962 yep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball yep it does mate. Could do with both]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not him again but someone with some of his attributes...  #Everton's midfield was found wanting again on Saturday.  Carlo Ancelotti may well add that to his list of summer to-do's  https://t.co/nq92jK6QJb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewRuscoe: PLEASE RETWEET | If you fancy an opportunity playing at tier 2 level of Welsh Football with @ptfcseasiders then please co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK: https://t.co/Wdpud5somo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[STOP ONLINE ABUSE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RJConway92: This piece is free.   This piece is discussing just a fraction of the damage and pure pain social media abuse causes.   Thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinBuckland1 @DAHughes_ @Tony_Scott11 @EFCMatt1 @ATNCAST look at him scurrying to deny his WD roots. Sad.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DAHughes_ @GavinBuckland1 @Tony_Scott11 @EFCMatt1 @ATNCAST you can have some as well if you want mouth. Wait for the smoke off these lanvins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinBuckland1 @DAHughes_ @Tony_Scott11 @EFCMatt1 @ATNCAST I'm pulling on the purple blazer as we speak to go and sort out Tony hess hess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EFCMatt1 @ATNCAST @GavinBuckland1 @Tony_Scott11 Newcastle (twice), Fulham, Burnley, Leeds....wasted opps mate!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball @Paddy_Boyland Good point. I think it's his time]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theesk Congratulations Paul you must be rightly a v proud man today]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland:  New Gwlad Tidings   A boost in the race for Europe  What's behind Pickford's improvement?  Do Everton need more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland @MattJFootball I nearly lost it when the script banged on about mowing your crop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BehindTheLife3 hahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis sessions back at Finch Farm with Davide Ancelotti  Baines  Frustration but determination to learn    Two managers with different agendas cant fit him in   Why Antony Gordons loan to #PNE failed  what next for #Evertons gifted winger   https://t.co/wkxiFIscOp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ATNCAST: New episode just in    @GavinBuckland1   @GregOK  @Tony_Scott11  Coleman contact, Max Aarons latest, marque signing in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DAHughes_: When Ross Barkley left Everton in unceremonious circumstances at 24, he stated that he wanted to be a 'world-class midfielde]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm sure a lot of #Everton fans will be rooting for @FGRFC_Official now that Jimmy Ball, son of one of the best players to pull on the royal blue shirt, is leading their promotion charge.  Lovely interview w/@Paddy_Boyland   https://t.co/Hi7sKLfhLI https://t.co/4DSyNFedQW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: Jimmy Ball is following in the footsteps of dad Alan Jr  grandad Alan Sr by managing in the Football League   Pleasure]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @josephmdurso: New: Sportsbet just signed a deal worth tens of millions with Southampton FC and also sponsors Arsenal.  Its business, hi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mjshrimper: Daniel Ek is rich, smart  , as far as Arsenal fans are concerned, has all the top tunes. But Stan Kroenke  the other US o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A refocused and maturing Jordan Pickford has been a growing positive for #Everton   https://t.co/MqpNOYbFk8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TherealKarlB 100% pal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brilliant way of telling a story this - nice work @domokeeffe   https://t.co/7WAwdmycZs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The best of us'  https://t.co/Jo4TnVYzqi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK: There was plenty of luck involved but Carlo Ancelotti was rewarded for being bold as #Everton picked up three points at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Staniforth7 Really? Was he the same?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weekend emphatically not ruined . #Everton made their own luck at the Emirates and saw another psychological barrier dismantled.  Thoughts on last night   https://t.co/R1qPSzFbNZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[That's a massive result at Arsenal for #Everton both in its historic Premier League context down there and for their Europa League ambitions.  Done the North London double this season! Who'd have thought it!?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hes a throw back. Hed go around booting the older lads in training and didnt give a monkeys  Another perfectly timed but fierce tackle from Ben Godfrey on Ceballos.  What a player #EFC   https://t.co/CRKYInjnXl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK: We spoke to some who experienced playing next to Ben Godfrey before his remarkable first term at Goodison Park.... #EFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GavinBuckland1 @DAHughes_ Better that you couldnt see most of it pal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DupontKoo @Paddy_Boyland Thanks Dupont. I can see him being a future leader definitely]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben came in and to be honest he ruffled a few feathers. He was running around in training throwing in big tackles. You know the phrase train as you play, well, he was doing that."   Team-mates recall what it's like to play with Ben Godfrey #EFC  https://t.co/xsF0KfSzBZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@scousemanblue yeah tend to agree mate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Trains as he plays - booting old pros in the air  Wardrobe shoulders   Wants to win every ball, always   Headers that go 50m, strikers in a heap  Asked some people who know what its like being in the same team as Ben Godfrey #EFC   https://t.co/CRKYInjnXl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ATNCAST: New podcast just dropped   @GregOK  @Tony_Scott11  @DAHughes_    Carlos comments on ESL  Moshiri's FFP claim  Rating]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK:     "Among the 14 [other clubs] Everton were kind of the leaders, the pioneers."  @Paddy_Boyland and @GregOK ha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelaniePrentic2: Dixie was gifted a Weatherall overcoat as they wanted him to endorse their product.  He said hed be happy to do that,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["My immediate reaction was they are joking. Is it a joke?" Ancelotti tells BBC sport about  his #ESL response]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: New Gwlad Tidings   Thoughts on Brands new deal - how successful has he been  what does he need to do this summer?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Everton led the fight against ESL with passion: heres the reasons why they took such a public, vocal stance (some known, some not so much)    W/@Paddy_Boyland   https://t.co/UEeLrDvWgk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I read this - only sitting down to agree now two months before his deal ends - as a generally satisfied endorsement of Brands' performance, with some caveats which weren't enough in the end to make Moshiri want to change direction #EFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marcel Brands has signed a new deal to remain in role as #Everton's DoF until 2024  https://t.co/5yc1xJUVF3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK:  Clubs pushed for points deductions for the 'six'  'How can we work with these people again?'  #MCFC players confront]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @squires_david: https://t.co/naJTDXV1TV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @philkecho: If anyone writes a book about this sorry affair one day, then they could do worse than look to Everton's statement, from thi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ATNCAST: New podcast dropped tonight   'The Old Blues' have their say on European super league, LFC  MUFC owners, Farhad Moshiri and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mjshrimper: You know they have just sneaked a 36-team Champions League with 225 games  VIP passes for two ESL-type clubs past the lot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamCrafton_: COLUMN: Why did the Super League fail? It failed because the Dirty Dozen lost every possible stakeholder; the fans, the m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @honigstein: Earlier, I've put it to a German club official that the Super League 12 must have some really clever ideas to get around al]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DowntownFrank Im so sorry this happened. Hope your daughter is ok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: #EFC calling for ESL plans to be "immediately withdrawn". Talk about "preposterous arrogance" and betrayal of national g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@joeNnashville @embassydavies @JoeNBC @NashSevereWx @rogbennett I will check it out forthwith, thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: Everton were vehement in their opposition to Project Big Picture  Dont expect this to be any different  @TheAthleticUK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK:  Players bored  untested in training  Assistant Joao Sacramento unpopular  Club unhappy with Mourinhos criticism]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @susie_dent: Word of the day is ingordigiousness: extreme greed; an insatiable desire for wealth at any cost.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The chance to dream, improve and strive for the elite stage via sporting merit is everything to him.   Let's hope players from the big 6 make their voices heard too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richarlison leading by example there with that RT.   This is a lad who dragged himself from poverty, knock-backs and rejection to forge a career thousands of miles from home  is still pushing to make it to the top and dream of CL football (hopefully with #Everton)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @David_Ornstein: Breaking: Jose Mourinho sacked as Tottenham manager @TheAthleticUK #THFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK:  Agreement between 12 clubs not contractually binding but significant statement of intent  #RMCF, #MUFC, #LFC  #AFC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DTathletic: Yaya Toure wants to make his peace with Pep Guardiola  He's even written a letter of apology - but Pep has blanked him  Tod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: Starting to see evidence that Marcel Brands' work with the #EFC academy is paying off  U18s have beaten Man City  Chels]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ATNCAST: Podcast  The Everton v Tottenham Hotspur match preview with @DAHughes_ @GregOK  @Tony_Scott11   Listen in  https://t.co/Ej]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AMcMonniesSport Thanks for such generous comments Alex. Glad you enjoyed it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @abbyellin: My #NYT story today. Uplilting. #Covid #Pandemic #goodnews https://t.co/niFY4wSJ13]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland:        The case for pace   How can Everton make more of James brilliance?   A timely injury boost a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK:  Poch v Pep  Qatar v Abu Dhabi  Possession v counter-attack   Zidane v Tuchel  43 v 3  Experience v invention  Wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If #Everton dont make the European places this season it will represent a failure and the captain  manager know it. Now they need to turn that fear into fight and urgency   https://t.co/W9x3pgGpjc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gbamin update #EFC   https://t.co/oMNJQiY22e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshieMcsquashy must be - how annoying!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshieMcsquashy why have they had to do that mate? The soundtrack was one of the great things about Scrubs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Worville: Everton are the side with the most injuries in the Premier League at the moment   Big Sam's West Brom only have 37 year-old]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EFCMatt1 @ATNCAST @GavinBuckland1 @Tony_Scott11 Cheers pal - I think it depends how Friday goes now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: In total, 24 #EFC players have spent time on the sidelines this season, missing a combined 149 games.   A huge total mad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: Ancelotti says the season is over for JP Gbamin. Player fell on his knee and he suffered a medial ligament injury. Mina]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking but sadly true - Jean-Philippe Gbamin has been injured again.   It's early doors with assessment but he may not play again this season.  Latest here  #EFC #Gbamin  https://t.co/ZgIjpc4tFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: A number of #EFC youngsters have caught the eye of Marcel Brands after shining in the Youth Cup. Some have already stepp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@azulfeehely @leonotjim Cheers pal - great piece]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidFo38145364 No. Just that I disagree with the sentiment hes not good enough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland @CBobblers1878 Much appreciated lads]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Paddy_Boyland: His return was described by Evertons head of medical as one of the best moments of my working life  But what can JP G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GJS41991 tbf the piece is defensive with caveats - as in, given time to think one-on-one he really has to improve. He's only just 24.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In staunch defence of Dominic Calvert-Lewin. A column. #EFC  https://t.co/vFGW1Eom0S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK: Harry Kane wants to leave #THFC - but can he?  Will push for a move if #THFC miss out on #UCL  #MCFC  #MUFC see him a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Popular in NFL, NHL  weighlighting for years Clears the sinuses and wobbles the head Shouldn't be used post concussion  The inside story of football's new habit for pre-game ammonia inhalants #EFC   https://t.co/ZalCvgH7Z3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@themindmapco @SkyNews ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Tony_Scott11: All on eyes on Liverpool over the next three days.  Aintee is going to be very different this year.  My piece on Scousers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK: Everton players such as Richarlison have been seen using smelling salts before a game as a marginal gain performance b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Was intrigued by what Richarlison, Holgate  other Premier League stars are sniffing in the tunnel before games so found out #EFC   Smelling salts are the new nose strips Vaporub: A short sharp shock to the senses Clears airways 0 proven benefits  https://t.co/SXDgx5NNyJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JT_Travels @jamesdrodriguez Cheers mate - technically he's one of the best I've ever seen play for Everton, if not THE best.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BostonBluenose Ahh ok got you. Thanks for explaining. Yeah next season will be fine its two with option of third]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BostonBluenose sorry mate I don't understand the question?]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>