<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[No surprise here...  The company said its vaccine generated $3.5 billion in revenue in the first three months of this year. https://t.co/uIANsprMee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJA1985 @PatrickGman @sallyKP You're an idiot... Database of all ivermectin COVID-19 studies. 90 studies, 49 peer reviewed, 53 with results comparing treatment and control groups. Submit updates/corrections below. FLCCC provides treatment recommendations.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ddunsky @deonandan Yeah with the unscientific garbage data modelling, it's been pseudoscientific since day 1.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DawnPea60654643 @DonkeyKonging @deonandan It is experimental - long term trials have not been completed and they've never had a successful mRNA vaccine in the past.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deonandan Too bad you like your ignorance... https://t.co/VaINiHIVvF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: India has 1.4B pop. Poor country with minimal health care infrastructure. Funeral pyres is a Hindu tradition. Makes for]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJA1985 @PatrickGman @sallyKP https://t.co/YDFkcbkPmD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PatrickGman @CJA1985 @sallyKP No the selfish fools are the idiots who blindly follow the government dogma. The government has been lying since day 1 but you're too entrenched to see it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJA1985 @PatrickGman @sallyKP You're a fucking idiot! Look it up, the information is readily available to everyone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulMitchell_AB Epidemiology is the scourge of the medical profession - no one should listen to idiot epidemiologists - get stuffed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KellyMartin_UK People who I believed to be reasonably intelligent have lost all sense during this debacle.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@heidi12312345 Immune]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ericaeliz067: Have you voted against the ONT lockdown extension yet? Results are close!! https://t.co/G5QrCPCJlx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SharkawyMD No one needs the vaccines - it is fully treatable except assholes such as you won't inform yourselves and you won't stand up to the government on behalf of your patients. Let's not forget that Mengele was a doctor too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JuliusRuechel: It was never abt churches, masks, or lockdowns. From day 1, it was a cultural battle abt whether we're still willing to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJA1985 @PatrickGman @sallyKP Look in the mirror when you use the word moron, if you're paying attention you'll note cases in India rose when they started mass vaccinations and stopped dispensing Ivermectin. https://t.co/vExBoMUK38]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ohthatstevenguy @AlbertaLeonidas @jkenney Supreme toxic stupidity - Kenney and all the Premiers should be subjected to competency hearings - they're acting like complete fucking idiots.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As warned by decades of studies masks are making people sick. Students are suffering a variety of mask related illness not the least of which is psychological. Making kids wear masks in school is child abuse. #TakeOffYourMask https://t.co/wBxFRbQkie]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fordnation is a heartless, soulless despot. #JailFordOpenOntario https://t.co/ckZjqvHxPI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChickFrmOntario Between 2000 and 4000 IU daily VitD, more if you are overweight or obese.  Add magnesium which aids VitD absorption and is critically important to heart health.  Add Quercetin to enhance your immune system response.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Propaganda - positive test results are not cases and anyone who dies within 28 days of a positive test has CV19 listed on the death certificate, regardless of the CoD. TPH is a criminal organization, amongst many other government agencies. https://t.co/cVwMzQk3tB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kahnkidz Supreme stupidity]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DBCooper8675309 @Bzubyk Garneau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@epdevilla https://t.co/pUNEgczy09]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Insanity! https://t.co/LjOehp37D5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ValValpuriam: Y'all know how to vote on this garbage...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpiggyMoon People who know this island will recognize its' iconic twin peaks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpiggyMoon https://t.co/ghj5qFUuS4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MatteaMerta: A friend in medical school now has to attend classes online because she is not taking the Cvid shot while everyone else is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CJA1985 @PatrickGman @sallyKP No it's reality, too bad you can't face it. Most people don't need the "vaccines" so getting it is just stupid. I trust my immune system to keep me safe from it just as I do with colds and flu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks to the CFIBs inaction... https://t.co/jEJjtMqcAh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sheeple... https://t.co/SxQhQDb6ZI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LysanderMurphy: Pigs gonna pig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope you realize you have been bamboozled. #FakeVaccines https://t.co/6Mn2AGNHv8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AZAugie @amolinadesigns @almaforarizona @pfizer Bullshit, produce the science that supports your statement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FairQuestions Thinking? Definitely not getting a vaccine for CV19 - aside from it being experimental the likelihood of me getting seriously ill from SARS-CoV-2 is very slim, so there's no point, especially when there's a 100% chance I will get a side-effect from the vaccine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Liberals are evil incarnate. Jail is too good for them; we need to bring back capital punishment. https://t.co/EFo39xOSKK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#DefundThePolice https://t.co/692xooG0ot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Leesa_marieee: @juliebeeeeee @SaskLass @elmontay @CTVKathyLe My 97 year old aunt had covid and barely had any symptoms and shes fine t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @emilia_suze: Absolutely    Its time for Fauci , the CDC to shut up with their nonsense  and time to stop pandering to bullying teachers]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VitD, magnesium, zinc and quercetin work synergistically to boost your immune system and quite possibly prevent CV19 infection. https://t.co/yotwiH4MD7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Undoubtedly true https://t.co/beLCWpzvyG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldWelsh16: Your weekly reminder that you are witnessing the largest social policy diaster in Canadian history.  And we have the num]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And always consider the source of any negativity. #WiseWords https://t.co/GKpKXPpzqZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolutely... https://t.co/WMC3A8sl7w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ford is fomenting an armed insurrection with talk such as this. There's no evidence of his bullshit statement and someone needs to haul him before the courts asap. Perhaps we need to inundate the RCMP and OPP with calls for his arrest. #JailFordOpenOntario https://t.co/uE2SaRdeED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jhutch43945987: Find out more!  Read the platform!   RT!  #PPC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And proceeded to ruin his chances for re-election in 2015, when Canadians voted him out. They didn't really want Turdope, they wanted rid of Harper, so you can blame the CPC for Turdope. Stop voting for the status quo, #VotePPC https://t.co/LT8JIBSqAt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Many theorized that the Covid-19 vaccines would affect fertility and its starting seem as though those conspiracy theories arent all that crazy." https://t.co/VaINiHrkE7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Their verdict is that there has never been a vaccine that has harmed as many people." https://t.co/cKSwbxvPKI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PaulMitchell_AB: This Covid-fascists goons are literally knocking on doors, were going into places of worship, were going into co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @erdocAA: The media cost Emily her life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boycott these assholes! https://t.co/7vDXj8m7NU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Willfully ignorant doctators... https://t.co/WAC0HX8nNt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@t7_linda @PooyaKazemi1983 All Public Health advice flies in the face of established science and they have done nothing to promote any kind of prevention. Public Health advice is killing more people than the virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PooyaKazemi1983 Why don't you start by explaining the mRNA gene therapy and the adenovirus cell manipulation. And explain why mRNA has been a dismal failure in the past and how it has changed with a rushed treatment. To say you're 110% pro-vaccine tells us you're another big pharma shill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excellent! Let's hope this is turning of the tide back to sanity. https://t.co/o2FX1sPr3O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tam should be fired; she's a danger to public health. Masks are ineffective protection from respiratory viruses in ANY environment!  https://t.co/gY3fTcXmz8 https://t.co/WP6Ac4tirT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Such irony... https://t.co/NJtukzYkHw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wholeheartedly agree! Now I know people are basically stupid. https://t.co/WQR0H4DkyU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government knows it can only push so far with closures, however, it can be ordered online so it is not society, it is totally on the government. Don't forget liquor stores are a cash cow. https://t.co/k70NTMzmqL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DiNovo is such a fucking idiot, it makes me wonder from which institute she escaped. https://t.co/uwex9Wzso9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one should pay any attention to the WHO; like our governments, they are trying to gaslight us. Time for people to stand up for their rights and put this evil back in its place. https://t.co/gSOvAQC3h5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JPLuisi1: The fact that this wasnt reported as Hundreds of anti-maskers... shows that the tied is turning.  #covid19]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rpoconnor: A federal cabinet full of unserious lightweights also has this utter embarrassment, whose conduct would be laughable if his]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The will of the people who are awake and willing to stand up for their rights is strong. Unfortunately we are in the minority; there are still far too many complacent sheeple for this to end soon. https://t.co/urghmVD5RR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You first! I assigned myself to the control group. BTW it is a criminal offense to promote an experimental treatment without giving patients informed consent, so why don't you inform all of us about the risks, etc? https://t.co/8RNPwwFCNj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CPSO is run by fascists and should be abolished. #EndMedicalFascism  https://t.co/gJLYDDxfn3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAnber: COVID is a virus thats slightly worse than the flu for the vast majority of people; at any given point is held by by less]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cara_zen_tales @E_vanLacey @alxyeee @RebelNewsOnline You're right, you idiots are far too numerous, but the vaccines will take care of that.  #EndTheLockdowns]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Golden_Pup: History and its narratives will spit on people who endorsed or turned a blind eye to the immense damage of lockdowns and th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When will we see crowds like this in Toronto? https://t.co/UPgplK4tv6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Too bad the majority of physicians don't take that commitment very seriously. https://t.co/LcnuhUEMmL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctors are making money hand over fist treating CoVID patients. #CanadaIsCorrupt https://t.co/tkugCpuNIO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NormalGuy223: Everyone in Canada who opposes lockdowns should be 100% behind Maxime Bernier right now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The complacency of the middle class is the kiss of death for Canada. #Sheeple #cdnpoli https://t.co/4y5yB0svJb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The RCMP is the modern day equivalent of the SS. https://t.co/d1jJkeUxwW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DrP_MD: I became a physician to promote health, scientific evidence and ethical advocacy for patients' interests.   If laws, regulation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roccogalatilaw Except for this... https://t.co/HaiCEHfEX7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EChin9331 @VancityReynolds @wick_22 @Cmdr_Hadfield @KidsHelpPhone Stop promoting experimental medical treatments; people are not being told the vaccines have not passed long term trials which means the government is violating the Nuremberg Code. Your tweet is criminal. #EndTheLockdowns https://t.co/paksIVSU4N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @laworfiction: Revealed IN COURT:  neither school nor govt conducted ANY assessment of the risk to children of harms of masks  unchall]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KPhysiotherapy @CBCToronto You're stupid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EileenOttawa @CBCToronto Data modelling is not science - it is predictive analytics which are only as good as the inputs. To date the OST models have been wildly inaccurate; not once have their predictions been correct.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Scienceandlogi5 @CBCToronto You're stupid and your handle is a joke.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realop60 @CBCToronto https://t.co/PCJH6oro2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: health experts are morally bankrupt and should be ignored as their misinformation is dangerous to the public good. The pandemic was over in May 2020 but these same health experts have prolonged it with their misinformed advice. #cdnpoli https://t.co/tLbTLZXYFq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How easily people overlook the fact Harper gave us Trudeau. People voted against him in 2015; had he not been such an asshole he might have won another term. https://t.co/8WpSWh8Igm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's overdue in Canada https://t.co/Z2c1RfLsfV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not until someone takes out Ford. #FireFordOpenOntario https://t.co/K3vcFILqzf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Their ignorance could be very costly... https://t.co/ITt4mKxQXJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sounds genocidal, to me, for a hospital to withhold a life-saving medication with a stellar safety record. #IvermectinSavesLives https://t.co/nucjkaBrUA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fuck off with your misleading headlines - it is a preliminary report! #MSMisAnEnemyOfThePeople  https://t.co/lPAKLofiw5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peakpilot: "Our duty to our patients is to present the evidence for different treatments and the risks. The patient can then make an in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: Following the same logic, I expect all incompetent politicians and bureaucrats responsible for the thousands of COVID de]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jjack1920 @CamGuthrie Just STFU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StephanieMcCrei @CamGuthrie Please keep your ignorance to yourself. Masks are virtue signalling nonsense and outside it is practically impossible to contract a virus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StephenMonk63 @CamGuthrie Your stupidity will be your downfall.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MrNeu_ @CamGuthrie People like you are the reason we're still locked down. Wake up, there's no scientific support for masks, social distancing etc. Though they try to deny it, the vaccines are experimental - none of them have completed long term trials.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CamGuthrie Masks are virtue signalling bullshit. Decades of high quality studies overwhelming conclude that masks are ineffective, unnecessary and harmful. #TakeOffYourMask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StoneSculptorJN Cutting emissions would be great if the whole world agreed but it's not happening so they need to focus efforts on alternative fuels and storing carbon. 4G Nuclear reactors could replace a lot of coal and gas power plants but we're not there yet.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>