<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 #Plandemic is enabled by the #ScumMedia https://t.co/9jIDZS9DWf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#UK where the terrorist government uses Police to stop freedom of movement  https://t.co/3Mz70kwTyB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#covid19 #covidmutation - nowhere as bad as the terrorists in government would like you to believe #WHO  https://t.co/j3EovFnaEl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#covid19 #covidmutation - nowhere as bad as the terrorists in government would like you to believe https://t.co/O0MebE7EH1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 has caused a mutant strain of government led by the two mutants Johnson and Hancock  https://t.co/9bwcgVjkSb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#covid19 #covidmutation is another government scam https://t.co/kLRzfymT8w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 #Tier4 #covidmutation - it is a massive fraud! https://t.co/OwbdTXrFeZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jaspersas @mikechamberlain https://t.co/XPOhJ6oFx4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NicolaWallITFC @CaptainCookUK @mikechamberlain Hands - Face - Space ! https://t.co/GDg8h09Jve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CaptainCookUK @mikechamberlain Well said  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 #CovidMutant #scamdemic https://t.co/KVTmH3BORI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EvaKBartlett I tell all the 'conspiracy theorists' I meet to stop watching the BBC and other #MSM and become truthers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danwootton @Francis_Hoar We don't have a democratic government any more. Democracy and the rule of law and the economy have all been trashed by these lunatics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickolasdreyfus Who but psychos would arrest a Doctor for telling the truth that the PCR test is not a diagnostic test for a virus and that lockdowns don't work ? https://t.co/qnFg2URWdS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nickolasdreyfus Of course they are. You only have to  watch this and listen to him to realise what a psycho he is https://t.co/lGwa4Z5elj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dedicating this to Johnson  Hancock and their #Tier4: 'Instant Karma's gonna get you Gonna knock you right on the head'  https://t.co/nGg8Won2Fg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SirGrahamBrady @CharlesWalkerMP  How much longer are you going to allow the charlatans Johnson and Hancock to ruin this country? They have to be removed and double quick. We are facing utter ruin and enslavement to the IMF.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BritainFree @Telegraph How has the cretin lasted so long? https://t.co/IHBV9RcaWj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #COVID19 'new variant' bullshit conveniently appears just in time for #Brexit and the reaction of Europe is full on isolation. Despite the fact this 'new variant' is already in Italy - but they are not being isolated https://t.co/buHWiPWbFg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@johnredwood Funny how the 'new variant' appears just in time for Brexit and the reaction of Europe is full on treachery. Despite the fact this 'new variant' is already in Italy and the Netherlands at least https://t.co/buHWiPWbFg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BillGates does want to control you and no it isn't a theory.  He wants : digital vaccine passports, subdermal chips, chips with sensors that will monitor body and brain activity, birth-control implant chips. He also owns 3.7M shares of Serco. #WiseUp https://t.co/VqkrgAaRaX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#covidmutation coronaviruses are constantly mutating and SARS-COV-2 has been mutating since at least March so quit the fear mongering - which 'surprisingly' coincides with Brexit happening https://t.co/tKysJ6oc1Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Explanation of the dangers of rushing science in the quest for a #COVID19 jab   https://t.co/E4jNhZWv8o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#tier4lockdown  makes sense - because all the previous lockdowns worked so well didn't they ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realsb4feelings @Nick_Pye No you can't. Tier4 is not even law it is just guidance.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesRe95125078 @Nick_Pye Bill Gates / Big Pharma. Boris practically worships Gates. Gates set up GAVI and CEPI and has major stakes in Big Pharma and the vax industry. Robert Kennedy Jr explains what these people are like https://t.co/41oemvVH0D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nick_Pye Who controls the UK government and western governments in general ? Robert Kennedy Jr explains who these psychos are and what their agenda is https://t.co/41oemvVH0D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PureGym Why are you rolling over for this criminal government ? Tier4 is only guidance - it is not law. You should fight to keep all your gyms open for the sake of your business and your members health.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVIDIOTS aka people who believe that following a bunch of nonsense draconian restrictions that did not work will now work this time - because its Christmas.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 is 14% of NHS hospital beds, 15% unoccupied. Boris Johnson is the #Joker https://t.co/AgkLR56Nl1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PoliticsPollss @liarpoliticians It will be in place forever. Unless we all #RiseUp and throw off our chains - starting with #Masks which are symbolic of being controlled and not being your authentic self. #MasksOff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolineCoramUK That'll be the 'high value business travellers' - they are immune to #COVID19 of course. BTW, don't question, just accept. After all, Boris the Clown is 'protecting' you. https://t.co/664mqxLA7j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nick_Pye Boris the Clown https://t.co/GONlLSPbTu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ReevesJek @kbeanie93 @JakeWri38029870 The 'emergency' services are going around arresting peaceful protesters at random. Meanwhile the 'majority of law abiding folk' are suffering at the hands of a criminally insane government because of a 'virus'. Insanity is doing the same over again  expecting a different result.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kbeanie93 In Ulster 1968 they held civil rights marches which were then banned and attacked by the RUC. Violence led to counter violence until the IRA mortared no 10 in 1991. Then peace was made. Let's hope it doesn't have to go that far this time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilDotObrien How about some leadership ? All we get is this clown - or is it the #Joker ? https://t.co/iQ3w2y1Ofa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson is UK's Pol Pot. A maniac who wants to return the UK to Year Zero. Ignore his criminal #Lockdown3 aka #tier4 . Lockdowns do not work https://t.co/m3tMDke3HB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 - who exactly are the conspiracy theorists again ?  https://t.co/ynSuBxbhe3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ara_MaHubbard No it is an utter waste of time. Almost as bad as listening to Boris Johnson. I don't like the royals (even though I am one myself) and what they stand for. What really sealed my hatred for them was this 'joke' about reincarnation by Prince Phillip https://t.co/zHitYSf8Cv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 https://t.co/CrAdy1fgoF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19Vaccine https://t.co/jO82rC10wu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@martyep74 @BelfastLive Spot on. The whole of the UK is being run by a gang of criminals. #SCAMDEMIC2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#oneruleforthem Tobias Ellwood MP is a #Covid19 hypocrite who said allowing families to meet over Christmas 'could be very dangerous indeed' and the next day attended a Christmas dinner for 27 guests at a London club. Bournemouth East recall your MP !  https://t.co/tQ3qRFssv8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gitmo where #Covid19 knows not to infect the guards. FFS #WiseUp people https://t.co/fMTFQJGygX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gorskon @karmanoscancer @McLarenHealth @Walgreens How do we know you even took it? Since you are a fake doctor you almost certainly faked the shot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 truth https://t.co/mRCq86VyGa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Pondleg You are doing a great job! Remember : illegitimi non carborundum. I like to listen to this when feeling down https://t.co/4MMaAiKs56]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 PCR 'test' that underpins the #SCAMDEMIC2020 aka #Plandemic has been condemned by #WHO for being run over too many cycles. This has been known for months. Stop mass PCR testing!  https://t.co/JETMjB4JV1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilDotObrien @ONS News for you. The #WHO agrees that PCR is a scam. https://t.co/JETMjB4JV1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Walkabout24 Abuser is spot on. They are terrorising the country. Ignore them and turn off #MSM.  #StopNewNormal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilDotObrien @ONS More lies and scare mongering because of totally unreliable #Covid19 testing. You should be ashamed. You are supposed to represent the people. Instead you are helping to perpetuate the #SCAMDEMIC2020  for the benefit of the psychopathic elite.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville Enjoy it while you still can! I expect the 'government' will get around to shutting down Cornwall in the name of #Covid19  when it suits them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A mutant #Covid19 strain in time for Christmas ? Who'd have thought the PTB wanted to cancel Christmas all along? https://t.co/YCWQS4gGuV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is how freedom dies in the name of #Covid19. Don't listen to the #MSM scumbags. https://t.co/YPuUj4fZxn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@goodrum_craig @airstripone84 @DaveShaw48 Evidence about PCR here and many other doctors have spoken out  https://t.co/teArEakS9v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#StopNewNormal - its all up to you! https://t.co/ru6b1CF2Fp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please consider supporting the campaign to to protect the Stonehenge landscape for future generations and stop the construction of a 2 billion dual carriageway through the Stonehenge World Heritage Site. https://t.co/DjwCVuwWfc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A New York Times investigation into the UKs handling of the pandemic reveals misuse of government funds on a massive scale during its Covid-19 response. Thanks NYT for stating the obvious.  https://t.co/SMYVA6MQ5Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calling all wild water swimmers. Here is some news for you.  https://t.co/oGBGyvJKvI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SilentRunning61 I give the old ones a break. They might have dementia or something. Its the young ones that amaze me. Such compliance, no defiance. Tragic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OldeTestamento @Francis_Hoar Money is created by the Bank of England - literally out of thin air or on a computer. Deliberate policy to debase the pound (and all national currencies). Why ? The eventual goal is to replace national currencies with a world currency so they need to create a monetary crisis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SilentRunning61 Where I live even people under 30 wear masks outside.  I am over 50 and I will not wear a mask - anywhere.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@swhotmess I don't wear a mask because #MasksDontWork and I will not be enslaved by bogus 'health' regulations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Covid19 - biggest scam in the history of the human race  #WiseUp people - its your freedom they are taking in the name of a 'virus' https://t.co/gEPu3SA48b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you brave enough ? Be brave.  I'm brave enough to live in never ending terror of #Covid19. I'm brave enough to do as I'm told without questioning it.  I'm brave enough to want to be tracked so I can be safe.    https://t.co/NVMc2OXIhn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Of course China has won the #Covid19 war. They created the virus in their labs, released it and controlled the world response via their #WHO and #BillGates a member of the Chinese Academy of Engineering https://t.co/SCZ9c4rGMd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#WiseUp and #RiseUp ! #CivilDisobedience  There is hope as Brits 'turn in' the #Covid19 scammers  https://t.co/BMYrZPpzDh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Audit concludes Dominion voting machines were intentionally designed to create systemic fraud in Michigan https://t.co/QjCyOASXDW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@suwillow @themood2020 Covid exists but is only as lethal as the flu. It has been hyped beyond belief]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@themood2020 Why don't they organise and fight back? That's what their union is for. If the union doesn't work them then start a new one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catemw100 @SpillerOfTea @2ears2wheels @MattHancock Matt Hancock is a world class scumbag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@guardian #Plandemic #Resist ! #tiersystem is #lockdown #CivilDisobedience https://t.co/O8V6mvmPnz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking #Plandemic #Resist ! #tiersystem is #lockdown #CivilDisobedience https://t.co/U6cCJbY1c1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@5_News #Plandemic #Resist ! #tiersystem is #lockdown #CivilDisobedience https://t.co/1btYjNDwmz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#tiersystem is a scam as is the whole #COVID19 #Plandemic #Resist ! #WiseUp and #RiseUp ! #CivilDisobedience  #StopNewNormal https://t.co/lsdvKfPhEa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When #government says it is "following the science" remember this :- the two biggest mass murdering governments of the 20th century were the Nazis who were following the 'science' of #eugenics and the Bolsheviks were following 'scientific' socialism.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#COVID19 aka #Plandemic aka #Scamdemic rests on 3 lies https://t.co/qu8kJX0NBf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#hypocritewatch There goes #BillGates again, telling us the way it is going to be. He acts like he is the leader of the #COVID19 cult and we are his acolytes doing his bidding. https://t.co/HR9zoCvHHa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Botanygeek Before you accuse others of racism first look at yourself in the mirror. If you see racism everywhere it is because your psychology has been warped by cultural marxist constructs which were designed to criticise and destroy traditional society.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Susan Michie is the SAGE Psychologist who has orchestrated the government's campaign of fear over #Covid19 the #Plandemic. She is a psychopath and a communist without a conscience. She wants to talk about what is fair. What a massive hypocrite. https://t.co/c2cZ9wd6Rb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The  #Pandemic is fake so don't let the #Covid19 'police' control you.  Choose #Freedom #StopNewNormal #MasksOff. Refuse the unsafe #CovidVaccine https://t.co/chVpxh47s8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #Covid19 #Scamdemic predicated on the fake #covidtest RT-PCR is now on borrowed time as the forces of truth close in - Johnson, Hancock, Fauci : your time is up you shills and liars https://t.co/NSd471Pm9c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan We are all sick and tired of both you and Boris]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GMB @PimlicoPlumbers It is illegal for @PimlicoPlumbers founder Charlie Mullins or any business to discriminate against customers like this. A person's medical history is private - he cannot demand access to this information. #PimlicoPlonkers more like.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@liarpoliticians @IainDale @LBC Its deliberate. They can't end the NHS but they want to. So instead they reduce the service by making appointments telephone only - eventually it will all be app based and the doctor could be anywhere cheap (India?). Some will choose to go private. Result is NHS shrinks  dies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Please stop calling the #PfizerBioNTech jab a vaccine. It is novel gene therapy. https://t.co/cK1vOHBvLn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Researcher finds #COVID19 related deaths exceeded deaths from heart diseases because there was a significant decrease in deaths due to heart disease. The total decrease in deaths by other causes almost exactly equals the increase in deaths by #COVID. https://t.co/qxOQTaA4wN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rob_miller12345 Forget 2022. Make it forever. This is the New Normal remember. It won't be rolled back until we #Resist. #StopNewNormal #MasksOff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealCarlVernon They will because they don't care.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrengrimes_ OK so two can play at this childish game. We ban their planes, their fishing boats, their food, everything they make cars etc. Ban their people from coming here. Sanction their EU commissioners. If its a non-shooting war they want then give it to them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sadiq Khan, London's terrorist in chief, continues to threaten Londoners https://t.co/ObNEtur5xC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PfizerBioNTech  #Moderna #CovidVaccine both contain an allergen and suspected carcinogen. Even the MHRA advises people with a history of significant allergic reactions not to opt for the Pfizer vaccine. https://t.co/Ijnq5fRjGY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#PfizerBioNTech  #Moderna #CovidVaccine both contain an allergen and suspected carcinogen. Also the spike protein mRNA of the vaccine could be absorbed by human cells  integrated which could induce cancer.  https://t.co/HU4yHiMkO2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During the Phase II/III trials, 50% of #PfizerCovidVaccine participants aged 18-55 experienced systemic adverse events within a month of their second dose of vaccine as did 100% of those injected with two doses of #Modernas vaccine. Please people stop taking it! #Covid19 #Resist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadian politician says #GreatReset is not a conspiracy theory, but an actual set of concrete proposals and #WEF is  he biggest gathering of global hypocrites in history". The  policies would create massive poverty. #Resist #GreatReject  https://t.co/ZR5rO3q0BZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LiquorElixir @darrengrimes_ You will be identified all right. Once you are nanochipped and 5G is everywhere. For now, your mobile phone is on all the time, connected to Facebook and Google. They know more about you than you know about yourself. If you have track and trace then your mask is worthless.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrengrimes_ This is why the psychopathic 'elite' call it the New Normal. They never want it to end. The better to control you.  #Resist and #RiseUp  #StopNewNormal #MasksOff]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#covid19 #CovidTesting https://t.co/XWkhJnnoQZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another 'side effect' of the #PfizerCovidVaccine  - but don't worry the MHRA says its safe. Duh !  #CovidVaccine  #COVID19  https://t.co/dhNAjzqLF1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrengrimes_ There is no border within the UK. Also England and Wales have the same legal system. How can something legal in England be illegal in Wales ? They just want to break up the UK and this must be stopped. Now.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>