<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@Sacha_Lord @MathewMKC I phoned Children's Services, Eastbourne Council and found that they are still working from home! Why?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ProKlausSchwab: Ive made my mind up...  I am going to be part of the Global Covid resistance no matter where that brings me. Poverty,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @opinionatedmum1: Having a road map  becomes pointless when you realise your mode of transport is an evil snail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NeilClark66 Nonsense. Everyone can simply say "I'm exempt."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: So the UK govts idea of a removal of restrictions on 21st June means people still having to wear masks in cinemas, thea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Chrissm07537852: @SuzanneEvans1 Now we know they extended the emergency powers to September and are still recruiting Covid Marshals]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeggyAlcazar @SuzanneEvans1 Brainwashed moron.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cherry23949630: @Non_Chicken @SuzanneEvans1 Something that nobody is addressing is the class aspect of mask wearing. Ministers who swan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SuzanneEvans1: I knew they would attempt to keep masks after June 21st. I just knew it, because they are the strongest icon of social c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Matthews_angst 10]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeremyVineOn5: Should we lift lockdown restrictions today?   One professor has suggested the UK's "past the pandemic" and urged people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk Buying books in supermarkets, WH Smith was deemed safe, but not in bookshops.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JujuliaGrace: What happened in court yday?  Matt Hancock was ordered by the High Court to reveal details of a WhatsApp group which wa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FamilyDefence: The UK column has been censored and taken down by YouTube and Vimeo!  The UK column is an outstanding news broadcaster,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fluffyclouds98: Whistleblower nurse yesterday.. https://t.co/JDyIsX4coD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Authors are now using photos of themselves in masks on their Amazon Authors Page. https://t.co/dDrxGKr5rx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: The bigger the lies and the longer they continue, the tougher the justice @MattHancock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @danielkotzin: My vaccination status is none of your business.  Your vaccination status is none of my business.  No ones vaccination st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Demo2020cracy: GO!!!!! AMSTERDAM  Anti lockdown protest today https://t.co/TonMzAcxux]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arwenstar: If you need to hear more about the level of indoctrination  utter stupidity thats going on rn: someone in a Mensa group sa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HabberleySteve: Tribunals have now set a precedent that you can be sacked for not wearing masks, whatever your condition or disability,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AntzWeb: Running a pub is a tough business as it is. Before convid, it was tough... Attracting people to use the pub, keeping a safe an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KatieM12121: When we are all living in the 'new normal' dystopia where we will have to be vaccinated 3+ times pa, undergo facial recogn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Heachy_1979: Vaccine passports are the biggest threat Western democracy has ever faced. They will not be confined to Covid they won't]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Martin4Liberty: @CarolineCoramUK @a_freedomnow I played golf yesterday with 2 vaxxed individuals, this morning when I awoke I had a ras]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Valkyrie20201: We must not allow our children to be forced to take the covid vaccine in September and that requires a concerted effort]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angelazhay: The daily reporting by the MSM of Covid stats is so crazed, it is just keeping people focussed on the Gov's fear strategy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealCarlVernon: Masks and anti-social distancing only end when you say no.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NeilClark66: Retaining mandatory masks  social distancing over the summer makes no sense on public health grounds but makes A LOT OF S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nick_the_geek78: A year ago it was about preventing NHS from getting overwhelmed. Now it's about covid passports, health discrimination]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thetruebluechef: Hearing police are doing spot checks of pubs in the area. Obviously weather is bad so checking people arent indoors. S]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ripx4nutmeg @life_explored I also wasted my time trying to listen to something that was not there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Demo2020cracy Passport to Pimlico!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LibertarianEcoS I also carried on my business, even when it was illegal. And when they were screaming "STAY AT HOME" I went out literally every day, as long as I liked. Fuck the lot of them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LibertarianEcoS I do not comply with any measure brought in since March 2020. I've never been punished or barred.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE: Activists protest against police bill at May Day rally in London https://t.co/Tg8M5oe9ri via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nick_the_geek78: Did you expect back in April '20 that a year later you'd have pandemic measures with no pandemic?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Andy_In_The_UK: How did we get from this...  "for most peoplethe vast majority of peoplethis will be a mild illness."  To this...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianxClark @straife1 @Drama419 @Breaking911 that's not gender, it's personality!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrianxClark @Drama419 @Breaking911 how many on this "scale", then?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SCRAP_IRON_RYAN: All my life I've always been a outcast the only reason you can see through the bullshit today is beasuse you can relat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: Imagine a vaccine so safe.... you have to be threatened to take it!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfroberts: Saw a toddler in a shop today. I smiled at her  she smiled back, which would to her now be very rare indeed to see. I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SueSuezep: The NHS belongs to the British People. The NHS is funded from general taxation and National Insurance contributions. It's ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BenRobe30554892 @CromwellStuff @BSimonward @MattHancock You should see the threads on Mumsnet! Women in their 20s and 30s desperate for their turn to get the jab. 40s women driving 100 miles to get it if not available locally!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timfprice: No meaningful change can happen until both the Tories and Labour Parties are razed to the ground. Both supported Lockdown. B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Farinances: Genuine question:  How can you gain 'emergency' approval for a separate, special product for use on people who aren't at ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @iainmartin1: No one is safe until everyone is safe has become one of those things that people say regularly (and slowly) on @bbcquestio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BCscifience: Our rights and freedoms are burning away, right in front of our eyes.  The fuel is compliance.   Stop feeding the fire!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoeharcombe: Politicians need to remember that they exist to serve their electorate; not to enslave it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamplingDanny: Shoom events will not be taking part in medical apartheid. Weve built the electronic music scene on core values of unit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DrTEB @DickDelingpole @tomhfh true]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BreesAnna: Dr. Hodkinson received his general medical degrees from Cambridge University (M.A., M.B., B. Chir.)Following a residency at]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @toadmeister: Do we really have to wait until there is absolutely no risk before we're allowed our freedoms back, asks @MissVHewson in @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Walkabout24: What's the correct term when a society discriminates against healthy people who make the effort to look after themselves?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@talkRADIO rubbish]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess which one received the ** ONLY ** media coverage. https://t.co/5eWhiZE17k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: 22 UK Covid deaths in the past 24 hours (deaths for any reason within 28 days of a positive test). 450 UK cancer dea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarfsee: London: Evil knows it must conquer-control the media first. You get that now, right?!? https://t.co/9qyo2BUYgX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@farhanjimale How else could his string of fucks contact him?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HumanRights4UK: We must universally and TOTALLY reject #VaccinePassports at all costs. They could in time create a 360 worldwide digit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Kavvasakiman: BORIS wants you to talk about CURTAINS, instead of the VACCINE PASSPORTS, he said we would never have... ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SoniaPoulton: My barrister Richard Munden will be speaking after lunch. Very much looking forward to it. As if we havent already heard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kbeanie93: Made the mistake of trying to watch Sunetra Gupta on BBC news. This is NOT journalism. She was spoken over. She was interrup]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsForAlI:  NEW: Big night tonight in Liverpool. 3,000 clubbers with no masks, Covid passports or social distancing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NoGreatReset: We must never accept any coercion to take a medical treatment. #NoVaccinePassports #NoVaccinePassportsAnywhere https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WohYeahWohYeah @TechPriestAVIFD @ElectionMapsUK @YouGov Trans support "lacking"? Fact is, the militant trans extremists have Labour's bollox in a vice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: I can't get my head around the fact that a tiny, group of people, a minuscule number.. make the most terrible choices,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevSent: Is everyone dead in Florida and Texas?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @smile28554950: They are calling them covid status certificates we need to stop referring to v*xxine passports and start using their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: MPs are our elected representatives. If they are not representing us, then they are not doing their job and therefore, shou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MirrorManStanly: @ZubyMusic If everybody is sick or potentially sick, they get to experiment on everybody. If you can make everybody af]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Your government has ZERO interest in your health and longevity.    Govt has an interest in something you probably would]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NewtonClarkeUK: Good morning everyone   Its now 30 April 2021 and lockdowns still dont work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HumanRights4UK: To every lawyer, judge, journalist, MP, etc.  you and your family WILL NOT ESCAPE #VaccinePassports, digital IDs and t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SmithTarquin: Tonight I reached 4000 followers ... mostly beautiful awake folk ... Ive got nothing but love for you #findyourtribe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SmithTarquin: My advice to those who are struggling, make connections with like minded people... you are not alone, there are many peop]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Mich1971C Why are you posting this on Twitter? Attention-seeking at its worst.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@darrengrimes_ "Hey grandma, I'm gonna shag around! Ain't that great? Why have they started calling me dartboard?"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UsockRich Judging by all the proud announcements on Facebook they took it to virtue-signal their blind compliance with the Tories.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClobukObrien: @buttonbox21 @treasa45 Im actually thinking of exist plans if this gets too much. What is the point of being around if t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheDoomedWorld: @buttonbox21 @Bobilly10 Time for a National Protest on why we pay National Insurance.  They have no right to deny treat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @buttonbox21: So without a swab the NHS wont treat you. Been told this morning, how long before, without the jab, the NHS wont treat y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FatEmperor: And now we see the Medieval Lockdown Nonsense Merchants scratching their unscientific heads: https://t.co/i2cVZTgwz0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennyJobbins: @UK_UNIFICATION @nicolawitch How dare you Boris make little ones wear masks and you and others not that is abuse and you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Arwenstar: Still cant get over this lunacy that you shouldnt hug family  friends until the govt says so - *and* that some people act]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Harms of Lockdowns, The Dangers of Censorship, And A Path Forward https://t.co/xvvx3brifa via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @leew2030: @lorrain00414525 Please spread this Ive just read this document on testing https://t.co/HIaJCTHOLY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @timfprice: *It's almost as if Covid is being used as cover to deliberately trash the economy, introduce a new central bank digital curr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SteveBakerHW: "Academics must urgently counter the very real danger of groupthink across a range of issues, starting with lockdown."  G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IanplatMink: @Unlocked_UK_ @FreeFromTyranny Dr Lees courage and moral integrity is just second to none. Brilliantly honestly consisten]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: Vaccine passports for domestic venue entry are one of the most illiberal and authoritarian ideas ever floated by a UK go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sheev_insidious: @DPJHodges Dan, we have the most corrupt government in history.  As a "journalist" of sorts,  you should be looking in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PeterStefanovi2: Looks like 13 million views on my film has finally had an impact!   Boris Johnson Now Facing Tough New Rules To Force]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HegKong: I can think of any other medical procedures that people boast about on social media, so why announce your vaccination to the w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@velvetlady21 @Chrisitv Who told you that the mask protects you? NOt the scientists, not the govt. Who?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BoyCharioteer: #BorisOut So Boris Johnson is able to overrule any finding that finds him guilty of corruption? Is that right? The rule]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@678Hank @samasjapi interesting he mentions the penis issue.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samasjapi: Serous question. What makes us see things that the masses can't? I'm not blessed with intelligence, and have never taken an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SaraHaboubi1: @IceMurph Where are you all? Where are all the pubs and restaurant owners? Hotel owners? Cinemas? Gyms? Where are you all]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>