<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@ickonic Is there an iOS app?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden has shown he wants to take away freedom of speech and assembly and advocated for law enforcement to search without a warrant. Whats next? We wont let people have due process of law? Slavery? Militia in our homes?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Washington Examiner (@dcexaminer) Tweeted: .@JoeBiden introduces his gun plan:  "No amendment to the Constitution is absolute." https://t.co/yMQVo7niSI https://t.co/L9kxh8hcU7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@zerohedge @MARFOOGLE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LionelMedia #MarkOfTheBeast]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fyithetruth @MomusNajmi @harrylitman By the way, as @RealCandaceO eloquently said, My freedom doesnt end where your fear begins.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fyithetruth @MomusNajmi @harrylitman How are you going to be infected if you got vaxxed? Why do you care what I do with my body? #MyBodyMyChoice its possible the vax may not even stop the spread.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@davidpakmanshow Comparing drunk driving to an accident doesn't make a whole lot of sense]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dpakman Might be useful/interesting/influential if you reported on the Ebola outbreaks in the U.S.  In case you didn't know, Ebola is way more deadly than COVID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dpakman Might be useful/interesting/influential if you reported on treatment using medication that we have had for several years and is safe, such as Ivermectin.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dpakman Might be useful/interesting/influential if you reported that the risk of a serious adverse effects to the vax is higher than the risk of dying. https://t.co/LO03oJmelx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dpakman Might be useful/interesting/influential if you reported the truth - that not all deaths have been proven to be due to COVID. A man fell off a ladder and never tested positive for COVID, but his death was declared to be the result of COVID.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dpakman Might be useful/interesting/influential to study how many in nursing homes are dying after getting the vax https://t.co/cffxm9BTG0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dpakman Might be useful/interesting/influential to study how many babies are being killed by the vax https://t.co/MmgZpeBa5K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kshadyacct4 @Marfoogle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MCHammer Youre a wise man! Unbelievable so many people are so incompetent that they cant understand this. Fauci is a perfect example. In the past year hes said dont wear a mask, wear a mask,  wear 4 masks. Scientists previously said smoking didnt cause cancer and the earth was flat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NNickPerry mlk wouldn't approve of your concentration camp bill. don't be a nazi, nick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaBRosenthal So we're allowed to decide whether or not to kill babies, but not whether or not we want to take the COVID vax, even if it may not stop the spread? What happened to "My Body, My Choice"?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaBRosenthal @SalazarSenate @HarryBBronson @RyanHealthNYC @CHCANYS @housingworks @CallenLorde @HarlemUnited @lac_news @EvergreenHS @ASAPNYS @COMPA_New_York @DPA_NY If you cared about people's health, you wouldn't mandate them to take an experimental substance with the likelihood of adverse effects, especially since it may not even stop the spread. You only have a liberal arts BA. You shouldn't be making medical decisions for me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaBRosenthal Umm if you think what Hitler was bad, maybe you shouldn't require people to take an experimental substance with the likelihood of paralysis, death, etc. If vax doesn't stop spread, it's only beneficial to person getting vax. What's next, nazi nick perrry's concentration camps?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LindaBRosenthal @SenKevinThomas You're such a hypocrite. You care about data privacy, but you don't care about fundamental human rights. Big tech is tracking people who take your nazi vax. These COVID IDs are a breach of privacy of medical information.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AIGeneratedName This sounds like he gets a second term and dies then]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I havent heard any complaint from @GameStop  The only people boohooing this week are self-righteous hypocritical elitists like you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[u have no understanding of the economy  working hard @SenWarren @GameStop  is benefitting greatly - they were near bankrupt  now they can pay their employees more  I hope expand to do online business  make games themselves. This was a #ReoccupyWallStreet action. https://t.co/TcFr3aQ6Ki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How convenient, Bidens secretarys bro in on this Ponzi scheme too @AOC @RepAOC @tedcruz @TulsiPress @RandPaul @SenSanders @BernieSanders @MarshaBlackburn @SenRickScott @marcorubio @SenMikeLee @RepMattGaetz @RepThomasMassie @SenGillibrand @AdamKinzinger @SenWarren https://t.co/JVV40Y5489]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is not ok. Biden and his crew need to be impeached - Kamala and the cabinet. Nancy Pelosi is corrupt like these hedge funders and RobbinG Hood too. So we need to appoint Leahy prez or Trump lol @tedcruz @AOC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yellen paid more to open her mouth than Stormy Daniels was paid to close hers. Prob more than she paid to open hers too.  https://t.co/dzLqQQ75Hj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Basically Im getting home two hours than planned. Not cool. @MetroNorth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Missed the train by a minute. Now I have ton wait almost an hour for the next train and it will take nearly an hour instead of HALF an hour to get to White Plains. And theres no place for me to even sit and wait. This is terrible service @MetroNorth]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NNickPerry looks like you're trying to pull off the same thing with your concentration camps bill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef You are huge hypocrites. Go eat shit useless mouth breathers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef Fuck off evil World Eugenics Forum]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actually, Im tuning maybe Q was Mike Pence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrohioPodcast @IlluminatiEyes @MaKaElectric @Marfoogle I thought he got COVID and died on Canadian Thanksgiving day in 2019]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[B**** stole my look!    https://t.co/IXHYY2W1Z7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So it seems this Q stuff isnt going to happen but I would like to know who this antisocial loser in their moms basement is. Hilary Clinton? Sasha Baron Cohen? Ted Cruz? @BrohioPodcast @IlluminatiEyes @MaKaElectric @Marfoogle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump must be sad that Biden is getting a bigger crowd for his inauguration. I hear there are 25,000 National Guard troops alone that will be in the crowd!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why so many NG  even Customs Enforcement  NYPD at the capitol? Why were some NG deputized 2b marshals? What's w/ all the fencing? I understand hype up security, but this seems excessive! I don't think I'll sleep for the next 24 hrs! @IlluminatiEyes @Marfoogle @MaKaElectric]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont think Im eligible to be in the Trump Army - I cant run a mile in less than a minute @donwinslow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What color are the uniforms of Trumps Army and where can I hear a recording of their anthem @donwinslow TIA!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lifesafeast @donwinslow Youre damn right. And they are not all racist and hateful terrorists. And I know @ScottBaio is older now, but hes not ugly to me! Stop stereotyping.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow Further, not all Trump supporters are white supremacists. Do @RealCandaceO @50cent (and I could go on) look like white supremacists?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow Its fine to disagree with someone. But you shouldnt call someone a terrorist just because they disagree with you:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow As someone who earns money writing, I would expect you to know better language than terrorist.  Its a loaded word. Its a legal classification.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow Indeed 1/6 was the new 9/11 - just as there were stereotypes that all Arabs are terrorists, now anyone who suppers Trump is considered a terrorist.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@donwinslow Its frightening you are calling 80+ million people terrorists. There are so many doctors, electricians, lawyers, plumbers, even my hairstylist, who prefer Trump to Biden.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zerosum24: Is this guy a alt-Q, or just onto something interesting with this wild theory? #HologramJoe https://t.co/CXccxMWZAq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YellowCube7 @Canberroo2 They r not social distancing!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Omg girl, please. Already proof BLM/Antifa part of the violence last week and the BLM/Antifa caused more deaths, injuries and destruction. I guess your pals and you need to be re-educated too for questioning the 2016 election results @aoc #hypocrite  https://t.co/MMiTwvi4zZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And you want to force the elderly to  have the vax? What kind of sick eugenicists are you @LindaBRosenthal @AndrewYang @NNickPerry https://t.co/tOFQ8chTJt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I used to love @Pocket but now it's not working anymore...looking for alternative]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AOC et al. want to make lists of Trump supporters. What for?https://t.co/tjmNLmt0UD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If people want to put children into re-education camps, I'm scared to think what they want to do with the parents. These are the same people who say it's bad Trump separates children from their families. And it is, but two wrongs don't make a right. https://t.co/uGohcZRsaC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What about the people who went into Capitol Hill but did not commit any violence or property destruction? Really, those are terrorists? People want to put them on the do-not-fly list.  https://t.co/QJW6fTK0sU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just like how there were stereotypes about anyone Middle Eastern being a terrorist after 9/11, it seems like the left is considering anyone who disagrees with them a terrorist or terrorist sympathizer.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I thought it was insulting when people called the storming of Capitol Hill "a 9/11 moment", but the left are making it that way. #magaterrorists is really a hashtag on here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I thought Obama was going to GTFO of other countries, but no, leave it to Trump! #MAGA https://t.co/e8OLt6WtTL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is some scary sh*t! @MaKaElectric @Marfoogle @IlluminatiEyes Nerds gonna kill us! WtF does he know about growing corn?! Hes gonna put vaccines in it! https://t.co/tjLg51UwRi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marfoogle Whats the point of this?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarlosD48575102 @TheWuhanClan @Breaking911 Ive already seen it lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Marfoogle By aLiens]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlacklistedNews And soon us?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IndigoLeo10 @disruptivedachs @PaulTheMartian Inauguration like 11 days away]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PS some of Trumps last tweets were Stay peaceful!, I am asking everyone at the U.S. Capitol to remain peaceful. No violence! and Go home with love  in peace!, showing the opposite of what is claimed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I look forward to your reply.  Sincerely,  Someone who actually went to law school]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[what specific language was likely to incite or produce imminent violence. Brandenburg v. Ohio, 395 U.S. 444 [1969] (mere advocacy of violence is protected speech)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For those calling for the Presidents impeachment, please advice what specific language Trump used that was directed to incite or produce imminent violence and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PolskaToMy @BlacklistedNews Filming Braveheart 2 without a permit lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Philly852 Ugh, our government is doing this? I dont want to pay taxes anymore LoL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Philly852 Maybe its counterfeit....lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MuadGrumps @JesseMatchey How valuable do u think Chuck e Cheese coins will be...lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JesseMatchey Sounds like a good question for Bill Gates, Klaus Schwab, and their crew because they keep talking about a cyber pandemic...it sounds like they have inside intel...I hope they are working with authorities to prevent this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FultzMeOnce @GordonGChang Also, climate change is cool...gonna use up so many more fossil fuels and stuff transporting stuff from Commie Land to here!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FultzMeOnce @GordonGChang Child labor, sweatshops, concentration camps, rampant harm to environment, pretty much no human rights, lying to rest of world about WuFlu, China is cool!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThePaulyShow @ihatematt Not for like 11 days]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@letoonarmy @Markgsparrow @TheSimonEvans I presume you own things now. Why dont you give it all away and go to North Korea to get a taste of what The Great Reset is all about.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Keithpoker1 @Markgsparrow @jenninemorgan I feel like that would be better than living in the great reset dystopia!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@letoonarmy @Markgsparrow @TheSimonEvans You will not even have a phone or computer to Tweet. You will not own a Twitter account. Sharing is still great, eh? You want to share underwear with other people?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@letoonarmy @Markgsparrow @TheSimonEvans You wont have children. You will not own any clothes, toothpaste, the place where you live. Likely you will be in a dorm-like facility in a bunk bed. Even prisoners can have things (as of now) like books. But you will have fewer rights than a prisoner.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndrewYang @TweetBenMax So you believe in religious freedom but not freedom from vaccines when its not even shown to stop transmission of virus?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLevineNYC @LindaBRosenthal Pharma companies have admitted unknown if vax causes infertility (Maybe eugenist Hitler wouldve loved vax too) or if stops spread to others. COVID not as bad as you make it out to be, boomer doomers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLevineNYC @LindaBRosenthal Youre such a slap in the face to WW veterans who fought for freedom  to stop Nazism. You only hold a BA  MA in lib arts, yet you want to force a vax, which is causing many side effects  deaths  long-term side effects unknown.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLevineNYC Dont compare a cold virus to smallpox, which was often deadly.  COVID has a 99% survival rate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkLevineNYC Stop spewing propaganda.  99% survival rate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Censorship Sux! What's ur handle on https://t.co/o5pwCpgnCu @DBrozeLiveFree @elonmusk @justinamash @RobertKennedyJr @TulsiGabbard @zerohedge @RealCandaceO @GovGaryJohnson @RandPaul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NNickPerry Ebola isnt a threat anymore, so why dont you trash your draconian tyrannical Nazi Bill]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NNickPerry PS you lose all credibility quoting the Wuhan Health Organization.  Its a corrupt group of evil greedy cronies.  Thank Trump were not part of WHO anymore!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@NNickPerry I did read it carefully Nazi Nick.  And its vague and opens up the door for concentration camps. Did you not ever learn of Ben Franklins quote that anyone who would give up freedom for security deserves neither?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mahoneyw @NNickPerry Its not a theory.  Can you even read, bro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRevAl @NNickPerry @NationalAction Because rioters like BLM and Antifa showed up.  Looks like Trump supporters are better because they dont disturb your protests!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PolitiFact @NNickPerry @PolitiFact didnt read Nazi Nicks bill!  @NNickPerry  This Bill is what Hitler did.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bad judgment @Westlaw to display article from @Reuters stating Trump supporters sieged Capitol Hill. Did you interview all of them? There is evidence that BLM and Antifa were there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know the crew is supposed to act as spectators, but when it comes to possible human rights violations, I hope you're doing your part to help.  @TLC @90DayFiance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TLC I love @90DayFiance and Julia is one of the people I love most on the show ever, but I'm worried she is the victim of human trafficking.  https://t.co/Fe80e10Jcm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hi @officialmcafee , so many people rely on Bill Gates as an expert in vaccines, but I think you built a good product (I still use!) that seems to prevent viruses more that Windows didnt, so since I trust your opinion more than his, what are your thoughts on the COVID vax? TIA!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What if more than 15% cant or dont want vax? Youre worse than the ICE camps performing hysterectomies b/c one can suffer worse consequences from the vax.  Youre like nazis. @NYGovCuomo @LindaBRosenthal  https://t.co/lFp8Xs8MId]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Yikes, this is operation blackjack stuff @MaKaElectric]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ksorbs Stop trying to force vaccines on us @LindaBRosenthal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wef except @wef spends all their time spreading propaganda and lies to usher in a technocracy under the guise a bug with a 99% survival rate #GreatReject]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you cared about the elderly, you wouldnt force a vax on them and enacted your nursing home policies @NYGovCuomo @AndrewYang  @LindaBRosenthal   https://t.co/Q4JaDSCip6]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>