<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrueNorthCentre: The province that has been touted by the federal Liberals as a role model and inspiration for Canadas carbon tax has]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[they are trying to bribe people by lying to them, they say take the vaccine and restrictions will be less. lol. they wont do anything. they want you to take an experimental shot for the flu. no thanks. #justsayno #RemoveThePM https://t.co/7URpCxCxzE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Blue26Jackson its our money they are printing for today but our grandkids and kids will be paying for it with very high taxes in the future. someone should shut off their printing press. lol. #Hyperinflation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PierrePoilievre too late to do anything except maybe try and buy a lot less so we dont have too much money chasing fewer goods. but doubt that will happen. hyperinflation has already started but its mild right now. by summer we are all screwed. oh except the very rich.they will suffer less]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PierrePoilievre its the Liberal party that is printing and spending our grandkids future now for no real current gains. same bullshit tyranny and by summer we all as Canadians will pay a huge price in everything we need to buy. stock up now because soon it will be toolate as hyperinflation hits]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Blue26Jackson: The only thing holding this system up is our compliance...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Blue26Jackson can we stop paying income taxes or does that not matter since the government owns its own printing press.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @signalapp: With the May 15th WhatsApp Terms of Service acceptance deadline fast approaching, Mark leads by example:  https://t.co/Mt5Yk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@francoislegault this is all political. you are a dictator. we will vote you out. there is no science or proof. show the people the proof. not what your health bureaucrats say is science. proof. idiot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Roy5Yves @francoislegault they want to keep us in lockdowns that way we stay out of the way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Roy5Yves @francoislegault in ontario no masks at work if 6 feet apart. in Quebec masks all the time at work. covid is only in quebec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AtemAknamkanon: @francoislegault Aucune des mesures ont raison d'tre!  Le couvre-feu n'a jamais eu lieu d'tre Tout est politique Tout]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LauraRosenCohen: This death, like many others, is on you @celliottability and @fordnation shame on you ==&gt;https://t.co/wRf8zmaBd8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RebelNewsOnline: Canadian expat kept from visiting sick mother because of COVID jail rules  FULL REPORT by @TheMenzoid: https://t.co/hw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierrePoilievre: FACT: If you define "Canadian content" as "any content created by any Canadian", there is 1000s of times more of it on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RubinReport: Lebron's political views in video form.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @calvinrobinson: What an utter disgrace these unions are.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricsElectrons: A large amount of black people are turning against social justice efforts because theyre tired of being told theyre t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Pagmenzies: Am I the only one who noticed that if it wasnt for a free and open Internet nobody would know that Canada is about to brin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jamiljivani: Trudeau thought because Canadians have endured lockdowns and stay at home orders that we would just continue taking it on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Overcoming Covid Fear https://t.co/RkZpUz1W0X via @YouTube wake up Canada. we have been fooled. and the lies continue on and on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@randyhillier @NML_Canada ya because she is a racist and so is the police chief. racist against freedom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RussellHillier: I asked the question and here's the answer.   No matter what province you live in, @MaximeBernier and @peoplespca is th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierrePoilievre: What's Canadian content?  When CBC endlessly regurgitates CNN stories about American politics, the authorities say it']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kelly79998198 does losing your rights not worry you? we live in a police state with dictators as premiers. mark my words if people dont wake up we are screwed by years end. https://t.co/OAbTrEQ167]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Kelly79998198 @anthonyfurey not even 50 percent of canadians will risk their lives for an experimental vaccine. it hasnt been approved just has emergency use authorization. and when i cant sue the drug company that makes me wonder why. because its a gamble. i will take my chances with covid.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: The College of Physicians and Surgeons of Ontario is wrong to try to silence doctors   https://t.co/w574k8z6Qs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@anthonyfurey i m so sick of my doctors worried about their licences in place of helping me, their patient. they are full of excuses.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cafreeland @JustinTrudeau @_DebSchulte @PatFinniganMP and you are going to destroy it with socialism. why dont you tell them that part. stop lying to people as it will be worse for you guys when everyone finds out you sold Canada out to the globalists who you actually work for https://t.co/B2V4cbQO2E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nuts2bee: @s_guilbeault C-10 is how it starts. https://t.co/0bZljAXqD4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CurmudgeonTired @LSolomonTweets @CPC_HQ @MaximeBernier we need to get @MaximeBernier elected or we are doomed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CurmudgeonTired: If veteran @LSolomonTweets says it's so, you take it to the bank!  @CPC_HQ is now a misnomered party with a globalist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roccogalatilaw crimes against humanity https://t.co/i3DkxMT2Dm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roccogalatilaw dr evil]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roccogalatilaw facist piece of shit. @WEF we will not comply]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: Do we need to say more? Evil, fascist  4th Reicher speaking 5 years ago. Still conspiracy theorists? Humans and human r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrissaccoccia1 lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheoFleury14 @GoodAlwaysWins_ how can he be a politician. dont they have to go through background checks?  or is he special]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dshrig: Another weekend, another set of protests against COVID restrictions across the world. My @RebelNewsOnline colleagues @SydFizzar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guccilibertaria: 412 days to flatten the curve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LegalizeitLala yep un elected health bureaucrats know best LOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Yanky_Pollak: A couple of minutes before the curfew around 30 cop cars were circling the park to make sure everyone stays COVID save an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Yanky_Pollak @RebelNewsOnline i guess there is no crime in Montreal anymore]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MaximeBernier @JdeMontreal #MSM lies all the time. i believe nothing they say anymore. i wont watch or support them in any way at all same with certain banks like ScotiaBank and #BoycottCocacola #BoycottLebronJames #BoycottNFL #BoycottWokism]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: PPC merchandise will soon be available on our online store!   La marchandise PPC sera bientt disponible dans notre bout]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Fox_Claire: Can someone tell these police officers about religious freedom?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jay_jay40438038 @TrueNorthCentre they probable paid their friends to plant trees and then kickback money to trudeau crime family. or maybe Liberals will say  They were virtual trees . lol. crooks. all of them and they are stealing our kids and grandkids futures.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chef_shar: @TrueNorthCentre They can stick their trees! Our country and world are being destroyed by totalitarian goverments worldwide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrueNorthCentre: In the 2019 election, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau promised Canada would plant two billion trees as a major part of t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CPHO_Canada https://t.co/2j7AbSXfI3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheMarieOakes: The Montreal police are patrolling around the park. Some park-goers have said it feels intimidating having the police]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMarieOakes @WestphalianNews tell the cops to kick rocks.  they are loitering. maybe they should go catch some drug dealers murderers or rapists.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CPHO_Canada https://t.co/ZxggsXSTHf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@livingintheWack @CPHO_Canada @DrBonnieHenry they have been winging it all and the lies are incredible. funny how only unelected health bureaucrats are allowed to talk. but not other doctors . critical thinking is necessary. experimental vaccine. you are the guinea pigs. if you take it https://t.co/r7u0cfuD8n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alliebug2000 @CPHO_Canada people with two vaccines dying will be the next stories. without vaccine under 70 and in good health 99.7 percent chance of survival from covid. period.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HamptonByHilton i sent you the message and the only things i will accept for them. i am pissed off if you cant tell. they are old and the condition of their room and the cost of it is criminal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HamptonByHilton i just tried to speak to my parents and my mom is now sounding sick from the filth she has been locked in for the past 24 hours and my dad hung up on me.  you better pray nothing happens to them health wise or i will sue your organization. 2000.00 for that. sick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BarrettWilson6: Wow! https://t.co/05IeG9ccxu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rpoconnor: Tone-deaf TV doctor avoids own advice; goes to store instead of getting delivery. Failing to mind his own business, publicly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bpalmabee: @Catthy1111 @SharkawyMD Single parents, parents without child care or supports... not everyone is privileged to leave their]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@francoislegault what is this. raises for public sector workers ?  get rid of the extra 10 percent gas tax we pay in quebec. stop giving more than cost of living which is 2 percent per year since you say inflation is only 2 percent. liars. frauds you are a fascist dictator who will get voted out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Pw2rXSJaCk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau for charges for crimes against humanity and shitting in our charter and bill of rights. shame on all of you and i hope you get what coming to all of you. fascist nazi tyrant dictators. https://t.co/UhMIwIrrXU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[then wear one. doesnt. bother me but i wont wear it.  fascist state of Quebec canada where jewish people in montreal are asked for their papers to be outside after 8 pm. and the police actually enforce these dictates.  i vote to elect @francoislegault @fordnation @CPHO_Canada]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[and have accomplished nothing. still cases no matter what you try it wont work. so give up and open everything and masks should be optional. wait where is the proof for that statement that masks work.  they do not work but if you feel safer with one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Quebec @francoislegault is a racist dictator and a fascist. open the economy or provide peer reviewed proof that curfews and lockdowns help. oh wait you cant because you have had over a year of free reign over the province with your health bureaucrats]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PierrePoilievre wait until your 100 dollars a week in groceries is 2 or 300 for the same or less items . my groceries have gone up 20 or 30 percent overall and after they cost a lot more than that government will steal your property. make sure you protect our property rights.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_LoveMTB_ @JustinTrudeau https://t.co/DgFezm9e3W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lincolnmjay: Another scene from yesterdays Freedom Rally in Montreal, Quebec.   What is the deal with the pepper spray? Is this necess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MikeBarrettON: On the anniversary of MP Gord Brown's passing my thoughts are with Gord's family. Missing you, my friend. https://t.co/s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @niki_jay_1: @Dukesbetterhalf "Stay safe" = Stay compliant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@niki_jay_1 @Dukesbetterhalf we are doing this for your safety. as if we dont know how to take care of ourselves.  if we get sick we go to the hospital. a monkey could figure it out.  #covidlie https://t.co/6toYBgtswX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[toronto airport. @CPHO_Canada @CPHO_Canada Theresa Tam are you trying to kill my parents you sick fuck. @fordnation gonna get sued all health bureaucrats in toronto going to get sued.  #fuckcovid https://t.co/3TNGR1oYFb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GovCanHealth  there is more disease in these hotel rooms than covid . my parents will probably get sick from the filth rather than getting covid or whatever @HamptonInnBMINL we will sue you. have pictures and video of the filth. dont ever stay at the one by the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[they are at the hampton inn and suites.  covid jail. @JCCFCanada this place should be sued. parents havent been outside in over 24 hrs. food was cold and arrived at 7:35 pm some cold chicken and cold rice. prisoners in Canada eat better than that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my parents are in quarantine hotel bu Toronto airport. they just emailed me and the place is filthy feces on washroom door, some jam on countertop , small bar fridge smelled like rotting food and the coffee machine made rust flavoured coffee. they are in hell. @JustinTrudeau]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roccogalatilaw it would be funny if they all quit and then who would be there to defend poor frail @JoeBiden]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: Protests in Europe over lockdowns. Watch till the end.   https://t.co/7fbLa10a9D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @roccogalatilaw: Who would have thought that of all the Tyrannical -Isms to plague and persecute  the masses, from fascism, colonialism,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@niki_jay_1 @Dukesbetterhalf we are all in this together= except if you are a politician or health bureaucrat.  feels good to be out of twitter jail. got a 24 hour ban again for speaking my mind again. this platform is not freedom of expression. #twitterlies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TejaShahzia: When will the 6 month long lockdown in Toronto start to work?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @cpso_ca: CPSO Statement on Public Health Misinformation: https://t.co/P06W4uKdNK   Please continue to check our regularly updated COVID]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cpso_ca physicians must not put their jobs before their patients well being. ask your doctor for the ingredients for each of the vaccines and what each chemical does to you long term. oh they cant rushed to market and no long term testing on side effects. https://t.co/OgSoUbfJZN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @anthonyfurey: The College of Physicians and Surgeons of Ontario is threatening to investigate and discipline doctors who make comments]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dockaurG @NursesCanadian what happened to My body, my choice?? LOL. maybe only applies to sex changes in children and murder of unborn babies. wake up sheeple. we live in a sick society with sick evil politicians in charge. fire and charge them all. they are all communists and deserve nuremberg trial https://t.co/7cXDtuj7uB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jas72628343 @dockaurG ingredients in the so called vaccine. if the government or your doctor tells you to drink a cup of poison would you do it? just like a rushed shot. you cant sue the government or the drug companies when something happens to you from taking it. 99.7% chance of surviving covid https://t.co/CnFtxzQBxp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @dockaurG: #NoVaccinePassports!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jas72628343 @dockaurG vaccine passports are racist like other forms of ID. lol. https://t.co/b78RhpTplC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@covidedout @RachelNotley i feel sorry for all the teenagers and small business owners that committed suicide or those who died waiting for surgeries and those that did with covid not from covid. so many lies. blind sheeple believe MSM and evil people in government and hospital staff https://t.co/V5GDfdPNfD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@covidedout @RachelNotley ya ok and those masks that you think protect you do absolutely nothing. nurses and doctors arent dropping dead in hospitals. this is not a pandemic but you want people to be scared like it is one. all lies will be revealed and all those involved in the lies will go to prison https://t.co/MbCQYYFYwz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RachelNotley ya bring a couple of signs that say BLM and it should be fine.  no questions will be asked.  why are you a communist. go to a communist country and you will fit in. you would t survive in a country like China etc. #Nuremberg2 for you and your commie fiends. https://t.co/Oj62YoOn7h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrueNorthCentre: ChinaAid observed nine instances of the government demolishing churches against the wishes of the congregations and hu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrueNorthCentre: The government has no business telling Canadians what they can and cant post online.  Members of Parliament need to s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PierrePoilievre: Trudeau said he admires China's basic dictatorship, called Castro a "remarkable leader"  said "freedom of expressio]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jkenney @jcmincalgary Kenney you are a communist NOT a conservative.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MaximeBernier: I voted against this alarmist nonsense.   Jai vot contre ces sottises alarmistes.  https://t.co/WoYoPULOus]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheBabylonBee @jcmincalgary what the fuck.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SpencerFernando @jcmincalgary is this for real? https://t.co/uCp07CI6sI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SpencerFernando: We Must Reject Curfews. https://t.co/Ez5ehrKQLq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RebelNewsOnline: At yesterday's press conference, Ontario Premier Doug Ford hinted at  a "fourth wave" and vaccine-resistant variants.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>