<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@RamblinAmblin @cagedinpod @FilmFloggers @WDStoryTime @TIDRPodshow @HarpyHourPod @InebriatedInput @Twisted_Pod @ShonenFlopCast @plot_family @OchoOrtizDisney @DrunkTheory @KudzuKillerspod @FNWFpodcast @coldcallers @GameForAMovieP1 @UGottaSeeThisPC @LadiesFrightPod @juryroompodcast @ReverieCrimePod @TIHIPodcast @MalicePodcast @CampfireClassi1 @Ray_Harryhausen @schlockandawe1 @biglittlechefGP @100thingspod @bestfilmeverpod @PodcastRiddle @KittyCostanza @ThePCCPodcast @WRatedPod @SDDFilmPodcast @TheEnigmaGriff @paulngriffshow @JawsForAMinute @TeaVTimePod My latest episode @PresenterAlex shared his wonderful experiences at various Comic Cons in the UK!  Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH I nominate: @markandmeuk @PillowsPod @PresenterAlex @ajblackwriter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   It was only a matter of time before a medical series landed on the podcast! This week, @robertmwallis j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PresenterAlex: This was such a great podcast to guest on!!! Catch me nerding out about one of my favourite things!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: We love a Comic Con here at Ramblin, so very excited to hear the latest @FandomentalsPod all about UK-based Cons!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Now!  I'm joined by @PresenterAlex as he shares some of his experiences at various Comic Cons here in the UK  #Podcast #Interview #Comiccon  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/PNKjxbA9O2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: NEW EPISODE! Join us as we invite @TheEnigmaGriff from @paulngriffshow to dig into the Tom Hanks-Shelley Long comedy 'TH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Tomorrow  In the meantime be sure to catch up on previous episodes including #StarTrek #Birdwatching #Running and more! Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH https://t.co/FA6UB3KEtn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ajblackwriter: For links both here and across the Pond, check out the page on my in-development personal website, which also has a few]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ajblackwriter: My second book, Star Trek, History and Us, is available from today in the U.K. in paperback, as well as on Kindle.  Limi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ajblackwriter: Also, if you want to hear me chattering about the book and #StarTrek in general, listen to me on @FandomentalsPod. https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE!  This week we're joined by @TheMovieNerdSB and things get heated as we discuss the equally fiery confron]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: #startrek with @ajblackwriter author of Star Trek, History and Us: A Reflection of the Past and Present Throughout the Franchise is out now on a variety of podcasting apps.   Beam it up into your ears now!   Links here:https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH https://t.co/3qNUyc8QPx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WRatedPod: Have you caught up with our Razzies special yet?  Daisy and Clare talk all thing Dolittle, Fantasy Island, The Wrong Missy a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #Podcast fans! Check out the show that explores various Fandoms throughout pop culture!  Previous topics include #Birdwatching #Disney #Jaws #Anime and more!  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: #StarTrek with @ajblackwriter is out now!  Here's a small clip from the episode where Tony starts to unpack one of the many reason's the show has had such a long lasting legacy https://t.co/0oPsOJsWb7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   Okurr! @DaisyVicEdwards joins the podcast this week to talk to me about #RuPaulsDragRace (US). We also]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PresenterAlex: So awesome to be a guest on this!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just finished recording a new episode with @PresenterAlex   I can't wait to share it with you all!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Podcast Fans! Check out the show that explores various Fandoms in Popular Culture!  The most recent episode covers #StarTrek and previous episode include #Running #Jaws #Pinball #BTS and more!  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/UibpfyBdiW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE  This week we're joined by @wickedsister69 to talk about one of the greatest jump-scares of all time, and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: #StarTrek with @ajblackwriter is out now!  We chat about all things #StarTrek and his latest book Star Trek, History and Us: Reflections of the Present and Past Throughout the Franchise  Podcast Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr  Book Link: https://t.co/riRUiHcnJe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for the feedback Andrew! This thread right here is what Fandomentals is all about  https://t.co/Ow5cR76YoX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ajblackwriter: ICYMI: I popped up on @FandomentalsPod this week talking all things #StarTrek and my new book Star Trek, History and Us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: https://t.co/y284FwEcay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ajblackwriter: This was enormous fun.   A wide ranging chat about #StarTrek and my new book Star Trek, History and Us, now available he]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Now I'm joined by returning guest @ajblackwriter to talk about #StarTrek   Check it out on #Spotify #ApplePodcasts  #Podomatic #GooglePodcasts and more! Available via these links: https://t.co/0Fyak7Ok4Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Tomorrow  It's time to boldly go where no one has gone before... https://t.co/GganSFQs9f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: NEW EPISODE - Join us as we take a look at Steven Spielberg's 1985 adaptation of Alice Walker's Pulitzer-Prize winning n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was reminded of my lovely chat about Birdwatching with @LGTHBlog today after spotting some ducklings  I'm curisous, what kind of Birdwatching do you enjoy? https://t.co/iUKw3ILjZS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WRatedPod: You suck! We suck! We all suck for vampires! Wait...  Tune into our brand new episode discussing Twilight parody Vampires Su]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: *EPISODE 9 IS HERE!!* @SimonHarknesstv joins us to chat about comedians going serious AND funny all in one w/Sofia Coppola']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE  Sarah  MJ are joined by @talkaboutfilm to discuss drunken boat antics and just how rich Hooper is!   LI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's a clip from the latest episode about Birdwatching  @LGTHBlog explains one of the main reasons that she enjoys this particular hobby  Full Episode is Available via the Link: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/5diP9mnSGx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keep an eye out for this episode next week! https://t.co/3pepEQDbRX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you enjoyed latest episode of Fandomentals be sure to check out Lucy's Podcast @TeaVTimePod    Get it on #soundcloud: https://t.co/Iw1xtBB0jC  Get it on #Spotify: https://t.co/n2PRmYpI0U]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Birdwatching with @LGTHBlog from @TeaVTimePod is out now! #podcast #birdwatching   Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   This week @roddersj04 joins the pod to chat NBC's hit comedy series #Superstore. We discuss why it's th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoying the podcast? Then why not leave a 5 Star Review on your favourite podcasting app?  If you do, let me know so I can thank you on the show! It's the least I can do https://t.co/EIKiILSSNj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Birdwatching with @LGTHBlog from @TeaVTimePod is now available  Check it out on your favourite podcasting app!  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE  Sarah  MJ are joined by an actual shark expert in the form of @CooperPalaeo to discuss the latest #Jaws]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #Podcast Fans!  Check out the show that explores various Fandoms! Previous topics include #Pinball, #Musicals, #Jaws, #Running  More!  Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Brand New Episode Out Now!  Grab your binoculars and listen to a lovely chat with @LGTHBlog from @TeaVTimePod about Birdwatching!  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/qabx3F5bNk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: *EPISODE 8 IS HERE* @DanielJLayton joins us to chat about two fish-out-of-water tales: everyone loves #AustinPowers but who]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: And here's the latest @FandomentalsPod with host of @TeaVTimePod, @LGTHBlog talking all things birdwatching!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LGTHBlog: Do you want to hear me get REALLY BORING about birds?? Of course you do   Thanks for having me on the pod @HarleyMumford! It]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Now  I'm joined by @LGTHBlog from @TeaVTimePod to discuss Birdwatching.  Grab your coat and binoculars and join us in exploring one of this wonderful topic. #podcast #hobbies #birdwatching   Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   This week @ScreenQueue joins the pod to discuss the utterly wonderful #Fleabag! We discuss all things H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: Happy Easter, have a BRAND NEW episode! We're donning our Deerstalker Hats to deduce what we can from Barry Levinson' s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Tomorrow  Be sure to catch up on the latest episodes here: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: **IT'S TUESDAY, IT'S NEW EPISODE DAY!!!** @FilmFan1971 joins us to get a little musical with two hilarious pastiches that k]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE  Sarah  MJ are joined by Gary from @FilmChoose podcast to discuss the latest #Jaws moment! Featuring ico]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Here's a clip from my latest episode with @adharanand from @WayoftheRunner talking about Ultra Running  Full Episode Available via these links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/dL9WZHZ8L0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the last episode we talked about Running  So I'm curious, are any of you guys runners? If so, what kind of running? What do you love about it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another episode recorded  I can't wait to share with you all https://t.co/j8wLC3ueIy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   Better late than never! This week, @ItsSophieDavies joins the pod to talk about #BoJackHorseman. We dis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WRatedPod: Grab yourself a dunkaccino and settle down for our latest episode on Jack and Jill. We talk with @London_Lou as we try to es]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Running with Adharanand Finn from @WayoftheRunner is available now!  Learn about the cultures and life lessons found in Running as Adharanand talks us through his time in countries such as Kenya, Japan and more!  Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE  Sarah  MJ are joined by @HomeOneBlaine to discuss Hooper's arrival at the Brody table! Talking more sne]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: *EPISODE 6 IS HERE!* @HelenLOHara joins us to chat about two underrated/underseen gems:  ZAZ's 2nd film and @KFremonCraig ']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: As mentioned in our latest episode, here is teen Andy's home-made 'Back to the Future' polo shirt that never made it to]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Brand New Episode Out Now!  Ever wondered why someone would get into Ultra Running? Check out my conversation about Running with host of @WayoftheRunner @adharanand to find out  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Now!  Check out my conversation about Running with author @adharanand from @WayoftheRunner   Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beand New Episode Out Tomorrow  Catch up on the latest episode which involves a crossover with @RamblinAmblin very own @Josh_Glenn where explore The Matrix  Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH https://t.co/aRqqK3nedp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's crossover time!! Check out the latest episode of @RamblinAmblin to hear me chat with Andrew and Josh about Back to the Future https://t.co/P3cNn2Vp97]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Episode Out Monday  Catch up on the latest episodes here: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE!  Sarah  MJ are joined by @frontage2 to talk about this lovely scene involving Brody  son. We get into]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod: NEW EPISODE   You can have episode 5 early, as a treat.  What a joy it was to discuss #ComeDineWithMe with @Presenter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Josh_Glenn @DKsMum @RamblinAmblin https://t.co/9OMtAm3sRP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out this snippet from my chat with @Josh_Glenn from @RamblinAmblin about #TheMatrix   Links to the Full Episode: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/VYMGHdBOnv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #Podcast Fans!  Check out the show that explores various Fandoms across pop culture!  Previous topics include, Disney Animation, #BTS , The Rocky Franchise, Non-Fiction Writing and more!  Links:https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: **IT'S HERE - EPISODE FIVE** Film critic @TomJBeasley says "YES" to joining us as we delve into two underrated modern rom-c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Previous Chris Liepe has a Brand New Course with @PeripheryBand very own @SPENCESOTELO   Learn More: https://t.co/RUb45jYqZG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WRatedPod: Do you like pink glitter, comic sans, and have Brattitude?  Well, youre in luck. Join us and special guest @billiemelissa_]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/x5kgA6eVbS https://t.co/yo4Aqb3CLS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next episode of Fandomentals is edited and ready to drop in a weeks time.  Be sure to catch up with previous episodes including our latest where @RamblinAmblin very own @Josh_Glenn explains why you're wrong about #TheMatrix sequels  Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #Podcast Fans!  Check out the show that explores Fandoms across pop culture! Previous topics include #TheMatrix, #Wrestling, #Pinball, #Godzilla and more!  Links:https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   This week, @LGTHBlog and @kirac_98 head to the Missouri Ozarks to chat all things, you guessed it, #Oza]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: *EPISODE FOUR IS LIVE!* @SophieAthawes joins us to chat about two gems where sporting apparatus help overcome insurmountabl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JawsForAMinute: NEW EPISODE  This week @sarahbuddery  @MJSmith891 dive into the scene in which Mrs Kintner confronts Brody and the s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: New Episode Out Now!  Enter The Matrix with my latest guest @Josh_Glenn from @RamblinAmblin   Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr https://t.co/azOzLkcNeW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey podcast fans! Check out the show that explores various fandoms throughout pop culture!  Previous topics include #TheMatrix, Non-Fiction Writing, #DisneyAnimation, DJ's and many more topics  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Now  I'm joined by @Josh_Glenn from @RamblinAmblin to discuss #thematrix   Check it out via #Podomatic or wherever you get your podcasts  Links: https://t.co/0Fyak7wJdr Podomatic Stream: https://t.co/inY1TX7h8P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: HEY YOU GUYS - NEW EPISODE!  Friend  fellow Warwick Film Grad Seb Jones joins us to chart the map of Richard Donner's "]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Episode Out Monday  In the meantime catch up on the last episode where I got incredible insight and tips on exploring your voice with Chris Liepe  #podcast #chrisliepe #vocalcoach #singing #music #voice   Links:https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TeaVTimePod:  NEW EPISODE   This week, @Buck3131 joins @LGTHBlog to chat about a little show (/sarcasm) called #WandaVision! This w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RamblinAmblin: #FF Show some love to our pals, collaborators, supporters and previous guests!    @JawsForAMinute @FandomentalsPod @WRat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Episode Arriving on Monday  @RamblinAmblin fans get ready! https://t.co/yNTKnsE4bS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PillowsPod: *EPISODE 3 IS LIVE* @scottwritesfilm  @clarisselou delve into the world of "the office" with a 1960's musical comedy class]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to sink your teeth into another episode of @JawsForAMinute https://t.co/3A7uSU8O3C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Explore the joys of signing with my guest Chris Liepe on the latest podcast episode!  Available via the links here:https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #Podcast Fans  Check out the show thats explores Fandoms across popular culture.  Previous topics include #singing #eddievanhalen #weightlifting #Jaws and more!  Available here: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Check out the latest episode of the show where I get invaluable advice from Vocal Coach and YouTube sensation Chris Liepe  Links: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH  #singing #podcast #music #vocalcoach #chrisliepe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WRatedPod: Its here - part TWO of our deep dive on I Know Who Killed me with @WhitlockAndPope!!  Youve heard all about the plot - now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Here's a clip from the latest guest on the show Chris Liepe   He shares his greatest piece of advice for anyone who wants to learn how to sing  Links to the Episode: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH https://t.co/a8c01v8YWL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to dive into the scene behind that awesome theme song!!  Check out the latest episode from @JawsForAMinute today! https://t.co/gY20ifQkPg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Singing with Chris Liepe is now available to listen too here: https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH  If you haven't already be sure to check out his Youtube Channel here: https://t.co/nxm8rUCIbJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey #podcast fans! Check out the show that explores various fandoms with passionate and insightful guests!   Previous topics include #Godzilla , #BTS , #Teaching, #Singing and more!  https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another episode of @TeaVTimePod is here! Grab you tipple of choice and enjoy the show https://t.co/9yj0mJu8PL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Now  I chat with Chris Liepe (Vocal Coach) about his journey through music and the joys of teaching others to sing  Links:https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH https://t.co/1KRRxNqBNB https://t.co/MjVKPpt6aZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brand New Episode Out Today!  I talk with Vocal Coach Chris Liepe about his passion for Signing  Hear from the guy who's been helping so many people online to discover their voice  Links:https://t.co/Z0GzQxSsTH]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>