<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[ "I feel that we are more than ready to write the next chapter of L'Oral history." Nicolas Hieronimus officially takes over as Chief Executive of the L'Oral Group and has started his first journey with our employees in our Ormes and Noveal factories. Discover his visit  https://t.co/5X1v1EPSgT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @4womeninscience: You are a Doctor in #science and want to propose your project to the world of science? Submit your application for the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Katheri80943054 Yes you are :) Have a nice day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#MondayMotivation   Our brand #LorealParis is celebrating the 50th anniversary of the most powerful slogan "Because We're Worth It"! and for the occasion, @ViolaDavis has a message for you: you are worth it. #WorthIt https://t.co/7W9CuV9jTP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wondering who are the creators of our brands? Get ready to discover their inspiring stories  learn how they create the #beautythatmoves the world through entrepreneurship, innovation, and passion!    Stay tuned with our new Rendez-Vous: One day, One founder. https://t.co/ZuT62zAKDo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stmacqua @ImogenRCoePhD @JulieSLalonde @iHollaback Congratulations on your training.  Together, we can fight against street haressment!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@actresskaycee @violadavis Thank you @actresskaycee, but credit goes to our fantastic brand @LOrealParisUSA ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@animalsony To do this for a whole group all at once would be a massive undertaking. Its important to start somewhere, and the experience gained by Garnier through the Leaping Bunny approval process will now be shared across all brands of the LOral Group. 2/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@animalsony The LOral Group is made up of many brands and the Group as a whole is not approved as cruelty free under the Leaping Bunny programme. Leaping Bunny approval is a very thorough process. For Garnier, for example, more than 500 suppliers and 3,000 ingredients had to be checked.1/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@animalsony Hello, LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals. We are for a world without animal testing. Since 1989, we have not tested the safety of our products on animals, 14 years before regulations required us to do so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LOrealUSA: LOral USA will open a brand-new, state-of-the-art second headquarters in the Los Angeles area in early 2022.   Our 25-ac]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our teams are our heroes.   They are the foundation of the way we work at L'Oral, and their #health and #safety are our core values. Malcolm, Global VP of Health and Safety, explains how we keep our teams and front-line workers safe and healthy during the global pandemic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LOrealUSA: I use three words to describe my vision: continuity, confidence and ambition, Nicolas Hieronimus, LOrals incoming globa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@libbyroach1 @JulieSLalonde @iHollaback Congrats @libbyroach1  Together, lets fight against street harassement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ImogenRCoePhD @JulieSLalonde @iHollaback Congrats @ImogenRCoePhD ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you ready to plunge into the history of Notre-Dame de Paris?   We are excited to launch Notre-Dame de Paris, the Experience, a virtual immersion using #HistoPad augmented reality technology developed by @Histovery at the World Expo in Dubai.   @francedubai2020 #Expo2020 https://t.co/BseLS4M9uq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lilzeon @ESCP_bs Good luck to the students from @ESCP_bs! We're thrilled to invent the future of beauty together, with technology that opens up a new era of possibilities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Powerful video of Humanitys impacts on Earth since 1984.   A warning signal which reminds us that we have only a little less than a decade to act. We must join forces to address the global #environmental emergency. https://t.co/LVHoKxfWOV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GauravModified By 2030, 100% of the plastic used in our product packaging will be from recycled or biobased sources. Find out more about our commitments to preserve natural resources here   https://t.co/wkoHOaZUN8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GauravModified Hello. We understand your concern. In 2007 LOral deployed a responsible packaging policy for product and transport packaging, extended to point-of-sale displays in 2015. We reduce the amount of resources by optimizing size and weight, and search for more sustainable materials.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dr__Guess By 2030, 100% of the plastic used in our product packaging will be from recycled or biobased sources. Find out more about our commitments to preserve natural resources here  https://t.co/wkoHOaZUN8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dr__Guess Hi, thank you for your question. In 2007 LOral deployed a responsible packaging policy for product and transport packaging, extended to point-of-sale displays in 2015. We reduce the amount of resources by optimizing size and weight, and search for more sustainable materials.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justplainbrayan Since 2014 shampoos, bath gels and many make up products made in China have not required animal testing. From the beginning of May 2021, imported non-functional products (with a safety certificate from their country of origin), will no longer require animal testing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justplainbrayan Hello, L'Oral does not carry out any animal testing in our labs in China! For a decade, we have been working with the Chinese authorities to adopt non-animal methods so that China has removed  animal testing requirement for the majority of cosmetics sold in the country.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JayBec2015 Hello, the fact that not all our brands are certified does not mean that products are tested on animals. However, some L'Oral brands are still not Cruelty Free because they are sold in markets where regulation requires animal testing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some of our brands are already PETA certified (IT Cosmetics, Urban Decay, NYX Professional) and Garnier was recently certified by Cruelty Free International (Leaping Bunny).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miamillerauthor Hello Mia, thank you for your comment. The fact that not all our brands are certified does not mean that products are tested on animals. Garnier recently underwent certification and we are now considering which brand will go next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gabbaliciouss Hi Joan,  The fact that not all our brands are certified does not mean that products are tested on animals. Garnier recently underwent certification and we are now considering which brand will go next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YvonneHooper20 Hi Yvonne, thank you for question. Since 1989, LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals, 14 years before regulations required us to do so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarollynR40 It's our wish too and that's why we are working with the HSI in different international forums to encourage authorities to move to animal free methods for testing cosmetic products.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BECAUSE OUR PLANET IS WORTH IT', L'Oral Paris is launching its sustainability program committed to reducing its carbon emissions by 50% per product by 2030 and investing 10 million euros in environmental projects.  #LOrealForTheFuture #OurPlanetIsWorthIt #LOrealParis https://t.co/jciJjO21H2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GaynorRogers311 Actually, since 2014, many make up products made in China no longer require animal testing. From the beginning of May 2021, imported non-functional products will no longer require it, providing they have a safety certificate. More information here: https://t.co/cabtEgcbYQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarollynR40 During this time, weve trained around 100 Chinese scientists, and 50 different organizations in how to use non-animal methods for themselves.  Have a great day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarollynR40 Hello Carollyn,  We believe that by being present in China we can help drive real change. In fact, for over 10 years weve been working hand-in-hand with Chinese authorities and scientists to get non-animal methods recognized and replace animal testing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@monchichigirl1 Hello,  LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals.  Since 1989, we have not tested the safety of our products on animals, 14 years before regulations required us to do so. Have a great day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LucyWil80023672 Hello Lucy,  L'Oral does not test any of its products on animals, nor carry out any animal testing in our labs in China. Have a great day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notmeghana Hello Meghna,  LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals. We are for a world without animal testing. Have a great day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We are proud to announce a new nomination to the Groups Executive Committee.   Asmita Dubey is appointed Chief Digital Officer and member of the Groups Executive Committee. She succeeds Lubomira Rochet, after 7 years at LOral.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LOrealCommitted: Today we celebrate #EarthDay: a reminder that we have only a decade to act and that we must join forces to address the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today is Earth Day -   At L'Oral, our commitment is to ensure that our activities are respectful of the planetary boundaries   #LOrealfortheFuture #EarthDay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@7798i Hello Selvy, thank you for your question.  LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals. Have a great day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CreativityandInnovationDay   In today's world, creativity  innovation are key to transforming the beauty experience.   Discover our list of 5 L'Oral groundbreaking beauty innovations over the years. https://t.co/TkAMLM7zD8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some of our brands are already PETA certified (IT Cosmetics, Urban Decay, NYX Professional) and Garnier was recently certified by Cruelty Free International (Leaping Bunny). Have a good day 2/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amparo64229141 Hello, we are not but the fact that not all our brands are certified does not mean that products are tested on animals. Garnier recently underwent certification and we are now considering which brand will go next. 1/2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StudyatIESEG @IESEG Congratulation to Anas Gmez, Daniela Benitez  Margarida Anacleto ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@harsh_taggar Congrats ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Men are much more discerning about their skin, about the fragrances that they wear, about their hair"   Vismay Sharma, SAPMENA President at L'Oral discusses future beauty trends  consumer behavior.   Thank you @CNBCi and @_karengilchrist. https://t.co/H2MV1aTORX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wwd: The @Loreal executive outlined key changes at the company under his leadership during the groups annual general meeting. https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chief Digital Officer @ljubomira at L'Oral will join the @IRGRealGrowth webinar series to talk about her leadership journey and L'Oral's digital transformation.   Friday April 23 at 2PM BST. Register here: https://t.co/Bn7LnF6EKm #digitaltransformation #humanizinggrowth https://t.co/BPb0QHPnpB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lengyankanren @ljubomira @IRGRealGrowth Thank you for your interest @lengyankanren. In fact, the link is not working correctly. Please find here the correct link: https://t.co/uc4s22SVzk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Let's take a look at the Ourika Community Gardens by #YSLBeauty in the sun-soaked part of the Moroccan Atlas mountains.   By 2025, 100% of new launches will contain at least one ingredient sourced from the gardens. https://t.co/B6JoObnaXI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: Nicolas Hieronimus is set to take over as chief executive at the beauty giant. He faces no crisis, but challenges do loom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[First quarter 2021 sales] Check out @cnbccharlotte's interview with Jean-Paul Agon, chairman and CEO of L'Oreal, on @cnbcipr. They discuss how make-up sales are rebounding in high-vaccination countries like Israel and the US.  https://t.co/ZV34FiMDNl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @voguebusiness: Skincare is an outperformer, with sales up 22 per cent. @Loreal chairman and chief executive Jean-Paul Agon believes tha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philina_puig Thank you @philina_puig ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaelhugs Thank you for your message @michaelhugs. LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals. Since 1989, we have not tested the safety of our products on animals, 14 years before regulations required us to do so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Anna96062340 Hello @Anna96062340, thanks for reaching out. At LOral, we care for animal welfare and do not test on animals. We are for a world without animal testing. Since 1989, we have not tested the safety of our products on animals, 14 years before regulations required us to do so.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jjadecita Thanks for your message @jjadecita, we understand your concern. L'Oral stopped testing on animals in 1989.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your VOICE has the power to make a difference.   On #InternationalVoiceDay, discover whose voices inspired @ladygaga, the new face of #ValentinoVoceViva https://t.co/z0r39O2VRy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[First quarter 2021 sales] LOral #Finance: Remarkable growth in Asia Pacific at +23.8% like-for-like, with mainland China at +37.9%, and strong recovery in North America : https://t.co/IxVggxNPhu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[First quarter 2021 sales] LOral #Finance: Significantly outperforming the market with three Divisions in double-digit growth : https://t.co/2qmRIeQHC9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[First quarter 2021 sales] LOral #Finance: Sales at 7.61 billion euros, +10.2% like-for-like : https://t.co/2qmRIeQHC9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[First quarter 2021 sales] LOral #Finance: Strong return to growth at +10.2% like-for-like.   https://t.co/2qmRIeQHC9 https://t.co/txraoXu9tI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pixels OR eye-shadow pigments?    Take a look at this interpretation of Van Gogh's and Vermeer's artwork from our brand #shuuemura. #InternationalArtDay #ShuArtistry https://t.co/Dmiy5Mag1A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mehmetozgun_ Hi, Mehmet! LOral does not carry out any test on animals anywhere in the world. LOral has been at the forefront of alternative methods for over 30 years. To learn more about our policy, click here: https://t.co/ouupp8sD63. Have a nice day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EduGold Thanks :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered where your luxury iconic beauty products are made?   They are taken care of by our #operations team in our Lassigny plant in France, which is 100% dedicated to makeup for our luxury division. https://t.co/kGfZOuZnYp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VogueParis: Elie Saab is launching a makeup collaboration with LOral Paris https://t.co/J3QlI1m5Oc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Our brand #Cacharel has teamed with @Inspiringgirlsf an international NGO, to inspire young girls to aim high in their career choices and fulfill their true potential through the power of role models.  Did you know? https://t.co/vWgzm30Wp5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlottearnal No, we do not test any of ours products or ingredients on animals, nor carry out any animal testing in our labs in China.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#RamadanKareem to all those celebrating across the country and around the world! https://t.co/G6gMSnjt6w]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[During Anti-Street Harassment Week, #LorealParis encourages EVERYONE to fight street harassment.   Get trained on the 5Ds methodology to learn how to react to street harassment: https://t.co/fchVCk8zEl    #WeStandUp @CelineDion @CamilaAccess @Nikolajcw @Ajanaomi_king @iHollaback https://t.co/9PsqOaeBMr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[  Take part in the L'Oral Research  Innovation Scientific MasterClass: an event dedicated to #startups, giving you the possibility to learn or develop scientific skills  meet experts from the industry to reveal the #beauty of your tech.   Sign up   https://t.co/kHXjfovM6V https://t.co/PRFhEFjL3g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LOral does not test any of its cosmetic products nor ingredients in any of its brands on animals. Some of our brands are already PETA certified (IT Cosmetics, Urban Decay, NYX Professional) and Garnier was recently certified by Cruelty Free International (Leaping Bunny).]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaneyN123 Thank you for your question Jane. At LOral, we care for animal welfare and do not test on animals. The fact that not all our brands are certified does not mean that products are tested on animals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ANAmarketers We look forward to listening to @ljubomira on @ANAmarketers ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Together, we can contribute to a world without animal testing.   Listen to Gladys, she has been working at LOral for 18 years in product safety and has been passionate about developing non-animal methods.  #ForAWorldWithNoAnimalTesting https://t.co/JwhMgbsVAU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KathyRo44136915 Hi Kathy! This is LOrals corporate account and we do not deal with products directly. Please contact L'Oral directly on its website https://t.co/dmN0qQRiYT. Have a beautiful day! Anna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Samba23413 Hello, the website is https://t.co/dmN0qQRiYT. You have to choose your Location (top right) and then select the appropriate country and service. Have a beautiful day!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@imbapcap Hello, Thank you for expressing your interest in L'Oral!  This is LOrals corporate account and we do not deal with partnerships directly. You can check out our website to learn more: https://t.co/3DZxs6ndzS Have a great day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Samba23413 Hello @Samba23413  We are sorry to hear this! This is LOrals corporate account and we do not deal with products directly. Please contact L'Oral Paris on its website to get support. Have a nice day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 40 years ago, we led the development of human reconstructed skin that is more accurate for analyzing how cosmetic ingredients  products will behave on human skin.    Meet Rodrigo, CEO of Episkin in Brazil  #ForAWorldWithNoAnimalTesting https://t.co/caK4TI3Rnt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over the past few years, China has removed the requirement to do any animal testing for the great majority of cosmetics sold in the country.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charlottearnal Hi Charlotte, Thank you for your question. For over 10 years we have been working with the Chinese authorities to adopt non-animal methods for all cosmetic products.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ What are you doing on April 13th? Register for the LOral Scientific Masterclass, an event dedicated to #startups, and meet the best scientists of the beauty industry!    Sign-up here: https://t.co/aylfSdZUSq  #BeautyTech #BeautyScience #ScMC https://t.co/Wbey1gwkez]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At LOral, we care for animal welfare and we do not test on animals.    Listen to Valrie, Director of alternative methods  reconstructed skin.   #ForAWorldWithNoAnimalTesting https://t.co/zey6eehQnq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DenyzeDArcy Hi, Denyze! We're sorry to hear this. This is L'Oral corporate account and we don't deal with products nor suppliers directly. Can you tell us more about your situation and where you are located, please? We'll redirect you to our appropriate service. Thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KayleighBlaker Thank you Kayleigh  Keep safe too!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KayleighBlaker Hi Kayleigh, This is LOrals corporate account and we do not deal with products directly. Please contact L'Oral UK on its website (https://t.co/Kzch5ra1Ad) and at this email address UKconsumeradvice@loreal.com. Have a beautiful day, Anna]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 30 000 hair pros, hair geeks  hair lovers gathered online to attend the live reveal of a haircare innovation: METAL DETOX.   Rendez-vous on Youtube to know more: https://t.co/w2nnIilV1n   #lorealpro #metaldetox #byprosforpros]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@andychester_ Hello @andychester_, thank you for your message. The credit goes to our great brand @LOrealParisUSA !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LawSchoolOnline @LValloor Hi @LawSchoolOnline, we love our new mascot! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ChristineDobb16 Thank you ! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FMTYAustralia Thank you for your support ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Are you ready to discover our new disruptive #innovation that truly changes coloration, balayage  lightening?    STAY TUNED...  #lorealpro #metaldetox #gamechanger #byprosforpros https://t.co/WHA0nCL4pw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@slbeckett Hi @slbeckett, Thank you for your suggestion!  This is LOrals corporate account and we do not deal with products directly :) Please contact @lorealparisfr directly on its website   Have a beautiful day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rocknroller1962 We're glad to know that our product is a part of your nightly routine, thank you for this sweet message!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Parabens, what are they for? Should we avoid them?     We answer all your questions about parabens here: https://t.co/yxFPLxMrL9  #InsideOurProducts https://t.co/ZC4ruwck1W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@10043535_ Hello, thank you for your question. In order to know if your product contains alcohol, we invite you to check the list of ingredients on the packaging. To learn more: https://t.co/29n5Wn66nN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@orangulandtrust Thank you for your support  @orangulandtrust!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>