<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Busy day at a busy dock, one out, two in at the start of the ebb tide  #ships #docks #pilot #shiphandling #pilotage #maritime https://t.co/3zYokGU9GG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCMM_UK: JOB OPPORTUNITY  @HCMM_UK  is creating a new full-time position entitled Education  Outreach Manager. For more information,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: ABP News Release: Humber Freeport Bid Launched https://t.co/zf4UtYEPCa #Freeports #ABPHumber #Humber #KeepingBritainTrading]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Hullhistorynews: "In the deep midwinter..." One of the Humber lightships #frozen in at Brough Haven 1963 (Local Studies George Priestle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ready to depart from Immingham lock on the MV Bulker Bee 10, waiting for the Knutsen sisters Eli and Birgit to pass by before being given clearance to proceed #ships #shiphandling #pilot #piloting #harbour #maritime #maritimeindustry https://t.co/AsM79JgXLe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nephropseu: Shipping density out of hte Humber.  Clear delinetion of offshore windfarms. #RenewableEnergy https://t.co/T0daibWSD8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Departure from Hulls William Wright Dock this morning on the general cargo vessel SWE-CARRIER, bound for Sweden  #ships #shipping #pilot #Humber #humberpilot #shiphandling #Hull #timelapse https://t.co/HWu3nc3eRc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CEXHCC: The Red Ensign is flying at @Hullccnews today to mark Merchant Navy Day, to raise awareness of our nations dependence on profe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCMM_UK: HCMM Announcement - Young Officers' Committee   We are pleased to announce the creation of our new Young Officers' Committee]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super Saturday dance around Goole Dock on the Russian vessel Mekhanik Pyatlin #ships #timelapse #humber #pilots #humberpilots #goole #shiphandling https://t.co/XMtUfG9NYm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cargo of steel inbound for Groveport on the River Trent. When fully loaded we have to ride the flood tide and time our arrival for HW, maintaining just 20cm minimum UKC in daylight hours #shiphandling  #humberpilots #navigablemud @PDPorts https://t.co/QlPozzRt7O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hicapted: Shout out to Capt Simon who is driving this pilot launch in Sydney, Australia. 336m boxship trying to safely embark the Pilot]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hicapted @philbent Four to five normally depending on speed of the ship and strength of the tide....unless we have to stop and anchor for bunkers which adds a couple of hours on]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taken a few days ago, departure from Flixborough on the River Trent, outbound for sea, a 45 mile journey to the pilot station #humberpilot #shipping #ships #TimeLapse #springtide #navigation https://t.co/NQm1Y8rPVv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCMM_UK: A first for @HCMM_UK; today we held the first ever virtual Court Meeting, with the election of our new Master Captain @chadder]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excellent service from @atombeers...ordered online at 8 this morning and delivered for free by 3pm !! #supportlocal https://t.co/5ivqCPzRUc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IainAMackinnon: @jimwaterson Shipping, meanwhile, carries on with its vital role of bringing in 95% of all the imports which the countr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Thurston1799: Congratulations to the finalists of the #Thurston sponsored East  North Yorkshire Pool Series. Event 1 winner Ed Cunneyw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hicapted: This is how we go to work.   Now imagine this at night, in the dark, pouring rain, ship rolling. You never see those videos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wf4pIFgyXG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You know its a big ship when you cant really see your tugs from the bridge and the main deck fills the screen on your time lapse ! Just a steady 158000 tonne, 48m beam and an eye watering 23m climb to negotiate to get off the thing  #ships #Humber #pilot #training https://t.co/0lbrJv0OwU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another successful evening as a @careersatsea ambassador at the new @MaritimeHumber college...plenty of positive conversations, and a nice cup of coffee too  https://t.co/mIiugDAhT3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MTaylorsYork: Thank you for your wonderful hospitality.  Such a joy to be a guest in our own Hall.  A wonderful way to start the countd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another fantastic Christmas Lunch of the North East Outport of the @HCMM_UK  at the @MTaylorsYork where we welcomed the Master of the company, and other esteemed guests! https://t.co/eOjzi8M9PZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doing my bit for #careersatsea  https://t.co/dHcpfrmb3H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philbent  I always find them extra 7 thousandths make all the difference]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can we go back and do it all again ! Absolute scenes !! Cricket...bloody hell  #ashes #BenStokes #TestCricket #history #bestdayever https://t.co/9zc69An7va]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Howzzit from this angle @benstokes38 ?? https://t.co/UMUC53dc3D]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Robb_Robinson: Come along and find out more about the Viola Project. This vessel sailed off to war from Hull in September 1914, was inv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats odd, even  #ships #language #pilots #humberpilot https://t.co/XVuFs6XOlv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Youll never get a job looking out the window  #careersatsea #ships #shipping #humberpilot #riverpilot #shiphandling #sunset https://t.co/nHWxTD5h1g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some snaps of my first few days back on the river...piloting ships in the summer months is an actual pleasure  #pilotlife #ShipsInPics #ships #foodonships #riverhumber #humberpilot https://t.co/1M5GX3UtCk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get behind this project...Hull's maritime history is both significant and extraordinary and deserves to be celebrated #HullYes #HullYMC https://t.co/yUV9cJrFjt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Might be a few spots of rain in the air Capt  #humberpilot #ships #rollonsummer https://t.co/JvZizqZVNp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fetched this one in this morning, lovely little ship, nice size for manoeuvring around Goole at just 75m...very hospitable Romanian crew too which made it a nice job despite being through the night #humberpilot #shiphandling #itsnotajobitsahobby https://t.co/8HnCYl8AvX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCMM_UK: From our Installation Dinner last Friday! It can also be found via our #YouTube channel https://t.co/N04iLicWfq ENJOY!  @JimBa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HullMaritime: We've created a powerful film invoking the sense of pride in those of us born on the tide    While we reflect on our pas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great turnout yesterday at the North East outport @HCMM_UK meeting in York and delighted to be joined by CO Roy Tanner of @YorkSeaCadets where we were able to present them with a donation to help send a cadet to sea. Even the local news showed up https://t.co/MapkRNr1Rn https://t.co/h7halSy5Ed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some close quarters ship handling on show there  https://t.co/Z5W1eF1r04]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philbent That was my cup yesterday ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Six years of university, not to mention the countless trainings and courses done since, I can safely say Ive never looked forward to a PowerPoint presentation as much as I am doing for tonight  @DaveGorman https://t.co/WdTjPv82VF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drnicholasevans: The amazing former-Pilot Office at Hull. Look up and see the room designed to view vessels arriving along the Humber h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HCMM_UK: Here was @HQSWellington at High Tide this morning! Home to @HCMM_UK. Retweet if you work onboard a ship! @MaritimeUK @promarin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Humber Pilot in action, skilfully manoeuvring a ship round the knuckle against the tide  https://t.co/Yd2VspA2RP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Needed considerable help from the Little Shuva tug getting her in and swung in the wind last night. Came across from Arkhangelsk, her home port, with a cargo of timber. #humberpilots #shipsinpics #shiphandling https://t.co/W7svNyTm7B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peter_levy: Great report on the work of the Humber pilots if you missed it. Would love to have gone as well! https://t.co/SATVXRAQSB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fullersimon1 @philbent No chance of putting the band back together now is there, @fullersimon1 has gone solo !! @Chriscase200 @philbent https://t.co/MdEa0r6Dn2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SarahCorkerNews: If you missed our report on @looknorthBBC  @BBCBreakfast yesterday featuring @ABPHumber fantastic marine pilots, here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great video !! Good view down Albert Dock too as a ship is departing  https://t.co/38IfKeJDmi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This mornings job into Immingham, the UKs biggest port!! Maybe containers full of last minute gifts for the big man to pick up on his way  https://t.co/yQbmjC0dqG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SarahCorkerNews: What a day to be filming on the Humber Estuary with @ABPHumber marine pilots. 2 metre waves and 40mph winds. @joecamer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My new house has a roof :) https://t.co/g38EVquayH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @fullersimon1: Barrow Haven Inbound on MV Perseus #barrowuponhumber #humber #shipsinpics https://t.co/tKVb05ND0n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Absolute pleasure to attend #ofcon2018 right on my doorstep in Hull and meet some legends of the British screen ! @BeingBoycie @SueHolderness #tohullandback #onlyfools https://t.co/IqDJtmiO0s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: Today we're filming a safety video in #Grimsby so our pilots know what to do in case of an emergency if they go overboard ht]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: ABP News Release: ABP Humbers Pilotage Team Swells in Numbers Read the full story here: https://t.co/p0w8zKqvXI   #mari]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@looknorthBBC @discoverHullEY @Humberbeat Slight inaccuracy in the video...the Humber is indeed the busiest estuary in the country but with tens of thousands of shipping movements every year, not quite every day ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DazBCooper @SaviourMedical @abports21 @UKPILOTS Yes mate, was a bit of an eye opener in relation to piloting life, sure youll enjoy it! Hope youre settling in well, no doubt will bump into you soon!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very sobering indeed  https://t.co/b8yPNIaxVf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SaviourMedical @abports21 @UKPILOTS Excellent course, really enjoyed it and more importantly learnt more then I few things that I didn't know, definitely not just a refresher, cheers Paul!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KevinVallance1: Apparently some ship operators are annoyed that dangerousladders are sharing photos of noncompliant pilot ladders on so]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulNCurry1 @Chriscase200]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Starting to look like a house  #newhome #fruitmarket #bealhomes #cantwait https://t.co/rVahifrhUB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8 days off done, back to work to keep me out of trouble for another 10 days  #ships #rule15 #crossing #humber #humberpilot #tanker #windy https://t.co/Ih5zaXJNJb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The office for today #London #hqswellington #mastermariners @ London, United Kingdom https://t.co/ZAuEk6n08f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fullersimon1 Sure is !! If its good for me on a night out, its good for me in Goole too ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This morning's job up to Goole...she handles a treat for an old girl (relatively speaking, she's older then me anyway ) perfect size ship for this old port, no bouncing off walls to get to where you need to be  https://t.co/CE3wHd69Pi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stunning evening on the Humber last night...taken from the bridge of the Eco Nemesis gas tanker heading up the river for South Killingholme https://t.co/DjOVOMVwR7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My new house starting to take shape  https://t.co/CExUJn07Kw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @stratusimagery: Humber Bridge at sunrise @Hull_Yorkshire #humberbridge #hull #Yorkshire #aerialphotography #ThePhotoHour https://t.co/F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pjedekker: The sun setting over the river Humber with Louise Knutsen watching.  #sunset #riverhumber #Immingham #LouiseKnutsen https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @careersatsea: On #volunteerrecognitionday we want to thank all of our Careers at Sea Ambassadors who attend schools and youth groups ar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @VHEY_UK: Want to explore a new part of the world? #visithull https://t.co/vo53JQYkbK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unbelievable response from an MP to my tweet that disagreed with her view on who can comment on the gender pay gap! This is more akin to a school playground and a sad indictment of the contempt with which @UKLabour holds for anybody who has an alternative view to theirs  https://t.co/y8cCTCRykL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DianaJohnsonMP @looknorthBBC @EmmaHardyMP Wow !! What an utterly obnoxious comment from an MP!! Another reason to add to the list of the many why, despite living in a labour stronghold (which is the only reason youre elected) Id never vote for you or your horrible party! Keep talking @MichelleDewbs ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Todays job, taking this green machine gas tanker, the JS Chuka, up to South Killingholme with an apprentice pilot conducting the passage #shipsinpics #humberpilot #shiphandling #careersatsea #mentoring #keepingbritaintrading https://t.co/6nFf1yTIXE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philbent You obviously never worked on a cruise ship  https://t.co/qJxg1bay6n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some snaps of my first couple of days back at work taking two RMS ships out to sea from Goole after theyd dropped off a load of steel! Gorgeous weather both days, maybe summer is on the way  #ships #Humber #humberpilot #navigation #shiphandling https://t.co/o74fDbcq7h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angus_young61: When you didn't need a bridge to cross the River Hull https://t.co/9VARlplLaA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Playing @SoccerSaturday roulette today despite all the postponements and who scores first?! Only Carlisle isnt it !! So watch out Carlisle, 12 Yorkshire boys heading your way  https://t.co/6QNSVRwyM0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pjedekker: All waiting for a place in port. Busy day for #VTSHumber. #shipping #riverhumber https://t.co/bckycPq9RF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: The Port of #Hull in the #snow - spare a thought this week for our frontline colleagues who work in all weather to keep Brit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: It's tight, but thanks to our skilled marine pilots she just fits through the lock in the Port of #Immingham https://t.co/Lh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: Our pilots work 24/7 to bring ships safely into Port #Immingham https://t.co/lsP190RxqB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FruitMarketHull: .@GQMagazine love #Hull!  After visiting our beautiful city, they put all their fave places into a guide, including @T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ABPHumber: Our hardworking Humber pilot Daminda has found a Golden Envelope containing 5 in a work car... you deserve it! #RAKDay http]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@philbent Agreed...and not beyond the realms of possibility ;)! I always remember looking at the Bosphorus bridge when alongside in Istanbul and thinking why hasn't the Humber done that?!? https://t.co/5pVfV1H2S1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I get to "drive" under it as well as over it and certainly an impressive structure with cracking views!! Best scenery in the UK?! Not so sure, but then I haven't driven everywhere so will have to acquiesce to the "experts" :)!! https://t.co/DSso21uBzv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @angus_young61: It's probably Hull's most famous bridge at the moment. Here's a smashing shot of Scott St Bridge from the @hulldailymail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interesting video and article giving in a little insight into what I do for a living and also those that ensure I get on and off ships safely #humber #pilot #navigation #allweathers https://t.co/UfR2HxILMN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Don0555: "City of Rotterdam  Primula Seaways Collision.   Legal process can supercede and compromise the advancement of maritime safet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Snapped bringing some Russian wood into the port of Hull this morning  #humberpilot #shiphandling Now time for another week off  https://t.co/Zd9TaMGvwp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brought this one in on Friday night!! Taken a little while to get going but good for the crew to get some rest no doubt  https://t.co/sXK3wGOtfC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How's your morning commute?  Mine looks a bit like this, especially this last week after Ophelia and Brian blazed through  https://t.co/AftDrqZOm2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going to be a breezy few days at work  #piloting #Humber #shipsdontlikewind https://t.co/B2JNb1DND0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UKPILOTS: #dangerousladders  @maibgovuk  Report published into @LondonPortAuth pilot fatality 2016.  https://t.co/V5MZUyM3WU https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @careersatsea: New day. New adventure. Be a part of it. #careersatsea https://t.co/hc6Nj8Mcmg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hicapted: #Pilots manage risk, keep #ports operating efficiently, not just drive #ships. This video from Capt Ray of #SanFranciscoBarPi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CityandLivery @AirPilotsCo The history page of HCMM website also makes reference to the Honourable East India company but that was dissolved by parliament in 1874.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CityandLivery @AirPilotsCo Perhaps "becoming" meaning at the time it was awarded in 1928? The pilots have only recently been bestowed the same title I believe]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>