<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EssexPR: Im going to leave this here... Im absolutely livid. From : The Governments own Impact Assessment Report. https://t.co/8051y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shiftychicken @Nightingale_31 @BBGRichie Piratechain is the way forward.. The true rebellion coin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nightingale_31 I'll support you, fb is very much asleep though]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DDawgly: Canadian Supreme Court has accepted the case for Crimes Against Humanity presented by Dr. Reiner Fuellmich, R.F. Kennedy jnr,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caroldecker ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrsSMHI: You call me a conspiracy theorist. If I'm wrong, what's the worst that can happen to me? I end up with egg on my face and have]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Sacha_Lord: Remember when the Government wanted me to sign the gagging order?  Todays the day to release their own report, which Im n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Ven It really is]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: ALL over-50s will get a third Covid jab before winter: Booster shots will be given alongside flu vaccinations - with tr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: This isnt normal. https://t.co/i2pRdKWjEr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @reasonoverfear: I never imagined that speaking up against the tsunami of self inflicted destruction of peoples health would risk my li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheInfamousKata: Also, give a shout out to @Human_actionLLC and follow them for a bonus entry!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheInfamousKata: In honor of @Human_actionLLC (one of my favorite merch stores) coming back, I've decided to do a Pirate Chain giveaway]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@garethicke What a mess]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmmaUK We do need to plan this in seriousness]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shimmerwood1 'Con' tracts signed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caroldecker @BorisJohnson @MattHancock @Iromg @Sacha_Lord @talkRADIO It's a nightmare, an absolute nightmare]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheConWom: Vaccinating children is a crime against humanity https://t.co/2KmfsVeo2G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PirateChain @BPSAA_Official Great news indeed... Look forward to the release]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BerwickJeff @binance $ARRR all the way... Get it listed @binance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BerwickJeff: Soon there will be a number of good wallets for $ARRR, even a hardware wallet.  And, once it starts getting on some larger]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: when big corporations are off the leash and in tandem with govt thats fascism or corporatism as mussolini termed it. CORPORAT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PirateChain: Are You Taking Your Privacy Seriously? | Captain Draeth speaks to The Coin Republic.  https://t.co/PlB66K1Kq8  #crypto #pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KochSookma: @GeekgirlNZ @AndyBird21 @AngryFleas No virus has EVER been proven to be pathogenic- what we call a virus is a RESPONSE to c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 Ffs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AI_Clayton: Guy Fawkes - Born 400 years too soon  https://t.co/wUbNm5l1ky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kicknrip Exactly how I feel]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DollarVigilante: How To Find Happiness In a Crazy World. on @rumblevideo --&gt; https://t.co/oBFDksA4iJ  #Covid19 #CryptoCurrency #Life #M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baaaaaaaaaaa https://t.co/2rC98ED0Cd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@borderowl62 @Tania_Jane1966 They certainly are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 Angers me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@battleaxeBrit1 Right and left is an illusion... It's all divide and conquer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattHancock I'll take a bullet before you coerce me Hancock]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeneneKerr @petshopboys Exactly. We will create our own utopia, our own free society with our own entertainment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DeneneKerr @petshopboys Live music is my biggest passion, I'll never attend a gig again if this is what it takes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GillianMcKeith We won't, we have fighting to the very bitter end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pub_that: Maybe we shouldnt have even tried to open tonight. A few turned up but not enough to cover wages ect. 1 very sad death annou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A band I've always adored, with a vile coercian for rescheduled dates.  Disgusting. https://t.co/M7rUOejl5B https://t.co/O0BqEGBxF7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ColbenJill: My friend just received an acknowledgement, today, of the VAERS report she submitted on FEBRUARY TENTH. Yall...theyre nea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@roxannerandel I do understand the reality. I'm a carer for my partner and we have two kids. I will never have a vaccine, and I'm prepared to lose my business and our home.  I'll find a way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see someone enjoying the tshirt  Tommy Cooper (Unisex T-Shirt) https://t.co/eRboaKk808 https://t.co/FnTkOoo8ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BreesAnna It's just some dude divorcing another dude]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OfficialVoiceOV: More regions are added to UK #worlwidedemonstration https://t.co/O5k7gxGHJi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aww  https://t.co/JPwf12OFFA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ZubyMusic: You're always one 'crisis' away from a dictatorship.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClareCraigPath: This should be damning for SAGE.  https://t.co/IR7WDyl5bK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 I really need to learn from you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: Covid poses an incredibly low risk to children.  https://t.co/h2VekLuLGR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 Definitely... It's the big one. Covid is just the precursor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PirateARRRmada Thanks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PirateARRRmada Pub in the UK here, but I have accommodation that I would like to accept $ARRR as payment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JamesMelville: As hospitalisations and death rates are now significantly below the 5-year average in the UK, this is now less about the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 Speechless by this cult]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Davedragonman9 Superstar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@caroldecker @thejamesmax @talkRADIO Love you ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoylieBoyle Thanks for your support]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Nightingale_31 Amazing.. I hope we can visit one day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nightingale_31: This is going to be the worst move Ive ever made but I dont care Im sick of these fuck sheep! We are leaving booking]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tinataste @shanehodgkiss2 I can't speak for all pubs, but it's a real struggle to buy the beer from breweries when under those conditions. We need to breweries to step up now.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TRILBYS1 I've had the odd few in when it's quiet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Albion_Rover: We are all Pavlovs dogs now   Excellent article by @DrBruceScott on @ukcolumn  https://t.co/0xaQIzFQ5a via @ukcolumn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LooBLoo5 He really is.  Definitely pisses the bed every night.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just wrong https://t.co/gHJrJiKyeW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFreds: Mines going well. Just got a new phone for 50  https://t.co/AbyAbGRJlD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom's a gobshite https://t.co/705vLhofzO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@James87007856 I have been]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DanGall82960767 Not yet... Be good to get a team going]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HallcrossThe You too guys, much love]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My wonderful mother just bought be this signed @ianbrown beauty in Afflecks.  Cheered me up, God love her. https://t.co/zXRPknWuyz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ianbrown The finest of albums... Thank you Ian]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ianbrown: 32 years today STONE ROSES album was released. Songs about insurrection, class war, regicide, corrupt parliament,overthrowing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MoneroWhore: #XMR $ARRR  Its not left or right Its the state vs you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 You're missing nothing x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WarbirdWarrior  Good plan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyguy77: Reminder - Belgian Minister Somers is vaccinated in a media-effective manner. https://t.co/SPssMYpfTY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just coughed in the arndale, think they wanted me shot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[33 https://t.co/LtvlIvqEnS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Manchester City centre, my daughters birthday treat, masked dystopian nightmare.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shanehodgkiss2 Exactly Shane]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_IDONTCOMPLY_ ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@peteaustin6 @pub_that We apparently will be allowed to by hospitable by allowing people inside]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blackswan_t2 The amount of people easily bought sickens me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pub_that It's definitely a very tough trade. Keep going.... Keep smiling.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pub_that Yeah, tbh they've been pretty good.  To add to it my shelter that spent money on has just poured through, all the furniture soaked too. You have to laugh...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@miguel_says Thank you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pub_that Hard to say, we've a better chance for sure... But even then it'll be tough going.  I'm getting tired of it tbh, I'm only fighting now because the pub means so much to many of our regulars. If we go, I wouldn't be surprised if it never opens again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: So...who was awarded this lucrative contract then???? Provision of Media buying services for COVID 19 campaigns.  Award]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pub_that It's a business that's draining money... Not sustainable in the slightest atm.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @UnityNewsNet: BOMBSHELL... UK Government just signed a 320 million ad contract for Covid 19 related ads till March 2022! We are being]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @blackswan_t2:  https://t.co/WEvcVXhn4u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Running a pub is a tough business as it is. Before convid, it was tough... Attracting people to use the pub, keeping a safe and pleasant environment, with great service, entertainment, food etc.  With this weather its practically impossible.  Not sure how long I can do this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GillianMcKeith: 'WE THE PEOPLE' need to have a voice in how our government trashes our money..... This company (see below screenshot of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmmaUK @MattHancock Did Klaus Schwab paddle your ass cheeks?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FloraBe24713480 @ChrisHelme Sorry only just seen your reply. Absolutely, I will never ever support such dystopian nonsense ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tomhfh Journalism would be a refreshing change... But your paymasters would never allow it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheFreds: Reward!!! https://t.co/FTGGzp2S2A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@spencermorgan93 There's plenty, we're on an island]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StreamOfIceberg Him and Hancock would be a piss poor fight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pikeyporl That and $ARRR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharlieEmmaUK @BluebirdLoki @ianbrown She's a star]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>