<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Japan dreamin    #nails https://t.co/2nMUB6udw4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[sleepytime tea   Link to these cute double wall borosilicate glass cups: https://t.co/CcxvpiKcqN ad https://t.co/7iA8s2QxHt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cutest crop top sports tank. The padding is comfortable and supportive!!  https://t.co/spMGQk2Uws AD https://t.co/0gT1nAQFgN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tvisgreat: This is Makhia Bryant https://t.co/5Nb6bHhWcH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @imagine_sunsets: Journal your way to positive thinking! Check out this Amazon deal: Getting to Good: A Guided Journal by Welsh PhD, Ele]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AskChefDennis: Did you know you could find my recipes @KitchenfulUS It's an all-in-one meal planning  grocery shopping app that will h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themomtessorian: 4 child led ways to get your child to focus and concentrate https://t.co/CojLQx4leE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Lynndeeee: 10th Anniversary Dinner: A Decade of Good Food - A Thousand Country Roads https://t.co/mf8Be55Dzb #10thweddinganniversary #f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BBabushka: HolaHolaHola Beautifuls! A #FBF 2012 #Repost for 2021 Resolutions and Chinese New Year, BB's Cuban Way. #ChineseNewYear #Lun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @liveluvtx: YOU are more than just your credit score. But your credit can't fix itself. Let https://t.co/ublrVxXIqF help you with a free]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IMVoyager: 30 Places To Visit Near Bangalore Within 100 Kms Click to check: https://t.co/5nzyShOxxT  #travel #daytrip #Bangalore #Benga]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CensieJ: In divorce there is grief, there is sadness, there is pain, there is guilt and there is hate.  Today I am reminding you and me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LifeWithKathy: #ad Valentine's Day is right around the corner. @Punchbowl has these wonderful digital Valentine's Day Cards you can sen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PinkNinjaBlogg: #ad We all have the right to good credit  the law is on your side to help fix mistakes! Enter the #giveaway for a chan]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drugstoredivas: Valentine's Day is on Sunday, so these DIY Bubble Wrap Heart Valentine's Day Cards are the perfect weekend project.  Fi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thiswortheylife: Print this packet out and use for Valentine's Day!  FREE Valentine's Worksheets For Kids https://t.co/SGNI3PcAW3 https]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zestysouthindia: Delicious Therali appam /Kumbilappam , cinnamon flavored steamed rice dessert sweetened with jaggery as well as coconu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ConservamomE: It's time to get organized, and do I have the perfect product line for you!  Head over to my page and check out how I'm o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HipMamasPlace: Chocolate Covered Strawberries are a #ValentinesDay MUST and here's the #recipe!   GO HERE: https://t.co/aBYeDbcona #ch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @geeklyamanda: #LAND starring @RealRobinWright, is in theaters today and I received some goodies in honor of its release! Check out my @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GrowUpBilingual: Sabias que si tienes una declaracin simple de impuestos puedes ser uno de los millones de Americanos que puede tomar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AndreaCoventry: #DailyAffirmation  I attract money effortlessly and easily.  https://t.co/P6WWPycjG4 https://t.co/WL4yrqhkO7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't forget to get your daily dose of vitamin D to kick the winter blues!At the same time, don't forget to stay safe and keep your community safe. Download the Covid Alert NJ app for up-to-date info!  https://t.co/hxTDuFmSh9    #ad @ChooseNJ #MaskUpNJ #slowthespread https://t.co/tSbHC4f2nr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Velvet nails  #nails #velvetnails https://t.co/tYxmlafRVt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One of my favorite night time teas is sleepy time herbal tea  I'm all about calming down those stress levels!  The VeeFine Tumbler keeps my coffee hot and my cold drinks cold for hours.   https://t.co/rMaTVviJar AD https://t.co/CTaYfo11Eu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @chamath: Facebook and @RobinhoodApp are the same:  They both trick you into thinking you are the customer. But, in fact, you are the pr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themomtessorian: Gift ideas for all the men in your life for any and all occasions! #valentinesday #fathersday #birthdays #christmas #g]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @poshonabudget: Wow! Keto Low Carb Mac and Cheese that readers seem to love!  https://t.co/VXTS6icliI https://t.co/vAQJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zestysouthindia: Delicous and simple fish curry made with spices and without coconut milk. This soul satisfying curry goes well with ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @imagine_sunsets: Galentine's day gift ideas your bestie will surely love! Check it out!   Funny Birthday, Valentines, Galentines Day Gi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[icy  nails  https://t.co/iqnnFCGAkk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ad @HormelFoods Happy Little Plants Protein Puffs are plant-based snacks with 16 grams of PROTEIN!! Available in 3 flavors: Cinnamon Sugar, Ranch  Nacho Cheese.  Found them here: https://t.co/CdD9o2PqPB #proteinpuffs https://t.co/3dUi4GP7mM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Pack on @PrimeVideo is such an adorable show! #ad Its a new unscripted series that is basically a dog version of The Amazing Race!! For more info: https://t.co/Tg14zWC7rv #packedweekend https://t.co/z7brwhkuZR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sick drone footage  https://t.co/gYyWvMBCay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My favorite oversized puffer is on sale for only $45 ( originally $198). Also comes in tan. Its reversible. One side vegan leather, other faux fur.    #liketkit #LTKsalealert #LTKgiftspo #LTKunder50 https://t.co/O3cecfI01E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super soft and luxe teddy coat is on sale for 50% off! Last day and almost sold out! True to size.  #liketkit #LTKgiftspo #LTKunder100 #LTKsalealert https://t.co/pDcMr5Xt1f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @alpha_trained: Learn how to train a Blue Heeler Puppy not to bite with these tips. These proven methods will help you nip the nipping i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @geeklyamanda: On HULU TODAY #DreamworksTrollsTopia series bringing back all those lovable #Trolls! Check out the best quotes from the s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PinkNinjaBlogg: Answer a few questions to receive your free birth chart by email from @CA_Psychics and learn what the stars say about y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trendycyndie: #Ad New @ShebaBrand docuseries #CatsThatRuleTheWorld reveals cats superpowers to reduce stressprovide unconditional lov]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @certifiedWAHM: It's the Season of Giving at Robinsons Townville Meycauayan Bulacan #OurSeasonOfGivingAtRobinsonsTownville https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MandeeandCo: Never stress again about where you are going to put your handbag while out in public! Introducing @theClipa ! It's the ins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ShelleyWebbRN: Because of my family history of heart disease, Istriveto live a heart-healthy life.Join mein pledging tohelp stop t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CensieJ: Connect with a Tarot Psychic for just $1/minute. @CA_Psychics are top rated experts in love  relationships, destiny  life pa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jsismee: Check out my Full Review of Rodan and Fields Multi-Function Eye Cream! #RodanFields #Ad #PRGift #Skincare #SkincareRoutine #Sk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lifeofagingerk8: #AD My doggos  I couldn't have been more excited to get up this morning to check out The Pack on Amazon @PrimeVideo!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @goodbuysalltime: How Cute are these Carters #Santa is my Bestie #Christmas #Holiday #pajamas ?? *FREE SHIPPING* #ad Size 3T https://]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thesupermomlife: It's #PeanutButterFudgeDay! If you love peanut butter and chocolate as much as we do, you have to try our  @reeses Pea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NightHelperBlog: @TheCroods : A New Age Movie is coming to theaters on November 25th, and you can win Fandango tickets here. https://t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themomtessorian: DIY all natural, multi-purpose cleaner with essential oils https://t.co/aceSTE9T8h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EvrydayShortcut: #Ad Meet Denali, the climbing adventure cat! A new documentary series titled, The #CatsThatRuleTheWorld, from @ShebaBr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @365DaysofBaking: You'll never believe how much incredible flavor there is in just one bite of these incredible Cranberry Pecan Goat Che]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rbrosemer: #Ad Meet Galileo and Bigler, participants in a prison cat training program. Their moving story is the first episode in a doc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peytonmomma: Don't miss @TheCroodsNewAge when it hits theaters nationwide 11/25! Read all about it   #ad https://t.co/odLHo00CZI  #RWM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @icsfblog: Enter to Win a Teach My Preschooler at Home Kit https://t.co/rqibinpHRx via @icsfblog #preschool #toddler #homeschool #giveaw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thiswortheylife: With so much information out about COVID-19, we each have a part to play in stopping the spread. Get tips from @Michig]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MontessoriWrite: Montessori for Your Baby  https://t.co/KXykqBoNZb https://t.co/9wOTs59jrF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TracisStar: #ad Tonight these guys and I will be watching #thepackonprime - a new global adventure show where pups  their humans compe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GirlGoneMom: #Ad Xfinity @ComcastPhillyNJ makes being home for the holidays a great place to be! NEW holiday features and programming a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @poshonabudget: This Vegan No Bake Cheesecake is also SUGAR FREE!  https://t.co/hCHLUhpMR4 https://t.co/d4g2kuYJul]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AskChefDennis: CBD Hemp Oil Works because Endocannabinoids and their receptors are found throughout the body: in the brain, organs, co]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mommys_Busy: Tobi Robot Smartwatch Giveaway https://t.co/LaiuDEjhBY #win #tobi #toys #gifts #kids #contest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @forevermymoon: Brite Brush Perfect Stocking Stuffer Giveaway! https://t.co/JXQyJyqiFw  #Giveaway open to continental US only. Must be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Home_and_Loving: Shop my sale: 20% off. https://t.co/YSurJcxFpx #etsy #homesteadplanners #etsyfinds #etsygifts #etsysale #etsycoupon #s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DukesnDuchesses: Are you drawn to #vintage items? Check out these amazing vintage things to collect ... they'll all add more fun and in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking forward to some cuddles with Stella while watching The Pack on Amazon Prime this weekend #ad Its a new unscripted series that is basically a dog version of The Amazing Race!! For more info: https://t.co/BO0zc0jP1T #packedweekend https://t.co/10iHxq6Zug]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ElizObihFrank: Wishing all a safe and positive month of November. Stay Safe #November #VOTE https://t.co/FBrLZyRnxC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @positive_kismet: Wishing all a safe and positive month of November. Stay Safe #November #VOTE https://t.co/AtFEHw3Dr9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tammy1999: Love the farmhouse look? Here are some decor ideas for Christmas &gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/Omi7t32u28  #decor #christmas  via @tammy1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @tammy1999: For those of you who love to use video online, check out this deal of 50% on Ubeesize Cell Phone Ring Lights and Tripods ad]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mommyelisa: Only Elisa Knows: What Is an Alternative Way to Smoking? https://t.co/LpaH0i29fN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mommyelisa: Are you interested in becoming a Talent Manager for Agencies? Here's a tutorial on how to join and become one Check this ou]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AskChefDennis: Happy #FoodieFriday  What's on your dinner menu this weekend? Why not fire up the grill and #Grill up deliciousness with]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AskChefDennis: Happy #NationalNachosDay and #FoodieFriday  Why not celebrate with my  OMG delicious Spicy Loaded Tater Tot Nachos? You]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @travel2next: 10 Things To Do In Jackson Hole In Winter https://t.co/9VEuTp4PuG via @travel2next #usa #jacksonhole #winter #wyoming]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ntemid:  #UAPC20  https://t.co/mD9e9JFBDR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @yeahlifestyle: Head to the blog for my family's Traditional and Tasty French Tarte Aux Pommes Recipe: https://t.co/CoGuTFHO7I  #foodi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DogVills: Want to adopt a #dog but work all day? Check out 4 breeds that best tolerate being alone! https://t.co/erO6XQXiNC #pets]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DogVills: Thinking about trying out Stella and Chewy's Marie's Magical Dinner Dust but not sure if it's worth buying? Check out our ful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nicolesnmgl_: Christmas Decor: 8 Items to Fill Your Home with Holiday Cheer https://t.co/U1lucTkrvQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @nicolesnmgl_: How Lack of Sleep Affects Our Health https://t.co/BhpIexGnv5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @yeahfoodie: Here's my version of Ina Garten's warming and tasty Chicken Stew with Biscuits Recipe:   https://t.co/CRCClOFhBm   #food]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MrCJCalvert: PR Sample   So excited for the #Christmas @Elemis #TSV on @qvcuk tonight at 9pm then 12am   Choice of three lovely aromas!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drugstoredivas: Pete's family LOVES National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation Movie.  So it was easy for me to put together this partially]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MomGenerations: Anyone else love egg whites? I've been making Ham and Cheese Omelettes with @EgglandsBest and it's amazing. Come see my]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @musthavemom: This healthy turkey chili is my absolute FAVORITE chili in the world. It is even a Weight Watchers turkey chili recipe but]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @poshonabudget: Sugar Free Cream Cheese Frosting (low carb!)  https://t.co/C9TbWai437 https://t.co/uBAvTntPnH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @WhisperAmber: Have a Middle Schooler? Know someone with a Middle Schooler? Well, these kids can be intriguing creatures. Here's what a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @trendycyndie: #ad See my top pick from the Athleta Holiday Gift Guide! and then shop for yours! #ATHLETAGIFTGUIDE   https://t.co/]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ANationOfMoms: Enter to win a Clearly Filtered Water Pitcher (ARV $75): https://t.co/QH1DmpPbWP @las930 #giveaway #win #cleanwater #swe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sueparks2003: GIVEAWAY- DON'T MISS THIS! Chef Garden Best of Season vegetable box Giveaway! Chef Garden offers the freshest veggies del]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @peasandpeonies: Balsamic Pork Loin Roast - Sweet and Savory Meals https://t.co/2No7bS0ue6 via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bbeautybits: How to Get Rid of Maskne - All You Need to Know https://t.co/eLF3lBm3OP  #maskne #acne #skincareproducts #skincaretips htt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 Ways To Give Back To Your Community    https://t.co/In4iNXCfxt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cold, dry months bring extra challenges to our skin and health. So, please remember to take extra care of yourself. Today, Im sharing 5 wellness products that can help you feel and look better this winter #ad #winterwellnessbbxx @BabbleBoxxTeam https://t.co/NCLVsBmpe2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MontessoriWrite: What can you do to challenge racism? Find resources here:  https://t.co/YS6ZQEGyRz  #ROCequity https://t.co/lD45SnUgab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FLChefNicole: Looking for a delicious Thanksgiving turkey recipe to try this year? Check out this ultimate collection of over 60 ways t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @themomtessorian: 13 festive Montessori Practical Life activities for December https://t.co/b8JpJ69VGl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CensieJ: Traditional Turkey sandwiches, turkey soup with stuffing, and salad, oh my! Do not let those Thanksgiving leftovers go to wast]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @inspirationfor: Wanna be the hostess with the mostess this Thanksgiving? Get a @blueapron Thanksgiving feast, pair it with some of thei]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>