<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharKrol No, but it does help... maybe if I actively disliked the music it'd be different? Not had that though.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Brndby]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Happy Piano Day! Head over to our Instagram, over the course of today, to watch some incredible piano sessions from some]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Eyds Evensen (@eydis_evensen) and @VanessaCarlton lead Best Fit's Piano Day celebrations on Instagram https://t.co/n2BwW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @thesefootytimes @ParmaCalcio_en Giroud WISHES he was this dashing https://t.co/vFuog9EOtt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @kodzhicks https://t.co/w1wkZDayQM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @kodzhicks Not sure you want to start this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @kodzhicks https://t.co/SOa1GX1OJL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealSirTomJones: It was a joy to chat to @jenlong for @bestfitmusics podcast #TalkTheLine give our chat a listen below ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dan1lamb @JoshisButler90 This is the smuggest thing youve ever written]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Shh, dont let Liverpool find out]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paulbridgewater: Looking to add some new young writers to our list for 2021 - esp for profile features on UK rap, RB etc. HMU on here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: The incredible @phoebe_bridgers opens up to @lucybourton on how she made Kyoto into the best song of 2020 - as voted fo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: From Shaybo to Charli, Rina to Phoebe, Dua to Taylor, and BTS to Sufjan, heres our definitive rankings of the best songs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: As the worst year in history draws to a close, here's our ranking of the best records of 2020 https://t.co/z8kj8A6b8u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: As she ends 2020 on a high with a bunch of accolades for debut SAWAYAMA - including @bestfitmusic's album of the year - @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharKrol 100%. Uni students (at least in my area) probably still the worst offenders though ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Bath City to the UCL!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 https://t.co/0CAqjm8kUp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Well if youve got Billy Sharp on the front, Id wager McGoldrick?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TylerDamara If youre looking for in-ear, I really like the Bose SoundSport ones! The bass is great on those.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 *laughs in baby*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Go go g'job]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/5Vm7oGNSpR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kitrichardsonuk This is great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kitrichardsonuk: My favourite interview for a while; Jon is a lovely man and we do not deserve this band.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Savage. Rage quit?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Also put in a really derogatory bid for Simen at every opportunity - see if you can unsettle him and piss off the buying club at the same time. Petty vengeance tastes sweet, my friend.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 I'd resign, personally. Clear out your desk and move somewhere where your opinion is truly respected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @thesefootytimes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Hes living his best life!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 I raise you my new one https://t.co/Ojo7roin1u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @duttypaul: ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @OfficialFPL @dan1lamb @kodzhicks Blocked and reported]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: The lasting impact of Nobuo Uematsu ( ) and the music of Final Fantasy https://t.co/zH1OEid9oF https://t.co/wmVxEwhXE4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dan1lamb @RottenTomatoes Videogame adaptations are almost always terrible, and Fallout (as much as I love it) has hardly had the smoothest ride over the past few years. I would love to be surprised!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dan1lamb @RottenTomatoes I would love this to be good, but I'll hang fire on getting my hopes up ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Over 1000 artists unite for #LetTheMusicPlay campaign and call on UK government to save live music https://t.co/FfQc6UdQF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ace_jace https://t.co/71yPJi7p8C]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/CFy2C8GxDU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 @dan1lamb @kodzhicks Youre going DOWN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TygFkIX1Fe #TheShowMustBePaused #BlackLivesMatter https://t.co/M9Js4l0wKP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @richthane: we've got an unbelievable week of music lined up for the @bestfitmusic IG Live series.  THANEFEST   Tonight: @chrisleehuts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CharKrol Such a good read ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/jAPSly39uC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LoudAndQuietMag ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@LoudAndQuietMag needs a hand - subscribe to this fantastic mag (for less than a quid a week) to help it survive.  If you need an extra incentive beyond the super cool shit on their pages, you'll get bonus goodies with your subscription &gt; https://t.co/CepNBD0Xkw https://t.co/KldyhOCLk1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Best Fit's annual new music showcase venue @thelexington have launched a crowdfunder to prevent permanent closure after t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thelexington: We've launched a crowdfund as we need to ask for your help. We're committed to paying our staff in full for as long as po]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TedneyNash @laurendown @Photo_Parri @Cerysimo @kitrichardsonuk @TylerDamara @alexcornetto @KCBobCut @remotepostmusic @fenderqueer @pkinsella2 @putnam39 @howtojesswell @scrtmeetingblog @Dave_Rowlinson Right back atcha - thanks for pulling all this together! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TedneyNash: I asked some of the finest music writers (and me) from the @bestfitmusic family  friends community to choose their nine pi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TedneyNash Good luck; godspeed!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #4 cause I missed it - Sigur Rs were unlike anything I'd ever heard at the time when Takk... came out. So transportive and visual.  https://t.co/dwZojBzUgM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #9 - Almost certainly the band that kickstarted my love of Scandi music. 156 remains one of my favourite songs ever.  https://t.co/QPWimPVbQc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #8 - This was a song on the first album I ever reviewed for @bestfitmusic back in 2012. I haven't listened to it in years but it definitely had an impact.  https://t.co/HYQkk63ZLH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(No slight to Linkin Park there, they are amazing, but I think I bought a bunch of OPM singles straight away afterwards after realising I could choose my own music)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #7 - Linkin Park's Hybrid Theory was the first album I bought (though I got Eiffel 65's debut as a present). Was the start of me finding my own music instead of leeching off my parents, who in hindsight had much better taste than I did.  https://t.co/HU6dgxDkTi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #6 - Cocteau Twins were a mainstay of my childhood as both parents loved them. I was apparently born while Heaven Or Las Vegas (this song in particular) was playing.  https://t.co/JbLECMziir]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #5 - Weekend In The City is almost certainly my favourite album of all time, and I think this was the first track I heard from it when my Dad was playing it in the car.  https://t.co/oNBFms4Fds]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #3 - sorry @TedneyNash, I've been pants at this. The first song I loved that I discovered 8tracks (if anyone remembers that) in about 2008 as I started to realise there was more music than pop-punk in the world.  https://t.co/IC0nSZIU91]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #2 - Take Me Out by @Franz_Ferdinand. My first gig was FF at Portsmouth Guildhall in 2004, and they were first band I properly loved. Still know all the words that debut.  https://t.co/o1KzzS7aoq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NINE SONGS #1 - Here Comes Your Man by @PIXIES. Doolittle is amazing + was always playing when I was a kid, but I can only pick one song from it, and I had this one on while I got married.   Go @CharKrol @howtojesswell @lukepcartledge @alexleethomson   https://t.co/hnABRSZgLs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ @TedneyNash has started nominating people to do their own personal Nine Songs (from @bestfitmusic's long-running series: https://t.co/ds9NxH5dzx), which is a brilliant idea, and I'm up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@paulbridgewater @sxsw @nastycherryband @buzzardbuzzard @mypizzagirl @lauranhibberd @MurderCapital_ @beachtapeband @jenlong ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: A new #VirtualPint fundraiser has been launched to support independent venues across the country with prizes including fe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Musicians from outside the UK will have to pay to perform in the country from 2021 https://t.co/sAgjLQAkno https://t.co/F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Pixies, King Krule, Big Thief, Angel Olsen lead End of the Roads 2020 line-up (+ 50 other names announced today includin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tried to write to put into words just how great these albums are for @bestfitmusics Albums Of The Year: https://t.co/XM7iRIoeDs https://t.co/wsv9VuNxuR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: From @SELFESTEEM___ to @LittleSimz and everything in between, here's our list of the best records of 2019 https://t.co/z3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turns out listening to just one song on repeat for approx. three weeks really skews the results on this  https://t.co/ufJFU9WMun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  There's just one more to day to make sure you're able to vote in the #GE2019. Register now at https://t.co/FWLs4o4WGk -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  JUST ADDED: @porridgeradio!    They're playing our new music fest in January alongside @justmustard and @NewPhoneWhoDi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  Ticket alert!   Five Day Forecast 2020 is ON SALE NOW. Grab yours via @dicefm: https://t.co/42kDrdxc5g  Join us at @th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  Say hi to the artists playing the 2020 Forecast:   Alfie Templeman  Chartreuse  Common Holly   Delilah Montagu  Di]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  Here we go: the first lineup announcement for Five Day Forecast 2020, our essential new music festival at The Lexington]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JoshisButler90 Football's the worst. Now I only watch *checks notes* the rugby?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  We can't wait to unveil what's planned for the 2020 Five Day Forecast... revisit our 2019 edition: https://t.co/BoslR3b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  FIVE DAY FORECAST 2020   Our new music festival at @thelexington is back in January.  We're giving away a pair of 5-da]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: 12 albums that should've also got a Mercury Prize nomination https://t.co/SVBt3RGfB0 https://t.co/zsm90g2blI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @guardianeco: 'You did not act in time': Greta Thunberg's full speech to MPs https://t.co/CjMMXUwF4l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: S/O to anyone with a camera and love of music to come join our family  https://t.co/5QHd1NS0z1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @rockaway_fest: Theres only a few bands that come along with that inescapable fire in their eyes. The momentum behind them is undeniabl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: The music industry pays tribute to Hers https://t.co/nhhzz7tPqY https://t.co/VVUTm8jwQ4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @richthane: the only New Music Friday playlist you need  get on @bestfitmusic Discovery w/ new beauts from @weareshura @sam3vian @carol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kitrichardsonuk: Hey folks :) @bestfitmusic are looking for features writers to help us expand our coverage of rap, grime, hip hop and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sebdehesdin Interesting/terrifying]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @paulbridgewater: Look mom, we made an official SXSW showcase  https://t.co/2Ws32j1YJp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An excellent and important read  https://t.co/qG3jL1sNN6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lovely woozy sounds to beat the cold from @Oliver_Wilde/@PetShimmers https://t.co/GetbmaWgpa https://t.co/JjvFjGYeGg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarinaDiamandis: 8 days. https://t.co/DPZzfUOFZh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Beirut's Zach Condon (@bandBeirut) talks about the songs that inspire him as the band are announced for their only UK fes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/6jNcMHxtdT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is gonna be amazing  https://t.co/OYcc2eMXkC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic:  Five Day Forecast Portraits by @Photo_Parri   The opening night of our new music showcase was a blast! We go again toni]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Damn this is gonna be SO good. The Best, even  https://t.co/ABGl66b5Ri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: We're delighted to be able to share with you that our special guest headliners for Five Day Forecast 2019 are the terrifi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: Rising star Emily Burns (@BurnsEmily) takes on recent single "Damn Good Liar" for her debut Best Fit session ahead of her]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bestfitmusic: We're delighted to welcome another wave of acts to Five Day Forecast 2019, our celebration of the year's essential new mu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The @bestfitmusic albums of the year list is out + its as usual its all killer, no filler  wrote about the brilliant records from @idlesband, @tovestyrke, and @0PN  https://t.co/Eqn3Jy7BQG]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>