<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_Art_By_Steve_: May the 4th be with you, always.   "A fixed point in time", said The Doctor, "I can't interfere!"  #StarWars #4thofMay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ian Chesterton going from "I will fight this dude with my bare hands if he calls me 'young man' again" to *rolls eyes at the Doctor's every move* warms my heart.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RCpEy7qgMv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MochaQuokka: Finding this way too funny right now. https://t.co/cBi4XO2hmm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eclipsednyx ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[me at 2 am looking for beans https://t.co/aiYydpvgOJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[idk I'm only halfway and it's so specifically Doctor Who...I can't really put my finger on it. I really love it so far!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First seasons of series are so cool to watch!  You can see all the different directions the show tries in its search for the right one, and at one point you get that one episode where you're like "this...this is it!".  And I really think it's The Keys of Marinus for DW.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blufruity *stares at all the velvet stuff I bought this year* yeah...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fairycat23 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@13andfam Thank you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Neon_gel Thank you so much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ineternity_ao3 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@swordlesbi TY!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my favorite Master, Sacha Dhawan!  #doctorwho https://t.co/SSw4VYNuZB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @spacethirteen:                                      if doctor who           is your comfort show]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Schpogster: I don't know why I find Doctor Who so darn funny with memes but I definitely have a few more up my sleeve for later  #13th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@The_Patrex Sending all the good vibes and the luck your way!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeroOf3Faces seeing how i tend to just smash buttons harder when they don't work I guess I'd feel the same.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AristideTwain I love that by this point of the story the Doctor doesn't accept her as being sentient yet and generally has no idea how she functions. I think the stuck button thing is wildly relatable if we compared it to later problems they will have with the her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It reminded of that one time my TV was acting up and my first instinct was "gasp! ghosts!" but I was actually just sitting on the remote...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[btw the vibes of The Edge of Destriction are unparalleled and now I can see why people compared it to Midnight, but can we please talk how the solution to all of that was "Oh the button was stuck ihihih silly me."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Help him. https://t.co/Qfoo6QVN14]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blufruity One more episode and I'll become an Ian Chesterton stan account]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lophial It's exceeding all of my expectations ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Piango  https://t.co/eKcg1BILm2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[on a side note I'm making memes of a 60 yo show https://t.co/dFABag3MkU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I need to apologize for ever doubting the people who told me the First Doctor had chaotic gremlin energy. I was a fool and didn't know better.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blufruity that's true! I've been putting off starting Classic Who for so long now, I guess I'm scared of committing. But yeah, this may be a good chance to start!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pondering if re-listening to everything Eight related or starting Classic Who...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just discovered procreate gradient maps are useful for color studies. Also, give me 13 in a suit, please, I beg you. https://t.co/ZE0L2Nk2ry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@averybee_ Rick on a good day and 12 in The Magician's Apprentice have bff potential]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just a little boi https://t.co/Suv3zOrAhq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pinn_M_CU:  #DoctorWho https://t.co/EROABDSndX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AristideTwain https://t.co/HEhAVsJaKc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OmegaMysterium Yeah even before TTC they sort of kissed... twice. Idk how well that would've worked back then either.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every time someone says "The Master and The Doctor could be siblings" there is a fairy somewhere that falls down dead]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IvanArnerich: To celebrate 10 years since series 6, here's a duo i'd love to see more of! The Eleventh Doctor and River Song! But why i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/OuS8vRC9xO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One day I'll stop drawing the Eleven to cope. Today is not that day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dyingotters Expressionism and Impressionism are my faves...while I really can't get into cubism...&lt;.&lt;]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Svm4Zo2YWu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think 12 era is by far the most rewatchable. Season 9 my beloved  https://t.co/TcBtXk43o8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eclipsednyx  ooooooooooh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dhawanstan__ Thank you! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@eclipsednyx I knew you'd like it ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont ask where 12 and Missy are, you dont wanna know]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4iSGI88SZY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Doinkadect: https://t.co/xcCrgOILfI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Traditional art feels so weird when you are not used to it anymore. My hand decided to develop a different style on its own... https://t.co/SBxIa9ze3l]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_cosmicangst My eyes are dry, help]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting started in here too  #artfol #artfolapp https://t.co/LL2g9Dht0I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More of this clown (+bonus Liv  Helen) https://t.co/QalYeVJPmn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@deusadotrovao ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bringing back this oldie to celebrate David Tennant's birthday!  #DoctorWho https://t.co/FQ0KTgbuOI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SrFritzofTARDIS: It's DT's 50th birthday today!  Here's to the massive collab me and @denzikken have ever done so far, worth it!  We'v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4f8ifn5HhA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TIM3LORDE She's lovely! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Well...what do you think?" "Uhm..." "You look like a dandy pirate." https://t.co/RI0R0eA9hf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyways, I'm not dead. Just very very busy. https://t.co/xfWzgOmT4Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KedrStuff This is gorgeous! &lt;3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @KedrStuff:       ()   #doctorwho https://t.co/f8SJKtfsjB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarvelousMop I need to make sure my followers know I'm trash.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just to stay safe. I love The Timeless child reveal and Clara Oswald is my wife.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[" Boo! The Timeles Child destroy the canon!!! "  Clara Oswald, with plot armor thicker than a wall, convincing 3 Doctors not to destroy Gallifrey: "Like that's hard."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lophial Peri: Doctor, do you want stripes or tartan? Six: Yes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lophial also this https://t.co/ZZKoQBr2IS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@blufruity Bless you, I thought I was the only one...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SafeSpaceDrWho: Today is the only day this year you can retweet this   #DoctorWho #Easter https://t.co/jGnkE5NEny]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eh... https://t.co/ip3RzBFrGC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alicantesurname Im sketching while listening so maybe Ill post something in the next days ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Nonsense we're always hungry" is still, to this day, one of the most random, inexplicable piece of lore I didn't know I needed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm off on my fourth listening of Masterful because why the hell not]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MayomKun: Ghost Ship https://t.co/YWsk6gzum5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dhawanstan__ glad you noticed! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And here we go again https://t.co/LLGe9FkUWP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lophial: Onto the 3rd Doctor on my classic who watch ! #DoctorWho #bigfinish @bbcdoctorwho @bigfinish https://t.co/zC5d6ipSE8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IvanArnerich He actually doesn't want to rule the universe, he just needs a nap]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk Flawless tastes as usual ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For the record, I also just realized that most of my favorite episodes are from group 3.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are only 3 kinds of title in DW 1) The __ of (the) __ 2) __ and__ 3) *Opens dictionary. Points at random, short word.*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @carcaneloce: "Home" The 13th Doctor.  #doctorwho #thirteenthdoctor #JodieWhittaker #art #Fanart #digitalart #gallifrey #landscape #tard]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimelessOwen I get this too 100%. For me it's both the duality of not wanting Clara's death, but also not wanting to deminish all the Doctor's emotional journey in Heaven Sent, if it makes sense.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @The66Ramblers: Wishing everyone peace, love, and acceptance on #TransDayOfVisibility and every day beside! https://t.co/OmSxhdvvB0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marshcaps I feel this in my bones]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk He did scream "You are my life!" to his ex just before falling head first into the Eye of Harmony. It sounds pretty embarassing, I can see why he would avoid the subject. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk Looking up "Denial" in the dictionary to see if they updated it with his face.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk The Master would totally roast 9 for the leather jacket and definitely make some stupid "imitation is the sincerest form of flattery" comment about his shaved head.  I have...many thoughts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk Damn Rae, now I have to add this to my wishlist]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still thinking about a year ago, right after the reveal, when some fans talked about Dhawan!Master as being played by a "middle aged man", and feeling impossibly old.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Overflowinglnk Picky people without imagination or sense of humor can be so grating sometimes...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh, to realize that the Monk and Missy have the same dynamic as GlaDOS and Wheatley from Portal 2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ClownyWriter Thank you! Glad you liked it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Valc0_: #DoctorWho https://t.co/osmAY0M59J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dropping this one here  https://t.co/o5NJ97c1A0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @lophial: Big smile for the Doctor we've all been waiting for!   #DoctorWho @bbcdoctorwho @bigfinish https://t.co/iqhQmEna2h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IvanArnerich Same here! Doom Coalition is up there with the Divergent Universe for me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@IvanArnerich LOVED IT! R2 is a bit of a hit or miss for me...I appreciated that they explained the genie/Artron thing cause otherwise that two parter felt weirdly out of place. Seizure and basically everything in R3 was phenomenal though. And the Masters at the end&lt;3! "Hello you"?!? I gasped!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I can't believe there are more fics on the container x canal thing than on the Eleven.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>