<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays It looks like the Giants are visiting the tiny people in their hobbit house]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Steve_in_TO @sfgiantsfan55 @ScottAdamsSays According to Fauci doesnt matter- you still have to wear a mask or 3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jackmurphylive: This cant be real.   Is it real? https://t.co/I7q9VFeuW2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich It reveals that the American Resident has a leash and is being handled-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get ready for the freaks! https://t.co/tTLkZjqgx7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: Did Maxine Waters INCITE VIOLENCE when asking people for more 'confrontational' protests?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where are the parents? https://t.co/yyO6FKvms6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The SCIENCE says masks are useless and adversely affect your health.   https://t.co/laMg5jwARV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yet Fauci... https://t.co/vIhViAzk0i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The main stream media keeps pushing this fake narrative- if there really was a pandemic we would see many many many more people falling ill and the death rates would exceed the annual normal parameters. https://t.co/h46lQzMPrf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No vaxx for me https://t.co/hfF47kM6QF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Muzzling citizens to groom them to be compliant https://t.co/TcO1jgX06o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No jab needed for Chyna virus! https://t.co/ufhulgJQby]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays I thought BLM was a result of Trump and his racist policies Kamala Harris said   riots would end if Trump resigned and was no longer in office. What happened? The riots are getting worse, the gun violence is getting worse, and BLM and Antifa are set to destroy more cities.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And we have mandatory vaxx for the least deadly pandemic in history you are being played! https://t.co/MwXNCkv9XL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obtaining an ID has nothing to do with race The main stream media narrative seems to be insinuating some races are too stupid to know how to obtain an ID now that is racist!! https://t.co/SAA485gHN3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anything for the narrative and when they receive the money- they have no use for their people https://t.co/yqFCPGNMED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now we pay illegal immigrants who break the law compensation as a reward for breaking the law? https://t.co/BZmQmtuTkT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A tragic side effect of vaccines is death!! https://t.co/TKHbnF1iHb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TimRunsHisMouth: One of these is ok and gets excused... the other isn't... https://t.co/3ttMrNzClv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The voter ID narrative is blatant racism! https://t.co/ohLvOnePFY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/OJQF7LDHmM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RealTina40: If you can take your mask off while sitting at a restaurant table .. why cant kids take it off at their desks ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: You cant fly on a plane without an ID. But Democrats have a problem with using one to vote?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Easter! Great series - depicts the people who knew Jesus through their eyes. It is free on the app or YouTube over Easter! Happy Watching!  https://t.co/u7iApqZEeY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8VKT7yAGrJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth That is not the way our Constitution works- sorry- your doomsday scenario is unacceptable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaxx https://t.co/PLeIXAoie2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No Vaccines and No Masks- Imagine that!! https://t.co/DBmsCdLPU4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talking evil heads!! https://t.co/IOLGHLqMai]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When will the American people stop obeying these maniacal billionaires and their 2 tier system? #NoMore https://t.co/m8wxvzO3rV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoVaxx https://t.co/lmm4C7J1db]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media bias, manipulation and controlling the narrative.. https://t.co/JmufOtYYKi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Lockdowns do not work!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hate crime that the main stream media complete ignores because the victim is white and the perpetrator is black. This narrative needs to change immediately! #AllLivesMatter https://t.co/FRz8dplfym]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World-wide COVID-19 Lawsuits The Media Isn't Telling You About  DRUTHERS https://t.co/Mwwtu0IhzR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People are now guinea pigs insurance companies even know better - no payouts to those who are vaccinated with the experimental jab! https://t.co/Obw8XjMV43]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ma6r7c2s6G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your government does not love and care for you- this experimental vaccine is for them not you! https://t.co/9Q5YZHAnKI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/F9q8tsfJtP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/e2qYAKWmwu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cargo ship drew giant penis in Red Sea before wedging itself in Suez Canal - SHTF - https://t.co/PLkCVbSouk https://t.co/2qbsKsUzYx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @mattgaetz Safer gun control starts with keeping guns out of the hands of criminals and illegal aliens by keeping guns in the hands of law abiding citizens. Dont be so naive to believe a criminal will abide by a law that makes guns illegal.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RepVernonJones: Democrats sure love to talk an awful lot about Jim Crow considering they were the ones that created it.   If they think]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: BREAKING REPORT: Washington state lawmakers push to FAST-TRACK WAYS for the terminally ill TO 'DIE with dignity'...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IngrahamAngle: We need planes at the ready in Texas to fly all border crossers home.  We cannot, nor should we, hold them for extended]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am so tired of this BS how would the press know what is morally white? Stupid https://t.co/Ojw65OuNRc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hypocrisy of the left! #AllLivesMatter https://t.co/NhodVhPIQH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blatant racism!! https://t.co/XYLSDEDgq3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: The Biden Administration:  -Releases illegal migrants into your neighborhood without a court date.  -Uses your tax dollars]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jsolomonReports: CNNs prime-time ratings have plunged 45% in the past five weeks | Just The News https://t.co/lb4umkWxiU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: BREAKING REPORT: Biden considering executive action on gun control, Psaki says...  WHAT SAY YOU?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoCovidVaccine The fundamental right to avoid imposed human experimentation is rooted in the Nuremberg Code of 1947, ratified by the 1964 Declaration of Helsinki, codified in the US Code of Federal Regulations  adopted by California Legislature.  No]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[(COVID Coronavirus Silver Bullet?) FLCCC Alliance testifies to senate co... https://t.co/eHx7mGN8ru via @YouTube]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#CloseTheBorder https://t.co/OsEY2Bkaw6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoMasks https://t.co/75bzAlp2oP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cokedupoptions What the hell is that?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Cokedupoptions: Really enjoyed the Bitcoin networking event in Miami last night! https://t.co/TLQxNOBuwu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The gene therapy promoted by Pfizer can inadvertently allow all variants of Coronavirus to invade your system- causing severe illness or according to a former Gates foundation board member who also works for the German equivalent of the CDC. https://t.co/zakusyFm5e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zn6av6h8zo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liar, liar pants on fire https://t.co/ThztZ4UFKb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6JG1nPxjOK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[brainwashing was successful. no critical thinking- this is a virus that has a 99.9% survival rate and the MRNA jab was not approved by the FDA for 20 years because in animal trials almost all the animals died when they came in contact with the real virus. This is experimental. https://t.co/1M5LaASm5M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BLM is a cover for money laundering and slush funds https://t.co/eIHr3xPeXS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grooming the population to be servile, docile, dependent and accepting of narratives promoted by the media https://t.co/oNRboTCC8m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The CoronaVirus just keeps getting more and more ridiculous https://t.co/clDNl4cZxf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden, the President who promotes human trafficking and violating human rights, at war in the Middle East all the while increasing the price of gas to $5.00 per gallon. Hope you all are happy. https://t.co/24T3Uthbon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cartoon sniffing is wrong  but a person in power taking advantage of his position and sniffing an underage child is ok? https://t.co/TZ0VM2Daiy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @IngrahamAngle: Literally no adult alive wonders why.  They all know why.  But the WaPo wont report on it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PCR testing is a fraud https://t.co/HDeVM1DuMr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why are they pushing vaccines so hard? https://t.co/NjJ9jUcEuF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The government is grooming you to become enslaved, dumbed down, and reliant on hand outs. Wake up! https://t.co/34bmyWvIpU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The triangle and 666 - stop standing 6 feet apart- it is a method of satan worship https://t.co/pw7zIoHptf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where in the Declaration of Independence does it say freedoms are granted by the CDC? Just asking because I could not find it. https://t.co/JRZbn0th5j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Biden administration making America great again! LOL https://t.co/cBzNIOaD83]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is promoting all this transgender nonsense? https://t.co/3r5LyAlyWh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Soon we will all be rid of that evil tyrant Gavin Newsom!! https://t.co/37a9Y7jTOC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesJa69049176 @cybrpete @w_terrence Why are you such a bottom feeder cant you respond properly? Who raised you -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence Congress does not have the power to designate state governors as the final arbiters, a lineup of legislators and legal scholars have argued. There are 2 arguments for who has the constitutional power to decide which electors to choose. Some jurists say its the VP!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence The problem is, theres a voluminous body of legal analysis arguing that the Electoral Count Act is unconstitutional. Congress has no business granting itself the authority to decide which slate of electors is the correct one and which votes should be rejected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence If two sets of electors are presented for counting, the House and Senate need to separately vote on which set is legitimate and which should be rejected. If each chamber votes differently, the set certified by the states governor should count.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence Then, in rather convoluted language, the law says that Congress members can object. At least one objection from each chamber is needed to trigger a separate vote by both House and Senate on the objections. If both chambers agree, the objected voters are rejected.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence Then, it says the House and Senate leaders each designate two tellers. The VP opens the envelopes with the vote certificates and hands them to the tellers for counting. The tellers then read them out loud, count them, and hand them back to the VP to announce the results. .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence The Electoral Count Act of 1887, currently known as 3 U.S. Code Section 15, establishes a procedure for how the votes are counted, how to raise objections, and how to resolve disputes. First, it says that the vice president indeed presides over the proceedings.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence The President of the Senate shall, in the presence of the Senate and House of Representatives, open all the certificates and the votes shall then be counted, the 1804 amendment says. .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ja_ron_man @cybrpete @w_terrence The counting of votes is primarily governed by the 12th Amendment of the Constitution and the amended Electoral Count Act. The Constitution simply states that electors of each state have to meet, make a list of their votes, which they shall sign and certify.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cybrpete @w_terrence That is not true. Pence could have refused to certify the electoral votes because the state legislatures had improperly changed the laws prior to the election. Furthermore, he could have challenged the electoral votes because of voter fraud. Here we are today-]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new porn.. meanwhile Cardi B WAP receives a grammy and no backlash.. https://t.co/CivumKakng]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoMasks https://t.co/IUgFYD4LJC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The degenerates in control of the media are desperately trying to shove this nonsensical narrative down our throats! https://t.co/hR6v53SskR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And dont drag me into your psychosis. https://t.co/IH3gvawrRz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AfeGTFOLTd]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RealTina40 Fake news media- what else do we expect but the fake news to do what it does best- twist the facts and attack the truth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JennaEllisEsq: This is evil. https://t.co/RoLjVe834j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why is this Justice the only one to dissent and state the laws proper application. The rest of those spineless Justices say nothing and cower in the corner of hypocrisy. https://t.co/Fhe3DtT3mu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ https://t.co/cmfEUZorTI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Science the virus only appears when the media wants it to appear.. https://t.co/Rf4jLtO719]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vaccinate and ask questions later that is if you are alive to ask any questions... https://t.co/tGIGg2V4nU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden administration BLOCKED Texas from increasing  its power 1 week prior to catastrophic polar vortex weather causing hundreds of thousands to freeze. https://t.co/1iGRBc5MRM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Lb6zcNjT3K sign the petition to investigate the Biden crime family]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>