<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton average under 6 shots per game in PL matches without Calvert-Lewin this season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FanalyticsPod: Dominic Calvert Lewin is unavailable for Everton tonight.  He has only missed 4 games in the #PremierLeague this season,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@daviddownie17 Apologies Dave, little break from social media! Was indeed the most time he spent high-speed running in a PL game this season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Worville: Everton are the side with the most injuries in the Premier League at the moment   Big Sam's West Brom only have 37 year-old]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MelissaReddy_: Remember the 2016 League Cup final? I do, but not for match-related reasons unfortunately...   This was hard to write. I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Godfrey made more blocks v West Brom (all in the box) than any Everton players made in a PL game over the last 3 seasons https://t.co/oI1GtSE1jr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordan Pickfords now made 10 saves since last conceding - joint best run of his Everton career]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Davies now winning the ball more than ever, losing it less than ever and reading the game as well as any https://t.co/M3AE4GxldX]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looked at the stats behind Tom Davies recent form https://t.co/bjftcZvjgk via @SkySports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Still genuinely the most Everton lost the ball (statistically!) in a match since 2010, that game v Leics]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlueRoomEFC:  "He was a constant magnet to the ball...he made 13 clearances, his most in a Premier League game in three years."  @m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton superb on Salah/Mane - just 1 shot from Salah, fewest at Anfield this season, and most Manes been tackled/lost the ball while dribbling in over 3 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most tackles Tom Davies made in an Everton game in 2 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkySportsPL: @Carra23  Team selections   Score predictions   Key stats   @psmithXI is joined by @Carra23, @benransomsky, @VinnOConn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yerry Mina made more headed clearances v Leeds than any Everton players had in a PL game for 3 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AdamDatasmith: What can Everton expect from Josh King? https://t.co/Ah9uHCwyKK via @SkySports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @xGPhilosophy: This is only the second time this season than Newcastle have accumulated more than 2.00(xG).  The other occasion was also]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkySportsPL:  Liverpool   Man City   Chelsea   How the Premier League table look like based on expected goals ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball @daviddownie17 @MichaelDeAsha @RoperCarl @MrAncelotti In answer to the third one, has highest top speed of any Everton player this season!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jhdharrison1: How often does your #GK help your team defend corners?  #McCarthy has been the king   #Martinez, #Ederson, #Alisson  #M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3rd time this season Everton have held a 1-goal lead throughout the 2nd half, without facing a single shot on target - hadnt done that in any PL game over previous 5 seasons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@greenallefc Good stat!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball @richarlison97 Hahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sigurdsson created or took every single Everton shot while on the pitch v Chelsea - most creative game for club in over 3 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Furniss: Dominic Calvert-Lewin is a superb player  is going to be one of the best English strikers in recent times.  I've looked]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton have conceded more goals from outside the box in their last 2 games than theyve scored from their last 158 shots outside the box]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EFCMatt1 Haha, not that Ive seen but sure its round the corner]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Evertons worst defensive display in almost 3 years, in terms of xG against - 101 PL games]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Rodriguez and Lucas Digne have created more chances from open play in PL this season than this current Everton XI combined]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkySportsPL:  Solskjaer's 100th game in charge   Liverpool injury latest   Stats to look out for   @psmithXI is joined by Jamie Redk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton the first side to score 2+ headed goals v Liverpool in 118 PL games]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball @TheBlueRoomEFC @CalvertLewin14 Lots of different ways of looking at it, its all tracking data. Doucoures covered more ground than any EFC player so far this season and his avg speed is second highest - so, constantly moving. Kinds of fits that impression of him eating up the ground]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball @TheBlueRoomEFC @CalvertLewin14 So, its the top speed theyve reached when on the field - may not have been a situation to go flat out. But, Giroud/Haller so far though, not on field long]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheBlueRoomEFC @CalvertLewin14 Has fastest top speed of any striker in PL so far this season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ghostgoal: In-depth look at the evolution of Dominic Calvert-Lewins game.   Quickest Everton player  Getting in the box more  Incre]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 goals and 2 assists for James Rodriguez in first 2 PL apps at Goodison Park - no Everton player recorded 2+ goals and assists at home in all of last season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton now with more xG in 4 PL games this season (and most in PL) than in final 10 games of last season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thats the only time Zahas failed to dribble round a single opponent in a PL game at home in the last 4 seasons]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheBlueRoomEFC @jamesdrodriguez To be fair, a sprint is classed as reaching +25km/h, or level 25 on a treadmill! His average speed during the game was faster than several others]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lee_efc78 Thanks mate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlueRoomEFC:  | "The ball followed him around like never before...  "He had 80 touches, his most ever...he also dribbled past 11]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Rodriguez created more chances from open play on debut than any Everton players created in clubs last 20 matches]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Matt_Furniss Haha - that is a lot of shots...!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doucoure ideally boosts attacking threat from midfield; had more shots and touches in box than Davies, Schneiderlin, Delph, Gomes and Sigurdsson managed combined for Everton last season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Rodriguez created 5+ chances in 3 of his last 6 league starts - no Everton players created 5+ chances in any game this year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Allan had more tackles than anyone in Serie A over last few seasons; averaged almost double as many per 90 mins as current Everton CMs. Hopefully an immediate upgrade]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @joe_strange: Allan, Rodriguez and now Doucoure are on their way, but Ancelotti (and Brands) still have issues to fix in defence, on the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dannyecho90 @EllBretland Gylfis late hit v West Ham in October]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EllBretland Goals outside the box by Everton in PL this season: 1 (from 153 attempts)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRobVera Haha - Digne highest top speed. All CBs now around 35km/h. Mina fastest. Though, guess acceleration/agility etc maybe more important - and harder to work out!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keane top speed pre lockdown: 33 km/h. Since lockdown: 35 km/h. Also covered more distance per 90 mins since PL restart https://t.co/4o03B4SM3O]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRobVera Haha, so true]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRobVera Yeah, probably do a better job than most (all?) current EFC CMs in that formation so, as you say, price is key. Kinda feels a road weve been down before, which is almost certainly unfair. He is younger than I thought]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRobVera Not had a chance to look properly yet - guess hes a CM more comfortable in a 4-4-2 but, personally feels a liiiittle bit... meh!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @skysports_PatD: Worth looking out for Seamus Colemans post match interview from today. Criticises the attitude and desire of the Evert]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tom_bennett1234 Not many! https://t.co/LzcuMm7P4M]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@teewhughes1 Was below 65% v Norwich and Southampton, which is pretty grim!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Such a struggle for Everton getting forward - fewer touches in the box than any PL side since the restart, by some way. Just 1 in that - fewest in a half all season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[And Andre Gomes dribbled past more than any other PL player since football returned. CM surely main focus for transfer window]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[195 mins (and counting, at time of sub) since Sigurdsson last won the ball back for Everton via a tackle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBlueRoomEFC:  ON @BLUEROOMEXTRA: @Matt_Cheetham's Stats Pack   https://t.co/t8Pw1ej67J #EFC   @michaelkeane04 the magnet.  @ant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keane won every aerial duel in the box in that but, equally impressive keeping Vardy quiet, with rest of defence. First time Vardys had 30+ touches without recording a single shot in over 3 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Mm, just seems bizarre. If striker picks up knock/subbed early, nobody else to throw on if chasing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Any word from Carlo on why keeps picking 2 GKs?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton best PL record from corners since Ancelotti took over. Avg goal every 11 taken (next best ratio 1 in 22); 6th goal tonight in 13 games - 2 more than any other club]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @J_P_Manuel: Last one for the last match of the day, the Merseyside derby https://t.co/SVCXDR119F]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two successes of Evertons set-up in that: Mane dispossessed more often than in any PL game since Sept, mostly by Coleman, and Alexander-Arnold prevented from creating a single chance from open play for one of few times this season]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make that Evertons youngest starting XI in a PL Merseyside Derby - half the outfield starters 23 or under]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@saintgrizz Haha! Now thats awesome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheAthleticUK: Which Premier League teams employ tactical fouls most often?   https://t.co/7WWLulO3l7 https://t.co/v3I3zeqWzL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@grandoldteam @TheBlueRoomEFC @stevejohnson95 @MrAncelotti @GavinBuckland1 @prenno @EvertonNewsFeed @james_corbett @deCoubertin @MattJFootball @MichaelDeAsha @lesroberts77 @katereillyjames Absolutely - brilliant resource and constantly used. Would struggle without it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkySportsPL:  @Carra23 v @Tim_Cahill   The former Liverpool man battled an Everton legend in our tricky Premier League quiz...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkySportsPL:  Everton's MVP: @richarlison97]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMattBungard @MattJFootball Haha, look after it - shirt was far tighter fit than I remember... Good memories!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMattBungard @MattJFootball Oh and youll appreciate the YouTube vid more!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheMattBungard @MattJFootball Hit 15 mins in ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MattJFootball @TheMattBungard !!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Love it Paddy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@exiledtoffee Actually dribbled past more times than any other player so far this weekend]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gigHaWatt No tackles or interventions, no chances created, fewest sprints - only Richarlison had fewer touches of those to play whole game]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bittertoffee 0 tackles, 0 interceptions, just 4 sprints, joint fewest...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Record 36 tackles by Everton in Decembers win v Chelsea - just 4 in that first half]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Paddy_Boyland Enjoyed this Paddy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@danblight Only Chelsea/City have faced fewer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gigHaWatt 39% - 2nd most in PL behind Chelsea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@KevPerry02 62%]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7th goal Pickfords conceded from outside box in PL this season - no goalkeepers let in more]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10th straight season both Baines and Coleman start a PL game for Everton. First time in over a year]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Ben_Islington: Spoke with man of the moment Mason Holgate this week for @SkySportsPL #EFC   Everton's rising star on developing at West]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Appreciate @psmithXI and @nicholaspwright for letting me on this and spending much of it raving about Calvert-Lewin and Richarlison https://t.co/qbwIXOuNjz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @StatsBomb: Check out the post on site for some bonus pod related visualisations and information: https://t.co/XvXV1sLYvB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stevejohnson95 Superb, as per]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richarlison just the 2nd Everton player to reach double figures in successive PL seasons this century]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@legsy43 Ha! Ill opt to disagree, but interesting view none the less]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@legsy43 Im intrigued - why cant you have a headed shot?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@McleishJim Thanks mate, kind of you to say]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looked at some of the stats that make Richarlison key to Everton. Already made more tackles, created more chances and dribbled past more defenders than in all of last season: https://t.co/R8NdylVOZU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BenDinnery: @Paddy_Boyland Faster than any player on record (@PremierInjuries) Patrick.    https://t.co/7OMGiNRPfE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheRobVera Hey Rob - most categories would show him dipping a bit from last season, where was more middle of the pack. A lot of GKs can fluctuate quite drastically season to season, though, given how small their contributions can be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EfcSl @carlos_bluearmy @rogerefc Yeah, EFC fairly good for that - 5 sides have faced fewer shots this season]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>