<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@navyinks Excellent, love it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DigitalTolkien @jtauber Excellent!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@unamccormack I remember that show! Bertie cut his hand and died of tetanus in the Victoria incarnation. "I'm fine, 'tis but a scratch..."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DigitalTolkien Niches are the way to go, I live in one :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Findegil172 Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bass_042 Thanks, thought you'd enjoy this one!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarieBreta @GIFConGLA Excellent!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YMPhillips @Ashmears Thanks I'm really glad you enjoyed it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JaneCornwell10 Glad you like them Jane!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TolkienGuide @MarieBreta @GIFConGLA I think I saw that in an old edition...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TolkienGuide @MarieBreta @GIFConGLA Of course, Dwarves make light of any burden. Damn it, they probably took them all the way to Erebor :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarieBreta @GIFConGLA Party like it's TA 2941! https://t.co/094HTgC44v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarieBreta @GIFConGLA Hope you had a great day, happy birthday!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dudeseid Happy you enjoyed it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@colinrosenthal @or2doxor2graphy Yes, a sad loss he will be missed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Peplow23 @Earth_and_Oak Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs Wow, they are extremely cool by the way]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Earth_and_Oak Thanks very much, happy you like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs Excellent!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs Sorry that should have said "particularly" not "particular", excuse the typo!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs Yes some are from the Bestiary, quite a collection that was. Thanks for sharing your images by the way, I particular like the second one, great comic book aesthetic with the framing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ShirePropaganda @Masato_Sanjouin Could be...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GirlswSabers Enjoy!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@or2doxor2graphy He's awesome, one of a kind]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Masato_Sanjouin @ShirePropaganda There's a reason for this, rooted in Iukhimov's art historical influences, which I can't tell you about...yet :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Dr_Dimitra_Fimi @LukeBShelton @TolkienSociety @mythsoc @TamsinBarlow @hobbitgay @emmekamalei @GIFConGLA Thanks @Dr_Dimitra_Fimi! Have a great @GIFConGLA!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LukeBShelton @TolkienSociety @mythsoc @Dr_Dimitra_Fimi @TamsinBarlow @hobbitgay @emmekamalei Thanks Luke!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@or2doxor2graphy Thanks, I always like to seek out something a little different!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlymUniPGR Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Freyalyn Thanks, very kind of you to say so!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gatharion Happy you liked it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MissMaryJane03 Thanks!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@StarryKnightRPG Thanks for that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@taarente Thanks, I hope so!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookworm474 There's so much interesting stuff out there to uncover and talk about :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlueMastermaid You're welcome, glad you like them!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EmFeatherWeight @BlogTolkien Thank you I certainly will!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bookworm474 Thank you and I'm glad you liked it! More images to come!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@happystuart060 I have, I love it's prog weirdness!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jogom Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Charliesophia3 That's nice to know, thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkOrdesky Thanks, I appreciate that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YviEvLe @theoneringnet Thanks, I will!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MinorFaustina Something to do with the translation, this image is Russian and descriptions vary. Plus Hordley may just like tall dwarves...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LabyrinthOnVHS Thank you, I'm very happy you enjoyed it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EHakkanson Very happy you like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HoldenEve Thanks very much!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GenevieveCogman Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ashmears Thank you, I certainly shall!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sureed67 Happy you enjoyed it! I'm always looking for something different and interesting to uncover]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ed_morland Glad you liked it! That Boromir image is one of my favourites, featured in thesis some moons ago...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkOrdesky You're welcome, glad you enjoyed it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Salsasweetheart It's a great image!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dthalstead You're welcome! Should be more following in due course...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mike_grenier Happy you like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bigbrothercd Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dthalstead Thanks, glad you enjoyed it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@STORI3D_PAST Yes, it's a wonderful moment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@studyinmadeline Thanks!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@13nitish Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 20 of our visual trek through key #LOTR scenes brings us to the Stone of Erech, gathering place of the Dead. Focussing on the unearthly black dome is Rob Alexander (c. 1997), whilst revealing the eerie panoply of the Oathbreaker's summoning is Lda Holubov (2019) #Tolkien https://t.co/24fvwYyE5T]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 19 of our visual journey through key #LOTR scenes and we find ourselves alongside Frodo, Sam and Gollum at the Crossroads. Depicting the Orc-scrawled but still unbowed statue of the old king are Cor Blok (c. 1960) and Patrick Wynne (c.1982) #Tolkien https://t.co/OVKuLTUZNH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 18 of our visual quest through key #LOTR scenes finds us at the wreck of Isengard with a besieged Saruman confronting Gandalf and co. Portraying Grma's palantr shot with intertextual verve is Sergei Iukhimov (1990) whilst Igor Kordej (1995) opts for the full vista #Tolkien https://t.co/YHAJM0ifwP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 17 of our visual trek through key #LOTR scenes grants us a ringside seat as the Ents unleash their green fury upon Isengard. Portraying howling, frenzied tree herders amidst deadly flying debris are trusty heroes Ian Miller (c. 1978) and Aleksandr Kortich (c. 1980s) #Tolkien https://t.co/BkmrdyVJ1v]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 16 of our visual quest to uncover key #LOTR scenes brings us to Helm's Deep and the Battle of the Hornburg. Placing us up close and personal to the Uruks and hillmen is Ian Miller (detail, c.1978) whereas unleashing axe, arrow and Andril is Anton Lomaev (c. 2000) #Tolkien https://t.co/G7iVZ29otv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 15 of our visual escapade through key #LOTR scenes and we join four weary travellers as they enter the golden hall of Meduseld in Rohan. Illuminating the tapestry of Eorl the Young with a ray of morning sunlight are Pauline Martin (c. 1978) and Joan Wyatt (c. 1979) #Tolkien https://t.co/Bh4daCVxmi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 14 of our visual odyssey through key #LOTR scenes and we join Treebeard, Merry and Pippin deep within Fangorn forest. Conjuring two superbly gnarled, mossy Ent encounters are fantasy/sci fi elder Rodney Matthews (1989) and conceptual wizard Alvaro Ramirez (c. 2019) #Tolkien https://t.co/Q6iDUawmP3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 13 of our visual foray into key #LOTR scenes brings us to the Uruk-hai as plucky Hobbit lad Pippin plots his and Merry's daring escape. Taking advantage of Uglk's head-lopping is Cor Blok (c. 1960), whilst depositing the Elven brooch is Aleksandr Kortich (c. 1980s) #Tolkien https://t.co/2NtQybSNWF]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 12 of our visual journey through key #LOTR scenes brings us to the point of no return for flawed hero Boromir. Pitting him against the orcs in xylographic fashion is Mathieu Prost (c. 2020) and conjuring the pains of St Sebastian is my old pal Sergei Iukhimov (1988) #Tolkien https://t.co/N8kOw1DP5B]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 11 of our visual foray into key #LOTR scenes brings us to the banks of the Silverlode as Galadriel distributes gifts to the Fellowship. Tim Kirk's Elven Queen hands Frodo the Phial (c.1974) whilst Denis Gordeev's Gimli begs for a lock of her golden hair (c. 2015) #Tolkien https://t.co/ddK95z7R8L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 10 of our visual odyssey through key #LOTR moments brings us to Caras Galadhon, city of the Galadhrim in Lothlrien. Preparing to send the Fellowship up among the high mallorn flets are early pioneer Joan Wyatt (1979) and the luminous brush of Ulla Thynell (c. 2013) #Tolkien https://t.co/zvvbOw97g7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 9 of our visual trek through key #LOTR scenes brings us to the fiery denouement of the Fellowshp's sojourn in Moria darkness at the bridge of Khazad-dm. Poised to plunge Gandalf and the Balrog into the abyss are Ryichi Terashima (c. 1972) and Roger Garland (1983) #Tolkien https://t.co/NkA4Q0EBE4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 8 of our visual quest to discover key #LOTR scenes depicted by different illustrators and today we encounter the Fellowship besieged by ravenous Wargs. Taking us within a whisker of the snapping teeth are Igor Kordej (c. 1995) and Catherine Karina Chmiel (c. 2003) #Tolkien https://t.co/zjamdBLlNC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 7 of our visual trek through key #LOTR moments and tonight we witness Elrond's fiery flashback tale of of the Forging of the One Ring. Presenting Sauron in his most infamous moment are pen and ink wizard Patrick Wynne (c.1990) and boldly graphic Krampusvon (2018) #Tolkien https://t.co/ZlspKnwxEL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 6 of our visual expedition through key #LOTR scenes finds us at the sharp end of Asfaloth's mad dash across the Ford of Bruinen. Subjecting Frodo to the evil attentions of the Ringwraiths are minimalist Cor Blok (c. 1960) and old-school hero Angus McBride (c. 1989) #Tolkien https://t.co/9JXIVG0djy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 5 of our visual odyssey through pivotal scenes from #LOTR brings us to a rarely depicted but oft imagined clash of powers - Gandalf versus the Nazgl at Weathertop. First up we have Sarah Beach's subtle 1986 monochrome followed by Theodore Matthews' vivid 2016 riot #Tolkien https://t.co/93BYLaw53L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 4 of our visual tour through key scenes of #LotR illustrated by different artists deposits us deep within a Barrow Downs burial mound. Offering up the Hobbits to the creeping undead sword-hand of the Wight are Alexander Nikolaev (1991) and Matthew Stewart (2013) #Tolkien https://t.co/DRZ4DrAPbQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 3 of our visual trek through #LotR viewing key scenes  from different illustrators brings us to four young Hobbits (plus ponies) on the threshold of the Old Forest. Sending them into the shadows are the enigmatic Mary Fairburn (1968) and Hungary's Gyz Vida (1981) #Tolkien https://t.co/49Gvye8k8W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Part 2 of our whistle-stop visual tour through #LotR taking in key scenes by different illustrators. Tonight we happen upon Bilbo's Long-expected Party, first as a Breughel-esque character study by Inger Edelfeldt (1983) then a painterly mood piece by Lidia Postma (1997) #Tolkien https://t.co/p8wye0e5KB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As a little thank you to all the kind souls who have borne my ramblings to the verge of 1000 followers I present a whistle stop visual tour of #LotR  Same scene/two artists - first up Gandalf arrives in Hobbiton by Michael Kaluta (c. 1993) and Sergei Iukhimov (1991) #Tolkien https://t.co/3E7GZgM4i1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Tolkien illustration MEGA-THREAD Alert! Lately I've been on a visual odyssey, happily tweeting key #LotR moments as depicted by two different illustrators. I'm not finished yet (haven't even reached Mordor) but have a look at the journey so far... (Image: Roger Garland c.1987) https://t.co/69swuHAX3a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Synstistute That's one of the things I liked about the design it is ambiguous enough to suggest many things including the eye!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Bass_042 Thanks, hope you'll like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@contentcatnip Thank you! I'm hoping people will find it interesting when it comes out!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BruceLe13221055 Thanks! I thought that, plus it's ambiguous enough to suggest other things too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Synstistute Thanks! If you're referring to the backdrop, its a contemporary mandala image with a little bit of animation added from myself]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SamJaneBastone @unamccormack Thank you :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@The_Tolkienist @alas_not_me Excellent!! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alas_not_me Thank you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Trotter_Tolkien Thanks, hope you'll like it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As promised I've been making a video series devoted to #Tolkien illustration where I delve into the hidden corners in search of treasures. Episode 1 is scheduled for May, so here's a little preview of the opening titles.  Leave reality at the door people.. https://t.co/OnXneqkemx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cenacdj @Dr_Dimitra_Fimi Thank you, great to see it in facsimile form!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UnionisedDavid He produced a small number of Tolkien pieces, this and his Fall of Gondolin are very memorable]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UnionisedDavid Oh yes, he is rocking that hat, and I believe they were a 70s prog-rock band :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bulgarian comic book artist Sotir Gelev's illustrations for Duga magazine's 1986   cartoon strip channels the spirit of Asterix and Calvin and Hobbes into a superbly snappy, colourful format. Yes, Bilbo's blonde, but who cares when Thranduil looks this cool #Tolkien https://t.co/CR3p8F1tyt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarieBreta Yes indeed, a sad loss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@contentcatnip Yes, although I must admit when I was a kid I thought the rotten egg smell was one of the coolest things about the place!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Favourite detail from a #Tolkien illustration no. 11... EVERY mad, colour-saturated detail in John Blanche's riotous The Battle of Five Armies (c.1979). Ok, if I had to choose just one, it's got to be the Warg who's lost his rider but doesn't care because he is in the zone #warg https://t.co/8JOrHw0L9n]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LukeBShelton Fantastic, I'll second every word! Dimitra was examiner for my Iukhimov thesis and has been incredibly supportive and encouraging. Imho no one deserves that award more!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LukeBShelton: Dimitra Fimi: A Scholar for ourTime https://t.co/LdqRNJQsiZ]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>