<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@RubinReport Well the political side of the Star Wars prequel stories was based on the story of Julius Caesar and the corruption of Rome. So...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As much as I love the work Ron DeSantis has done fighting against Covid, Professor Murphy is right in his analysis of the troubling trend that DeSantis' action sets here... https://t.co/ISHU8xPFAN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dream of some brave Catholic bishop(s) in America doing this to Joseph Biden. It would be the Act of the Century. #CatholicTwitter https://t.co/qdQx0Cfo0G]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could not have said it better. This definitely the vibe coming from the elites right now. #NoMoreMasks #NoVaccinePassports #NoCovidVaccine #NoVaccine https://t.co/18HN0cP5ND]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SchumersN @jhaskinscabrera Very brave kid. Kudos to him for that level of bravery!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thevivafrei I don't know if I've seen a starker contrast in doggie attitudes #lol]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Leo04847568 @jhaskinscabrera Amen! Usually they are only wearing them because customers complain! We need to let businesses, managers  employees know that we appreciate them NOT wearing masks so that we can push back against the few who try to impose this unhealthy practice. #ForgetYourMask #NoMoreMasks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jhaskinscabrera Went in to shake shop w/o a mask. Clerk on duty (who apparently was part of management) didn't have a mask on either. After placing order told her "Thank you for not wearing a mask". She appreciated the thanks and said she couldn't wait for the nuttiness to end. #NoMoreMasks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still feeling things out on Bitcoin, so retweet isn't an endorsement of Bitcoin. However this is a beautiful image explaining inflation. (The only thing which would make it better is to have two 1 oz gold coins in the pic, one on each sheet, to drive the point home more deeply). https://t.co/VE2bEh2jze]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It was only a matter of time before it got to this point. @chrispavlovski could your team get the good doctor and company set up for livestreaming on @rumblevideo in short order so they have a place to go once Youtube finally axes their live show? https://t.co/SEgUuHhkXe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow https://t.co/Uhg8BCWwu9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TaylorRMarshall I see what you did there! #Clever]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@barnes_law @thevivafrei @barnes_law Share on Locals and Rumble please!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@patrickmadrid There is also a reason Saint Brendan described the perishing of one of his crew on his legendary voyage in a volcanic eruption as a descent into hell.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May God Help the people of Canada suffering under the tyranny of the #SunsetThief]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@denisrancourt Disgusting abuse in the academic system. Sorry to hear you are being treated like this when trying to tell the truth Professor!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MannheimSteam Extremely Relaxing!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeremymunson Thank you. Please DM me a good email address to reach you at and we'll go about setting up the interview time and other particulars.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jeremymunson Hello sir! Wondering if you would be willing to join me and a co-host as a guest on my self-determination-oriented podcast to discuss HF2423. Here is a sample of our work: https://t.co/MPEaLdww0K Please tweet a response if interested and we can DM from there!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs Thats a good look! You look a lot like Reagan with his horses!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@barnes_law @thevivafrei Okay this is AWESOME...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jhaskinscabrera Checked mask policy on front door of grocery store to see if there was a health exemption I could invoke if confronted for not wearing one. Once I saw there was, I walked in, got my stuff, paid  left. No one confronted me. #ForgetYourMask #NoMoreMasks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jhaskinscabrera Came across another maskless customer in grocery store today and told him: "Thank you for not wearing a mask". We both smiled, laughed and continued shopping. #ForgetYourMask #NoMoreMasks #NoMoreLockdowns #NoVaccinePassports]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thevivafrei So this was what you meant when you said in this vlawg: "I Need to Feed a Dog!" https://t.co/PSZjTBlEDw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hopefully we have our 1989 - 1991 moment coming very soon... https://t.co/0YALmkLd5s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make that Three. #MyBodyMyChoice https://t.co/XByWQyleUg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['No one wants to be the last person on the sinking ship of lockdowns and mask mandates.' Well said Mr McAdams! #NoMoreMasks! #NoMoreLockdowns!  @RonPaulInstitut https://t.co/wUDnxEBpOH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bravo @getongab for a polite well-formulated response. Shame on you @GovAbbott; you are no friend of true freedom. #StandWithGab https://t.co/jmGKdsbNf6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll bet @barnes_law will be involved in this much-needed effort also. https://t.co/wh4a3Q51A7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very Wise Words #NoMoreMasks #NoMoreLockdowns https://t.co/xm5KpoTIwq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks be to God! #nomoremasks #NoMoreLockdowns https://t.co/KOrr12UXtl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Overjoyed to see what I hope will be the definitive study and history of this tragedy being put forward at last. https://t.co/bHA00PZE8E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thevivafrei Aw man! You didn't include the best part of the vlawg in this clip where you bellowed at Winston: "What Are You Doing To The Chair?!" #PuppyMoment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thevivafrei This is why I don't publish my podcasts and other videos on Youtube any more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remember Men that We are Dust and to Dust we shall Return. #GodBeWithUs #AshWednesday]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rest in Peace #RushLimbaugh We will never forget you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is one of the funniest things I have seen in a while  https://t.co/G9UC4tbdO4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best Answer. Bravo. https://t.co/CemObNNJzH]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I cannot think of a more powerful symbol of how lawless America is right now than this scene right here. https://t.co/NjZK97O2hm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#NoMoreMasks! https://t.co/Weyk28xWKs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[January 28, 2021: The second major battle of the #AmericanCivilWar: The shutdown of whats left of the Free Market on Wall Street through the elites' scandalous response to the #RobinHood #GameStop trading events of the day which wiped out huge portions of the elites' wealth.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bonniekristian Good Grief! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh this is way too funny! RIP Jackie Gleason  Audrey Meadows https://t.co/j3Dkh4jAsO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rest in Peace #LarryKing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulWilson34 @GoinsReport @JarredPMooney @m_b_baker @davidrodez @Quidquidestest @mstebbins @TonyGehrig @SWeidenkopf @LifeNewsHQ @kerry_edu  @aejkohl @DictatorPope @jackhunter74 @peterschweizer @MBSepulveda @tbaggaley @BastiatVzla @CHRISBRANCO69 @LilLibertarians @TWoodsSuggests]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I fully expect to be purged from Twitter along with other @RonPaul supporters very soon. I urge my followers to follow me over to the following locations. On @parler_app at https://t.co/BEYzEn9Tnw and on @getongab at https://t.co/zOmz4eDdTB #Parler #Gab #GoodbyeTwitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If there was any more proof we need secession, yesterday proved it. https://t.co/yashopn3a1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulWilson34 @GoinsReport]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching this live this evening was pretty hilarious. This is why kids are NOT allowed to play with the thermostat! https://t.co/95bg2L6f2j]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Truth Exists. The Incarnation Happened. #MerryChristmas #Jesusisborn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThomasEWoods @jhaskinscabrera Always a pleasure to listen to @ThomasEWoods and @jhaskinscabrera have a sane conversation over the current insanity.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BirkMatt Its a slap in the face from people who deep down despise us and our freedom-loving ways.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RaymondArroyo: Star of wonder...star of night...star of royal beauty bright.... #GreatConjunction https://t.co/VuZwoyzi6K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Elites do not yet realize they have activated their own self-destruct sequence. https://t.co/MjHE0LUAZb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I knew when these things were unfolding at the Vatican last year that God would undoubtedly have to respond with punishment. However I had no idea of the extent to which the demonic activity went  the full impact it has had on the heart of the Church until I read this #GodHelpUs https://t.co/DH97bmKmp0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very Powerful. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is becoming an American hero and may become the greatest member of the Kennedy family because of his brave crusade against the medical tyranny of this age. God Bless RFK Jr! https://t.co/xnjRsF8BEr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThomasEWoods How is that even possible? Venus isn't in the Solar System's habitable zone. Even without the clouds and acid it would be way too hot for earth-based life...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThoBishop My joy as an educator is beyond comparison at hearing Patrick Newman is writing a book on US History.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[May God have mercy on the departed #JohnLeCarre. I pray that in his last hours he finally realized what it was he had so long been searching for (a search he alluded to in "A Legacy of Spies") and threw himself on the mercy of God as his earthly journey came to an end.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This interview happened BEFORE the COVID pandemic restrictions started. Everyone should see this! https://t.co/vtLEDIUdA4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Things just got very interesting. I sense that something major will unfold very very soon. What form that will take... Only God knows, its any man's guess. #GodHelpUs #FreedomMatters https://t.co/mKm7bRJboN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I would be very sorry to do anything to jeopardize the great gift our Founding Fathers gave us. But if your neighbor's house is burning you do NOT just fold your hands and watch. It is PAST time to remove these tyrants. #FreedomMatters #NoMoreLockdowns #NoMoreMasks https://t.co/jgXNmjrNUB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rest in Peace Walter Williams and Thank you for all that you did for the cause of freedom. We will never forget you. Pray for us!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This was a brave NFL player to go on the record exposing the lies with a clear story of what happened to him. Spread the word! #NoMoreLockdowns #NoMoreMasks #FreedomMatters https://t.co/lrkhQxlSSU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I couldn't have described the situation better. Very well said Mrs Cabrera! https://t.co/zc4k5L00oK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm here to tell you that this man is dead on CORRECT. Licensing is a monopoly tactic meant to restrict entry into the teaching field. It in NO WAY guarantees quality of education for the students under the teacher's tutelage. #EndTeacherLicensing #FreedomMatters https://t.co/5ylgtjoAwk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Youtube  the other members of the Social Media Monopoly are now coming after @ThomasEWoods  @mises @mises_media for telling the truth. I wondered how long it would be before that happened. They went after the Trumpistas first. Now they're coming for the Paulistas also. #Freedom https://t.co/vHKfmWbLD3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I've reached this point also. #NoMoreMasks #NoMoreLockdowns #FreedomMatters https://t.co/Np7eFHBPM1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I agree with this. Well Done @denisrancourt ! https://t.co/Cxt0SYWbBE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TaylorRMarshall Take comfort @TaylorRMarshall! "If they insult and hate you all because of Me, Blessed, Blessed are you!"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveSkojec Huh?! Andy Williams, Roger Whittaker, Mannheim Steamroller and the Statler Brothers are all just as worth listening to as Michael Buble!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Bishopoftyler: The devil uses doubt  confusion to increase darkness  division. Pray that leaders of Church  State may seek light  c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Atlas telling it as it is. We would do well to take his warning into account. #FreedomMatters #StepUp https://t.co/toIvooiNgk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ShameOnYou ! #NoMoreLockdowns !  #NoMoreMasks !  #FreedomOfSpeech ! #FreePeople ! #Freedom ! #GodHelpUs ! https://t.co/D6oMCX9oTf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What we saw in DC is just the beginning. The anger is growing. Its ready to explode. Civil War is almost here. #StopTheSteaI #GodHelpAmerica]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Even Chicken Little had the decency to hush eventually" Very well said @AlexBerenson ! #NoMoreMasks #NoMoreLockdowns #FamilyMatters #LeaveUsAlone https://t.co/sPebNUY8Kp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["There was Death upon the Emperor and Night upon the Pope." - G.K. Chesterton (Ballad of the White Horse) #Elections2020 #CatholicTwitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveSkojec Its only happened in 1800 and 1824, thats why most people don't know about this constitutional aspect to the dispute...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SteveSkojec I predict actual violent civil war within six months...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very Well Said Mr. @BirkMatt ! https://t.co/j6wVELwpHC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read, Take Heart, and PRAY! #CatholicTwitter  https://t.co/AwUIwxH62A]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII @Project_Veritas Keep up your great work James  Company! We're praying for you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet Its the deep breath before the plunge... #Elections2020 #CivilWar]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulWilson34 Its early. Just wait. 1876 Redux with the bloody ending this time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@EricDJuly https://t.co/6OnxhO58qE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulWilson34 Its looking like Civil War to me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So this is how Civil War begins... With vote fraud and disputed vote counts. #Elections2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I Voted! #ElectionNight #Elections2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It gives me great hope for the future of the Church when I see prominent Catholics like @SteveSkojec and @TaylorRMarshall have the humility to publicly admit they were wrong on something they did and to ask forgiveness. God Bless you both gentlemen. #CatholicTwitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulWilson34]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If our election system worked the way our Founding Fathers intended it to, we would be looking at a four party race instead of a two party one, which would make for some very interesting situations to unfold after November 3:  @270toWin https://t.co/jED1MEeFF1 #2020election]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PaulWilson34 You were dead on in your prediction of the new form of religious persecution however.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The amount of disinformation and attempted fraud which will be unleashed starting tomorrow will be horrific... https://t.co/exLh5SND9W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EricRSammons: Today is the feast of Blessed Martyr Theodore Romzha. An Eastern Catholic bishop, he was assassinated on this day in 1947]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Knows his #History this one does. #Yoda https://t.co/RFwrULJRqI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BirkMatt Makes sense when you consider what the Big Bang Theory really is: "God said 'Let There Be Light!' BANG! There was Light."]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BrionMcClanahan My students will read him and learn about him!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wish some government officials north and east of South Dakota's border would learn this. https://t.co/Y0drjziLIZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RonPaul @ThomasEWoods @AlexBerenson @jeffdeist @ryanmcmaken]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very Well Said @PoliticallyRick ! https://t.co/FHnDXeXm33]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>