<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[@lickallthisjam followed u!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lickallthisjam omg whats ur username??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @perlamontan: when chanel doesnt have a timeline from the 30s-40s on their site bc they know.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan how convenient!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[chanel is getting mad because other brands using tweed is erasing their brands history or whatever, but isnt that what chanel does best?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan me https://t.co/uKpFPQlb6P]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarioAAbad wait except dg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarioAAbad i love how she credit everything wow]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@st_fulton what elsa schiaparelli did with pink was iconic, but no one says anything when another brand use it. you cant really copy a fabric.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SAINTLIAR not u coming for my grandma aesthetic ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@claudioslimane the fishnets ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itgirltrin most beautiful tweed jacket is just what gets me :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[i really hate how certain things have to be synonymous with certain brands. chanel doesnt own tweed/co-ords just because karl beat it to death for 30 years. https://t.co/YbYzTEiLXV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cailleachsplaid @madeofchampagne NEVER]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan @madeofchampagne @cailleachsplaid WHO SCOOPS CAKE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@cailleachsplaid @perlamontan EXACTLY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@oatmilkmaid ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[libra rising and it changes everyday because libra rising https://t.co/yoStwZKYDs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@shadyasashade cm nlkli tdik lemez by szab benedek s a galaxisok]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan @infurgadiso they can do anything !!! istg!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HFMetGala: Until next time... #HFMetGala2021 https://t.co/Qk0o4mA5BP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan @HFMetGala UR SO BEAUTIFUL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@heyfashiongeek i love this so much!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @EillynCalvo: To my #HFMetGala2021 friends, i signed up to participate in this, but I think I will do it in a different way. Talking abo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SAINTLIAR UR SO COOL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan @HFMetGala happens to the best of us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dolls4prada ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HFMetGala: We're absolutely blown away by all the amazing #HFMetGala2021 looks so far! If you want to commemorate today with our ebook,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hfashionnmuse LOVE!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pyer_princess: yall this ebook is gonna be so good i cant wait to fill it w these looks! yall are truly, truly incredible  make su]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@YaaMazz @HFMetGala UR SO TALENTED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tearcessation @HFMetGala OMFG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MarkeyTopher those are HIS accounts ...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wrkhs @pughatory ur reviewing disney movies on letterboxd rn!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notlewy on twitter  tiktok!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@notlewy hi!! sorry i didnt know your twitter. ill add it to the thread!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dolls4prada THIS IS INCREDIBLE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MODAAMUSE BARELY FOUR PAGES]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MODAAMUSE OMG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Iibragf: https://t.co/zXxf7VLGqZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MODAAMUSE your mind !!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MIUCClAMUSE @HFMetGala YES QIU HAO SUPREMACY!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LAVIDAPRADA AMAZING]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lovvverboyyy @HFMetGala you are amazing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tabitribe @HFMetGala INCREDIBLE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@foreverurmuse love this!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itgurlT https://t.co/On01xNA2zD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@demnalenciaga DONT BE!! I KNOW ITS AMAZING!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@itgurlT i wont him ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@demnalenciaga IM SO EXCITED]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@demnalenciaga WHOA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RetailOop i dont know him personally, but you might be able to reach him through tik tok! his account is @ notlewy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan bagel twt here we come!! #ilikebread]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@farshogar_ @iolsi lmao i think its like chew-gy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[im not sure if the shoe is limited edition or if hes just saying that the shoe is hard to come by since theyve been so hyped. if theyre LE, nike can go too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HD_HugoDumas i do this at every meal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@iolsi the opposite of trendy, but also not basic enough to be a wardrobe staple.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@riacoseph agreed... theyre on my list too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@samjstudios same. i much rather by from independents than any of the brands ran by conglomerates ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stellaviktor hes the worst. i read it only to understand this concept, but i still see so many people reference it or his other writings as if its groundbreaking information. :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dietwintour although i hate him, looss ornament and crime shows the application of this idea.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[resellers are going to hell https://t.co/gEH0GA76AV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thom browne muse when?? https://t.co/Q1ffZYSqFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[last on this: this is about the movement that gained popularity in 20th century europe, when the term minimalism was created - an idea that pushes towards homogeneity. there are some cultures that look more minimalist than others but theres still cultural identity within them]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@wrkhs @perlamontan @infurgadiso @MODAAMUSE dont even get me started with you!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@perlamontan @pyer_princess @infurgadiso @MODAAMUSE WHO MADE YOU THE SALES ASSOCIATE???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@infurgadiso @perlamontan @MODAAMUSE IM WEARING GREEN IN THE ZOOM PICS TOO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mooglare thats fair! i have respect for a lot of designers, i just have disrespect for a lot more. :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @pyer_princess: ok but stop jumping on ppl. thats also part of the mean girl shit. no one needs to hear 30 ppl yelling at them about th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MODAAMUSE why buy from prada when you can fist fight your friends over who gets which sofi sweater ??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the more i learn about high fashion, the less i want to own it tbh.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@01000011___ i hadnt seen that video. i deleted the tweet suggesting her account, people were just replying with that main video of hers so i figured she was fine.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brendaeke1 @voguewrld no need to apologize!! boosted!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@01000011___ yeah im not sure what point shes trying to make here]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thierrymulger ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@01000011___ weve discussed this in some of my classes at uni. one girl has recently started talking about it on tik tok, but from the videos ive seen she provides sources.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the idea that you have to be a consumer of luxury fashion in order to have valid criticism for or against it is a very capitalist mindset. being an art collector doesnt make you an art critic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@tabibutts back in business baby!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michofthestars  shes right !!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pyer_princess a lot of yall on art twitter without owning a $110m basquiat]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kl_auner efficiency without emotion or identity doesnt seem so efficient.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yvessaintangel shes so right]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this extends even further than minimalism as an aesthetic. minimalism as a lifestyle and the idea of only keeping what counts almost always excludes any form of ornamentation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[adolf loos, austrian architect  early proponent of minimalism, described ornamentation as something thats barbaric  criminal. international style/ the modern architecture of 20s-30s was intentionally designed for western comfortability.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[right like lets talk about how minimalism started as a form of cultural erasure. https://t.co/20l7V5mI5x]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ive come to realize that my taste in fashion is looking like im wearing a costume every single day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@angelmillk me too ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[miranda bodyshamed and overworked andy. her work environment was so abusive. im glad that guy convinced her to leave.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[its every day... https://t.co/Mr3gylccmE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wrkhs: thinking about this one year difference in the hftmg team  https://t.co/KvpFbTqRTl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @shad0w_yoon: WHAT'S HAPPENING IN COLOMBIA? A thread in english #ParoNacional28A  #NoALaReformaTributaria https://t.co/wCRqQ2s13r]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@aaprilaries it was written by a child  marketed to children so people could learn the weight of the holocaust from someone their age. its supposed to teach people about her humanity  that she was just a regular kid who never asked to be a historical figure thats scrutinized on the internet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@laqerfeld lmk when!! ill be ur backup!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thinking about the day when chair twitter all fought the official sunny d account over the ergonomics of their bottles. thats history!!! https://t.co/W4jfcFsSNO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lickallthisjam YES ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dolls4prada haha i get that a lot !! ty!! xx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[letterboxd is down as im watching cmbyn... this is all armie hammers fault]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheKimbino depends on your tolerance to horror!! that one genuinely disturbed me :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[skirts from saint laurent fall 21 rtw https://t.co/PievkTqAT4]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>