<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[I cant be positive about this shit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[now I gotta deal with mom]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I get there and you decided to take the bus I waited in the parking lot then decided to walk in to check if your still there asked around but no]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Out of the days you chose not to wait dad  you still had the nerves to call me  not respond back]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont even want to deal with it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is going to be a bullshit ass day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aight Im logging off ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont let it limit you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Find it. Your brain works wonders if you let it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[there are people out there who walked away with the highest degree court count  that are still moving. Dont let that wall make you feel cornered  subject you that you cant move onwards, whether if its breaking through it, climbing over or digging under. Theres always a way.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Brosephh_: You gotta sacrifice to make it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[its nice to try.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the creative process you end up opening yourself up publicly but the biggest fear we have is being judged by the people. With art  telling a story, its actually meant to be told  shared so dont fear it, embrace it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I had 11 jobs total so far]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just updated my resume, whos hiring.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just go with the flow ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uhhh yeah I cant think of anything for a headline lol ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ima keep this dumber down just because no ones wants to talk about anything, besides the momentarily movement, were all smart  it is okay to talk about things whether if it feels unnecessary or irrelevant but if you dont start then when... think about it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You guys dont even understand the concept of it, why in the hell do I have to do it back.. not fair at all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Or is it because everyone that I love thinks Im crazy to be thinking in this type of behavior which makes me completely insane just because you guys are so to goody shoes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have these apparitions that would come  haunt me during my night dreams before the morning starts.. its like a jet lag feeling about not having enough sleep for the most part. I wonder if the message is more important then what I face every single night..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But out of topic though I want to beat these little ass teenagers in front of my house I swears theyre doing the most]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With the frame of being consistent I can only do so much  thats why I need to start to doing YT for further explanations  exploring more about myself of my day to day living.. (so you guys can understand more) I apologize sincerely. - M.C.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I may not have spoken about my passion for filmmaking or photography lately is because I have been super stressed about my personal life, with all that has happen, I know I havent been accordingly up to date with current projects but just know it wasnt my intentions to do that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ dont even get me started with you either]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[and Im not taking buts from them everything needs to go because if this continues there wont be any space to stay live in #hoarders]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this is why I dont let my parents get involved between my process especially when it come to yard work or having sentimental values of an object.. you told me to clean, Im going to sweep no questions.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[its like dad cmon you want to save this tree when you have multiple lying around the property  it isnt fair on me to keep having to redo this process over time like jfc dad its sad get rid of it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[cant believe my dad still wants to recover a fallen tree when Ive already cut the roots outs  about that bitch over to the dumpster. Smfh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ITSJUST_ANTHONY tutors for what be more specific!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whatre you talking about, just get rid of it for good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThanksKaren !!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ThanksKaren Trust your instincts]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[its ridiculous cause you want answers by when your throw your little body language around its like okay I understand but you gotta understand as well when I have my body language whos filling the cup more?!?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its the same energy I receive back with you  when I do it its like Im wrong for it or even doing it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[at the end of the day everythings out of control but my own.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[but again though guys Im not trying to sound unappreciated, Im extremely grateful to have my parents here with me today  will always be cause you guys are my reminder ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Its been a constant battle of mine  to be honest theres more to it. I just needed to vent.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After all It all does build ups to this tension, I have to release at some point, family  work  obviously having time for myself to cope  meditate about everything that has happened.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[cause it does get frustrating constantly hearing over your shoulder about do this, do that  after that could you call  then you guys ask me what is wrong after a whole days worth of work for you guys that I could of done for myself about the path I want to take, you know..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive tried many times without being angry  as calm as possible towards you guys about me being a freelancer but you guys cant seem to grasp  understand what my nature of a 9-5 is  im sorry you guys dont understand remote work but its what I gotta do at the end each projects]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mom I love you so much but you gotta stop having the past be your reference to turn my future down, of course I understand that I gotta take care of you  dad but it doesnt mean you can make my life miserable  not let me live happy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If its not that, its always the other.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great just what I needed more work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Life is always on, man, I never get a break from it. Doesnt matter where I go, I can never get away from it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It feels good huh, doesnt it. thats exactly the reason why I dont do it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To be continued,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, thank you @ZackSnyder !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe were just trying to hard, when really it is closer it is to far ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlagueMami Youll build more from people who you dont even know because they give you a different perspective from what youve been rewinding about]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlagueMami Then stop hanging out with the same people]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I can make you feel.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlagueMami lets be real, time heals but just know your team is counting on you as well as much as youre counting on them too. Dont forget that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlagueMami Manifesting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning ooooo good morning ooooo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[its not easy being a photographer sometimes we gotta bend over backwards hoping that the clouds dont move a slightest centimeter in mid moment before we realize we gotta change our settings again ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how do you transition Michael Chanhthasenh to Make It Known Everywhere or how do you incorporate the two together? ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Out of every post why would you tag me on that one?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How much are you missing out on life by just living inside your own little bunker of judgements  its not that your missing out your really secretly saying is that deep down ur not really certain about ur beliefs enough that you want to get around people who might challenge them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Strawberry banana shake sounds ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it normal to keep track of your gear or is it just me?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[yeah Mikey you already got it you just let your doubts get the best of you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[like I said it before and let me say it again let me talk my shit let me live.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[so if you feel like Im talking specifically to you then my paragraphs are speaking volume  as much as you want to ignore it.. its like I said communication is the key  the truth is somewhere in between this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[at the end of the day its our choice to make up for who we want to be, dont get me wrong I couldnt have done it without those who has been supporting me  god knows ima ten fold that shit. Let me talk my shit for the mean time cause honestly I only have the internet to talk too]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lol aight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[launch  fly]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[03/29/2021 - mom ~ sad conversations]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The truth was spoken somewhere today  hopefully you understand why the gestures were so loud]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wonder if fishs just swim to shore when they get caught into something like its a common thing as if were a hospital to them like like hey I was walking  I got myself into a net can you help me?  the other fish responds nah you gotta see them humans about that one  ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[meet me half way, its only fair period]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Like come on guys, we can do better, like for me to tweet  reach out speaks a lot of volume for my community but thats no the point though.  The point is to be above it, 5 years, 10 years from now  ask yourself does it really matter, on some real shit mf.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If I have to approach just to make a little sense in your head so be it, as long as that little sense makes a broader understanding to why than I am fine with it  hopefully becomes a better contribution.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What I need to do is find peace with war at the same time  thats the battle you guys constantly go through  I give you guys major props on that for being so level headed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ima just this out there its cause Aries season, out of any fucking season it had to be this one Smfh Im sorry in advance]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Like I said Im hurt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ yeah let me talk my shit cause being nice doesnt go so long aight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[including the rest of the original squad but they would have to do more, the only advice I want to give is that regardless of who I am you should still support who I am because lately it hasnt been that way  10 years from now are you going to still behave this way.. lmk #fam]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I miss my nigga Franco  it sucks he wont even communicate back because of the shit Im going through but thats life for real.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[gosh I need to make more sense.. ridiculous!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I poured my heart n soul just trying to get you guys to understand about the rhythm of what was happening with my life but if my guy isnt involved then you guys have to do better cause nobody in the wants to overhear a member talk about their 9-5 while youre doing it, period!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont leave him in the dust like how have youve done to me, just know I wanted everyone to be on the same page. The same script, the same atmosphere  the same goal. Thats why I did my best on my part, communicating.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My only Q is where is Franco at... you guys are pushing content.. but my guy, thats my guy..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont understand how beautiful people exist like what the fuck god]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @BVCxTDS: @michaelchanh ???]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just want to throw my phone away from me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[But seriously though you guys are really pissing my off]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[annoying fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ima buy a sign that says that fr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[21s1 ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just hope yall are in that same cycle because if not I am sorry for wasting your time, you need to work on yourself  understand why  how you feel about others..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ yeah Im hurt. Im hurt because of just time in general  that you couldnt even be a civilized person to actually appreciate another person time not communicate back of whats going on. Thats why things flop, thats why things fall apart  that is why we cant move forward..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I dont owe you guys anything at all, in fact I dont even understand why you guys could possibly be hurt towards me, Ive never done anything wrong besides verbal communication  if you dont like the truth so be it I didnt need you guys in the first place.. thanks for using me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[funny isnt it, that I have you guys in my portfolio but you guys dont want to showcase me publicly but why is that though? That statement let alone speaks volume  it isnt me who has a problem or so I think. if anything Im only just hurt remembering it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Put your reps in people!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[need to buy a printer for photos]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I just bought my domains ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imposter syndrome]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Got it]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>