<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @RallyNate: https://t.co/VYUvU8AqOC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire That's because @KingJames turned out to be some kind of peice of  person.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire @sunny well good thing you don't make the law, sometimes I forget you're some kind of piece of  lawyer. On a piece of  show with more pieces of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DineshDSouza: This woman just DESTROYED Alyssa Milano.  You are everything you preach against. https://t.co/ZbAUa8dU1R]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2:  https://t.co/IyOl1r5zhL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyb0t While they are all there a drone strike would be appropriate.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Of course the allegations are true because @JohnKerry is a piece of swap creature.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GadSaad: He's right. It's that simple. https://t.co/3jVVNuY7SM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @AdamSchiff @RepAdamSchiff is such a piece of  why would anyone vote for him.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyb0t Not to mention will get you killed]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr No one and I mean NO ONE is gonna take that dude serious. Conservative or not. @Caitlyn_Jenner]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @atensnut: Listen till the end..... is this real? https://t.co/5skj5sFumS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles No one and I mean NO ONE takes that dude serious. Bahahahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @Caitlyn_Jenner No one and I mean NO ONE is gonna take that dude serious. Conservative or not.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @michaeljknowles @ericgarcetti @ericgarcetti is a ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Who cares what that  LeBron says.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyb0t And Ghadaffi only wanted the gold standard for his country so of course we invaded his country.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @ChrisChristie  no one will ever vote for you. Don't bother no one takes you serious.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Raiders @georgelopez Why put that PUTO @georgelopez in that awesome room. FTP!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Starbucks I banned you years ago because your stupid "woke" policies. All started with that homeless/cop incident in Philadelphia. Haven't looked at you since.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 He needed to be found guilty. I still feel George overdosed and was a life long criminal. But those cops fucked up. Jus sayin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 That's OK, we all know @RepMaxineWaters is a ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity That's because @RepMaxineWaters is a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @MaxineWaters you are a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Fuck @chrissyteigen she is a piece of .  I'll probably get banned now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: https://t.co/Xtm5VrAUuL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: https://t.co/s1PJzShUMg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Fuck you @Trevornoah you piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Thank you @Jim_Jordan for standing up for us, I wish you represented us in Southern California. Fuck Fauci!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @megynkelly: God bless the @nypost https://t.co/RwsP7hhrMT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @TheRock He would say some shit like this on the debate stage https://t.co/yz0DZEkAhu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Bahahaha @TheRock running for president would be hilarious.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drdrew I would still give my body the chance to fight it off naturally, if I even get covid-19 or what ever variant they decide is the flavor of the day. #nocovidvaccine]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @mattgaetz: OMG!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS You suck!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @conspiracyb0t: False flag events are fear-mongering schemes to convince people to sacrifice vital freedoms for greater security, not re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @HillaryClinton maybe you should shout the funk up you crooked dirty bitch]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@UncleCharlie50 It should be a National Holiday. Let's go Cardinals! See ya in STL in September https://t.co/omszzINUeT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @drefanzor: https://t.co/0DpF29rs18]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CBedfordDC: There are a lot of horrible, powerful people in this country who never want the lockdown regime to end. We need to stand up]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: This is a teacher?  https://t.co/3ejEmPEkzT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Acyn: Question: Would you mind putting on a mask for us? Ted Cruz: Yeah when Im talking to the TV camera, Im not going to wear a mask]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyb0t Let's find out. Tell us]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS https://t.co/51h7SxZjFz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Kamala the Hyena strikes again...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Or like when you and yo bitch as husband went with Jeffrey? Yeah I know right...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottBaio @JohnKerry Scott you keep forgetting he is a piece of  and will be gone soon in a embarrassing way for being a traitor.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GStephanopoulos @GMA Who cares you are a fear mongering piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@POTUS But we don't need a vaccine when the survival rate is 99%. If your 70 or older it is 94%.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @James78141017:   "It's a mic box you idiot"  - brainwashed sheep https://t.co/iu5iNjNzY2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sgtmortar Hellyes!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Bahahaha I almost forgot @NBA was actually playing games... bahahahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TrumpStudents: Basement Biden! @Jim_Jordan https://t.co/CsyRSHnJnT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@drdavidsamadi I hope it will not, but it sure looks like a mandated vaccine card is necessary to even leave the house soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thebradfordfile: RETWEET if you have not watched one single hour of @CNN in 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @charliekirk11: RT if you couldnt care less about what the royal family has to say on Oprah]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ScottBaio @pattonoswalt aren't you a pedo? Yeah, you should stay quiet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @SpeakerPelosi you should breathalyzer test before you talk in chamber and in front of the camera you piece of !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @RepSwalwell @ericswalwell you are a piece of !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Michael Moore's baby picture https://t.co/sly5enNLzJ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity That's because @GavinNewsom is still trying to justify his totalitarianism. Gavin is a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Cardinals @Jhicks007 Great but is he gonna stay healthy. I know that's hard to predict but the Cardinals need him to throw that 100+ fast ball. Not change ups or curve balls. Batters can't see his FB... let's go Cardinals!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elonmusk You shouldn't say funny things like this. A lot of people will believe you. Hahahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Bahahaha @BilldeBlasio just because your probably gonna tell the truth about @NYGovCuomo doesn't mean New Yorkers like you any more than Big Fredo.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Who cares what @Alyssa_Milano says. She is a piece of  hack]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut OANN is also...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire First off why is Jeremy Lin still playing?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ReopenCASchools @PorscheCutie @RichardGrenell @TheLeoTerrell @JamesBradleyCA @KevinKileyCA @BuzzPatterson @georgelopez @GavinNewsom are both putos!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amuse @Acosta @Acosta on the record do you denounce the violence from @BLM and ANTIFA you fuckin piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@conspiracyb0t Fuck a @ladygaga we know what you are]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr That's because @RepJerryNadler wants hamburgers. Not to mention he is a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@RobertJohnDavi @BetteMidler they keep obsessing over his taxes. He pays big money to keep him out of trouble and also keeps himself out of trouble. The rest of the political environment needs to be very careful or they're next.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Ilhan You are a piece of ,  not because of LGBTQXY. Because you hate the USA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax @BarackObama @springsteen "Renegade" a person who deserts and betrays an organization, country, or set of principles. How awesome! You pieces of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr What the hell is Garth Algar saying?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr What the hell is Garth Algar saying?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheFirstonTV @JohnKerry John you're a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@thehill @JohnKerry you are a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @robsmithonline: How Joe Biden Thinks Black People Use Computers https://t.co/f4fiNkd5Ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgePapa19: Nikki Haley said Trump would begin to feel isolated due to his actions. Now she is begging for a meeting and he decli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Sorry @BetteMidler but you are not just a piece of ,  you are an idiot for thinking that's how it works. Bahahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Of course that laughing hyena Kamala Harris is making the phone calls for that piece of  ill- legitimate president]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @Acosta I would say it, but you already know your a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire @BetoORourke you are such a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckCallesto: BREAKING REPORT: Receipts show CNN PAID Antifa Agitator John Sullivan who attended Capitol Riots...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DineshDSouza: The class was successful! The bombs went off! https://t.co/8rRF2O72ks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse No thank you, no vaccine needed. But thanks anyways.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire @BillGates Shut up, you are a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Nice try @NYGovCuomo you piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@atensnut @NYGovCuomo great job NY citizens, you voted for a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@newsmax Nice picture, with him wearing his covid 19 jersey]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire And for this reason is why you should stay away from drugs, kids. Just say no. @SeanPenn you are a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@seanhannity It sounds good to the sheeple that still listen to that laughing hyena.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ksorbs: So California is requiring signature verification for Gavin Newsoms recall, but didnt require it for the mail in ballots. How]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CSinclairtv: https://t.co/nmA5TVYBzg  . @PeteButtigieg says the U.S could raise gas tax, Mike Kucharski, VP of JKC Trucking tells us wh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @catturd2: Lol - Piers Morgan blocked me.   He must not like this photo ... https://t.co/OnHX5RfdFN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: MVDV just destroyed the entire media in this clip. Absolute must-watch. https://t.co/RqyruxI3AD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GStephanopoulos you are such a partisan hack. You are a piece of ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @newsmax: 'Cuomo scandal': Cuomo aide admits New York hid nursing home deaths https://t.co/BOWcTOZ3R6 https://t.co/KCiEFTSV9Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr Anyone that wears glasses like @ReverendWarnock he is a Snakeoil Salesman]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>