<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#BoardGameArt and colors for #Glow was spot on. A pleasure,,,, and facilitates game play.  (RandMcNally greens and blue def not the way to go for #BoardgameMaps anyway.) [src: Publisher] https://t.co/SggY55ouEb]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kinda cool that #SCOUT! is on the package @xitoliv #BoardGameAccessories https://t.co/5fo1yTSoGB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoardGamerSteph That was some box of Dominion cards, and it was good to see that app.  (Im undecided on using the specified combos vs the random app-generated sets. Both have merits.). Plus, I liked counting the end-game points like that,,, Fun!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lornaegg I received those two today too!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive already played this game maybe too many times but the #BGA implementation is well done and it affords me the opportunity to play w a few friends remotely who only like to play a certain subset of #BoardGames. https://t.co/OJKAw3ctG2]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PeaceLoveNGames @PonchoRebound Looks like you picked a great time to visit, too.   I have friends there who love it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dont have many grail games left but I had been wanting to try this one. #AquaMirabilis #BoardGame. Soon. https://t.co/dyqe5j8Igm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Managing in the face of Global Impact. #EnergyEmpire #BoardGame https://t.co/J3Q2FmuPJE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love seeing #BoardGameStore s everywhere https://t.co/TjukOLQMrg Happy to see the partnership with the University; think this is a sign of things to come elsewhere-- Owing to the timing of everything, I've not been to this one yet but I look forward to it! https://t.co/UFzdJStCj9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheGameBoyGeek I see what you did there]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer I like this app bc I like data.  It continues to grow, which is fun. I recorded the actual price of my collection (without, and then with international shipping)on BGG, but seeing mkt value is an indicator tho I try not to look at the total.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I like #Qwirkle in all of its forms, incl cards. It's all about #HandManagement and you can get locked out of sets -- or lock yourself out. There are a few versions; this is the German ed. #QwirkleCards. https://t.co/8G0TyvjCx8]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @sarahschauer: especially drinking games, everyone gets 5 cards, but 3 cards are facedown, turn to the person on the left and ask for c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#FlowerField Straightforward resource collection #boardgame but there can be more to it by considering #HandManagement, Tile selection, end-game goals, and what's left behind for other players.Great execution  @nuttepp  https://t.co/gwE3IzrvuD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyway maybe one of those cookies can record my online plays bc I am totally losing track across all of the platforms.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I opened 3 #boardgame sites in my browser (#BGA, Tabletopia, and BGG) and using Lightbeam (free chrome plug in, anyone can use) looked at the 3rd party connections that open behind the scenes. The triangular nodes are sites like google analytics (all 3 have that one in common). https://t.co/hwg8rhpsLc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer I refrained from adding something positive and philosophical based on such periods in my own life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer Sorry Rand.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jonpower When I was 7 I drew a map of our city block - including each house and building with all of their multistory decks, fire escapes, and out buildings - so I could calculate the number of exterior steps. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonJScheuber I went back to read this;  thanks for highlighting]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnlnwmn What I meant to say is that it *might* help. ^This was where I went right outside of NYC. Amazingly well run by the Natl Guard.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnlnwmn Boiron Arnica gel. (I even used it immediately prior to jab 1. I also did the arm exercises they give you which seem silly but seem to help it circulate. That, and drinking a lot.) Hope  ok soon. https://t.co/Kh6hwdqVXV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@mori_boardgame @CraftyPlayers I have the 2p exp. sitting on my desk beside me, high in the queue!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ZombiePox tide is turning  #BoardGames https://t.co/vfNwIH8hgw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lornaegg @mori_boardgame Me too.  Re rules,,, one way or another there will be]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@onigonta  + thank you for taking time to list everything!  me: ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[W all the online #BoardGame playing Ive tried BlueLight-filtering glasses. Some are so strong its hard to discern certain colors. As a result, my awareness of (and reliance on) the symbols  other accommodations games may have has really been heightened.  [Good publisher test.] https://t.co/YK1iJWe9iW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer @RealityGameme V interested in the 2p #KingThiefMinister!   I'm guessing that the cards differ as well....]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoardGameGran Oh I love that one!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Huddyrx The one and only !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LeonJScheuber and the new version of #GoodsMaker ( havent investigated the changes yet aside from the art..... tomorrow)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@theglassdie My fav too. Cant tell you how many hours I spent wandering the aisles while my family amused themselves outside in the car  even though we had a long drive ahead of us (GenCon). Rare that I do something like that but this place was that special and I guess they just knew that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the days before I browsed #BoardGameStore s with stylus clicks https://t.co/WBStnw7Ljs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh boy! Just look at the clean design of those cards! #BoardGameArt  https://t.co/Esayt75fcE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlacedWorker Certainly challenges w The Mind (and lots of other games), but I could see attaining a playable level w the other two ,,, at least based on how I play them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoardGameGeek Connecticut as well  all summer  but being 12 hrs further south you get a head start on us,,,, both w pollen and outdoor gaming!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellalovesbg Thats great!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Machines could learn many tabletop #BoardGames well enough to beat humans; it's all about data -- being able to provide them with enough observable instances of play. One human could never process as many play throughs in 1 lifetime. There's also RL, being used now w Video Games: https://t.co/cdmOCPqDu3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Working w some AI image analysis software today so of course I had to run game-related content through it.  None of the #boardgame designers / artists / reviewers were recognised, but it did well w category buckets based on the art (#SantiagoDeCuba in this case). https://t.co/Fz64NMnhYU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@OpinionatedGmrs What's better than an Anticipation post?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My best read today. Anything that mentions being happy just because you know certain games exist is already up there--   Of course, the game that caught my attention immediately looks likely to have next to no availability.  Plenty of others, though! https://t.co/5WGdbkoqDI]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serious #BoardGameArt https://t.co/vGCLMTRTt9]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone's out  about for #MajestyForTheRealm  Nothing wrong w a bit of #CardDrafting. #MarcAndr https://t.co/7RLjCZ5nvg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@elucidarian @evilmastergamer @425suzanne I definitely watch foreign language content. Sometimes the auto translate even works,,,,,,These reviews are sometimes even more valuable because there might not be anything else available]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gengelstein @gmtgames Nice layout  w 63 pages users need some help w navigation, so I even liked the 1st page - Table of Contents (could be a clickable pdf...). I also like the gameplay summary / core concepts, as well as the board overview (I sometimes mark up a board like this as a teaching aid.) https://t.co/YanLtgN8OZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BoardGame box designs can be so compelling;  I saw #SupplyLine  and was immediately interested in learning more-- @ $14/32cards it's poss. https://t.co/LQ1TaVNpNZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnlnwmn ,,, I thought twice after saying BUT the size and finish is so nice THAT as an artist and gamer I think whimsy is best .... plus, you have to stop right when they tighten so it's meant to be!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@dnlnwmn I admit I'd be distracted by the alignment of the slots though I aspire not to be  and anyway I'm not sure how it would be done so this is prob better.  Ours are capped so I've not had to ponder over this important issue yet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@teoismatt I notice: soda/coke vs pop, sofa / couch, tag sales v garage sale, highway / freeway, the pronunciation of aunt  actually a lot of pronunciation diffs.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My 1994 copy of #Pirateer is off to its new home.  I had forgotten how nice the tokens are ,,, stackable, ridged, and weighing in at over 2 oz. https://t.co/np4dsYUxUL]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheOneTAR I MKd absolutely everything else in the house *except for* the #boardgames.  I just dont know if I could do it although at some point,,,, Ill have to I guess.  2 went today. At least its a start]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@officialgogos Get up and go]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheOneTAR Makes me so happy just to see that trail!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@TheOneTAR @CrystalDax Classic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What a *fantastic* idea! I am going to adopt it w attribution in my AfterDays aka as soon as I can. https://t.co/6pMzlKomYY]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[0x9A3b8675a8016bFcEFF4E4B69a964AA465Ce1383]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xitoliv @CraftyPlayers @shzwtk GREAT job by ALL of the artists--]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ Vince- https://t.co/xgIrLdd5Gt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PonchoRebound I was just reading about CryptoKitties today. Had NO idea... (Im interested in the details of a blockchain puzzle.)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive neither played #AGameOfThrones nor watched the show but somehow I have 7,000 cards  #CardGames https://t.co/pT3A8C69Li]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@beth_sobel @annamaria_jp @AspieGamerGirl You are consuming it, through your skin ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@bgramblings We sure are keeping it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@amanda_mfd No fun and you are not alone. The same thing happened to someone here,,,, I think were all moving around less  or at least differently.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bought #Dragonwood for the kids  #BGA has a nice implementation of this filler too. #FamilyGames https://t.co/gnPs2W4NqC]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@xitoliv @LeonJScheuber Wonder whatever happened to that card-driven rollandwrite #Toraja you brought from there the yr before,,,, I kinda liked it and thought it was pretty far along]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It was a #ColorfulPyramid. # https://t.co/0yazVTmSXZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's fun to come across older #boardgames NIS at local game stores, or even online. #Hamburgum was published in 2007 and it's still readily available -- even though I don't think it's been reprinted since. We like it, even w #Navegador and #Concordia here. @RioGrandeGames https://t.co/1UQYwLgmlQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JeffreyAllers I think that's one sign of a good game!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Boardgametruckr dirt bike DIRT BIKE omg but maybe I need one of those TOO!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@kjrevia @dnlnwmn That looks like fun!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Gralem02 Your own commute must be quite different now, too, in that regard.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For years my commute was a straight shot #OnTheUnderground to Piccadilly Circus and then a short walk on to St James' Square. I arrived early and left late, so every once in awhile when I'd step out during the day encountering throngs of tourists would always surprise me. https://t.co/MiMqS2FDMu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheKevinGrote: Hi! My name is Kevin and I like photographing board games in really interesting and creative ways! This photo of Ticket]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@coastingat6 I like the Q. Is there an all-of-the-above option ?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @uchibacoya: (^.^)// https://t.co/qySYRJKNVV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer Just last wkend i designed a floor plan, and also wrote a list of preferred features. This was not on the list.  (Game area was included  tho)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#Merv is *still* in its box on a table in my office bc long ago I decided one ought not rush through certain stages on a relationship as each one can b enjoyable for what it is. That I am enjoying the preview of this design is an understatement. #BoardGameArt https://t.co/wqdeSIXHbg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Played #TashKalar online while I wait for myself to make wooden makers for our copy -- unless @CzechGames or BGG beats me to it. Rly like this #BoardGame. https://t.co/Uhj77ih9br]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How theme influences the design of game play is a frequent topic, but #RedRising is a good example of how it's affected the graphic design.I am just so taken with the board, the palette and the layout of the many cards. Really adds to the enjoyment! @JameyStegmaier #BoardGames https://t.co/OYFgCeVB4K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ellalovesbg @ThinkerThemer Its unbelievably immersive. I retreated to the safety of  Wander]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@lornaegg I love this edition, too!  We do have it (this one is a gift), but I want to get it out again.  I am very creative and mostly give board games for gifts,,,,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today marks 1 year since I was last out of the house -- for Sat AM @G2Summit. Not sure where we'd be without #BoardGames. Also feel fortunate that I recognize most of the people in this vid. This event is always a real *fav*. https://t.co/OuPrIM3s2J]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am often impressed w the care sellers take to package #BoardGames for shipping (and I spend a disproportionate amt of time myself). This shrink-wrap method worked really well; not even the tiniest dent and minimal superfluous materials. https://t.co/kOmipNDC9Z]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[# player aid translated for tomorrow's #CardGame. #GoodsMaker is straightforward, but @nannann2002's aid provides a nice overview for someone still new to gaming. https://t.co/NugWd8aEUU]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A few advance plays of #UmbraVia, which has an interesting claw-back mech as players get closer to winning (their ability to win points is diluted).  [@MeepleU &gt; good overview vid]. Multiplayer #AbstractStrategy #BoardGame @PandasaurusGame   Fine w 2 but sweet spot might be 3p. https://t.co/rVptxtxvhQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hypnotic Basin and the Fountain of Youth were good while on a Sunken Reef #SingleTurnPB of 18 #ResArcana #HotCombos https://t.co/Irlp7g8aHQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@PlacedWorker V exciting!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BoardGameGeek @Gigamic Classic - Thanks for sharing.   I was trying so hard to listen that I didn't expect the dice!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#ForSale: a new theme w excellent new #boardgameART + Advisors. Hadnt seen this on KS https://t.co/1vCG8W7UTz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JeffreyAllers: Testing the solo version of my train game prototype. It's a fun puzzle, and I think it simulates the unpredictability of]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#BoardGame #ComponentDrop :: Fortunately they all fell into place #LostRuinsofArnak https://t.co/YICqE3AxO4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@BlueCubeBGs A case of finding joy in the simple things [Also got a new chair recently ... must be the only one who found the Aeron uncomfortable.  I did use it for 20 yrs., plus my son loves it.  I'm happy with the new one and it looks like this -- although I did add Rollerblade wheels.]]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Correction: #  theTokens: #WoodenComponents https://t.co/Q2vjLdEZDv]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I take no credit 4 finding # #SquareOnSale, just for loving it and appreciating those who brought it to my attention.  I have a real soft spot for sitting around a table w this #BoardGame. #AbstractStrategy https://t.co/FckLREmA28]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer Their video is pretty good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Designing 3D printable inserts.  How did I miss this trend #BoardGameAccessories https://t.co/vSI0Ev0bUB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quick 2p pickup of #Pioneers  #AbstractStrategy fr @QueengamesUS https://t.co/wIdiy9NDsy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MeepleLady Hysterical! Hahaha]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@yelmelnobrainer @Bruno_Faidutti Wow Rand!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ #BoardGameArt cover for Farsi #Citadels [:  @Bruno_Faidutti] https://t.co/JF2YId9SSd]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>