<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HRFMichael: Mridul worked at Shakti Women's Aid for nearly 10 years, she's a passionate campaigner and advocate for all women and has a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This warms my heart so much. A lovely pic of two of my bipolar heroes. Warrior women  https://t.co/lRKWazhRdc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh:  #WeAreTheSalon  Lost, Looking  Found the Salon's first anthology is coming summer 2021! Check out the hashtag and our]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A tremendous thank you to @EdNapierPublish and all the students working on Lost, Looking and Found. You were all great to work with  https://t.co/uWMZBXY1gQ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At my desk today doing some content writing. Hardly glamorous, but us freelancers wear many hats.  #freelancer #workingfromhome #contentmarketing #billsnpay https://t.co/3tLFokzFu1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @PortyLibrary: Morning Porty!  As it's #StarWarsDay, I was hoping for the blazing suns of Tatooine, instead we've got the clouds, wind a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TaylorHunterUK: I'm looking to speak to people involved in youth arts and theatre. Broadway Baby is in the early stages of a programme]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Anyone who has been to our Salon events will know what a fabulous guest Catherine Simpson is: chatty, informative, humour]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Catching up with the first season of the L Word Generation Q. Its so great watching it! Its like being reunited with good friends.  @thelwordgenq @jenniferbeals @Leisha_Hailey @katemoennig #Queerculture #LWord https://t.co/8QuDHU1nuu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ViccyIsWriting Haha! Kids brains are amazing! While getting ready for school on Thursday, the 8 yo informed me that the brain is still active 7 minutes after death. We also discussed the best and worst ways to die! Cheery chat for a morning ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LR_Lam I was just discussing this the other day. Whats happening in India is heartbreaking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ricky_ballboy @Cheyneshair @LitEdinburgh https://t.co/2d9srQUbEM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ricky_ballboy @Cheyneshair @LitEdinburgh Looking lush! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Rubywax: Mindfulness isnt some fluffy pastime where you have to find your inner elf. Its more like taming a bucking bronco which may]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enjoying catching up on @PantsPodReview. Love the banter between @Leisha_Hailey and @katemoennig  #HappyFriday #TheLWord #Showtimelegends]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SianySianySiany: We have had such a great response to the @UKWritingAwards since announcing yesterday! Freelance writers deserve indust]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Young_E_H: Hello! Time is running out to prepare your submissions to the issue of @shoreinf I'm editing, for TRANS, NONBINARY and GENDE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @MarblesMag: Folk, it'd be a really good idea to jump on this]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HeatherParryUK: the unsung heroes of culture in the pandemic are the tech people who set up a zoom call in advance of the event to make]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great night! Very proud of all the work thats going into this. Good to hear @cath_simpson13 and @ricky_ballboy talking about their work.  #WeAreTheSalon #Anthologyauthor #BookTwitter https://t.co/kSdeKDuz4L]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CarolaHuttmann: @LitEdinburgh @EdNapierPublish @cath_simpson13 @ricky_ballboy @jackjamwrites @s_caldwell_ @BethPublishing @martha_mrb @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jackjamwrites: So proud of the Lost, Looking  Found team tonight  @LitEdinburgh @EdNapierPublish #WeAreTheSalon]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to this. Proud to be part of Salons first anthology too! https://t.co/UXAT9DLTkw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Yesterday's Big News (apart from bookshops re-opening, which was exciting) was the cover reveal for our Anthology. Want t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Young_E_H: Hello! Time is running out to prepare your submissions to the issue of @shoreinf I'm editing, for TRANS, NONBINARY and GENDE]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beautiful cover for the anthology. Excellent work from the publishing team at Napier! @EdNapierPublish  https://t.co/BDLr7deJ6Q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very exciting news! Also cannot wait for the Cover Reveal!  #Anthologyauthor #lostlookingandfound #WritingCommunity https://t.co/VwJRB9tdZR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @HeatherParryUK: if you're pissed about the Tories intentionally letting 150k people die of covid wait until you find out about the addi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loooove #bookpost. #MondayVibes #BooksToMakeYouSmile #Bibliotherapy https://t.co/9J2fNMxczZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I never knew this. Very impressive! https://t.co/aGP0jlufeT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK You are extremely lucky. Most people will never have that level of support because its not possible. I say enjoy it while you can ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@romiescoffee @LitEdinburgh I havent actually read it. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very excited to see the cover!! https://t.co/KfOmw86dUn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Young_E_H: Hello! I'm very excited to be guest editing an issue of @shoreinf: SUBMISSIONS CALL OPEN 11 - 13 MAY! We want short science]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samatlounge: Yet, industry folk keep saying this most definitely doesnt happen. ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Karensbookbag: Celebrate the 10th anniversary of #WorldBookNight by grabbing this special edition of short stories by top authors! Its]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: With the evenings getting longer, our April Salon will be held in daylight. No need to close the curtains: come along and]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Today we are delighted to announce that Joy Hendry is a part of Lost, Looking  Found  Reminder: you can still get a FR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@heathermmcd Amazing opportunity!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This will be one hell of a book when its out! Cant wait to read it! https://t.co/f6NQQ25xAa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LitEdinburgh @romiescoffee That should read nook envy not book envy! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excited to see what treasures will appear on this years list!  https://t.co/v5l7nzMcyq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LitEdinburgh @romiescoffee I have serious window/reading book envy! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LindseyFraser: While theres a lot of football news today that I dont understand or much care about, lets not forget that there are f]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh:  MAILING LIST  FREE BOOK  If you fancy the chance of winning a free copy of Lost, Looking  Found, sign up to our mail]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Gutter_Magazine: Today on the Gutter blog: HJ Giles' personal account of the first few months of lockdown, when very little of the situ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back to writing after the Easter break. First job is to transfer what Ive written of the book to Scrivener. I feel each task will be punctuated by a coffee today!  #springtime #amwriting #MondayMotivation]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @siblings_comedy: ALL DAY TODAY  TONIGHT  https://t.co/JtgVOcLE3u]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheStage: Outgoing government disability champion Andrew Miller (@AndrewM_Arts) looked back over his time in the role this week. He war]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ricky is both a great guy and a great writer! Proud to be getting published alongside him. #Lostlookingandfound  https://t.co/X2tK44OH3i]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sarasheridan This was a captivating and utterly morbid read. Mind blown!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Tickets for our April Salon went on sale yesterday. By 'on sale' we mean 'FREE' - all of our regular events are free to a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SianySianySiany: It's Freelance Writing Jobs Day! So many brilliant freelance gigs and calls for pitches in this issue. It's free to su]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: COMPETITION ALERT   Need to stay up to date with all things anthology? Sign up to our mailing list today via the link b]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brought my coffee machine out to the sticks with me. Enjoying a real coffee in bed  #bliss #easterholidays#writerslife https://t.co/4Xw1TLhvt4]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh:  We're excited to announce that Susan Nickalls is also a part of our anthology: Lost, Looking  Found!   Follow the lin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Our good friends at Shoreline of Infinity are hosting one of their legendary (or 'futurary?') Event Horizon things online]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Good Folks! If you would like to support @LitEdinburgh a little more we have set up a @buymeacoffee page from one off pay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LolaKeeley_ *sending (pre-coffee)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LolaKeeley_ Send you luck and all the good vibes ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Did we mention that we're publishing an anthology this year? In case you missed out, we're going to tell you all about it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Snuggled up in bed with coffee, catching up with book news online. Happy Sunday! Hope your all having a relaxed Sunday too  #sundayvibes #bliss]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CarolaHuttmann @LitEdinburgh @bethanynelson98 @s_caldwell @EdNapierPublish @anitagovan @emmalaurascott @KatyaBacica @martha_mrb @mmklopfer @natrowlandart @writerlynds Youre so welcome! ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Our April Salon will be on Tuesday, 27th, 6pm. Normally, our Eastertide Salon is a light-hearted meeting when we have an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @openbookreading: We are THRILLED to announce that our third Unbound Writer in Residence will be the fantastic @HeatherParryUK! Stay tun]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cant wait for the next Cymera festival! https://t.co/wOd7XwSzfD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Edinburgh Literary Salon (@LitEdinburgh) is Edinburgh Literary Salon events and Anthology    You can support by buying a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So proud to be published alongside writers like @JenBitesPeople in the upcoming anthology. Cant wait to find out the next author reveal! #WritingCommunity #anthology #Lostlookingandfound #Edinburgh https://t.co/ZxwzRAJ9xz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samatlounge: As always, happy to use my tiny platform to lift up any and all marginalised groups. In particular, if any trans writers c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @heathermmcd: So, nice news: I'm joining @PublishScotland as Events  Programme Support Officer for the next year. PS have been a consta]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@SianySianySiany I have major desk envy! Its beautiful ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Luwallerr: As part of my MLitt, I am creating a new online magazine called Prickly Pear Magazine. Submissions are currently open!! Fi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LGB Alliance are a disgrace and they do not represent the views of the LGBTQ+ community https://t.co/ZzuimD1GYm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@siblings_comedy I know! It doesn't seem that far fetched!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another author reveal for #Lostlookingandfound.  https://t.co/4BEXXpDhjP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feeling very loved today.   The wee plant is a gift from my partners daughter to celebrate some recent writing success! (Shes too cute!)   And a box packed full of vegan chocolate treats for Easter from Aadam!  https://t.co/gwWVpDI9jG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Joannechocolat: Another person, using my words to suggest an endorsement. Yesterday it was for an online event I've never heard of. Tod]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh:  The wonderful @julie_galante is another of the wonderful contributors to Lost, Looking  Found   Find out more about h]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @AyeWrite: #AyeWrite is back!   From 14  23 May 2021, well be bringing Glasgows annual book festival to you in an online format. W]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Haha! Good one  https://t.co/ynlKXaVLKa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Young_E_H: Hello to my fellow trans  nonbinary science fiction writers!! I will be guest editing an issue of @shoreinf just for us! Th]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LR_Lam: I get to work with Eris on this book next year and I am E X C I T E]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@ViccyIsWriting That is adorable! Thanks for sharing that little piece of joy ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @samatlounge: *rolls eyes*]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just wanted to say a big thank you to @LindseyFraser for a very encouraging and inspiring Zoom book chat today. Im still on a high! Thanks also to @CreativeScots and the #OurVoices team for making it happen.   #amwriting #Nonfiction #DreamBig ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So proud of one of my favourite humans! Go @Young_E_H  I cant wait to read this book!  #BookTwitter #author #Booktrust #WritingCommunity https://t.co/nAaIG3EtMk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @katemoennig: Not just today but everyday, Trans rights are human rights. #TransDayOfVisibility https://t.co/ElrjrCF2Iu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: Another great event happening on the internet: the SBT @scottishbktrust New Writers Showcase is tomorrow,  Wednesday 31st]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @bipolarpsychol1: Today is the world bipolar day. Twenty years ago, I knew next to nothing about #bipolardisorder. I was studying to bec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LitEdinburgh @EdNapierPublish Thanks for the retweet @anitagovan ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @TheBookerPrizes: Congratulations to ric Vuillard and Mark Polizzotti who have been nominated for the 2021 International Booker longlis]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another author reveal for the anthology!  #lostlookingandfound #anthology #WritingCommunity #books https://t.co/r5tMvWoVoq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On #WorldBipolarDay I want to give a shout out to those of you who are living with bipolar disorder. Never give up on hope. Weve got this!  #bipolardisorder #bipolarcommunity #MentalHealthMatters https://t.co/UNAVN8OOvR]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh: The Mythical March Salon from Your Home is actually happening, tonight at 6pm til 7.15+ Check out Daniel Allison's storyt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Young_E_H: TWO MORE DAYS FOLKS! There's still a few more tickets left for the launch of BITTERHALL, dark and delicious new novel by @He]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Im so thrilled to be part of the @LitEdinburgh anthology!  Follow them to find out more about the authors involved and when you can expect to see it on shelves!  #anthology #writerslife #publishingpromo #lostlookingandfound https://t.co/coRmFUuoyM]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh:  @SharonaSampson is another fantastic writer that we're excited to announce is part of Lost, Looking  Found   Keep an]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Young_E_H ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @kirstylogan: When @HeatherParryUK and I started @TeenageScream_ 3 years ago, I didnt expect that two pals waffling about 90s trash hor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @LitEdinburgh:  Happy Saturday! Today we get to reveal that @cath_simpson13 is another of the amazing writers in Lost, Looking  Found]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>