<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Spoke to @gorillaz about creativity during a pandemic, their hopes for the future, working with Robert Smith, and why unity is the answer.  https://t.co/SxR5yB7928]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You can seemingly hear them read out a kinda nasty but also vvvv true tweet I wrote about those stupid tangerine shades Dundee United fans wear on this podcast, if youre inclined. https://t.co/ToWCFan8cN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @christopheslade: me, @oneofthosefaces, @wildarms_xo, @jamespdf_ and Linda Valenziano are making a newsletter!   it's about the global m]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had a really wonderful time chatting to Klaus Voormann about Plastic Ono Band, the impact Yoko Ono had on John Lennons life, the end of the Beatles, and Phil Spectors - ahem - *curious* production style.  https://t.co/BD8QdIr4qg]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @zoyashvikh: did one of these myself not too long ago - robin is a great editor and clash is great fun. get applying!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sven Vaths appearance at the Liverpool rave didnt sit right with me - hes courted controversy with plague rave sets, and it disrupted the optics of what should have been a moment of pure joy:  https://t.co/5YIk9kDI4s]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weve had quite a few successful internships in the past 12 months, and everyone has been lovely. A great success rate! Also, you dont have to trot down to London, which is a massive bonus.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A lot of students are in need of internships for course credit right now. Is this you? Clash offer week long remote internships, email robin@clashmusic.com to arrange a placement.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@alexjpollard Love this!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@euanmccolm Will check them out! I love the everlys but only really know that imperial period. Obvs lots to uncover!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@euanmccolm Had no idea the everlys covered mr soul! Every day is a school day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @wf_pritchard: This is a subject I spend an inordinate amount of time thinking about, so felt good to get some words down about it - wit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feel like this is being missed by the rest of the UK - and indeed by the bulk of Scotland, tbh - but NTIA Scotland taking their own government to court is enormous, surely?  https://t.co/gUD7WQ6ibu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @thedalstonyears: For the last month, @Lucy_Osborne and I have been looking into sexual misconduct allegations against the actor Noel Cl]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We love @ShazSherazis taste (and words!) so much that were launching a new column on the site, bringing together his passion for alt RB, future soul, left field pop *and more* into one place.  Come for the tunes, stay for the eloquence!  https://t.co/kXDFQa1wyp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Oldfirmfacts1 Those stupid tangerine sunglasses]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@grantrindner @NylonMag @musichorsegirl Love this band!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quite a way out in the family tree but David Murray was a pioneering Scottish racing driver, of all things.  &gt;&gt; https://t.co/gIYte3k5cP https://t.co/Tqa3lUK0I0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spoke to the inspirational @AlfaMist about his new album Bring Backs, which moves from hip hop production to folk, all under the viscus of jazz. Its a super record, well worth exploring!  https://t.co/yJ9ds0dltD]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JessPartridge @Jem_Collins Yep happy to chat on Robin@clashmusic.com]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClashMagazine: An MF DOOM NFT will go up for auction today - featuring a never before seen video, and physical items...  50% of the pro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lads! https://t.co/HyWt3sTfUw]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daniel Eks tone deaf bid for Arsenal ownership illustrates how broken both music and football truly are - musicians literally cannot make ends meet.  https://t.co/Usp2W3gShk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deeply concerning letter from Scottish music bosses warning of catastrophic job losses...   Extremely tough times.  https://t.co/Uwf9qgnr9N]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@pipjontaylor Love carbisdale! Is it back open?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hugely enjoyed @skipperAitken  @JimHunter22 discussing Poltney riots - incredible to hear that Gavin Brown Clarke was arguably Britains first Marxist MP... Radical history at @3rdGroats!  https://t.co/EPL9SHENYB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@luberachi @kaigalway @TheDoughBros @genofeves !!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sat inside on a sunny day but hugely enjoyed this discussion of Caithness dialect for @FestivalJo - learned a lot, found old preconceptions brushed aside.  Weel don @HNM_AHendry wis a fair craic!  https://t.co/kyHX8NKRbc]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@fd33123 @gorillaz For the magazine!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fantastic. https://t.co/6Zs66RqWG1]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jenny_stevens: Aspiring journalists! Deadline for this years Scott Trust Bursary scheme is approaching. It changed my life, it could c]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really detest the way major news outlets use drill rapper as a smear, as a dog whistle for much darker prejudices - its wrong, and its got to stop.  https://t.co/wjGmmjST9K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gave the ever-excellent @peckhamsoul a shout out in this handy Clash compiled list of fantastic record shops.  From Dundee to Penzance!   https://t.co/5QdAcwgAWj]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Simon__Harper: PERSONAL (BIG) NEWS: Introducing my new baby, @sharpercontent - a consultancy and service agency dedicated to providing]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Highly recommend @_deepshahs excellent @jai_paul timeline for your hump day reading...  10 years, two songs, the mystery and the majesty:  https://t.co/5mTxmYoePV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@euanmccolm Have you seen them live? They are still absolutely phenomenal! The current drummer is awesome.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JimGellatly @BBCSportsound Hes a troll by this point Jim...!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@nasimiyu &lt;3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClashMagazine: To some, slowed + reverb is a vital mosaic of Gen Z creativity. To others, it's a gentrified take on DJ Screw's legacy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clash - well, Garry Jones - has made a great big three part documentary about live music, the impact of the pandemic, and finding a forward path.  Im in it and (thanks to digital technology) I look very dashing!  https://t.co/0RzispZ7CB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spoke to Fred again... about the changing role of the producer, making history with Stormzy, and his incoming album project with Brian Eno.  https://t.co/5Hnkob3TYf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AJ Traceys comments on grime struck a sore spot with many - but its just part of a wider erasure of the sound from the UK music landscape.  Grime deserves a lot lot better than to be the object of derision.  https://t.co/d7hRbmeN8K]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MyCoolTea I mean about six more people introduced to Illmatic so Ill take that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thread! https://t.co/EyNAwcb4o3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justplayed Did les fleur des lys or the move ever take him to task over those borrowed riffs, I wonder?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wow this has made my week! :) https://t.co/jef1CtEQag]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ScreamOfficial: CLASH @ClashMagazine   Photography: Josie Hall Creative Direction: Rob Meyers Fashion: Lydia Simpson Hair: Kei Terada @]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hayleycscott (I know theyre Scottish but red photo innit)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@hayleycscott ??? https://t.co/npP96naSAA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spoke to @ScreamOfficial frontman Bobby Gillespie about his working class Glasgow childhood, his new record with @jehnbeth and a lot more besides for the fifth and final cover of #Clash118  https://t.co/H3PdS4MXcp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ONE MORE COVER TO COME. #Clash118]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @hellomtthw: For my CLASH debut! I spoke to @madisonbeer about life before and after Life Support, navigating self-care and her increasi]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClashMagazine: The exquisite @madisonbeer is the fourth face of #Clash118.  My fans see me and they hear me they know me and my heart]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[V much love @solongmariannes profile of the excellent multi-author lockdown zine @cocoon_zine   Support print media! Please! That would be nice!  https://t.co/RwPaM7WaLf]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.@IDK is the second face of #Clash118   Really happy to have @GrantBrydon write this one - its a v insightful piece that moves from IDKs birth in London to chairing a groundbreaking Harvard course.  https://t.co/yLuHvHltep]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spoke to @gorillaz for the cover of Clash - theres a *tonne* of ace stuff inside as well, including new writers (wheyyyy) and old friends too!  https://t.co/q57dqjqV5q]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @ClashMagazine: .@gorillaz are the first cover stars of #Clash118  We discover how the challenges of the pandemic pushed them towards re]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @James_H_Ninja: Happy Avril 14th! #AphexTwin   Short improv straight to phone of this classic tune on my slightly out of tune piano (bei]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@JessPartridge Oooohhhh!! And fear of men! Mt wolf were v buzzy at one point too.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @FarnorthScot: The Landscape of the Highlands of Scotland is no wilderness. And the built environment is just as impressive as the wide]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@helefonix ;-) https://t.co/C9KIDS4GVZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@helefonix I did not no! A nice surprise]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you get time today have a look through this - a fantastic exhibition, cant recommend it enough. Powerful and really illuminating! https://t.co/da3jeLm4mz]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@Jay_W_Taylor I love it sooooo much]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOSH DARN! https://t.co/ahSzS00Ojh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@_rhysthomas_ Peckham soul, flashback, sounds of the universe, eldica, world of echo, and had a few things from Tome records.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rahellothere Do you need an email mate? Can send one]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@jessieatkinsonx Im a beautiful butterfly! Oh just cause Im a ladybird I have to be a girl, eh?!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justplayed Peter Buck, a man never afraid to voice his opinion!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@justplayed Ive a real soft spot for Up - some spectacular work on that record!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@rob_chute Isle of Man isnt it? They used to do the Manx anthem live in concert (I am told)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@brianconey We can say one thing for certain: Protestants hate ABBA...!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@sof_mcnulty @arielzetina @DJmag Yay!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LuvlyAssistant Lol its too late in the evening for jokes ;-)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@LuvlyAssistant Do you have a link to your article as Ive never seen it...?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Oldfirmfacts1: Solidarity with Glen Kamara]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Found the whole Lava La Rue vs La Roux thing to be hilarious, so did a wee potted history on band name disputes.  Featuring: Dinosaurs Jr, London Suede, and James Murphy being a v grumpy man indeed.  https://t.co/65wce28j1H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@AndrewAHannah Well that just doesnt add up since youre so youthful, Andrew]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OMG Godspeed You! Black Emperor are playing Glasgow Barrowland?!?  https://t.co/xbK9zBuaGm]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@stevebarham1893 Thats unreal!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @marthajsc_: ahhhhh my copy of @ClashRobin's book has arrived and it's brilliant  https://t.co/Tf5tHq9T9H]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@marthajsc_ Oh wow!!! Thats proper early! Where did you order it?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@FarnorthScot Looks like castlehill by the harbour...?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Really love @lucyharbrons writing and she smashes the nail on the head with this one.  https://t.co/L6Acu1bzEW]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @limitedmitch: I know this video is going to be shared a million times today, but for anyone wondering why DMX being unwell is a big dea]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obvs it depends on the application etc but not funding Dummy seems cruel given some of the titles who did actually access support. Doesnt seem to be much rhyme nor reason to this process. https://t.co/yYZEi8XghG]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @plasmatron: I made a Creation records playlist https://t.co/EWfrZDmWQ5]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@MVinny69 The action and the creation on the same Bill...! Cor!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@GailRossSNP @HI_Voices @HNM_AHendry @Baseline53 @MuseumWick Its definitely dirdy as in hard working; the phrase dirdy day for a rainy yet productive chores day is a favourite too!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Picked Felt as a vital Creation listen.  Texted Lawrence once to set up an interview, asked if he was around. Few days later he replied: Im always kind of around...  https://t.co/51NMzS95A0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@devilmatt Have you been to the moomim shop in Camden? They might have it (after April 12th...)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An update sure to thrill my followers - the final package arrived! All the way from sunny Finland! It was posted in January...! https://t.co/43DMfnv1T0]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@CuttsTash @joanne_does_it @BraceYourselfPR @HelpMusiciansUK This looks ace!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@gameOFshane Fair. I like mbv tho - a great record!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lots of great music coming out just now - especially keen for people to spend time with @dcodrycleanonlys debut album, out on Friday.  https://t.co/0UEN7y9cDu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy mbv day my friends  https://t.co/G9L0M8Hbki]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Mos_Stef_: Please share!! https://t.co/lizXB5OjyO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @SkyNews: Its my baby, hes my treasure, hes my oxygen.   Mother of missing Oxford student Richard Okorogheye, Evidence Joel gives a]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Found the forming of @secretlyunion to be truly inspiring - can collective action create solutions for rampant overwork, poor mental health, and other issues endemic to the music industry...? If so, what form could this take?  https://t.co/gaJq90d82Y]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[@msclairebiddles What book is it? Also, lol, Keith the paragon of chastity...!]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>