<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Dem Rep. Ron Kind slammed over spa controversy in new ad - https://t.co/8v9a1CZAXY #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calif. woman uses racist slur to accuse Latino policeman of racism - https://t.co/wqi7Eb8Kv9 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two tornadoes rock Ellis County, Texas - https://t.co/hK5J0Piayu #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: TONIGHT on THE REAL STORY!  Were joined by an incredible cast of characters:   @kelliwardaz @AZGOP  @RepJamesComer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From the Desk of Donald J. Trump goes live on internet - https://t.co/DVPhHJMjnE #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 charged in human smuggling operation in Houston - https://t.co/8aCW1nuH4E #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nefertari_25: Tonight on Tipping Point @OANN   I talk to  @TomFitton from @JudicialWatch  @JonSchweppe  @RepBrianBabin  @ErickKaardal]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fentanyl floods across U.S. southern border - https://t.co/P4WxRBs7Km #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Windham, N.H. citizens protest board meeting, demand to stop the steal - https://t.co/RRTLUVRS9l #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanNewsManBall: Tonight on Real America  @OANN   Special guests- @4KidsandCountry  @OchsenbeinMD  @TheBradenEllis  @AndrewHGiuliani]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Trump is back - in blog form!   https://t.co/5owT41vAKx]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden evades herd immunity question, tries to steal credit for vaccines - https://t.co/miaseO4Ft1 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Controversial Photo Of Chauvin Juror #52 Prompts Legal Questions - https://t.co/BEP8MRXGFU #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @STEPHMHAMILL: Hi! We have a lot to cover tonight !! I hope you will tune in to @OANN at 6PM EST. @RubinReport , Congressman @RepRalphNo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fla. Gov. DeSantis revokes last remaining COVID restrictions, says Fla. has low COVID rate - https://t.co/XdjBo2zF10 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MarketWrap Wall St closes mostly lower amid interest rate fears  DJIA +0.06%, 19.80 points at 34,133  NASDAQ -1.88%, 261.6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New CIA recruitment ad criticized for overdose of woke ideas - https://t.co/smkPbqrl5Y #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antrim County plaintiffs to introduce new evidence on voting systems https://t.co/98JwDiYXC7 #OANN @JackPosobiec]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MORE Kaplan says he believes interest rates will start to rise in 2022, forecasting the economy will be on track to reach]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #NEW Dallas Fed President Robert Kaplan tells @MarketWatch it's time to begin talking about slowing QE  I think it will ma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @jennfranconews: AG Garland is requesting an additional $85M in funding from Congress to help DOJ  FBI fight domestic terrorism, accord]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rep. Scalise: Americans are rejecting socialism - https://t.co/ETY8feULdp #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #NEW The U.S. trade deficit rises to a new record high in March as the country's economic recovery outpaces global partners]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MORE Yellen: "It may be that interest rates will have to rise somewhat to make sure that our economy doesnt overheat. Eve]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MarketWatch Tech sell-off accelerates as Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen says interest rates may have to rise to prevent o]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYPD searching for suspect who attack Asian woman with a hammer - https://t.co/PSElmlXBuW #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Vice President Mike Pence set to headline N.H. GOP fundraiser - https://t.co/yGb1USpy8S #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Show your support for MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell. Go to https://t.co/fRWcVddMOh and enter promo code OAN at checkout! https://t.co/2Is3CH9zXq]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Pollster: Republican base 'totally loyal' to President Trump https://t.co/D0QDmCR3xO #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenna Ellis challenges Rep. Liz Cheney to live debate of stolen election - https://t.co/Qtx53Q0fSV #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_StephanieMyers: Letter found here: https://t.co/feUxmkBZqS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @_StephanieMyers: NEW: Reps. @Jim_Jordan  @RepAndyBiggsAZ send a letter to FBI Director Christopher Wray, wanting answers to why the FB]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RPT: 'Nonpartisan' money being used to oust Fla. Gov. Ron DeSantis in 2022 https://t.co/ChR9eyOU00 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate Minority Leader McConnell: No Republicans will support Biden infrastructure plan - https://t.co/g03LHYqFAB #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning! Tune in to One America News for the latest!  (Photo: The U.S. Capitol Dome is silhouetted against the rising sun in Washington, D.C. -- J. David Ake via AP) #OANN https://t.co/oDI4KnYmYe]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MarketWatch Wall Street falls at the open as tech shares pullback]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @Nefertari_25: Tonight on Tipping Point @OANN   I talk to  @AndrewHGiuliani  @Autry  @HvonSpakovsky  @RMConservative  @michaeljohns   Ab]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: TONIGHT on THE REAL STORY!  Were joined by an incredible cast of characters:   @ericbolling   @MattWhitaker46 @Ameri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike Lindell Tackles Election Fraud https://t.co/OcPjQwVdWd #OANN @PearsonSharp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Evidence points to vulnerabilities in U.S. voting systems https://t.co/0xGyQuhws2 #OANN @PearsonSharp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secy. of State: Our purpose is not to hold China back - https://t.co/mTdhyRQQCJ #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MarketWrap Wall St closes mixed as investors shift into "reopening stocks"  DJIA +0.70%, 238.45 points at 34,113  NASDAQ -]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #NEW U.S. manufacturing growth slows in April amid higher prices, supply shortages  @IHSMarkitPMI slips to 60.5 at the end]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Back the Blue rally postponed due to BLM, Antifa threats https://t.co/FVtMKsTcCS #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: President Trump on TX-06's special election:  "Please explain to the Democrats and RINOs that the reason Texas-06 complet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bidens bloated infrastructure plan criticized by Republican lawmakers - https://t.co/x1nQ3F9IU9 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SpaceX Dragon Mission Complete, Returns to Earth - https://t.co/iXZREoUSyD #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sen. Mitt Romney gets booed at Utah GOP convention - https://t.co/J72IVZKw2p #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Susan Wright heading to runoff election for Texas congressional seat previously held by late husband - https://t.co/xmAQF7dC28 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calif. opens second emergency child migrant center in L.A. County - https://t.co/7GIS1AvEn1 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former FDA Chief Gottlieb says 10M  teens could be vaccinated by beginning of school year - https://t.co/JpzLiI6bKm #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: Ron DeSantis is about to sign a law banning social media companies from deplatforming  He is able to do so because he has]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: President Trump congratulates @SusanWrightTX6:  "Congratulations to Susan Wright on her great surge yesterday which made]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @GretaLWall: #MarketWatch Wall St begins new month of trade higher]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: https://t.co/fQDfCF7Pe7]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariz. audit chief says probe of 2020 fraud is gaining momentum - https://t.co/RJOAOSnLdZ #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning! Tune in to One America News for the latest!  (Photo: An American flag flaps in the wind in Denver, Colo. -- David Zalubowski via AP) #OANN https://t.co/KHYVeu0OJu]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @christina_bobb: @Garrett_Archer This is completely false.  Im the only @OANN reporter in AZ and I havent been in the Coliseum since I]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: #WeeklyBriefing: Join @christina_bobb in Ariz. this weekend as she discusses the latest political fights in the state with Ariz.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: With historic ratings  rapid growth, @OANN is now #HIRING for various positions in California and Washington, D.C.   For more in]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: Join @christina_bobb and forensic expert Col. Phil Waldron as they investigate latest revelations coming from the forensic audit]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: An historic pandemic forced states to make changes in the 2020 election process. More Americans than ever before voted, yet milli]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: Deep state sniper Kash Patel, the man who exposed the fraud and hoax of Russiagate, leads an exclusive discussion behind the scen]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: #HappeningNow 2020 election audit underway in Ariz. Tune in for LIVE reports throughout the week!  Also, visit https://t.co/22zD6]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: One America News is launching a brand new social media platform -- https://t.co/c6YAEOe8JO.  FINALLY -- you have the freedom to e]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: #OANN decided to #MakeTheSwitch to #Rumble, where we can freely report the news without restrictions or censorship.   Subscribe t]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: Join @NatalieJHarp for "The Real Story" as she breaks through a world of conflicting narratives and fake news to bring you the fa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: Don't miss Tipping Point on One America News!   Tune in weeknights at 9 p.m. EST / 6 p.m. PST as Kara McKinney brings a fresh per]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: Are you sick and tired of the biased, fake news media that's tearing our country apart?   Tune in weeknights on One America News]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: Join @STEPHMHAMILL weeknights on One America News  take a closer look at the days headlines. Stephanie is a straight shooter who]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @OANN: If your cable company doesn't offer @OANN, Enjoy the 24/7 LIVE Feed of @OANN on Roku, nominal cost of only $4.99/mo.  How to: Fro]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesPHerring: I appreciate and acknowledge the "significant corrections" retracting earlier reporting issued by WaPo and NYT. Yet ho]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Army investigation finds Vanessa Guillen was sexually harassed - https://t.co/KH2mRnneEy #OANN https://t.co/rIvhQqjpQr]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Empire State Building celebrates 90th Anniversary - https://t.co/dMxh7tkrLT #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fla. Legislature passes election strengthening bill, Gov. DeSantis says hell sign - https://t.co/Dq5k8vsEli #OANN https://t.co/CWW7Xq6Bbt]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wall to Wall: Mitch Roschelle on the American Families Plan - @GretaLWall - https://t.co/ENZOBSa7EP #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wall to Wall: Mitch Roschelle on Consumer Spending, Inflation @GretaLWall - https://t.co/KWMbJcbWdZ #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White House signals openness to diplomacy with N. Korea after policy review - https://t.co/tbIK41c5XU #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calif. to release 76,000 inmates early to cut prison population - https://t.co/qG4HlMBVAW  #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @CSinclairtv: https://t.co/CpJuz4MuVP]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC says 100M Americans fully vaccinated as goal date for full reopening is July 1st - https://t.co/XoVZuTAtxm #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[90  migrants found in suspected smuggling ring in Texas - https://t.co/bxfAJ2cmIo #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: OANs @CharlesPHerring stated publicly that this unequivocally never happened   Now WaPo has retracted https://t.co/xExHZ]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @JackPosobiec: BREAKING: WaPo has retracted their reporting on OAN and the FBI https://t.co/BclG9cA5dp]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sen. Manchin: Washington D.C. statehood shouldnt be granted through unilateral congressional action - https://t.co/wvpO3nV1nm #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calif. extradition request delayed for Harvey Weinstein - https://t.co/yGEuedFb4d #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump supporter reveals Northern Calif. Antifa hit list - https://t.co/qFKP4EDDsa #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One-on-One with N.Y. Gubernatorial Candidate Rep. Lee Zeldin (part 1) @_StephanieMyers - https://t.co/eNjif6VR6H #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: President Trump to TX-6:  "Today is Election Day in Texas, go out and vote for @SusanWrightTX6. She will be strong on the]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good morning! Tune in to @OANN for the latest.  (A pedestrian, wearing a protective face mask walks past the American flag video board in Times Square. Photo by Justin Heiman/Getty Images) #OANN https://t.co/Yl9fnc1Gyh]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: President Trump reacts to Twitter's stock "plunging" today:  "Twitter stock 'plunged' as results are no longer cutting it]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate conservatives react to Biden Joint Congress address: https://t.co/NKzFUmmYq2 #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media caught using CCP-tied experts on Wuhan Lab theory @JackPosobiec -  https://t.co/K1pDPci2Rr #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fla. legislature passes social media deplatforming bill: @JackPosobiec - https://t.co/xDr0YihPuJ #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Newsmax settles Dominion lawsuit, issues retraction on 2020 coverage - https://t.co/j5s5ZAjSrF #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reps. Matt Gaetz, MTG launch Put America First fundraising Cmte - https://t.co/Dzcrqnmk2w #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you, President Trump!   "Congratulations to One America News @OANN on their great ratings surge. Also, for their love of the United States of America!"   Your nation, your news.  #OANN https://t.co/fWZGZPVXjA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vt. Army Natl Guard combat units open to women - https://t.co/rbdtXP1w2t #OANN]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @NatalieJHarp: TONIGHT on THE REAL STORY!  Were joined by an incredible cast of characters:   Mike Lindell  @dougmastriano  @chri]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT @DanNewsManBall: On Real America Tonight... 4/30/2021 https://t.co/9emFUzCOLb  See you 8pm EST/5pm PST  @realannapaulina @RepFredKeller]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>